(Episode 23)
KTX 738 from Busan
bound to Seoul derailed...
and the wounded are currently
sent to nearby Daejeon Hospital.
There were 387 people on board,
and we do not have
the number of casualties yet.
- President Baek Gyeong Ah...
- How did you know...
about the train accident?
Said the cause of the accident
has not been confirmed yet.
Can I really go back in time?
Young.
Mom.
Goodness.
December 21, 2019...
at 11:11 p.m., she has passed away.
Young...
No. No!
No!
I thought I'd be able to save her
if I reset.
But it's tormenting
to watch Young die...
every single time.
There will come a day...
when Young will fully recover,
if you endure through time.
How?
Enjoy it. Enjoy your time.
You can enjoy watching people...
within that time that only you know.
Nothing is more fun than that.
These are...
the people I'm interested in.
("Incumbent Detective
Arrested as a Serial Killer")
The culprit will run away soon,
and two more people will die.
If...
this person disappears...
If that's made possible,
what do you think will happen?
What if you bring back
the 10 victims alive...
and reset together?
Are you acquainted
with Ji Hyeong Ju?
I know a lot about you too,
Mr. Oh Myung Chul.
And that you'll kill
Detective Ji Hyeong Ju today.
But...
do you know what true revenge is?
It's way too easy...
to simply kill him.
True revenge is...
making him live in torment...
until the day he dies.
Everything has begun again.
It'll be an interesting year.
(Advisory Director Hwang No Sub)
What's this?
I was told to give you this
when you two make a visit.
So he must have known
that we would come to him.
(The clockwork of time
disturbs the silent dawn.)
Hey.
What?
Okay.
What's wrong?
Park Sun Ho escaped.
It's not over yet.
What happened?
The vehicle overturned while trying
to dodge a motorcycle.
He got out and took the motorcycle.
He even took the weapon
inside the vehicle.
- Where's Captain Heo?
- He's in a meeting.
We need to wait
until the RIU asks for our help.
Do you have any idea
where he could be?
(The clockwork of time
disturbs the silent dawn.)
Shin.
Don't you think...
it's time for us to prepare
for the next reset?
You were always busy
around this time of the year...
because of Young.
That's why...
I'm thinking of getting help
from someone else.
Someone else?
I hope you'll be able
to remember something now.
Do you still have the photo...
that Ms. Lee Shin gave you?
If you succeed,
come to Zian Clinic to meet with me.
- "Succeed"?
- I'd like to offer you...
the one and only opportunity...
to wash away your sins.
I'm talking about the reset.
Who are you?
If you were to kill me right now,
keep in mind...
that you will never get to reset.
You'll understand everything soon.
We three will go through
the next reset.
But sir...
("Pieces of Destiny")
(The clockwork of time
disturbs the silent dawn.)
(Chapter 1, The Signal of Fate)
(Volume 9, Two Memories)
It's January 9.
That's two days before the reset.
One of us...
will die then.
And Park Sun Ho
would still be at large.
Do you think they knew...
that he'd escape?
Yes, if this had happened before.
It's just like how they knew
when we'd die.
Then why did he go to the cafe
that day?
Do you think he went there
to kill Professor Hwang?
If that's the case,
he spared his life.
What if Professor Hwang
offered a deal?
The reset?
If Mr. Park goes through
with the reset,
he'll no longer be
a serial killer...
who has run away.
I know Park Sun Ho was here.
Didn't you arrest him?
I was curious
how you bought this place...
immediately after the reset.
It turned out the former director
of Zian Clinic...
was an advisory director
at Samo Pharmaceuticals.
I bet Prof. Hwang led and planned...
the experiment.
What's your role in all this?
Are you an accomplice?
Or his puppet?
I don't think you should be worried
about me.
If Detective Park Sun Ho escaped,
aren't you and Ms. Shin Ga Hyeon...
in grave danger?
Yes, we know.
We can talk more about him
back at the police station.
You are under arrest
for concealing a criminal.
You have the right to remain silent
and the right to an attorney.
What are you doing?
It was such a large-scale case,
so we received many tip-offs.
I suppose these aren't necessary.
(Temporarily closed due to
personal reasons)
Have you given it some thought?
It's true that Mr. Park Sun Ho
visited the clinic.
I didn't want to get involved,
so I told him to leave immediately.
I have no idea where he went.
And there's no reason for him
to have told me.
Then why are the CCTV footages
from that day missing?
Maybe the cameras had an error.
- I don't do those things.
- You're right.
Ms. Song does.
Professor Hwang was with you two,
am I right?
That's why the footages
were deleted, right?
You can take your time.
We can detain you
for up to 48 hours.
Detective Ji.
I promise to come back
for the next interrogation.
So please let me go.
I beg you.
Tell me where he went.
That's all I want to know.
I beg you as well.
My daughter...
will die tonight.
I need to be by her side.
So your plan is to make me stay here
until January 11.
Is that right?
That's correct.
You need to arrive there
safe and sound...
in order to go through the reset.
How did you find that place?
I was very desperate.
I wanted to die.
But when I woke up,
I found myself at this spot again.
I traveled back exactly a year
back in time.
I can't imagine...
what that feels like.
You'll experience this yourself
very soon.
I'm sure we'll be great partners.
Are you using your child now?
No, Detective Ji.
I mean it.
I ask of you, please.
Where is...
Park Sun Ho right now?
I really don't know.
Please believe me.
What about Professor Hwang?
You know where he is, don't you?
Isn't tonight the last day
you'll spend with your child?
Yet you're still trying to
defend Professor Hwang?
You don't know...
how to reset, do you?
That's why
you're trying to protect him.
If something happens to him,
you won't be able to reset either.
Even if your child dies,
all you have to do is reset.
Is that so?
You'll find a tiny medicine bottle
in that box.
You need to...
administer the drug tonight.
Me?
What if something goes wrong?
All clinical tests...
come with side effects.
What do you mean?
Wait, will you do that to Young?
But why?
No, I can't do that
even if I knew the reason.
I can't take things this far.
You will...
end up doing it,
because you always have.
(VIP Ward)
(VIP 2: Lee Young,
female, 7 years old)
Ms. Song! What are you doing?
Over here. Is there anyone around?
She injected something
into her body. Hurry!
Ms. Song!
Charge to 150 joules.
Charging to 150 joules.
Doctor, we're ready.
1, 2, 3.
Cleared. Shock.
Charge to 200 joules.
Charging to 200 joules.
You need to prepare yourself
for the worst.
December 21, 2019...
at 11:11 p.m.,
she has passed away.
Is Young all right?
Are you sure she's okay?
Her vitals look stable.
She'll wake up soon
when we give her a few more drugs.
Ms. Shin Ga Hyeon
suddenly showed up.
I'm sorry.
It's all right.
You better hide for a while.
I'll contact you again.
Hey, you're here.
Come in.
What brings you here?
You two are acquainted?
Young lived thanks to her.
What do you mean?
Thank you.
Did it always happen...
on the same day at the same time?
But this time, she lived,
although the fate of one's death was
never supposed to change.
If I hadn't seen her,
your child would've died again.
And you would've believed
that it was her fate.
Professor Hwang
wouldn't have done that.
He's the one
who always helped Young...
with those clinical tests.
Why would he do this?
He probably needed you to reset.
In order to make you reset time,
he needed the child to die.
Do you still have no idea...
who really had been...
making your child suffer?
In order to make you reset time,
he needed the child to die.
Do you still have no idea...
who really had been
making your child suffer?
Was it all because of me?
Did you have to live through
that much pain because of me?
Hyeong Ju.
Did you finish
giving your testimony?
Yes.
I got Ms. Song on the wanted list.
I'm sure we'll hear about her soon.
Her child lived...
thanks to you.
She was never supposed to die.
I'm glad
I got to save her like this.
How can he kill that little child...
six times?
Do you think Ms. Lee Shin...
began to understand how we felt?
How it feels to have
someone else toy with our lives.
(January 1, KTX car 738,
January 9, January 11, reset)
(January 9)
Come in, Ga Hyeon.
Take a seat.
Ms. Seo Yeon Soo died.
Died? I can't even believe...
that he committed suicide.
It must be a coincidence.
They might be lines from poems...
or just common celebratory messages.
Do you think someone
who knows everything...
thinks this is nothing
but fun entertainment?
I was starting to get
attached to you, Ga Hyeon.
I'm sorry things ended up like this.
"Attached" to me?
You lied about everything
and put up an act.
Yet you were "attached"?
When you give this your best,
you end up forgetting
that you're acting.
You were at
Ms. So Hye In's flower shop...
on purpose, weren't you?
You're right.
That flower shop was
the least dangerous place,
so I went there myself.
It's a pleasure...
to watch something
that only I know unfolds...
at the time that only I know.
It was thrilling.
Why do you do this?
When you become my age,
most things don't seem that amusing.
Ever since I knew I could reset,
I was never bored.
This reset was
more special than ever.
I got to witness
even the sound of your breaths...
right by your side.
So after you used Ms. Lee Shin
as your front...
and watched everything unfold,
did you feel like
you became a deity or something?
A deity?
No deity will tell you
your fate before it happens.
I already told everyone
about their fate.
You received the card.
Who do you think it'll be
among those two?
About Detective Ji.
(Final Episode)
How did you know I was here?
Today is your daughter's
death anniversary.
You and I have repeated...
the year several times now.
Were you...
really going to kill Young?
Did the professor
order you to do it?
Is that so?
I'm sorry.
You know how much pain...
she suffered from
better than anyone.
How could you do this to her?
How?
That was the only way
for me to see my daughter too.
What did you say?
He promised to take me with him...
for the next reset.
But your daughter died
three years ago.
You can only go back a year.
Did he leave that out to you?
All clinical tests...
come with side effects.
What do you mean?
Wait, will you do that to Young?
No, I can't do that
even if I knew the reason.
I can't take things this far.
You will...
end up doing it,
because you always have.
(Ms. Song)
Have you been killing Young
all this time?
Every single year?
Because you need me for the reset,
did you sacrifice my daughter?
I only did it for you, Shin.
For me?
How long do you think
your daughter can live?
Just because she's alive now,
does it mean she'll last
one more month or year?
Before she dies, do you think
someone will develop the cure?
As a doctor, you know the answer
better than anyone.
I didn't want you to make
a difficult decision.
I didn't want you
to rely on an uncertain future...
and be foolish enough to give up...
living the perfect year.
You should have at least given me
a chance to decide.
About Detective Ji.
Aren't you curious
about how he'll die?
You know, Samo Pharmaceuticals
where Professor Hwang is working at?
I looked into it, and this company
has a lot of problems.
It's about the clinical trial
they conducted at the sanatorium.
They requested to develop
a new drug with rigged data.
And there's a record
that they were investigated by...
What's wrong? Did something happen?
No.
Something is up.
What about Ms. Song?
No. Not yet.
I see. Okay.
Just because she's alive now,
does it mean she'll last
one more month or year?
Before she dies, do you think
someone will develop the cure?
There are 13 days left
until the reset.
This time, you'll decide.
You made the right decision.
I knew you'd make
the right decision.
But under one condition.
Please keep Detective Park Sun Ho
out of this.
He's too dangerous.
Of course.
I wasn't going to go through
the reset with him, to begin with.
I was just playing along...
until Detective Ji was eliminated.
Right about now, he's probably...
preparing to take
his role diligently.
Arrest warrant?
On what grounds?
On the grounds of attempted
murder and instigation to murder.
Song Ji Hyun reported it
to Seoul Makang Police Station.
I asked you
to be a bit more patient.
I thought you'd be happy
with my decision.
Isn't that why you told me
the truth about Professor Hwang?
Back then...
Things have changed now.
The same goes for me.
I no longer have a reason
to obey his orders.
An arrest warrant for Hwang No Sub
has been issued.
That's a relief.
We can detain him
for at least 48 hours.
We'll catch him before the reset
and stop it.
We'd be able to put an end to this
if Park Sun Ho is with him.
Professor Hwang said that
Mujin was his hometown.
The resetting place
was about two hours from Seoul.
Mujin is about that far as well.
Maybe they're hiding there.
Sa Kyung, did you receive
any reports about Park Sun Ho...
being spotted in Mujin?
Hold on.
Yes, there was one.
But the CCTV footage was too poor...
to verify it.
And one more thing.
Can you check if Hwang No Sub
lived in Mujin?
- Text me.
- Okay.
I should go right now.
Right now?
We need to catch Park Sun Ho
before tomorrow comes.
I'll tell Sa Kyung to come here
just in case.
Don't go anywhere and stay at home.
Hyeong Ju.
About Detective Ji...
Aren't you curious
about how he'll die?
He dies while trying to save you.
And it's extremely gruesome.
Will Hyeong Ju die because of me?
Is this true?
Will he die while trying to save me?
Where?
You must know.
Tell me.
I'm sorry.
You and Detective Ji
are going to do everything...
in your power to stop
Professor Hwang.
But you see, I need him.
Are you saying you'll go through
the reset once again?
I've thought about it,
and that's the right thing to do.
Once January 11th passes,
I won't be able to bring Young
back to life anymore.
I decided to choose the safe path...
over the unseen future.
How do you know
if that future will happen...
in a year or a decade?
You could be stopping her...
from turning 10 or even 20.
The fate of death...
can never be changed.
You're wrong.
It can be.
I'll show you.
If he dies while trying to save me,
then we just need to stay apart.
If that's what it takes,
I'll do it.
I'd like to report something.
I think I spotted Park Sun Ho,
the escaped criminal, in Mujin.
Hyeong Ju.
Let's stay alive...
no matter what.
Of course.
(January 9, January 11 Reset)
(January 9)
We need to hurry.
If something happens to me,
you won't be able to reset.
Don't forget that
and make sure to do your job.
You two are acquainted?
Young lived thanks to her.
Will Hyeong Ju die because of me?
Is this true?
Will he die while trying to save me?
Where?
You must know. Tell me.
Why aren't you arresting
Professor Hwang?
We're investigating.
First, you should turn yourself in.
He's at Zian Clinic right now.
(Psychiatrist Lee Shin)
(Ji Hyeong Ju, Shin Ga Hyeon)
(Ji Hyeong Ju, 32 years old)
(Shin Ga Hyeon, 28 years old)
- Hello?
- Get out of there right now.
What?
This is the first
and the last time...
you'll be getting my help.
We're back here again,
Professor Hwang No Sub.
I wonder if you knew everything
that happened to us...
from the moment
we first gathered here...
until now.
If everything was predictable,
that'd be boring.
Where is Park Sun Ho?
Fine by me. You can take your time.
I was going
to detain you first anyway.
Why do you think
there was only one card?
That's because you and Ga Hyeon...
died on the same day
and at the same place.
She already knows this.
Did she not tell you?
What did you say?
Ga Hyeon.
Ji Hyeong Ju.
Touch her, and I'll kill you.
That all depends on your actions.
First, rip that arrest warrant.
And come here right now...
- if you want to save her.
- Where are you?
Where am I?
I'm at your headquarters.
You know what will happen to her
if you bring others with you, right?
- Hyeong Ju.
- Ga Hyeon.
Don't be afraid. I'll be there soon.
I'm okay, so please don't come.
Please.
Ga Hyeon. Ga Hyeon.
He still has the arrest warrant.
He wants you to rip that up...
if you want to save her.
Keep her alive for now.
I'm curious...
about how you two will end up.
You should hurry.
There's not much time
until everything is over.
When he arrives, eliminate
both of them without a trace.
That's your ticket to the reset.
The reset ticket.
Ga Hyeon.
(Detective Jin Sa Kyung)
Tell her that you're
at your friend's house,
and not to worry about you.
Then, send her back.
(Detective Jin Sa Kyung)
We should go to somewhere else.
Yes, Detective Jin.
Hyeong Ju, see you there.
Do you know...
how you two died
in your previous life?
(I sent you the episode
about Samson.)
(Please review it
and send me your comments.)
(Detective Ji Hyeong Ju)
(Seoul Makang Police Station)
The person you have reached
is unavailable.
You'll be connected
to the voicemail box.
(Let's meet here.
Don't tell anyone. Come alone.)
I wouldn't have run away
if I was only going to kill you...
just because you caught me.
Let's leave Ga Hyeon out of this.
This webtoon artist, Maru,
is dying because of you.
Detective Ji.
Detective Ji?
Maru.
Do you know
why Hyeong Ju went through...
the reset?
It was because
Oh Myung Chul killed you.
To save you,
he went through the reset.
I regretted like crazy...
that I came...
to save a scumbag like you.
If you cared about Hyeong Ju
even for a bit,
turn yourself in now.
And stop this now.
Okay.
I know how deeply he cared about me.
So after I go through the reset,
I will be careful not to get caught.
Then, I might not kill you.
He's late.
He must be here about now.
You won't be able to kill Hyeong Ju.
I won't let you.
I can't kill?
The only person I couldn't kill
was Professor Hwang.
And I'll kill that old man
once I'm done with the reset.
As long as I put my mind to it,
I can kill anyone.
Did you get that?
Ga Hyeon. Ga Hyeon!
I...
Hyeong Ju.
Ga Hyeon.
Let go!
Hang in there.
The ambulance will be here soon.
Hyeong Ju.
The autograph...
I'm sorry...
for not signing your book.
I will...
sign it...
next time.
Ga Hyeon.
Hyeong Ju.
Our fate today will affect
our fate tomorrow.
I'll make sure to catch the culprit,
so it doesn't come to that.
You're wrong.
It can be.
I'll show you.
Ga Hyeon truly changed your fate.
And I plan to do the same.
I must go through the reset.
I won't do it.
I decided to stay in the present.
I want to believe in the present
my daughter has.
And I'm also curious...
about her future
I've never seen before.
It's all thanks to you two.
I know I can't earn
your forgiveness.
But I will remember...
all of my wrongdoings...
and plan to accept
and face all of my punishment.
I must go back.
Another set of painful memories...
might be waiting for you there.
You may repeat the mistakes
I have made too.
I don't care.
What do I need to do?
As you already guessed,
only the professor knows the way.
Are you sure there's no other way?
I only know the way
up to the tunnel.
He told me that there's
a forked road...
at the end of the tunnel.
One way leads to the reset.
And the other way...
leads to death.
Good luck, Detective Ji.
Our fate today will affect
our fate tomorrow.
I don't think
I have a friend like you.
A friend who's willing to travel
back in time to save me.
I can at least make one friend
who would before I die, right?
You have me. I'm on my way.
- Are you leaving now?
- Yes.
- Are you sure you can go alone?
- Of course.
How did you...
It didn't matter which road I took.
They both gave me a chance...
as long as I wasn't afraid.
Mr. Hwang No Sub.
You're under arrest...
for violating Article 34
of the Pharmaceutical Affairs Act...
and committing
an illegal activity...
regarding the approval
of a plan for a clinical trial.
Do you think I'll be punished
for something like this?
To get out on parole, you will rot
in prison at least for a year...
no matter how hard you try.
It means
you won't be able to do the reset.
You will never...
be able to play
with other people's lives.
Mr. Park Sun Ho.
Hyeong Ju. How did you find me here?
You're under arrest for murdering
Hwang Seok Man, Lieutenant Kim,
Kim Moon Hong, and Park Hyun Jae
and abandoning their bodies.
You can hire an attorney,
remain silent...
Stay there.
Don't come near me.
It's all over.
This is where
the masterpiece was born.
Let's go, Maru.
Let's go. My gosh.
Excuse me. I'm sorry. Sorry.
I'm sorry.
Detective Ji.
Aren't you Detective Ji Hyeong Ju?
Can you...
recognize me?
Of course.
Really?
Aren't you the detective
who caught...
the serial killer detective
at Seoul Makang Police Station?
I saw you on the news.
By any chance,
are you the webtoon artist
of "Hidden Killer"?
Do you know me?
You are her, right? I wasn't sure.
I had been waiting
to get your autograph for a year,
but I couldn't get it in the end.
My autograph?
Well, yes. It's nothing.
Anyway,
it's nice to see you again.
I'll be looking forward
to finding out who Samson is.
Good luck, Maru.
Detective Ji.
Can I...
consult you about my work?
If you keep your promise.
Pardon?
The autograph.
Of course.
(We will remember our viewers
for 365 days a year.)
(365: Repeat the Year)