(Episode 17)
You won't have those detectives
in front of your room anymore.
I told you already.
Everything is a misunderstanding.
Do say hello...
to Detective Ji for me.
What about that guy?
He told me everything.
That you were falsely blamed
for the last incident.
That you were
deceived by that woman.
Ji Hyeong Ju said
something like that?
And he apologized too.
He said he was
also partially responsible.
What is this?
Hey, Mr. Detective.
Bae Jung Tae?
What is this photo?
Let's talk more about it in person.
I can only imagine...
how curious you must be
about that photo.
I sent it as a token
of my appreciation for your help,
so come before I change my mind.
I'll be waiting for you.
What's this?
He's early.
He sure came early.
Detective...
(Seoul Makang Police Station)
- You must be tired.
- Goodness.
It sure is like having a pick-me-up
to catch the culprit.
If it wasn't Bae Jung Tae,
it means we're back to ground zero.
We don't even have a suspect now.
Where do we begin investigating?
Let's stop thinking about this
and go catch a movie.
- Shall we?
- Should we?
Are there any movies without
dead bodies and detectives?
Dead bodies... One second.
What?
Yes, all right.
Why? Who was that?
(Shin Ga Hyeon)
(Police line, do not cross)
Hey, Hyeong Ju.
What happened?
I heard you reported this.
Yes, I came by because
we were going to meet up,
then I found him like that.
Let's go inside.
Is something going on?
Why won't you pick up your phone?
Mr. Choi Kyung Man's case was
first reported to...
one of the police stations in
Makang Police's jurisdiction, right?
Hyeong Ju.
Mr. Bae Jung Tae...
died.
What?
Hey, why did you come to see him?
Right.
Kim Se Rin's case
hasn't been resolved.
I was wondering if he knew anything.
And you came at this time?
To his house?
We were about to summon him
for kidnapping and confinement...
or as a testifier.
He's way too unpredictable.
I don't know what he was up to,
but he suddenly called me.
That's why...
I decided to come.
I see.
- Sun Ho!
- Yes?
You should go.
Did you find the culprit?
Not yet.
But why did you ask me
about Mr. Choi Kyung Man?
Starting with Mr. Choi Kyung Man,
Seo Yeon Soo,
Mr. Cha Jeung Seok, Ms. So Hye In,
the delivery man, Se Rin,
and now, Mr. Bae Jung Tae.
Their cases are all within
Makang Police's jurisdiction.
This cannot be a coincidence.
All of their deaths...
What if they're connected?
How?
What if it's a serial killer?
Mr. Choi Kyung Man,
the delivery man,
and everyone else
are ordinary people.
Unlike Se Rin's death,
their deaths weren't known
to the public.
"How did Ms. Lee Shin know
when and where they'd die?"
"Why was she interested in us
of all people?"
I checked all the cases,
and they all took place...
in the district
of Seoul Makang Police Station.
Do you remember what Ms. Lee said
at the cafe?
I was curious...
whether fate...
was destined or changeable.
That's why I carried out
this experiment.
Don't be too scared.
I still have hope
that you can change your fates.
If their deaths were accidental,
it's impossible to change
their fates.
But if there's a serial killer,
then it's different.
If we catch the killer,
we can change our fates.
So what if...
we were all murdered...
by someone?
What if that's why she chose us?
Hyeong Ju?
Was what I said too ridiculous?
No, I'm just a bit flustered.
I'll dig deeper.
I'm sure I'll find a lead...
through Bae Jung Tae's case.
I've scheduled your appointment.
Come to the hospital by 12 p.m.
the day after tomorrow.
Thanks.
The professor helped out
more than I did.
You should say thanks.
Okay. I'll see you then.
The cause of death
was excessive bleeding.
He was stabbed
through his left lung.
Judging by the stab wound,
I believe it was a knife...
that was 3cm thick and 10cm long.
After stabbing him,
the killer twisted the blade.
Darn it.
There were neither signs
of forced entry...
or physical altercation.
Do you think he knew the killer?
He was murdered merely 12 hours
after our men stopped watching him.
I believe the killer
had been watching him.
Are there any key suspects?
He borrowed money and was a gambler.
I'm sure we can come up with a list.
Can you think of anyone
in particular?
You knew him the best
among all of us.
I'm not sure.
All right.
Look into his rap sheet...
and see if you can narrow down
the suspect.
Since it happened at his house,
check his belongings...
and PF list once again.
Ask around about him...
and check the CCTV footages
around his house.
You have until our meeting
this evening.
There's... There's a serial killer?
Are you saying the one
who murdered Mr. Bae Jung Tae...
killed Se Rin as well?
This is just my speculation.
What did Detective Ji say?
He said he's going to investigate...
Bae Jung Tae's case.
(Attachment: 1 Audio File)
(Untitled)
I'm going to meet up
with Detective Ji Hyeong Ju.
I'll go to the hospital
as soon as I'm done.
Wait. Isn't this Mr. Bae Jung Tae?
He's early.
He sure came early.
Detective...
We couldn't find the killer's prints
on Bae Jung Tae's body.
He must be pretty meticulous,
but why is the crime scene
such a mess?
Is the forensic report not done yet?
No, they're still working
on Ms. Kim Se Rin's case.
The forensics team
is having a headache.
I think it's going
to take some time.
(A footprint, believed to be
the same one, found in the kitchen)
Sir, here are your new handcuffs.
Did you lose them?
I think I dropped them
at the crime scene.
Did you check your drawers?
We pay tax to purchase those.
Get a forensic analysis of this.
- Why?
- We didn't find this...
at Kim Se Rin's crime scene.
- Make this an exigency.
- Yes, sir.
What... What does this mean?
Detective...
Why would Detective Ji harm him?
I'm... I'm sure something's wrong.
- I can't believe this.
- But he clearly said, "Detective."
If this was what really happened,
then who recorded this?
Was it the late Bae Jung Tae?
Or was it the killer?
And how did the killer know
our numbers?
If Hyeong Ju is indeed the killer,
wouldn't that be too strange?
How about we report this
to the police?
They can look into this.
(Untitled)
The phone is turned off. Please
leave a message after the tone.
Hello.
Is the forensic report
for Bae Jung Tae's case...
not done yet?
Really?
Could you send it to me first?
Also, I'm sending in
another footprint.
Please analyze this as well.
Thank you.
Detective...
This is quite interesting.
It seems like...
someone wiretapped the crime scene.
We don't know who it is just yet.
I wonder what kind of face...
Ms. Shin Ga Hyeon made.
- Hello?
- This is Digital Security.
We've analyzed your voice recording.
There's a lot of static,
but the file wasn't fabricated.
It's comprised
of just one recording.
I'll email you the details.
What is your email address?
I'll...
I'll call you back later.
Ga Hyeon!
What brings you here?
I have to show you something.
What is it?
I can't show it to you here.
I'll show you inside.
Bae Jung Tae.
Did you kill him?
What?
What are you talking about?
Why would I kill him?
(New voice recording)
Detective...
That's Bae Jung Tae's voice,
and it wasn't edited.
I had it forensically analyzed too.
Did you really kill him?
- Hyeong Ju!
- Why did you play that for me?
Why?
Do you think I won't kill you here?
Go inside.
Ga Hyeon.
What's wrong? Is something going on?
No.
I have to be somewhere.
I'll call you later.
(Closed temporarily
due to personal reasons.)
Yes, Mr. Hwang.
I'll be at the cafe by six o'clock.
(Date: November 30, 2019,
Signature: Lee Shin)
What? Detective Ji did?
Yes, okay.
Why? What is it?
They're done with the forensic
examination of the scene.
But Ji Hyeong Ju took
the analysis of the footprints.
- When?
- This morning.
Oh, man.
Are you sure
we were going to meet at six?
Why isn't she coming?
The phone you have reached
is turned off.
- Goodness, her phone is off.
- Please leave your message...
What?
Do you think Ji Hyeong Ju
did something about her already?
- What are you doing?
- We should check...
with Detective Ji.
What if he notices
that we know about him?
But we can't just sit on our hands.
What if something really happens
to Ga Hyeon?
Whatever. You can do this alone
if you want to do it.
My goodness.
- He won't pick up.
- What is this guy doing?
I received a report
on Bae Jung Tae's case.
But it's kind of weird.
You killed him, didn't you?
Bae Jung Tae.
What do you mean?
I found this footprint
at Bae Jung Tae's house.
I clearly saw you
jumping over that wall.
Mr. Bae Jung Tae?
I already heard that
the footprints match.
Here.
Yes, I bought these.
But I put out number 21
in auction again.
The Starchio limited-edition
number 21...
you bought in auction.
Tell me.
You killed him, didn't you?
You killed everyone, didn't you?
You must be trying to
blame it all on me.
Nonsense.
What?
I have to meet Detective Ji now.
I'll be at the hospital
as soon as we're done talking.
He sure came early.
Detective...
(New recording)
I already saw everything.
I told the police already.
Even if I had to die,
I'm not going down alone.
Hey, Ko Jae Young.
You need to pull yourself together.
The one you saw isn't me.
You saw the real culprit!
Stop talking nonsense.
You already killed
Shin Ga Hyeon, didn't you?
Am I next?
Oh, maybe Mr. Hwang?
What are you talking about?
What about Ga Hyeon?
Captain, we have to report this
to our internal inspectors first.
Hey, Jin Sa Kyung.
It's not that
I'm suspicious of Detective Ji.
They're supposed to decide
the truth of this matter.
There could be a reason why
he didn't share the analysis result.
But this voice recording?
This is out of our hands.
How can you be suspicious
of your teammate?
I'm disappointed, Detective Jin.
Hey, Detective Nam, our job is
to be suspicious of our family too.
Even so, shouldn't we ask
Detective Ji first?
How can you want to
report this first?
Hey, Nam Soon Woo!
Hey, where are you?
- Things aren't good...
- Sun Ho, I need your help.
- What's wrong?
- Ga Hyeon is in danger.
That jerk will kill her too.
That jerk? What are you saying?
The one who killed Bae Jung Tae.
He already made a move.
I'm sure he did this.
He's going to kill Ga Hyeon too!
You need to speak in a language
I can understand.
Why would he kill Ga Hyeon?
Where's Ga Hyeon?
Why are you looking for her here?
Zian Clinic was the last place
her phone signal went off.
Really?
I haven't even seen her.
Stop lying.
Who's the culprit?
Where is Ga Hyeon?
You need to
catch the culprit yourself.
But you seem to be
the key suspect...
for Mr. Bae Jung Tae's case.
Please leave.
I know why you've been resetting.
(Samo Business Center)
Bae Jung Tae was right.
Your weakness.
Where is Ga Hyeon?
This footage is all we can provide.
Ga Hyeon!
Hyeong Ju.
Where are you?
Why did you turn off your phone?
I came to the office
because of work.
"The office"?
I sent you the Samson episode.
Please read and share your thoughts.
Samson? Samson is Ms. Son.
What?
Then please do take care of this.
Ga... Ga Hyeon.
There won't be a problem anymore.
Do you know what the CEO said?
That ever since...
I became your manager,
things have been unlucky.
The fan signing event,
the movie copyright contract,
and the promotion event.
He said I didn't do anything right.
Is that my fault?
You said you didn't want to
do anything!
So why do I have to be fired?
I'm sorry, Seung Min.
I didn't have any time...
to focus on anything else.
I'll talk to the CEO.
I'll help you get reinstated.
So please,
can you let my hands...
That again!
Those eyes again.
Why?
You don't even want to talk to me?
Should I leave already? Again?
Bae Jung Tae was right.
Your weakness.
Do you know...
how much I liked you?
I showed off to everyone that...
I became the manager
for "Hidden Killer".
I tried my best
to get on your good side.
So why do you ignore me? Why?
It really...
It really wasn't like that,
Seung Min.
There were...
some things that I couldn't share.
Things were...
really hard for me too!
Ms. Shin, why do you
keep ignoring me?
Hyeong Ju!
Hey, stop.
Ga Hyeon, are you okay?
Are you hurt?
I'm fine.
You're under emergency arrest
for kidnapping and confinement.
- Wait, Detective, no.
- You may consult an attorney.
- I was electrocuted...
- You may plead the Fifth.
I was attacked by her.
What if I didn't know
who Ms. Son was?
Samson? Samson is Ms. Son.
- What?
- Then please do take care of this.
Ga... Ga Hyeon.
Ji Han was about to reveal
who Samson is.
That's how far I got.
So who is Samson?
That brings me to my point.
Before we go in,
can you tell me about the identity?
Ms. Son is her manager.
Why did she suddenly bring that up?
Mr. Koo Seung Min was fired?
Yes, he received bribes
from event companies...
by using her fan signing event
and promotion event.
Those companies disclosed it to us
when the events got canceled.
Can you find out
Mr. Koo Seung Min's number?
His phone hasn't moved
to another area for an hour.
He's at Makang Bridge,
the way that heads to Sancheon.
Ko Jae Young was the one
who sent me that voice recording?
Does that mean
he was at the scene of his murder?
How?
We'll have to find out.
"We should trust each other."
You said that to me,
yet you suspected I was the culprit?
Come on.
Think about how I had to
get this forensically analyzed.
They said this wasn't forged,
- so I got suspicious...
- I should thank Koo Seung Min.
- He helped me get vindicated.
- It's not like that.
It's thanks to my theory.
The real culprit is a serial killer.
But you were with me...
when Mr. Cha Jeung Seok
and Ms. So Hye In...
- were presumed to have died.
- So...
That's why you aren't the culprit.
To be honest,
I wanted to do that to trust you.
There aren't many people...
whom we can trust.
Oh, it's only because
there aren't many of us left.
I guess I'm grateful
that you still trust me.
- I'm sorry. I'm...
- Wait.
I think your theory is right.
A serial killer.
There was a weird photo at the scene
of Bae Jung Tae's murder.
He took photos and left evidence.
And then, he left them
at Bae Jung Tae's house?
Why would the killer do that?
Where's the USB?
Here.
I reported it to the chief.
What did he say?
What do you think?
He said the same thing I said.
How could you assume
that this is a serial killing...
merely with those six photos?
That's why we should investigate.
Hyeong Ju, have you ever seen
a serial killing like this...
during the past seven years
on our team?
The victims' genders, age group,
occupations,
places of residence, or the MO.
What kind of serial killing
has no similarities?
Well...
Perhaps, the killer
feels pleasure...
in how his disguises are good...
and in how he fools the police well.
Based on the voice recording,
the killer is a detective.
You should call
the Seoul Metropolitan...
- Police Agency...
- First,
focus on summoning
Ko Seok Gyu's son.
Ko Jae Young sent this?
Are you talking
about Ko Seok Gyu's son?
- Yes.
- But how?
Did he wiretap the house?
Or is he the killer?
I don't think he's the killer.
I think he's a witness.
The witness?
Is this related to how you stole
the forensic report?
- I didn't...
- He didn't steal it.
He wanted to make up
for his mistake...
and catch the killer first.
- What?
- I had spotted someone suspicious,
but I let him go.
Thankfully, I found his footprint.
So I wanted to see
if his footprint matched...
the one at the crime scene.
I wanted to arrest him first.
And it turned out to be
Ko Jae Young, not the killer?
- Yes.
- If his footprint matched,
doesn't that mean he's the killer?
If that's the case, why would he
send the voice recording?
I think he sent that,
thinking I was the killer.
How ridiculous is that, right?
What are these looks
you're giving me?
Don't... Are you...
Don't tell me you think
I'm the killer.
Aren't we colleagues?
You are a key suspect.
I denied it.
I... I didn't...
I wasn't part of this.
How could you...
Hyeong Ju, come out for a second.
Sorry?
I'm taking you off of this case.
Captain Heo.
I received orders
from the higher-ups.
Since you're a key suspect,
all the evidence you've gathered...
will be invalidated.
If that happens, we'll have
to let go of the killer...
even if we catch him.
We'll focus on finding
Bae Jung Tae's killer.
You can investigate other cases...
or dig into Kim Se Rin's case.
Do whatever you like.
If there's a serial killer,
like you said,
you'll catch him either way.
Right?
What is this?
Mr. Bae Jung Tae sent this to me
before he was murdered.
What is this photo?
Let's just say
that it's Ms. Lee Shin's...
sole weakness.
It turns out she's a human
just like us, after all.
We're not the only ones
trembling in fear,
wondering when we'll die.
I'm sending you this
since I owe you one.
Come meet me
before I change my mind.
I'll be waiting.
A weakness?
Yes. What do you think he meant?
Who is she?
She's a psychiatrist
at Sejin Hospital.
When I had previously asked her
about Ms. Lee Shin,
she said she neither met
nor contacted her...
for the past three years.
This is fishy.
Do you think this is related
to this woman?
Who knows?
The one who was about to tell me
was murdered.
But I'm certain
that it's a weakness of hers.
All that I did
was show her this photo,
and she allowed me access
to Zian Clinic's CCTV footage.
(Choi Kyung Man: Heart attack,
Seo Yeon Soo: Fell)
(Samo Business Center)
I think this is it.
(April, 2019)
"Medi Forum"?
Ko Seok Gyu, the nominee
for Minister of Education,
will carry out his hearing tomorrow.
Which part of the hearing...
- is the most important to you?
- I'll be honest with my answers.
Please say a few words.
- Are you prepared?
- Please answer us.
- How did you prepare for it?
- Please comment.
I can't say for sure
about other things,
but he wants to hide
the crimes his son committed...
and hurt others
as collateral damage.
That kind of person can't be
the Minister of Education.
Why did it have to be today?
If it bothers you too much,
we can push back
his summons a few days.
What would you like to do?
So...
the dead guy was an ex-convict?
- Actually, I...
- It's fine.
In the worst-case scenario,
we can say that it was self-defense.
Did It happen at his house?
Yes.
I think we could make it look like
your son was abducted by him.
I'll let you decide, Attorney Han.
There should be as little commotion
as possible.
Do you actually think...
I killed someone?
It doesn't matter what I think.
Whether you actually did it or not,
there is no murderer
in this household.
Get ready and come out.
Dress as neatly as possible.
When I was Choi Min Ho,
I was too scared.
But this time, I'm going
to muster up the courage.
Look forward to tomorrow.
I'm going to meet up
with Detective Ji Hyeong Ju.
I'll go to the hospital
as soon as I'm done.
- What are you doing?
- Where's Bae Jung Tae's call log?
Captain Heo said you shouldn't...
I just need to check one thing.
Okay.
Here.
(Incoming, Outgoing)
What's wrong?
In the voice recording,
he was speaking...
with his sister.
I'll go to the hospital
as soon as I'm done.
That was his last call.
What? The phone that we found
at the crime scene showed...
that you were the last one
he talked with.
That means he had two phones.
The killer took it.
Then why did he leave
one of them behind?
Because they must've talked...
You better not be deceiving me.
(Jung Tae)
Okay. Thank you.
I received a call
when I got out of the hospital.
They wanted me to confirm his body.
He's always been like that.
He'd visit out of the blue
and surprise me.
Then he'd vanish.
Welcome...
We hadn't been in touch
for over a decade.
Then he suddenly visited me
in January.
Let go.
What's this? You just show up here
and shove me this? What is this?
With that much money,
you'll be okay...
even if you break up with that jerk.
If that jerk doesn't
want to divorce you,
call this number.
He didn't even come to my wedding.
He came to me
and told me to divorce my husband.
And he handed over a lot of money
I could never make in my life.
And he came to me
several months later...
and took me to a hospital.
(Sejin Hospital)
I didn't even get to thank him.
Now, he's gone forever.
Mr. Bae Jung Tae...
went on a very long
and difficult journey...
to save you.
I'm sure he'll be happy...
as long as you know
what he did for you.
(Bae Jung Tae, 010-648-0308)
This evidence proves
that you were...
at the scene on the day
of the victim's death.
And we have more evidence
that you were.
The recording file
you turned in yourself.
Did you kill...
- Bae Jung Tae?
- It wasn't me.
Then, how do you have
the recording file?
Bae Jung Tae blackmailed me
with a video.
I thought he might try to extort
money out of me with the video.
I wanted to find it
and get rid of it.
How are you feeling?
Darn it.
Ms. Lee Shin?
Why do you need her number
all of a sudden?
My gosh, we don't need to thank her.
I'll take care of it.
You just focus on getting better.
Ms. Lee Shin?
(Voice Recording)
I'm going to meet up
with Detective Ji Hyeong Ju.
I'll go to the hospital
as soon as I'm done.
He's early.
He sure came early.
Detective...
Jung Tae.
I didn't kill him.
Someone else killed him.
That means you know
who the culprit is.
I...
saw with my own eyes.
Ko Jae Young is extremely
anxious right now.
He heard Bae Jung Tae say...
he was going to meet up
with Hyeong Ju on the phone.
And after hearing the word,
"detective",
if he connected the killer
with Hyeong Ju...
because he's easily associated
with the word,
his statement of what he saw
could be wrong.
Some witnesses switched
the genders of the culprits.
And a witness testified
it was a child,
but the culprit was
actually an old man.
So what?
Let's proceed with hypnosis.
It's certain that Ko Jae Young
was at the scene.
It is true that
he did witness something.
Once we remove
his distorted memories,
we'll find a lead.
Let's send him back for today...
and request hypnosis
for the next interrogation.
Yes, sir. Okay.
Sun Ho, is it over?
- Yes.
- What is it? How did he record it?
Does he remember anything
about the culprit?
Aren't you dying to find out?
Same here.
It's about time that I knew...
what on earth is happening to you.
- What do you mean?
- You said...
whoever killed Bae Jung Tae
will try to kill Ga Hyeon.
You don't even know
who the culprit is,
but how did you make that conclusion
that he'll go after Ga Hyeon?
Sun Ho, Bae Jung Tae
has a lot of burner phones.
No. Don't change the subject.
It's driving me crazy.
This has been going on for months.
Hyeong Ju.
Hey.
(White Czerny,
Seo Yeon Soo, Naeilro Junkyard)
(Investigate Kim Dae Sung,
Now Clinic)
(Park Young Gil, dead, car accident)
(Seo Yeon Soo, Bae Jung Tae,
Kim Se Rin, Ko Jae Young)
The names you wrote down
in your notebook.
You made these notes in January.
Then, you must have known this
since January.
And half of these people died.
What's going on? Is this Death Note?
How am I suppose to understand this?
Sun Ho.
Will you believe me
no matter what I tell you?
Yes. I'll believe whatever you say.
Will you believe me
if I say I came from the future?
There's this person
who can repeat a year.
That person made an offer,
so I came from the future.
From January 11, 2020...
to January 11, 2019.
We call that reset among ourselves.
Hey.
What on earth
are you saying right now?
What?
Do you think
I'm in the mood for jokes?
Are you kidding me?
You said you'd believe me.
This is Ms. Lee Shin's weak spot?
I looked into this.
It was a symposium held
by Samo Pharmaceuticals...
to present a new product.
They introduced a new drug
which is being developed...
by a German company called Ratshe.
It was a drug that treats...
an incurable disease
called Helgransis.
What? Helgransis?
Aunt!
My goodness. You're here, Young.
- Have you been well?
- Yes.
Let's see
how much prettier you got.
- Have you been well?
- Yes.
The immune system
attacks its own body.
It's a type of autoimmune disease.
Kidney, stomach, and lungs.
The internal organs begin
to solidify in this order.
When the pulmonary alveoli harden,
patients die because
they are unable to breathe.
Do you think this means
that Ms. Lee Shin is suffering...
from Helgransis?
It's a possibility.
The symptoms of this disease
can't be seen externally.
If you're right,
it means that she continues
to undergo the reset...
because of the incurable disease.
But...
why is this her weak spot?
If she keeps repeating her life,
she can continue to live.
That means...
if she can't undergo the reset,
she will die.
I'm sure you remember
Oh Myung Chul's case.
My goodness.
You're under arrest
for attempted murder.
You know that you're acting
really strange today.
Ahn Gyeong Nam. Oh Myung Chul.
How did you know
he would go to the judge?
I knew because that
already happened once in my life.
I knew that Soon Woo would
be able to catch Jo Doo Pal.
Soon Woo will catch Jo Doo Pal,
so don't worry about it.
I arrested Jo Doo Pal.
Operation complete.
This was Nam Soon Woo, over.
That's how I knew that too.
Reset.
Okay. Reset.
Okay. Then, does Ms. Shin Ga Hyeon
believe you too?
Can she believe you because she's
an artist and is very imaginative?
Is that why you guys
have been working together?
She went through the reset with me.
And the names you saw
in my notes...
They all underwent the reset.
Even the people who died?
Yes.
Someone out there is killing us.
I thought whoever killed
Bae Jung Tae would kill Ga Hyeon...
because of our connection.
Koo Seung Min isn't the culprit.
But there's still a murderer
who's trying to kill us.
Can you pull over?
(Choi Young Woong isn't
the only one that must be silenced.)
(Unless you want this to go viral,
contact me.)
- Let go of the sneakers.
- Throw it.
- Does it hurt? Does it?
- Get up.
- Min Ho, does it hurt?
- Hey.
- Go ahead. Do it.
- Does it hurt?
Hook your leg.
Who on earth are you?
You told Detective Park
about the reset?
What did he say?
It's the same reaction we had
when we heard about the reset.
But...
he said he'll just believe me.
He said a lot of the cases
were solved when he did.
He'll just believe you.
That's nice.
Of course.
As someone who's been suspected,
I'm the most grateful to hear that.
You know what?
I still don't regret
that I did the reset.
It's like a nightmare.
And it's still tough.
Even if I have to go
through the same thing,
as long as I get to save someone
who will believe me unconditionally,
I'll make the same decision.
You might want to undergo the reset,
but it's only possible
if you survive.
Of course, we'll survive...
because I'll catch the culprit.
What a surprise.
You played along today.
Darn it.
Where is it?
(Young Woong and Se Rin,
our 1st day together)
This is...
Look at him smiling.
Don't they look familiar?
Detective Park.
Did you think I was Hyeong Ju?
Darn it.
I didn't kill him.
Someone else killed him.
That means you know
who the culprit is.
I...
saw with my own eyes.
You finally found out who it was.
But you won't have a chance to talk.
Darn it.
(365: Repeat the Year)
How long have you been deceiving me?
I'll go. It's more useful
than you'd think.
If you just kill him,
that's too merciful.
She underwent a reset
after saving all the people first?
I'm sorry for putting you
in pain again.
Does it mean you witnessed the act?
Making him suffer in pain
until his last breath...
Ms. Lee Shin. She was the only one
who knew about me in advance.
I really hope I'm next.
I'll catch the culprit,
so it doesn't come to that.
That's true revenge.