(Episode 19)
(New text message)
Darn it.
(Young Woong and Se Rin,
our 1st day together)
This is...
Don't they look familiar?
Detective Park.
Did you think I was Hyeong Ju?
You finally found out who it was.
But you won't have a chance to talk.
Darn it.
People say...
souls get attached to things.
You won't be lonely.
Please spare my life,
Detective Park.
There's something I need you to do.
Hey, have you had lunch?
- Yes, sir.
This is a video
recently uploaded on social media.
He said he'll disclose the history
of Ko Jae Young,
the son of Ko Seok Gyu,
Minister of Education nominee.
Ko Seok Gyu,
the Minister of Education nominee...
just resigned from the campaign.
I truly apologize once again
to the people of our nation.
Justice prevails in the end.
- Hey, Sun Ho.
- Negative reactions of the video...
- led to the resignation of...
- When is Ko's questioning?
This Friday. Why?
- Ko held a press conference...
- Just because.
- At his house.
- I'm not sure if Ko Seok Gyu...
will cooperate in this situation.
We have to make them do it.
That's why we're detectives.
Don't worry.
I'll take care of everything.
There was a total of
four detectives...
who visited Bae Jung Tae in prison
including Hyeong Ju.
He has three previous charges,
and he was released
with a warning a few times,
so a total of six detectives
wrote an affidavit on him.
If we make it obvious that
we're checking their alibis,
they'll only get hostile.
Make sure our information
doesn't get leaked out.
Find out their alibis
in the most discreet way possible.
- Yes, sir.
What about that burner phone
Hyeong Ju found?
I found the call history,
and I requested the call history...
of the people whom he talked to
on the day of the incident.
Check if any of them are...
connected to these detectives
as soon as you have the result.
Soon Woo, find the pictures
of the said detectives...
before Ko Jae Young's questioning.
Yes, sir.
This is a list of detectives
who contacted Bae Jung Tae.
Are you sure
you can share this with me?
I shouldn't.
But I trust you.
Look.
Do any of them look familiar?
You may have passed them by
on your way to his house.
I'm not sure.
(Police Officer Information)
Here's one thing
that I just don't understand.
If all the people who reset
their lives got murdered,
then how were they able
to turn back time?
(Kim Se Rin)
So...
she prevented them from dying
and did the reset?
This isn't your webtoon's plot,
is it?
I wish it were.
If he's the only one blabbering
about this, I'd ignore him.
But you're saying the same thing.
But still,
I don't think
this is serial killing.
Is there a reason
you think that way?
These photos were found
at Bae Jung Tae's place.
How did he have them?
- Was he a witness?
- That's impossible.
He had a solid alibi
during Cha Jeung Seok's death.
Then who took these?
I'm not sure.
It's either the murderer...
or someone who already knew
the murders would take place.
What does the latter mean?
It's Ms. Lee Shin.
She's the only one who knows...
when and where we'll die.
If she took these,
that means she knows
who the killer is.
She said that Kim Se Rin's case
was unsolved.
Just like
the Maseong Serial Murders,
Perhaps, only the victims
were found.
But we can't trust her.
Why did you agree
to reset your life?
- What?
- Judging by this place,
I don't think it was for the money.
I thought it'd be fun.
I'd be able to catch the culprits,
and I looked forward to teasing you.
But I had no idea I'd face
such a heinous murderer.
How was I?
What do you think?
You were the same.
Were we still partners?
Of course.
Who else would put up with you?
I guess I was still a detective.
You're only good
at being a detective.
Did I get a special promotion?
You? A special promotion?
Oh, please. Don't be ridiculous.
You could catch this killer with me
and get that promotion if you want.
- Okay?
- Deal.
Okay.
Soon Woo, let's give them out today.
Shouldn't we solve this case first?
Everyone's stressed out about it.
Fine. If we fail to catch the killer
and the case becomes unsolved,
we can leave our relationship
unsolved as well.
That shouldn't happen.
You shouldn't leave
your lives unsolved.
- Soon Woo, let's work hard.
- Yes, ma'am.
- Give it to me.
- Give what?
The wedding invitation.
How did you know?
Don't be shy, now.
January 12 at 12 p.m., right?
Give it to me.
Sa Kyung, I promise to be there
this time.
What's with him?
He's so annoying.
Sa Kyung, were you married before?
What are you talking about?
I can understand!
Sa Kyung!
We expected that number
for our first test.
That's not a bad result.
We'll do a checkup once again
before the next clinical test.
I'd like her
to finish her test here.
Would that be possible?
As long as the schedule fits,
I don't see a problem with that.
I'll ask.
Thanks.
She'll be back as soon
as her meeting ends.
Have you been well?
Young.
On the day of Bae Jung Tae's death,
he was on the burner phone
four times.
One of them was his sister,
Ms. Bae Jung Hee.
The other three were burner phones.
And they're all off.
We can track
where they were turned off.
Do any of the locations overlap
with the detectives on that list?
For now, no.
Since this is
circumstantial evidence,
we can't be direct and track them.
Did you find any other leads?
Mr. Jang Jin Ho died
on March 27.
Se Rin died on November 9.
For a killer who murdered
11 people in a year,
don't you think
that's a long hiatus?
There must've been a reason...
why he had to pause
for seven months.
Seven months?
Seven months...
You've been eyeing Bae Jung Tae.
You finally got him.
What's your relationship
with the victim?
She seems to be Ga Hyeon's friend.
Bye.
How do you know Ji Hyeong Ju?
I guess he didn't tell you anything.
But then again,
you wouldn't believe it
even if he told you.
We have a...
You'd better tell me the truth.
We transcended time and space.
We went to the past together.
What a lunatic.
I know I sound like a lunatic,
but you must've come
all the way here...
because something was strange.
You want to know
what Detective Ji is hiding.
I'll explain them to you one by one,
so do me one favor.
"The Memories of a Murder".
The Maseong serial killer...
will be caught in August.
You can find out
if I'm lying or not by then.
It was true that they analyzed
the DNA once again...
- to catch the killer.
- He's the one...
who committed the seventh murder.
The police suspected someone
who was innocent.
This is my first time hearing that.
Who told you that?
What?
It feels like he did it.
It also happened in that area.
I want to feign ignorance too.
But I already know everything.
- What?
- There's no way...
you'd understand me if I said
I came from... Never mind.
Are you saying you and Hyeong Ju
came from the future?
It's not just us two.
There are a few more.
- More?
- If you want to know more,
do find someone for me.
His name is Choi Min Ho.
Jang Jin Ho is...
Park Young Gil's replacement?
These are the people
who died in my hands?
(Park Young Gil)
Let's see
if things go according to...
(Kim Se Rin, Park Young Gil,
Hwang No Sub)
their fate.
Kim Se Rin.
Are you next?
This time, it's me.
I'm going to die.
Ga Hyeon, please help me.
I'm sorry.
Destined to die.
Destined to kill.
I've been way too passive.
It'll be fun to be a little bolder.
What?
(Young Woong and Se Rin,
our 1st day together)
(Calls)
Hello? Mr. Bae Jung Tae?
Are you sure everything is resolved?
You aren't deceiving me, are you?
The officers who were
on stakeout will pull out as well.
You can go back home.
Detective...
I saw the news.
I'm sure Se Rin will...
thank you for taking courage.
My high school teacher
called me yesterday.
She apologized...
for ignoring me back then.
I see.
She said a detective came by...
and asked her about me.
A detective?
Yes.
He asked her what my relationship
with Ko Jae Young was like...
and for the school I transferred to.
Do you think
that was Detective Ji Hyeong Ju?
It's not Hyeong Ju.
(Handong Logistics)
Even if Ms. Lee Shin
sent these pictures,
she wouldn't have
made a move herself.
We need to talk.
I'm investigating
Mr. Bae Jung Tae's case.
We found unknown DNA...
at the crime scene.
Will you provide...
a sample of your DNA
to find the suspect?
I refuse.
If you refuse right now,
I might find you suspicious.
I never went to his house.
If you really need my DNA,
bring me a warrant.
I never said
the crime scene was his house.
I'll bring a warrant.
Why are we postponing
Ko Jae Young's hypnotic questioning?
His attorney asked us
to postpone the schedule.
- What's the reason?
- He just said it's personal.
Things already seem
pretty grim for him...
because of his bullying incident,
so I'm sure he just doesn't want
people to find out...
that he's getting questioned
for a murder case.
Unbelievable.
I treat him like a testifier,
and he does everything as he likes.
I'll request a warrant for next time
to make sure we stay on schedule.
(Daeil Industry)
Who are you?
(Call history: Bae Jung Tae)
(Choi Young Woong isn't the only one
who needs to stay silent.)
(Call me
if you don't want this to blow up.)
(Messages)
(5-63 Seongju-ro, come alone
if you want to save Ko Jae Young.)
Drop the gun and raise your hands.
- It's a misunderstanding...
- Drop the gun!
Step back. Step back.
Turn around. Turn around.
His gun.
Arrest him.
You may plead the Fifth...
Stop! Stop right there!
Hey!
40N5845.
- Car number 40N5845.
- We need backup.
(Shin Ga Hyeon)
- Yes?
- Ga Hyeon.
- I was about to...
- Where are you? At home?
I'm on my way home.
You need to go home now.
Go home and stay there.
What's going on?
The culprit knows me.
I just fell into his trap.
- What?
- I'll call you again.
Go home. And be careful.
Wait, Hyeong Ju. Hyeong...
Yes.
What?
My gosh, what's going on?
You're here.
Officers in a patrol division
found him during their rounds.
Detective Ji was...
about to get arrested in action,
but he refused and ran away.
What did the forensics say?
They have to conduct
a postmortem exam on him,
but it looks like he died
well over two days ago.
I'm sure he had been looking for
a good way to abandon his body.
Who are you?
Team Leader Jung Ju Hyeon
of Regional Investigation Unit.
As of this hour,
we're taking over this case.
Come in. Please move aside.
One second.
One second, let me take a look.
They found his vehicle.
The suspect got away.
I can't believe this.
The proof found on the scene
is pretty evident,
so it'll take some time
to investigate.
Do you also think
Hyeong Ju is the culprit?
No.
I trust him
no matter what anyone says.
Hyeong Ju said...
the culprit seems like
someone who knows him.
And I think so too.
I'm sure he used
Ko Jae Young to lure him there.
That means...
it has to be someone
who knows their relationship.
I have to go see Ms. Lee Shin.
I'll go.
It's more useful than you'd think.
I'm Detective Park Sun Ho
of Makang Police Station.
Yes.
We met before
at the police station...
when I went to see Detective Ji.
Yes.
Back then, I didn't know
you were this affluent.
What do you mean?
Your clinic looks amazing.
Thank you.
May I ask why you're here?
I came to ask you a few questions
about the cases I'm investigating.
Kim Se Rin,
Bae Jung Tae, and Ko Jae Young.
You know them, don't you?
Yes.
You know that
they've been murdered, right?
- Yes.
- The only thing...
those three had in common was
this place, Zian Clinic.
You're right.
They all happen to be
my acquaintance.
Do you know anything
about their deaths?
The news said...
the one who murdered
Mr. Ko Jae Young is...
Detective Ji Hyeong Ju.
What do you think?
Do you really think...
Detective Ji is a murderer?
What's more important is
the evidence, not what I think.
That's why I've been investigating.
Are you suspecting anyone?
If you let me know,
it'll help with my investigation.
Am I suspecting anyone?
I can't cause any confusion...
because of my pure suspicion.
That means there is someone
you're suspicious of.
No.
There isn't.
Sir, Ko Jae Young had gone missing
three days ago.
I think they kept it a secret
in case the reporters swarmed...
around them when they found out
that he was missing.
Ji Hyeong Ju didn't call you either?
No.
Darn it.
I don't know what he's thinking.
We should've reported this...
to the internal inspectors
during Bae Jung Tae's case.
Look what happened to him
in the end.
But Corporal Ji doesn't have
any motive to kill Ko Jae Young.
He had to wait until the hypnosis
to reveal the real culprit,
so he could clear his suspicion
about the recording file.
He could have killed the victim...
because he was scared
that he would be exposed.
- Hey, Jin Sa Kyung.
- I'm frustrated too.
Shouldn't he at least call us?
We need to know what's going on
if we're going to help him.
If you know,
will you really help him?
(Nam Soon Woo and Jin Sa Kyung,
Sunday, January 12, 2020)
- Soon Woo.
- Hyeong Ju, where are you?
I have a favor to ask you.
Hyeong Ju.
Soon Woo?
Hey, you can't be here.
If you don't arrest me,
you'll be suspended.
I did come here alone.
I'll be okay.
What?
Sun Ho.
How did you find this place?
I found this from the list of
closed buildings the city manages.
This area will be redeveloped,
so there are no houses here.
And no one will come here as well.
What's your plan now?
We must catch the real culprit.
He knows me. That's why
he lured me into his trap.
He even knows my phone number.
You could have made a statement
at the scene.
Why did you run away?
You really messed this up.
If I get caught now,
some people will be in danger.
What? What are you talking about?
My goodness. Why don't
we let him get some rest today?
Get some rest.
Okay.
It's me. Open up.
- Sun Ho.
- Hey.
You scared me.
I brought some stuff...
you might need.
And you should use this for now.
I need to reach you somehow.
Hey, you.
What did you ask Soon Woo to do?
Is that a lead to catch the culprit?
It's a copy of the forensic report.
(Forensic Report)
We found that
at Bae Jung Tae's house,
but not at the scene
where Kim Se Rin was killed.
If I found anything, I was planning
to confront Ms. Lee Shin...
- and make a deal...
- I visited her already.
- You did?
- I had to save you somehow,
so I was hoping
she'd explain everything to me.
Gosh, she wasn't easy.
I don't think she'll spill
that easily.
Oh, right.
The handcuffs that were
around Ko Jae Young's wrists...
were mine.
- Really?
- Yes.
That means the killer
not only knows me...
but is around me as well.
None of the detectives...
on that list were from our station.
And someone who has ties
to Bae Jung Tae...
- Sa Kyung is the only one.
- That's absurd.
Didn't you say you received a text?
Let me look into that number.
I might be able to find a lead.
Thanks.
You don't need to say that.
I bought some bread.
Actually, I wanted
to buy you a meal.
(Forensic Report)
"Cineole"?
(Cineole)
"Alpha-terpinyl acetate".
(Terpinyl Acetate)
(Components of Cardamom)
"Cardamom"?
Sir. Sir.
- Ga Hyeon.
- Hyeong Ju.
Take care of him for me.
- Are you okay?
Yes, thanks to you.
What happened? Did you lose him?
Is he the killer?
I think so.
My goodness.
Does that mean I almost died?
Did you take those photos...
in the USB?
What photos?
Why would he?
A small box was found
in Bae Jung Tae's house.
And there was a USB inside.
There were crime scene photos...
of all the people who had died.
And we found traces of cardamom
in that box.
It's a type of spice that you enjoy.
(Cardamom)
Sir, what is this?
It's a type of spice
called cardamom.
Adding a bit of this to your tea
will enhance the flavor.
Sir...
I did leave that box there.
But...
I have nothing to do
with the photos or the USB drive.
How could you?
I'm sorry.
Ms. Lee Shin was even aware
of Ko Jae Young's voice recording.
Since when have you been fooling me?
The day after Ms. Lee Shin
came to my cafe,
I had visited Zian Clinic.
I wondered which one of you
would come and beg.
But I didn't expect it to be you.
But then again, the fear of death...
has nothing to do with your age.
You're wrong.
I've always wanted to die.
The only thing I worry about...
is how my wife will live
after I die.
I came here to find out...
when I'll die.
If I were to tell you,
would you do anything?
No matter what it may be?
Did she say you'd die today?
No. She didn't tell me.
She said she'd tell me
when the time comes.
What did she make you do?
She wanted me to tell her
how the rest of us were doing...
and the things we talked about.
I thought telling her
those things...
wouldn't do you any harm.
We've gone through
many things together.
It was...
really painful for me.
I had no idea...
she made me deliver
such gruesome photos.
I don't care if I die tomorrow.
I'll stop informing her.
No.
Please keep doing it.
What?
But...
tell us...
whenever she makes you
do something.
That is,
if you even consider us
your friends.
She isn't the one...
who's sick.
(It hurts.)
(Lee Young, Mommy)
You want her to be discharged?
Yes.
Yes, I think this place
will be better for Young...
than the hospital.
Yes, ma'am. I'll do that.
It's her daughter.
She's been resetting...
because of her sick daughter.
I'm sorry for putting you
in pain again.
I'm sorry for getting sick again.
(Late Lee Young)
Let me...
join you, Young.
Mommy...
I got the cause of death
for Ko Jae Young.
(Autopsy Report)
He bled to death.
His left lung was pierced...
by a knife as wide as 3cm.
And the killer twisted the knife.
It's the same MO
from Bae Jung Tae's case.
And we got Bae Jung Tae's blood
on the murder weapon?
What?
The killer stabbed
Ko Jae Young with the knife...
he used to stab Bae Jung Tae.
Does it mean it was done
by the same guy?
It's a serial murder?
That's the direction
the RIU is taking.
That means Ji Hyeong Ju...
just became a serial killer.
Hyeong Ju.
Come on in.
You're staying here?
What about the food?
Well, you know...
Take a seat.
The air in here is pretty bad,
but I can't open the windows.
Even before we catch the culprit,
you might die from an illness.
Even if I die,
I'll make sure to catch that jerk.
Don't worry.
How?
You can't freely move around
because you're a wanted suspect.
I must use fate.
That jerk...
will probably come after us.
We will end up meeting him...
even if we don't try?
So...
I really hope I'm next.
Hyeong Ju.
Our fate today will affect
our fate tomorrow.
I'll make sure to catch the culprit,
so it doesn't come to that.
Well, whether you catch him or I do,
we'll catch him pretty soon, then.
(Missed call, Choi Young Woong)
Hello, Young Woong.
Really?
It would be mean a lot to me.
Okay. See you soon.
I think I might be able
to find the detective...
who was in contact
with Bae Jung Tae.
How?
There was a detective who came...
to Young Woong's school
and asked about Choi Min Ho.
He's going to meet with the teacher
who talked to the detective.
Could Bae Jung Tae...
and that detective be related
to our case?
As soon as Bae Jung Tae
got out of prison,
he told Ko Jae Young that
Choi Young Woong was Choi Min Ho.
How do you think he found that out
when he was locked up?
So you think that detective
must have done his legwork.
Yes. It's still a possibility.
I'll check on it and call you back.
Okay.
Thank you for your time.
Can you recognize...
the detective that came to
the school among these detectives?
Yes, Ga Hyeon.
The teacher said he wasn't...
on the list of detectives
I showed him.
I see. Right.
It's hard to recognize someone
just by looking at the photos.
We rarely get a lead that way.
Don't let it discourage you.
Okay. I'll call you again.
Go home before it gets dark.
Okay. I will.
Bye.
(Seoul Makang Police Station)
Ga Hyeon.
Did something happen?
What's wrong?
The detective that went
to Young Woong's school...
I found out who he is.
Who is it?
It's Detective Park.
Sun Ho?
What are you talking about?
On the day he came to the school...
He was on crutches.
The detective was on crutches.
We kept questioning...
why there hadn't been...
any murders for seven months.
Hold on, Ga Hyeon.
This is an awful joke you're making.
Young Woong's teacher...
identified him too.
I'm sure of it.
It was this detective.
- Let's go.
- Three.
Let's take 1 more. 1, 2, 3.
- Did you get it?
- Hyeong Ju,
can you smile a bit?
Yes. Why are you so grumpy?
- Look at him pretending to be cool.
- You need to show this.
- The autograph?
- Yes.
Let's take another one.
- All right.
- Smile.
Okay. Smile.
In 1, 2, 3.
That was great.
I'm sure he's mistaken.
Why would he do that?
Sun Ho is a detective.
Hyeong Ju.
The culprit is a detective too.
I know that. I know,
but even if every detective
in Korea is a suspect,
Sun Ho would never be one.
Bae Jung Tae...
was murdered on the day
when he was no longer a suspect.
Ko Jae Young...
had gone missing...
on his way back home
after the questioning.
And on the day
when his body was found,
the culprit sent
a text message to you.
The culprit knew exactly
how the investigation panned out...
and the relationship
between you and Ko Jae Young.
Someone so close to us
was able to do all of this,
but because
we trusted him so much...
and he was so close to us,
- we didn't even suspect him.
- Ga Hyeon.
This isn't a webtoon.
You can't just force the story
for the sake of finding the culprit.
I hope I'm imagining things too.
I hope I'm imagining
however I want...
because I'm desperate
to catch the culprit.
Sun Ho...
is like a family to me.
He's not someone you can
just accuse of being a murderer.
Hyeong Ju.
It's a trap.
He probably called the patrol
division after luring me in.
We didn't receive any reports.
The closed buildings
are being inspected.
They found it on their patrol.
I found this from the list of
closed buildings the city manages.
This area will be redeveloped,
so there are no houses here.
And no one will come here as well.
Hey, why are you wandering around?
If you need anything, just call me.
Sun Ho.
Yes.
How could you believe...
what I told you that easily?
- What?
- That we were killed...
by a serial killer.
There's no definite evidence.
But why did you believe me?
I still can't fully believe it.
We can't call it
a serial murder because...
a few common items like
a phone and gloves disappeared.
Who would believe that?
I'm just saying I'll believe you
because you said so.
Right.
Sun Ho, let me borrow your car.
My car? Why?
There are checkpoints...
all over the city to catch you.
Where will you go?
I just need to meet someone.
Who?
Give me your car key.
If you get caught,
say that you stole it from me.
Okay.
(Detective Park Sun Ho)
(Detective Park Sun Ho,
Slide to Answer)
But can't you just check
the security footage?
Sadly, that was
when the cameras got changed,
so there's no way
to prove your innocence.
I fell asleep
on my way down from the mountain.
Then I heard two women in a fight.
I left the park after she did.
What brings you here?
Excuse me.
Is there Mr. Choi Hyun Woo?
That's me. What is this about?
Well...
Detective Ji.
Detective Park asked me for a favor.
He said it was a simple accident,
but an innocent woman...
was in a tight spot
because she didn't have an alibi.
I know how that feels
because I had been falsely accused.
So I just made the report
as he asked.
He didn't commit suicide.
Given the circumstances,
it wasn't an accident.
Are you saying he was murdered?
The owner of a store
nearby testified...
that Cha Jeung Seok purchased
charcoal briquettes from him.
It's been a few years...
since we stopped selling
charcoal briquettes.
I would've remembered
if a detective came.
Why did you come here?
What if I wanted to call the police?
Who is...
the culprit?
I think you already know the answer.
I guess you didn't have
the courage to ask him yourself.
That's right.
It's Detective Park Sun Ho...
whom you had saved.
He's the culprit.
But Sun Ho died.
- But...
- It was actually quite easy.
You just had to avoid the place
on the day of your deaths.
Are you Mr. Cha Jeung Seok?
Where are you taking me?
What happened?
Did you really think
I would save you one at a time?
It was quite simple as long
as I took care of one culprit.
You know Ji Hyeong Ju?
And I know a lot about you,
Mr. Oh Myung Chul.
I know that you're going
to kill Ji Hyeong Ju today.
But do you know
what true revenge is?
If you just kill him,
that's too easy.
Making him suffer in pain...
until his last breath...
is true revenge.
But someone said...
the killing would be too easy.
It's better to let you live in pain
until the day you die.
That's true revenge.
Until my fifth reset,
Oh Myung Chul was trying to kill...
you.
But he failed every time...
and was arrested by you.
And all I did was
just twist that fate.
Thanks to Oh Myung Chul,
I was able to undergo
the reset with you all.
Everything was planned
from the get-go?
Are you telling me
because I saved him...
people died?
Is that what it is?
Why on earth are you doing this?
You have a child whom you must save.
You know firsthand
how painful death is.
That's why I gave you all a chance.
I wanted to see
if anyone would be able to...
change their fate.
Now that you know
who the culprit is,
you just need to catch him.
I'll keep watching to find out...
who will survive in the end...
and if changing one's fate
is possible.
Isn't that Detective Ji?
That's him.
Stop right there.
Stop.
Detective Ji.