Episode 13
You all remember.
the first phone call...
from Ms. Lee Shin, right?
It was the train derailment.
What are you talking about?
They were all alive.
What if it wasn't before the reset?
But the life before the reset?
What?
What if she observed us, so she knew
what would happen to us...
in advance?
That's right.
All of you...
were...
dead before.
It's cozy and nice.
I've always wanted to visit.
How long has it been?
Has it been around seven months?
Who are you?
- Where have you been...
- So?
Are you not happy to see me?
I'm sure you have many questions.
Look, let's hear her out first.
What do you mean
by we were dead?
During the first five resets,
you've all died each time.
But during the sixth,
I decided to save you.
And I've invited you
for the seventh.
Didn't we meet for the first time
at Zian Clinic?
So when and how
did you save our lives?
It was actually quite easy.
You just had to avoid the place
on the day of your deaths.
(The elevator is being repaired.)
- Fix it and come on over.
- Okay.
Mr. Choi couldn't go
to the get-together...
because he had to fix the elevator.
Ms. Seo couldn't go to the park
because her clothes got wet.
Mr. Cha was arrested
for compulsive gambling.
Are you Mr. Cha Jeung Seok?
Where are you taking me?
(Handong Logistics)
What happened?
Mr. Park was late to work
because of a flat tire.
Ms. So was out delivering flowers.
Flower delivery.
You all evaded death.
You saved our lives
through a phone call...
and a cup of coffee?
Do you really think we'd buy that?
If the fate is already known,
it's easy to change it.
You've all experienced it.
You saved your once-dead colleague.
You're walking once again.
You didn't need any superpowers,
did you?
Then...
what about us?
How did you save us?
I'm not sure.
How did I save you again?
What's wrong with you?
What grudge do you have against us?
I don't have any resentment
against you.
I just have a lot of time.
I was curious...
whether fate...
was destined...
or changeable.
That's why I carried out
this experiment.
I wondered how things would pan out
if I saved those who were...
meant to die and convinced them
to reset their lives.
I even gave you hints
by sending those bouquets.
Are our lives a joke to you?
- Detective Ji.
- Calm down, Detective Ji.
You don't have much time.
Do you want to spend what's
left of your time as an assailant?
Darn it!
Let me go!
Aren't you all curious...
when, where, and how you'll die?
If you're a bit more polite,
I could tell you.
"Polite"?
Did you say, "polite"?
And what's your definition of that?
Do you expect us to beg
and be willing to do anything...
like an animal being dragged
into a slaughterhouse?
If that's what you want to see,
you will never get what you want.
I wonder if you can be
this confident until the end.
The next victim...
will die a gruesome death.
Don't be too scared.
I still have hope...
that you can change your fates.
You're going to get even busier.
Stop right there. Stop!
Stop!
Detective Ji.
Do you think there's a way
to win against her?
We'll either tremble in fear
and die...
or save ourselves by begging.
Either way, it'll be what she wants.
I'm sure there's a way.
I'm positive.
The next victim...
will die a gruesome death.
Did you find him?
He neither emigrated nor died,
so why can't you find him?
Come on.
(Ko Seok Gyu)
("Ko Seok Gyu,
Minister of Education,")
("Soon to Undergo
Confirmation Hearing")
("Will He Make It?")
(Choi Kyung Man, 62 years old)
(Seo Yeon Soo, 29 years old)
(Cha Jeung Seok, 41 years old)
(So Hye In, 32 years old)
(Park Young Gil, 37 years old)
Hyeong Ju.
Ji Hyeong Ju.
What's on your mind?
I just called you.
Hey.
Someone's here to see you.
Who?
(Seoul Makang Police Station)
It's him, isn't he?
He's that senior you saved.
Why are you here?
You're the one who should tell me.
Don't you have any questions for me?
A detective of Violent Crimes.
That's a dangerous job.
And for people like you,
it can be threatening.
I know.
I'm sure you want to find something
and put those handcuffs on me.
I hope you do that before you die.
I clearly said...
the next person who dies
will die a gruesome death.
Don't you want to know who it'll be?
Your plan is evident.
You'll want to control me
with a few words I can't confirm.
I won't let you do that anymore.
In that case,
you'll have to do better.
You don't have much time left.
I put a tail on Ms. Song.
I don't know why all of you
gather at Zian Clinic...
or why you're dying one at a time.
But what I do know...
is that Lee Shin is capable
of anything.
It's as if she knows the future.
She knew everything about me.
Are you suggesting that
she had been putting on a show?
She might have done as she's told
because Lee Shin knows her weakness.
Anyway, ever since
Ms. Lee Shin came to the cafe,
Ms. Song had been very busy too.
What about this? What's this?
Right here. Take a closer look.
It's a law firm called
Park and Park Law Firm.
They're the best and the most
expensive attorneys in Korea.
Is she preparing
for a fight in the court?
There is something I'm suspecting.
(Seoul Makang Police Station)
When can we have the result?
All right. Thank you.
- Is that for Bae Jung Tae?
- Yes. You were right.
He applied for parole.
- When is the evaluation?
- Next week.
You know Attorney Park Won Jun
of Park and Park Law Firm, right?
He specializes in paroles.
He'll be 100 percent approved
if he has Park on his side.
Anyway, why do you suddenly
want to know about Bae Jung Tae?
I clearly said the next person
who dies will die a gruesome death.
You don't have much time left.
Thanks for looking into it.
Hey, Hyeong Ju...
What's with him?
Bae Jung Tae will be released soon.
Already?
Here.
(Apply for a visit)
Mr. Bae Jung Tae is
unable to see you today.
He's meeting someone else.
What?
You kept refusing to see me.
Why did you call?
Choi Min Ho.
You haven't found him, have you?
He's pretty difficult to find.
It was really tough for me
to find him too.
You haven't found him to this day,
but you found him
while you were stuck here?
- Do you expect me to believe that?
- I don't care if you do.
What's important is the fact.
I have Choi Min Ho in my hands now.
But over the last seven months,
my pricing for information
went up a little.
Are you asking for money again?
How much more do you need...
I don't need money.
I need you to help me
with something else.
Se Rin...
Ga Hyeon.
What's wrong?
Why were you at Zian Clinic?
Did you meet with Ms. Lee Shin?
Yes.
Why? What did she say?
You came much later than I expected.
I thought you would
come running first.
Can you just tell me...
when I'll die?
If you want to know something,
you'll have to pay the price.
But I don't want anything.
As you know,
I already have a lot.
What I need is...
fun.
She told me who'll die next.
When and how that person will die.
- What?
- She said she'll let me live...
if I let that person die.
She told me to choose...
either to save that person
or save myself.
What should I do, Ga Hyeon?
Who is it?
Who's that person?
Was it me?
Tell me.
Did she say I'll die next?
Yes, Ga Hyeon.
When?
Where?
How will I die?
Stop crying and start talking!
(Shin Ga Hyeon)
(You have 7 missed calls.)
(Kim Se Rin)
Ms. Lee.
It looks like
you had a good talk with her.
- Great job.
- Wait, Ms. Lee.
Don't worry.
I always keep my promises.
Should I escort her
to the counseling room?
It's way too late
for a counseling session.
This is fun.
Let's keep watching her.
Open the door.
Please open this door.
Will you please open this door?
I know you're in there.
You're lying again, aren't you?
You're experimenting with us again!
Open this door!
What about your appointment
with the professor?
I'll call.
Please!
Please.
Please...
The next person will...
die a gruesome death.
Please. Please open this door.
Stop lying.
You're lying, aren't you?
Gosh, it's freezing.
Man, are you working at home too?
- Let's eat.
- I'm not in the mood to drink.
That's exactly
when you should drink.
Here.
I heard
Bae Jung Tae will be released.
That jerk must have
some affluent person behind him...
to have Park and Park Law Firm
work for him.
How's your leg?
My legs still hurt.
They hurt even more whenever
you cause trouble. It hurts now.
Anyway, it's not like
this is the first time we got hurt.
We need to quit Violent Crimes
if we get scared of that.
You're right.
You live knowing you'll die one day.
You work as a detective
knowing you'll get hurt.
That's how I lived to this day.
Why am I suddenly scared?
Did I think I'm invincible?
Everyone is like that.
It seems like
death is for everyone else.
You feel like
death might just pass you by.
That's how you could live.
If you worry about death every day,
that's barely living.
Why are you suddenly so serious?
You aren't even drunk.
Here.
(Koo Seung Min)
(Missed calls:
Koo Seung Min, Kim Se Rin)
Is it Bae Jung Tae?
Is that why
you reappeared after seven months?
Why do you think so?
If not, there's no way
you'd give him...
the best law firm in Korea
to get him out on parole.
I knew it.
You really are a detective.
Is Bae Jung Tae
related to the death...
of the next person?
You have a lot of questions.
I thought there was
nothing you want to hear from me.
You said you won't
let me fool you anymore.
If you're scheming something
with a petty criminal like Bae,
then you'll never get me.
Detective Ji.
You should be thanking me.
I'm paying...
for the mistake you made.
What are you talking about?
Well, it's not like
a detective is a deity.
You could always make a mistake.
Don't be so hard on yourself.
Yes?
I'm sorry.
I'm expecting an important guest.
Ga Hyeon.
Why are you here?
I'll tell you later.
Was there an emergency last night?
Why were you looking for me
so desperately?
Is there a way for me to live?
If I do as you say,
could I really live?
Of course.
Only if you ask politely.
What do I have to do in return?
We'll have to
think about that together.
I think...
things will be even more fun
with you, Ga Hyeon.
We still have a lot of time.
You said I'm next.
Who said that?
- I never said that.
- What kind of a joke is this?
I'm not joking.
It means someone is lying.
Who do you think is...
lying?
Ga Hyeon.
What's wrong?
I heard I'll be next,
that I'll die next.
But it was a lie.
What are you talking about?
(Kim Se Rin)
Why are you calling her?
Se Rin.
Se Rin, are you home?
Who are you?
Are you looking for Se Rin?
Are you her friend?
Can you reach her right now?
I'm her sister.
Mom said she couldn't reach her,
so I came by. Is she not at home?
You... You're her sister?
- Her biological sister?
- Yes.
I was the weakling,
but my older sister
passed away first.
It was the same way
your friend passed away.
She got into a car accident.
She tried to save me
but got hit by the car instead.
Are you really her older sister?
This time, did she say I died?
If she's not here, she's probably
at the club room of her university.
Her university?
Isn't she a repeater?
I can't believe this.
(Volunteer Club Voluntas,
Jangmoon University)
- Kim Se Rin?
- You know, with Young Woong.
Oh, the terminally ill one?
"Terminally ill"?
She lied to Young Woong saying
she's terminally ill, got caught,
and created huge chaos.
She does look
pretty feeble and weak.
She fooled us too.
Young Woong is going to the army
because of her too.
She had been stalking him badly.
(Ms. Lee Shin: 1 image)
(Untitled)
Are you sure you can do anything?
Yes.
Who do you think will die next?
(Episode 14)
- Ms. Lee.
- It looks like you had...
a good talk with her. Great job.
- Ms. Lee.
- Don't worry.
I always keep my promises.
You should go on a trip
for the time being.
I advise you to get out of Seoul.
For how long?
Can you elaborate on that?
When you're safe,
I'll call you again.
Your friend didn't come back yet?
We need to get going now.
(Hongwoon Express)
The person you have reached
is unavailable.
You'll be directed
to the voicemail box.
What are you doing?
Young Woong!
(Kim Se Rin)
It's called Munchausen syndrome.
You know, the disorder that makes
you lie and pretend to be sick.
I was in a ramyeon box...
when I was abandoned
in front of an orphanage.
My parents were killed by robbers.
I was the only one who survived.
There's no cure yet.
I have three months at the most.
My gosh. Poor you.
She's buying people's sympathy
by lying to them.
She thinks
that's how people will love her.
I've done nothing wrong.
That wench was determined
to set me up.
Well, it's not like
a detective is a deity.
You could always make a mistake.
Don't be so hard on yourself.
You have a visitor.
What?
Okay. I'll call you later.
Ga Hyeon, Young Woong is gone.
He just left his phone.
And he disappeared.
I called the police,
but I can't report it
since it hasn't been 24 hours yet.
Ga Hyeon,
can you talk to the detective?
Can you ask him to find Young Woong?
Please?
I met your older sister.
The one who died in a car accident.
Your dead sister.
What?
Why did you lie to me?
Don't believe what she told you.
She has a lot of problems,
so she used to go
to therapy and stuff.
You were the one who had therapy.
You said you were retaking the CSAT
and your parents hated you.
They were all lies.
Are you...
taking my sister's word over mine?
Okay. Fine.
Suit yourself.
I don't care about what you think.
Young Woong.
Can you...
ask the detective to find him?
Please?
Please, Ga Hyeon.
Young Woong...
is at the police station.
What?
You are here...
to report Ms. Kim Se Rin?
That makes no sense.
Why would he do that?
I thought about letting this go
until I joined the military.
But after finding out that
she downloaded a tracking app,
I couldn't let it slide anymore.
I only did that
because I was worried about him.
She threatened me that she'd
kill herself if I broke up with her.
I'm sick of it now.
I really can't live
without him, Ga Hyeon.
It has to be that house.
I should have known
when she moved next door to mine.
I found out she approached me
with a plan.
Why do you think
I went through the reset?
I've done a lot of things
to meet Young Woong.
I can't give up like this.
Over my dead body. I can't.
Will you say you did this
because of Young Woong?
Are you sure you can do anything?
Yes.
Who do you think is next?
Next up...
is you.
How does it feel?
Aren't you scared?
Well, all of you will die anyway.
But being the next one to die...
must terrify you.
And if someone else gets terrified,
that will be
such good entertainment for me.
You choose, Se Rin.
To whom must you say this
to entertain me?
And think about what you should say
to make it more fun.
Then, I'll tell you...
how you can save yourself.
Why did you do it?
Why was it me?
You would have done the same.
The person you're closest to.
The person who will not doubt you.
You'd probably choose
that kind of person.
You... How could you?
Don't resent me.
You're scared of dying too.
You were at ease when
you found out it wasn't your turn.
So...
did Ms. Lee Shin tell you?
Did you sell me out
and save yourself?
Yes.
That's why I'm grateful to you.
Since I'm grateful to you,
let me ask one more favor.
Tell the detective...
to just send Young Woong home.
(Complaint, Choi Young Woong)
(Defendant: Kim Se Rin)
(Plaintiff: Choi Young Woong,
Presenter: Ji Hyeong Ju)
(Complaint, Choi Young Woong)
It's all done now.
Detective Ji.
I have something to tell you.
I started...
to date Se Rin
after the assault incident.
But now that I look back on it,
something was strange about that.
Unless you want me to go crazy,
call him now!
Kim Se Rin.
Do you know
where I should cut myself,
so I don't die and just get hurt?
I know it very well...
because I needed that often.
If you don't want to end up
like Bae Jung Tae, call him!
"Bae Jung Tae"? What do you mean?
Tell me! What do you mean by that?
That man asked her,
"What are you trying to pull?"
Who are you?
What are you trying to pull?
No matter how many times
I thought about it,
it sounded strange to me.
Are you saying...
it was all your doing?
Yes. It was me.
You and the police...
were all fooled by me.
Who'd believe an ex-convict?
Like I expected,
everyone believed me...
and put him behind bars.
Kim Se Rin.
Do you think you're an exception?
(Koo Seung Min)
Ms. Shin, are you in there?
Ms. Shin!
Ms. Shin?
Who... Who are you?
Ms. Shin. Ms. Shin.
Ms. Shin, you're bleeding.
Are you okay?
Oh, no. You're bleeding.
What should I do?
I'm so upset.
Shouldn't you report this
to the police?
Seung Min.
I'm sorry,
but I'd like to be alone.
Ms. Shin.
Please.
All right.
I'll be going, then.
Thank you, Ga Hyeon.
It must be pretty tough
because of that.
You always have to be the best.
You always have to
live up to other people's standards.
Cheers.
That was out of the blue.
I wonder why...
you've suddenly become curious
about that.
Whom did Kim Se Rin betray
this time around?
I know I'm late, but I'm willing
to listen to the truth now.
"The truth"?
I like that
you decided on this quickly.
What do you need me to do?
It may be difficult.
You may not understand.
But I'll make sure...
to compensate handsomely
for your work.
You have my word.
I want you to keep an eye on Se Rin.
Kim Se Rin?
She suffers
from an anxiety disorder.
She's unpredictable.
I'm just worried...
she might die.
Back then, I didn't understand
what she meant.
But now, I do.
She was worried
Se Rin would self-harm...
and end up dying.
I beg you.
The other students
feel uncomfortable about this.
I'm grateful that you like me,
but let's just stay as friends.
Why?
What did I do so wrong?
Why are you doing this to me?
Young Woong!
Se Rin, please!
Why are you doing this to me?
Young Woong!
What do you want?
Why are you crying
and making a fuss in public?
Why do you care?
Was he harassing you?
- What?
- If he wasn't, then never mind.
You see,
I can't stand scumbags
who harass women.
Can you help me?
Actually...
She said he was stalking her.
He wanted me to frighten him a bit.
I called both of them just now.
- Se Rin.
- I'm so scared.
Se Rin, are you there?
It's that house.
Did that scumbag do this?
You just need to scare him...
so that he won't come back.
This is exactly why
the police exist...
and we pay tax. You should've asked
Ji Hyeong Ju for help.
I thought you two were close.
(Young Woong, please come
to my house right now.)
What are you doing?
What are you doing? Hey, hey.
What are you... Stay still!
Hey!
What's wrong with you?
What are you doing?
Se Rin!
- Young Woong!
- Who are you?
Young Woong!
Who are you?
What are you trying to pull?
You did well.
You should run...
because no one's going
to believe you.
- Do you really want to die?
- Mr. Bae Jung Tae!
Then what about that
written statement?
What about it?
I just wrote down
what my lawyer told me.
He talked about my past crimes,
the circumstances, and the witness.
He said claiming innocence
would only worsen my sentence...
and that it'd be better
to just admit to it...
and aim for a lesser sentence.
Everything he said was correct.
That's why I wrote it.
If you want, you can sue her
for committing calumny.
You can request
for a retrial as well.
That's fine.
At first, I was determined...
to end her the moment I got out.
But now, I'm too lazy
to do anything.
Do you know why Ms. Lee Shin
helped you receive parole?
I guess she's paying me back...
for keeping an eye on Kim Se Rin.
Was there anything else
she asked you to do?
She didn't. I don't care
about that woman or Zian Clinic.
I won't even think
about going there.
I'm going to move back
to the countryside and farm.
And I'll die
when it's my time to die.
Young Woong, reported me?
No way. There's no way he did that!
Ms. Kim Se Rin, calm down.
Put the knife down.
Call Young Woong now!
Kim Se Rin!
Why are you here?
Call Young Woong now!
That guy isn't even your boyfriend.
You're just chasing him
like a madwoman!
No!
He even patted my head...
and waited for my bus.
We even had meals together.
Please!
You always cause trouble.
And why do we have to
clean up your mess?
I'm so sick of this!
Don't threaten us with your life.
You should really kill yourself.
What?
Let go of me!
Bring Young Woong here!
Call him now!
- Bring him here.
- Move.
Bring him here now!
Young Woong!
Se Rin.
Young Woong reported me.
I went back in time
just to be with him.
It's just like before the reset.
No, it's more awful.
I was really happy with him.
I keep thinking about
my previous life. I can't stand it.
I gave you a way out
from all of this.
Why are you still here?
Is he more important than your life?
If you die,
your love will be useless.
Without Young Woong,
my life is pointless.
Ms. Lee, let me do the reset
one more time.
Then, I'm sure
I can do a better job.
Please give me one more chance.
I'm begging you.
Fine.
Really?
To do that,
you must survive first, right?
At first, I was determined...
to end her the moment I got out.
But now, I'm too lazy
to do anything.
I'm going to move back
to the countryside and farm.
And I'll die
when it's my time to die.
(Happy Correction, Happy Citizen)
Did you sort everything
out with Se Rin?
I guess it wasn't a happy ending...
where you understood each other
and made up with her.
Even you couldn't...
forgive her that easily, right?
Does your daughter...
know that
she's going through the reset?
If she finds out
that she's repeating...
the same year over and over again
because of your cruel hobby,
what will your daughter think?
"Cruel hobby".
I'll try to match your description.
I'll tell you...
who's really next.
No.
I won't let you have power
over me anymore.
Ga Hyeon,
you could save this person.
Are you sure you won't regret it?
Hello?
(From Seoul to Haenam)
Sir, hold on!
Please open the door now. Hurry!
(Changsun Express)
(Sejin Hospital)
Her heart transplant surgery
went well.
It was hard to find a donor
who was a match to your sister.
But Ms. Lee made sure
she had a donor.
Jeong Ae.
That woman over there.
Who is she?
My gosh.
You don't believe me, do you?
Were you scared that I might get
back at Kim Se Rin?
You're going home, right?
You'll be relieved
once you drop me off at my home.
Then, give me a ride.
- Your younger sister...
- My gosh.
Let's not talk
about our personal lives.
Coming home was pretty easy
thanks to you.
Be careful.
And see you around.
I'll make sure
we never cross paths again.
Please forget about me.
Are we good now?
Tell me now.
Choi Min Ho is Choi Young Woong.
What?
You guys are tangled up
like a ball of yarn.
But...
let me go first.
There's so much
we have to catch up with, right?
(Kim Se Rin)
(Missed call, Kim Se Rin)
The person you are calling is
on another line.
You'll be directed
to the voicemail box.
(Trustworthy police, safe country)
(You have a new voicemail.
Press Call to listen to it.)
This is your first message.
Ga Hyeon, answer the phone.
I'm next.
I'll die.
I'm not lying this time.
I'm serious.
Ga Hyeon, I'm sorry.
I'm sorry.
Ga Hyeon, please save me.
(Recent Calls, Kim Se Rin)
Get a grip, Shin Ga Hyeon.
(Young Woong and Se Rin,
our 1st day together)
(365: Repeat the Year)
Isn't fate so fascinating?
Why did you let her die?
I would like to make a report.
Bae Jung Tae got out yesterday.
The decision is yours, Ms. Lee.
What is this? What did you do?
That's not true, right?
It's not, right?
This unexpected turn of event
will make it entertaining.
- I won't let you slide for this.
- I have high hopes.
Murder? I never thought
that would happen.
We just had an argument.
I didn't kill her.
- I really didn't kill her.
- Answer my questions!
Whether you're the culprit
or were committing another crime.
She died just now.