(Episode 21)
It might sound crazy,
but I'll do everything I can...
to not see you lying here.
- Sun Ho.
- It's Detective Park Sun Ho...
What?
Whom you had saved.
He's the culprit.
If you die like this, I'll kill you.
Hyeong Ju.
I seriously won't die.
Hey, Ga Hyeon.
What brings you here without a call?
I got worried
after what you said on the phone.
I heard you met Ms. Lee.
Right.
I'm fine.
I wasn't really expecting anything.
I see.
It would've been better
if she remembered anything.
You're right.
Yes.
Okay, then. Go in and get some rest.
Bye.
How could you believe...
what I told you that easily?
That we were killed
by a serial killer.
There's no definite evidence.
But why did you believe me?
Hyeong Ju.
Sun Ho wasn't here, was he?
Did he contact you in any way?
I...
I brought him here.
Ga Hyeon, are you okay?
Hyeong Ju.
I'm all right.
You were right.
Sun Ho...
killed those people.
It's not too late for us
to right the wrongs.
You're still a detective.
It's way too early to give up.
Do you also think...
Hyeong Ju is the culprit?
I trust him
no matter what anyone says.
Hyeong Ju said...
the culprit seems like
someone who knows him.
How can he...
How?
It's because of me.
Your life is also in danger
because of me.
So this is why I end up killing you.
So everything was planned?
All these people died...
because I brought him back to life?
Corporal Jin Sa Kyung.
Where's Detective Ji Hyeong Ju
right now?
We're doing our best
to look for him too.
You know this isn't the time
to show your comradeship, don't you?
You're getting married next month.
What did you and the captain of
Regional Investigation Unit discuss?
You didn't tell him
where Hyeong Ju is, did you?
Hey, Soon Woo.
We're obviously
helping a criminal take shelter.
We're detectives,
and this won't end
with a simple disciplinary action.
So that's why...
you told Captain Jung everything?
I know...
where Ji Hyeong Ju is.
I thought you should know
before Captain Jung does.
I'm sorry.
- Yes?
- Captain Heo.
This is Hyeong Ju.
I couldn't wrap my head around
some things you said.
Did you really save
each one of those people...
to reset?
"Reset"?
I'm not sure
what you're referring to.
Hyeong Ju told me already.
That he came back a year...
from the future along with you.
Detective Ji said that?
I have a good imagination,
so it wasn't that hard to believe.
By any chance,
did he tell you the reason...
behind his decision to reset?
"The reason"?
It was a very important reason.
It's something
you'd be interested in too.
What I am interested in is...
the fact that
everyone who reset with Hyeong Ju...
doesn't seem to be irrelevant to me.
So that's why I have a feeling...
that you may know
what my future holds.
The future?
From my experience,
there was no one
who overcame their destined death.
Not even one.
That means...
you'll be safe...
until everyone else dies.
That's all I know.
Right, one more thing.
What is this?
Let's call this your fate.
You'll find out soon.
It always happened.
Do you think it'll work?
I'll have to try.
I have no other choice.
Perhaps,
this could be why
we went through with the reset.
Perhaps,
this had to happen.
There was no one
who overcame their destined death.
Not even one.
Hyeong Ju.
Stop.
Detective Ji.
Maru, let's eat.
Come here.
Let's go for a walk.
Darn it.
Hey, Soon Woo.
What?
Hey, what's going on?
I have no idea.
Did he not tell you anything either?
He was determined to catch
the real culprit,
so why did he turn himself in?
Did he really do it?
You took those photos, didn't you?
Mr. Hwang agreed to testify
against you...
regarding your request.
You can easily become a suspect...
with the photos in that USB.
They're proof that you were present
at the crime scenes,
so you'll be suspected
as an accomplice at the least.
Do you think Ms. Lee Shin
will still have your back then?
The killer could've seen you.
You could've died.
What does she have on you
that you're going this far?
If you can help us,
we'll be able to...
get rid of Ms. Lee Shin
and the killer as well.
I beg you.
Ms. Song.
Why did you have to make things
so complicated...
if you were going
to turn yourself in anyway?
Thanks to you,
the chief may have to make...
a public apology, do you understand?
Since we've come to this,
let's pick the easy way.
Do you admit to the murders
of Bae Jung Tae and Ko Jae Young?
Detective Ji Hyeong Ju!
What are Ji Hyeong Ju
and Shin Ga Hyeon scheming?
You must know.
Tell me. Why did he turn himself in?
I... I don't know.
I don't know anything about this.
Did Ms. Lee Shin contact you
by any chance?
I was wondering if Ms. Song
reported to her.
No.
Something happened to my wife,
so I had to hurry to the sanitarium.
I'll contact you later.
It's nothing serious, right?
I'll have to see. We'll talk again.
(I'll have to see.
We'll talk again.)
(Ji Hyeong Ju, 32 years old)
(Shin Ga Hyeon, 28 years old)
They're the only ones left.
We found these cuffs
at the crime scene,
and they turned out to be yours.
We've also confirmed
that you used this burner phone...
to contact Bae Jung Tae
and Ko Jae Young.
There was also the text
about how they lured you.
You were the first one to find...
Bae Jung Tae's body and report it.
Perhaps, this could be
a fabricated scenario as well.
Conclusively,
we found these wounds...
on their stomachs.
The NFS believes...
it was the same killer.
Is that what you think as well?
Do you think it's the same killer?
Do you think
this is a serial murder?
Are you asking me?
If we overcome our fate,
how will it benefit you?
You always said that.
"I want to see you
overcoming your fate."
"That's why
I gave you another chance."
Is fate already decided,
or can it be changed?
That's why I decided to experiment.
What if I bring back the dead...
and reset the time?
Why did you take things so far
and do this with us?
It's a real drag to bear through...
a time without any hope.
I needed something fun to do
to live through this boring year.
I realized there are people
who suffer more than I do,
so it was comforting too.
You were so desperate
to save someone,
yet I didn't know
how you could be so cruel to us.
At first, I didn't get it,
but everything
definitely makes sense now.
You didn't reset the time
for your child.
You already know that.
It's because of you,
who can't bear to live on...
after the death of your child.
You keep running away back in time,
into the past.
It's time for you
to be honest with yourself.
Young, are you still mad at me?
You didn't keep your promise.
You said
we're going to ride on a train.
I wanted to keep my promise,
but we couldn't go
because you might get sick.
I'm not sick at all.
I want to ride on a train.
We have to go
to the hospital tomorrow.
As soon as you get well,
we can ride a train
every single day.
You're lying.
You always lie.
I don't like the hospital.
I'm not going.
Then will you continue to be sick?
You'll break my heart.
Mom, are you heartbroken?
No, I'm fine.
I only live for you, Young.
I don't care...
no matter what anyone says,
as long as
you can stay here with me.
I'll live through this.
I'll make sure I live through...
this time.
This is everything I can do for you.
Please do keep your promise.
Thank you. Thank you, Detective.
Thank you so much.
What's going on?
He was caught by
aerial patrol on the highway.
He said he made a mistake
while looking at the GPS,
so we let him off with a warning.
Why? Do you know him?
No.
- Get back to work.
- Yes, sir.
Let's call this your fate, Mr. Park.
You'll find out soon.
It always happened.
Hey. Where are you going?
To meet Ms. Shin Ga Hyeon.
I was wondering if she knows
anything about this situation.
Do you want to come along?
- No, go ahead.
- Okay.
I thought you would know...
what Hyeong Ju is up to.
He's not a guy who'd kill a man.
He even ran away
to catch the real culprit.
Why is he suddenly doing this?
You know something, don't you?
Ga Hyeon, we need to know
what's going on to help.
He said the evidence...
that can catch the culprit is
in the police station.
That's why he has no choice
but to get in there himself.
The evidence? What is it?
Ko Jae Young's phone.
He said it should be
in the evidence room.
Ko Jae Young
always had a headphone on.
And Hyeong Ju said...
the headphone wasn't
found on the scene.
What does that have to do
with his phone?
His headphone has...
a GPS tracking device...
that's connected to his phone.
If the real culprit
has his headphone...
or hid it somewhere,
we can find where it is.
Wait.
Then he could've just asked us.
Why would he come himself?
Because of reasons I can't share.
Thanks.
(Evidence Room)
Hyeong Ju.
How did you find this place?
(Episode 22)
How did you...
Hyeong Ju...
He wiretapped my house.
What should we do?
We could use this opportunity.
Mr. Choi Kyung Man's lottery ticket,
Ms. Seo Yeon Soo's phone,
and Mr. Cha Jeung Seok's music box.
Do you remember them?
But last time...
We can't call it
a serial murder because...
a few common items like
a phone and gloves disappeared.
"Gloves"?
Yes, but I don't know
whose gloves they were.
Are you saying he was collecting
the disappeared items...
as if they were trophies?
If he really did...
store victims' items somewhere,
that would be conclusive evidence.
Can you think of a place?
I'm going to make him...
lead the way.
Do you have proof?
I can find one if you help me.
After I turn myself in,
please send Sa Kyung
to Ms. Shin Ga Hyeon's place.
Don't tell her about this talk
we're having.
- Where are you going?
- To meet Ms. Shin Ga Hyeon.
I was wondering if she knows
anything about this situation.
Ko Jae Young's headphone
has a GPS tracking device...
that's connected to his phone.
If the real culprit
has his headphone...
or hid it somewhere,
we can find where it is.
And this.
This is Ji Hyeong Ju's alibi.
Ko Jae Young stopped recording
at 10:07 p.m.
Detective Ji arrived
at Bae Jung Tae's place...
at 10:10 p.m.
He isn't the detective
who was mentioned in the recording.
But he could be an accomplice.
What... What are these?
I found them
at Bae Jung Tae's place.
These photos were on the USB.
We were carrying out
an internal investigation...
because we suspected
the killer to be among us.
I know who the killer is.
And I know how to catch him.
There was no GPS.
Did you say that on purpose
because you knew I was wiretapping?
Is that why you turned yourself in?
How did you know the passcode?
It was your badge number.
07003.
Right.
We were such great partners.
Did you come here alone
so that I could kill you off?
Kill me. Kill me!
Don't you move.
Why did you have to come here?
Now, I have to kill you!
Don't come near me.
Stop!
Hyeong Ju...
Hyeong Ju.
- Stop right there!
- Hyeong Ju.
Hyeong Ju, are you okay?
He said he's only going
to speak with you.
You're the one who knows the best
about this case,
so please help us.
I can't believe
we're face-to-face in this room.
Life is full of surprises.
Why did you kill them?
Why did I?
Why?
There is no reason.
It just happened.
And it started from...
(Letter of Appointment,
Sergeant Park Sun Ho)
Excuse me. Hey.
Help... Help me, Detective.
Help me.
Detective.
If that jerk didn't say,
"detective",
I wouldn't have killed him.
- Lieutenant Park Sun Ho?
- Yes.
We have to install guard rails here.
It took me 12 years to get promoted.
I couldn't ruin my life...
because of this mere accident.
So you killed him?
Yes.
But on the case report,
there's no mention of "murder".
When he was driving the motorcycle,
he wasn't looking ahead.
The cause of death,
the skull fracture
caused by the fall.
Most of these cases were
closed as accidents.
I killed them,
but my murder wasn't
considered a real murder.
Isn't this awesome?
It was fun.
At last. I can't believe
I finally won the lottery.
Heart attack.
(327th Lottery)
Falling accident.
(I hope you'll be happy
in your next life...)
(and not meet someone like me.)
Suicide.
Fire.
I staged the scene
with a lot of creativity.
And everyone believed it.
(Flower)
I completely fooled everyone.
Except for you, Ji Hyeong Ju.
"My gosh, why wouldn't
this guy believe me?"
"Why does he keep suspecting more?"
I gave that a lot of thought.
And I found out why
after meeting Bae Jung Tae.
I knew why you didn't fall for it.
Are you saying you and Hyeong Ju
came from the future?
It's not just us two.
There are a few more.
The people
who traveled time with you.
I killed them.
No.
Jang Jin Ho wasn't among them.
The deliveryman.
(Handong Logistics)
Darn it.
Darn it. Where did I put the gloves?
I didn't know who he was,
but he was Park Young Gil's
replacement.
That's when...
I believed in the reset completely.
I thought,
"They are destined to die anyway."
"I'm destined to kill."
I didn't see why I should rack
my brain on this.
After realizing that,
I just killed without a reason.
Why did you frame me?
You should have just killed me too.
I couldn't imagine...
killing you.
So if you get caught
and are locked up here,
I wouldn't even have
a chance to kill you.
Then, you might not end up dead.
That was...
my way of showing
my consideration for you.
I was being considerate.
But when I saw how you were
on the run without getting caught,
I thought to myself I might end up
killing you with my own hands.
Thank you for saying that.
I regretted like crazy...
that I came...
to save a scumbag like you.
But I came back to catch you.
What are you talking about?
Are you telling me that I died?
Isn't that fascinating?
Think long and hard
about it in prison.
You dirty murderer.
Mr. Park Sun Ho.
I'll take this as your confession
to all the charges...
and end the interrogation here.
Darn it.
(Lieutenant Park Sun Ho)
- What's your name?
- Kim Eung Sam.
Hey.
Let me see.
I see. Did you do this to him?
Look at this jerk.
- Hey, you!
- Sun Ho.
- No.
- What's wrong with your hand?
- Your hand...
- Hey.
- He didn't hit me.
- Park Sun Ho!
- Park Sun Ho, what's up with you?
- My gosh.
- Hey, get out!
- You piece of trash!
- Get out.
- That jerk!
After he became a lieutenant,
he was really happy.
He bragged to everyone
that he was going to be a good cop.
But that's when it started.
He didn't even have...
a proper reason behind his murders.
It was just a game to him.
A game that proved
how perfect he was.
That kind of game.
He did prove...
that there's no perfect crime.
And that he's bound to face...
the punishment one day.
You set that straight, Hyeong Ju.
No, you changed it, Ga Hyeon.
I arrested Park Sun Ho.
I see.
I read the news article.
You said that
you were experimenting...
if people could change
their destiny.
You have your result now.
Your experiment...
will end with us.
I will do whatever it takes to stop
you from undergoing the reset.
I'll do everything in my power...
and stop you.
So you don't have
to go through the trouble...
of looking for your next victims.
Things will be interesting...
before the reset.
I'll look forward to it.
Mr. Park, an active detective
at Seoul Makang Police Station,
was revealed to have murdered
the son of Ko Seok Gyu,
the former nominee
for the Ministry of Education,
- A comment, please.
- Why did you kill him?
According to
the RIU's investigation,
it's been confirmed that there had
been additional 11 victims...
which shocked the public even more.
- Say something.
- Anything?
Say something.
How did you know
my dog's name is Maru?
Right. That's so interesting.
I just named the dog
after a webtoon artist I like.
I should give him an autograph,
right? It's the right thing to do.
Let's go. Hold on.
- Hyeong Ju.
- Hey.
Happy birthday.
I didn't know you follow
the lunar calendar.
But it is still my birthday today.
This feels strange.
It's nice to celebrate
my birthday alive.
In light of that,
I got you a present.
A present?
It's made of silk.
I want you to live a long life.
There's one more for Maru.
It's a matching item.
This is touching. Thank you.
Right. Bring the book,
"Hidden Killer" next time.
I'll sign it.
- What?
- It made me wonder...
why I didn't get it signed already.
Bring it next time.
It's made of silk.
I want you to live a long life.
You think this is over, right?
How's the cafe owner doing
these days? Is he good?
Take care.
Look out for each other.
Yes, Hyeong Ju.
He's not at the cafe.
Could he still be at the sanitorium?
Something happened to my wife,
so I had to hurry to the sanitarium.
That's the day...
he said that
he was at the sanitorium.
(Something happened to my wife.)
(It's okay, Ga Hyeon. Are you okay?
Let's talk tomorrow.)
The period.
(It's okay, Ga Hyeon. Are you okay?
Let's talk tomorrow.)
(I had to hurry to the sanitarium
I'll contact you later)
There's no period.
He always ends with the period.
The name of the guardian
is Hwang No Sub.
Can you tell me
when his last visit was?
There's no such guardian.
Do you know the name of the patient?
No.
Hold on. Hwang No Sub?
Are you looking
for Professor Hwang No Sub?
Professor?
It's this man.
Yes, it's him.
It's Professor Hwang No Sub.
He's running a clinical trial
with patients from here.
He comes here at least once a week.
- A clinical trial?
- His wife isn't staying here?
I heard that his wife is running
a business in the States.
I didn't want to
leave my wife in the sanitorium...
when I realized
I don't know when I'll die.
How is she doing?
Ever since that day,
her condition has worsened.
She couldn't even
recognize me yesterday.
Then, if he's a professor,
can you tell me where he works?
He used to work at Sejin Hospital.
But now, he's an advisory director
for Samo Pharmaceuticals.
Sejin Hospital?
The sanitorium
and a wife with dementia.
They were all lies.
Why would he lie about this?
If he was a professor
at Sejin Hospital,
it means that he knew
Ms. Lee Shin before the reset.
Let's not talk about this here.
Let's go somewhere else
and chat more.
I used to be a regular here.
My wife loved drinking coffee...
and wanted to open one
later on in life.
So I was able to buy this place,
thanks to the reset.
Then,
did Ms. Lee Shin order him
to gather us at the cafe...
from the get-go?
Detective.
He was here this Monday.
Monday?
That's after Sun Ho got arrested.
Hyeong Ju.
Why is Ms. Song here?
This is Professor Hwang's secretary.
- His secretary?
- Yes.
If you can help us,
we'll be able to...
get rid of Ms. Lee Shin
and the killer as well.
I beg you.
It was all an act.
It's as if she knows the future.
She knew everything about me.
The person Ms. Song
was terrified of...
wasn't Ms. Lee Shin.
It was Professor Hwang.
From the beginning, he made
Ms. Lee Shin take the front line.
And he had been watching
the whole thing from the back.
You're back, Professor Hwang.
Everyone must be utterly shocked.
I'll go back soon.
Yes, Professor.
I know that very well. Don't worry.
(Samo Pharmaceuticals)
Professor Hwang No Sub?
Yes.
Are you Detective Ji Hyeong Ju?
Yes, I am.
Please follow me.
Shin.
Don't you think...
it's time for us to prepare
for the next reset?
You were always busy
around this time of the year...
because of Young.
That's why...
I'm thinking of getting help
from someone else.
Someone else?
(Emergency Transport,
Ministry of Justice)
There was no one
who overcame their destined death.
Not even one.
That means you'll be safe...
until everyone else dies.
My gosh.
You'll find out soon.
It always happened.
(Advisory Director Hwang No Sub)
What's this?
He told me to give this to you
when you two come.
So he must have known
that we would come to him.
(365: Repeat the Year)
Who on earth are you?
I can meet Young again?
I'm enjoying the time I have.
What do you think will happen
if this guy is gone?
- Who are you?
- It will be a fun year.
- Park Sun Ho escaped.
- The three of us will...
do this together.
It wasn't over yet.
She said
our destined death won't change.
You'll end up doing it
as you have always done.