The person you are calling is
on another line.
You'll be directed
to the voicemail box.
Ga Hyeon, answer the phone.
I'm next.
I'm not lying this time.
I'm serious.
Ga Hyeon, I'm sorry.
I'm sorry.
Ga Hyeon, please save me.
(Recent Calls, Kim Se Rin)
The phone you have reached is
turned off. Leave your message.
You will be charged after the beep.
I'm not lying this time.
I'm serious.
I'm sorry.
Ga Hyeon, please save me.
I went to her house,
but she wasn't there.
And her phone is still turned off.
I hope she's lying,
and that this is
just me getting deceived again.
But what if
something happened to her?
Then what happens?
This is near her studio.
This was where
her phone was last used.
Wait.
This is Se Rin's phone.
Let's report her as missing first.
Young Woong is gone.
He just left his phone here.
He disappeared.
- What about her family...
- Young Woong's phone.
Se Rin has his phone.
(Calling Choi Young Woong)
The person you have reached
is unavailable.
It must be somewhere around here.
There's no way
she would be in a place like this.
Hyeong Ju.
No, right.
It's not her, is it?
Ga Hyeon.
Wait. Wait a second.
Hey.
You're right. Ms. Kim Se Rin
called you at 8:15 p.m.
All right. I'll contact you again
if I need more information from you.
Please take her home safely.
Yes.
This way, please.
The next victim...
will die a gruesome death.
She knew Se Rin would get murdered.
She knew.
Did you sleep well?
Yes. I mean...
Yes, Mother.
What was that?
Where did you learn to say that?
Ms. Song.
She said I was no longer a baby.
She said I had to mind my manners...
since I'll have to go
to school soon.
Do you want to go to school?
I'd also like to see you...
go to school.
Kim Se Rin, 19 years old.
Her family signed the autopsy paper,
and we requested an autopsy.
We'll only know the cause of death
once the autopsy results come out.
But the estimated time of death is
between 8 p.m...
and 12 a.m. last night.
It's a headache
to have no suspects...
and to have too many of them.
But we have two already.
- Two?
- One of them is Choi Young Woong,
her ex-boyfriend.
A few days ago, he reported her
for stalking him.
Is he the one who requested
a restraining order?
Yes. There's a high possibility...
that he and Se Rin fought
because of that.
- Who's the other suspect?
- Do you remember...
the assault case
at a studio in Sinyeong-dong?
She's the victim.
The assailant, Bae Jung Tae,
was discharged yesterday.
Gosh.
The results don't look good.
I'm not telling you to give up.
It's all up to you now.
Are you prepared for this?
Thanks.
Se Rin is dead.
She's dead.
So?
Se Rin did everything
you told her to do.
So why did she die?
Why did you let her die?
You said you quit work because
your friend committed suicide.
That was a lie, right?
There's no way...
you would mourn for someone else.
I'd like to report something.
When was the last time
you met Ms. Kim Se Rin?
It was right before I reported her
for stalking.
I saw her for the last time
at an expressway rest area.
When was the last time
you talked on the phone?
Yesterday,
at around 6:30 p.m.,
she called my friend.
- Was that it?
- Yes.
So that actually happened?
Young Woong.
Kim Se Rin, please!
She kept asking where I was.
So I just hung up on her.
Did she say anything else?
Not really.
Where were you between 8 p.m.
and 12 a.m. yesterday?
I was...
at my friend's house.
Are you talking about the friend
she called?
No.
It was another friend.
I confirmed
Mr. Choi Young Woong's alibi.
It checked out.
I checked the call she made
to his friend.
It lasted for 3 minutes
and 40 seconds.
3 minutes and 40 seconds?
What is it?
Is something on your mind?
No, nothing.
Ga Hyeon.
To be honest, when the news said...
that it was a woman in her 20s,
I was worried it was you.
So I called Detective Ji.
That's when I found out
it was Se Rin.
Ms. Lee Shin...
must've toyed with us again.
Actually,
Se Rin had lied...
about everything.
What?
I don't understand.
That's unbelievable.
You must've been greatly shocked.
You cared for her
like you were family.
You're right. I hated her so much.
That's why I told her
never to visit me again.
And it really happened.
She must've been terrified.
She must've felt...
extremely lonely.
I should've believed her
one last time.
Perhaps, I wasn't mad at her.
I might have been mad at myself...
for being so terrified
about dying next.
I visited Ms. Lee Shin.
I begged her to save my life
and said I'd do anything.
That's what I did
after acting all courageous.
Even at this age,
I still don't want to die.
It's understandable.
Actually,
I visited her as well.
I begged her to tell me
the date of my death.
But she didn't give in.
Whenever I think...
about leaving my sick wife behind,
it tortures me...
every single day.
What is it?
- What?
- I got Ms. Kim Se Rin's call logs.
I'm going to meet the last person
she spoke with.
What is it? Give it to me.
No. Summon her.
Why aren't you going in there?
Are you trying to intimidate her?
I thought you'd refuse to come here.
I'm surprised.
This is concerning Se Rin.
I should do everything I can
to help.
What did you two talk about?
I'm afraid I can't tell you.
I'm not allowed to disclose
my conversations with my patients.
You do know that, right?
Are you saying Ms. Kim Se Rin
was a patient at Zian Clinic?
Yes.
If not, how do you think I knew her?
I can show you the records.
That is, if you have a warrant.
Where were you on November 9,
between 8:00 p.m. to 12:00 a.m.?
Do you doubt me as the culprit?
It's just a formality.
If you aren't the culprit,
it's not that difficult to answer.
I was at Zian Clinic.
Could you turn in
the security footage?
If you need me to bring one,
I'll bring the warrant.
So this was your plan.
To investigate Zian Clinic
by using this case as an excuse.
It won't be easy.
It may be difficult,
but it's a great opportunity.
What are they talking about?
What on earth is Zian Clinic
that he wants to investigate it?
What we do know is that
this isn't the first time they met.
I didn't think
we had an honest talk in there.
Both the questions and answers.
I guess you're scared
that I might get a warrant.
Why? Is there something
you need to tell?
I can't believe
I'm the last one Se Rin talked to.
That's pretty sad.
If I had known,
I could have been nicer.
You're still in Seoul?
Yes. Because of Young Woong.
I gave you a chance to live,
but you're still looking
for Young Woong.
You can't blame me now.
I made sure I keep my promise.
Wait.
Was it me? Am I going to die?
When? Where?
Ma'am, what should I do now?
Se Rin.
Yes, ma'am.
It's...
too late.
Ms. Lee. Ms. Lee!
Isn't fate...
so fascinating?
In the end...
you end up living the life
you're destined to live.
Why are you taking things this far?
I told Se Rin
everything she can do to avoid this.
She's the one
who didn't do anything and died.
She was the first member
who could have changed her fate.
Then you must have known
she would've been killed.
That means you know the culprit.
Who was it? Bae Jung Tae?
I'm not sure.
Up until the last reset,
Se Rin's case was unresolved.
If the culprit is Bae Jung Tae,
This unexpected turn of event
will make it entertaining.
I really look forward to this,
Detective Ji.
- What?
- Come quickly.
Things are chaotic here.
What?
(Police line, do not cross)
What is this? What has he done?
- You're here.
- He did this as soon as he got out.
We have to run a DNA analysis,
but it's probably her.
We have...
a lot to discuss, don't we?
Why did you do that to me?
I did it because I wanted to
work things out with Young Woong.
I didn't think
the detective would show up.
I'm so sorry.
You do know that
you can't say a few words...
to make this okay, don't you?
What can I do...
to destroy you
without Ji Hyeong Ju finding out?
That's all I had on my mind...
over the last seven months.
There's not a lot of things
you can do in prison.
You aren't going to kill me,
are you?
You aren't that bad.
That's why you helped me.
Bad news.
I definitely want to...
kill you right now.
I haven't seen him for a few months.
He walked in with this woman.
Did she walk in willingly?
- Yes.
- Do you know what time it was?
I was on my way to work
in the afternoon,
so it was around 3:30 p.m.
"3:30 p.m."?
Are you sure it was
Mr. Bae Jung Tae?
What?
Well, it was definitely a man.
You can go back for now.
One second.
I just asked around,
and the woman next door
saw him at 3:30 p.m.
- Hello?
- But we got here at 4:00 p.m.
- Yes?
- Then who did that woman see?
This means he had an accomplice.
Yes.
Kim Se Rin's phone was...
found near her studio.
One second.
They found a record of
Ms. Kim Se Rin taking a taxi.
(Sa Kyung)
She took the taxi
at the bus terminal at 2:36 p.m.
Then she got off around
Bae Jung Tae's house in 40 minutes.
Did you get a hold
of the taxi driver?
Yes, I asked him
for the dashcam footage,
but he's out of town right now.
He'll see tomorrow at the earliest.
But she got in another taxi
after three hours.
Where did she go?
Back to her studio.
But she didn't leave from his house.
- Then?
- The hospital. Sejin Hospital.
Did she get hurt?
What's going on?
Hey. Where are you going?
- Hey.
- Hello?
Sa Kyung, request the security
footage from Sejin Hospital.
- I'll see you at the office.
- Yes, sir.
(Patient: Bae Jung Hee)
(Doctor: Lee So Jung,
Nurse: Im Soo Ji)
Excuse me.
Who are you?
Well...
I'm Detective Ji Hyeong Ju
of Makang Police Station.
By any chance,
can you reach Mr. Bae Jung Tae?
Why are you looking for my brother?
Wait, did he do something again?
No, he's just a suspect for now.
That's why I have to meet him.
A... A suspect?
Wait, did he do something
to that young lady?
"That young lady"?
The young lady
from seven months ago.
Why did you think so?
He said he'll return very soon...
with that young lady...
because he didn't do anything wrong,
and that she will
make his case for him.
Ga Hyeon.
Let's hold the funeral by ourselves.
We should let our family know.
A few of them already called
after seeing the news.
She was always
dying to get attention.
It's just as she hoped.
Let's just say she was a good girl
for not killing herself.
How can you say that?
She was murdered.
Even strangers pity her!
How can you say that as her parents?
Don't you think we have our reasons?
She's humiliating us like this
even after she died!
How can I say
anything good about her?
Let's go.
If I die,
my mom and dad will be sad,
won't they?
But I'm sure
they'll be a little sad.
Right?
No.
That's not going to happen,
so they won't be sad either.
("Looking for the Suspect of
the Manhole Murder Case")
(A university student, A,
had been found dead in a manhole...)
What about Ms. Kim Se Rin?
Are things not going
according to your plan?
That little brat...
deceived me again and ran away.
I know she does everything you say.
You have to call her here.
You have a lot of requests.
You can do that much for me
after all I've done for you.
Kim Se Rin, that brat.
This time, I will not let her live.
Quiet. One second.
I'm sorry.
I don't think...
you'll get another chance.
What?
Just now,
Ms. Kim Se Rin died.
Yes, Professor.
I know that very well. Don't worry.
I'll give you a call.
Is that girl
who's all over the news...
really Kim Se Rin?
You have no time
to walk around like this.
Mr. Bae Jung Tae,
you do know you are...
the key suspect, don't you?
You know the best that...
I didn't kill her!
I was here at Zian Clinic with you.
At that hour.
Exactly.
That's exactly why
you need to behave.
I'm the only one who can prove...
your innocence.
Then this should be easy.
You do remember that
I know your secrets, don't you?
That deal was only valid...
for your sister's life.
I've done more than enough for you.
I guess you forgot that I'm a thug.
- Mr. Bae Jung Tae.
- All you have to do is...
say a few things
at the police station.
My sister is
finally able to breathe again.
I can't let her live
as a murderer's sister.
Okay? I'm sure
you don't want your secret...
to be out in the world.
How can I trust you?
The decision is yours, Ms. Lee.
Mr. Choi Young Woong?
Yes.
It really looked like
he was hiding something.
Are you telling me
that he could be a suspect?
What if his friend was covering
for him with the alibi?
He does have a motive.
But...
he did seem genuinely surprised
when he heard about her death.
Then, what could he be hiding?
The last phone call he had
with Se Rin was over three minutes.
But he won't tell me
what he talked about with her.
I'm sure
that has to do with this case.
(Corporal Jin Sa Kyung)
Hey, I got the dashcam footage
from the taxi.
There really was an accomplice.
What?
Ko Jae Young.
Staying at my apartment
made me feel uncomfortable.
Until my place gets rented out,
I'm going to stay with my friend.
Isn't it really tough?
Perhaps,
I should have put up
with it a bit longer...
and gone on a trip with her
for the last time.
Then, she could have been alive now.
I keep regretting it.
What was...
the last thing Se Rin said to you?
Pardon?
I'm just curious.
I see. It wasn't that important.
Did you talk to Kim Se Rin with
the burner phone from Bae Jung Tae?
Did you send Bae Jung Tae's address
to her by using the same phone?
On November 9, around 3:30 p.m.,
Didn't you meet up with Kim Se Rin
in front of Bae Jung Tae's house?
By the way,
the college girl on the news...
is Kim Se Rin?
Is she dead?
From 8 p.m. to 12 a.m.
on November 9,
what did you do?
I guess she's really dead.
Answer my questions!
(Special Case Team)
Why did you meet with Kim Se Rin?
What did you do with Bae Jung Tae?
What are you doing?
Hey. Stop it. Let him go.
Good luck, sir.
Why is he already leaving?
What's going on?
He's only a testifier.
Summon him again
if you want to ask more questions.
You never interfered in such things.
What's going on?
I received orders
from the higher-ups.
Ko Jae Young is Ko Seok Gyu's son.
And who's he?
Isn't he the nominee
for the Minister of Education?
You're right.
Seeing how things are panning out
even before he's elected,
he's going to be
a terrible minister.
In this day and age, being the son
of a nominee for the minister...
shouldn't mean you're free
from being investigated.
I never said that.
Let's just let him go for now.
And once we gather more proof,
we can summon him once again.
It's better than
not being prepared...
and getting
on the wrong side of him.
Is there anyone else
who knows about this?
I can only stop this if you tell me.
Can we go?
Ko Jae Young was the one
who called Se Rin over?
Yes.
I can't understand...
why she'd listen to him
and go there.
This happened before
Bae Jung Tae arrived home...
which means those two were in on it.
Why would Ko Jae Young
do such a thing?
Se Rin once took a photo
of those two...
meeting up in secret.
Maybe Bae Jung Tae found out
Ko Jae Young's weakness.
I'm not sure.
What kind of weakness...
would the son of a nominee
for the minister have?
What? Minister?
He's the son of the nominee
for the Minister of Education.
Minister of Education?
Are you talking about Ko Seok Gyu?
Do you know him?
Ko Seok Gyu.
Don't you remember his hearing?
It happened before the reset.
All right, then.
Let's talk about your son.
Social media has been spreading
information about him.
What do you think about this?
Please give us an answer...
as a nominee for
the Minister of Education.
(Ko Seok Gyu, Nominee
for the Minister of Education)
Have you gotten in touch
with Bae Jung Tae yet?
(Before the reset)
Hello?
What?
Yes, she is my sister.
She killed someone?
(Violent Crimes
Investigation Team 3)
Ever since she got married,
she was physically assaulted
by her husband.
Her body was covered in wounds.
What a scumbag.
I'm glad she did it.
Where is she right now?
She attempted suicide
after killing him,
so she was carried to the hospital.
She tried to commit suicide?
Ms. Bae Jung Hee
has been suffering...
from dilated cardiomyopathy.
Were you not aware of this either?
- I am...
- What are you doing?
- I'm her older brother.
- You're not allowed to enter.
Jung Hee. Jung Hee.
- You may not enter.
- Please.
- No, sir.
- Jung Hee.
- We need backup here.
Please back away.
- Jung Hee.
- Requesting for a backup.
- Please stop.
Jung Hee.
Jung Hee...
Okay. I'll go.
Since I was able to save my sister,
please forgive me...
for being a horrible son.
Captain Heo.
I'm going to summon Ko Jae Young
once again.
Why did you go
to Kim Se Rin's place?
I wanted to know what
she and Bae Jung Tae talked about.
She arrived an hour later.
What were you so curious about
to wait for an entire hour?
What did you two talk about
that irked you so much?
I asked her to tell me,
but she got annoyed.
So we argued.
Then why did you argue
in front of someone else's house?
How may I help you?
The last thing
Se Rin talked about...
was Ko Jae Young, right?
You didn't go there to meet her.
Choi Young Woong... No.
You went to see Choi Min Ho.
The reason why she willingly went
to Bae Jung Tae's house...
was probably because of him as well.
(Young Woong and Se Rin,
our 1st day together)
Hello?
It's me, Ko Jae Young.
What's this number?
Choi Young Woong
is your boyfriend, right?
I have something to tell you
about him.
I'll send you an address.
Meet me there if you're curious.
I won't wait for long.
Sir, hold on!
Please open the door now. Hurry!
- Tell me what it's about.
- Follow me.
Where's this place?
Where is he?
Be careful.
And see you around.
I'll make sure
we never cross paths again.
Please forget about me.
Are we good now?
Tell me now.
Choi Min Ho is Choi Young Woong.
What?
There's a way...
you can save yourself from this.
Go and explain this to my sister.
I may be a thug,
but I'm not a scumbag
that beats women. Tell her that.
What do you mean when you said
Choi Min Ho is...
Choi Young Woong?
Why is Ko Jae Young
looking for my boyfriend?
Se Rin, you should consider
yourself very lucky.
If it weren't for my sister...
Ko Jae Young. It was that jerk.
Hey!
I've been waiting out here
for an hour.
He hasn't shown up at all.
Exactly. Find him if you have to
search every alley of Daehangno.
Why are you here again?
What are you trying to do to him?
What are you talking about?
Do you know how hard
it has been for my boyfriend?
Because of you,
he had to change his name,
transferred to a new school,
and moved around!
Why is that my fault?
I failed to recognize
this precious son of the minister.
School violence video.
Do I need to upload that again
for you to come to your senses?
(I will expose Ko Jae Young,
the son of the nominee...)
(for the Ministry of Education.)
- Let go of the sneakers.
- Throw it.
- Does it hurt? Does it?
- Get up.
- Min Ho, does it hurt?
- Hey.
- Go ahead. Do it.
- Does it hurt?
Hook your leg.
- Go over there.
- Can he crawl under you?
- My gosh, Min Ho. You lost weight.
- Hurry.
Just go under me.
- My gosh, can he actually do that?
- Let's do this.
- Eat this.
- Do it.
Min Ho, look over here.
- Eat it.
- Hey, Min Ho. What are you doing?
- Good boy. My dear pig.
- You must be starving.
Make the noise.
You must have found him
to stop him before the hearing.
How will you stop me?
You're unbelievable.
Don't you dare lay a finger on him.
I'll make your life worse
than your previous one.
(Sinyeong-dong)
Don't you dare lay a finger on him.
I'll make your life worse
than your previous one.
Will you keep lying to me?
Within 30 minutes
after you and Se Rin parted ways,
her phone was turned off.
And I already checked
that your alibi is false.
I didn't kill her.
I really didn't.
Then, tell me where you were.
There are usually
two types of people...
who can't prove their alibis.
Whether they are the culprit...
or were committing another crime.
Which one are you?
I was with Choi Min Ho.
I was just leaving
Kim Se Rin's house.
And my friend called me
and said he found Choi Min Ho.
I can't recognize you
even if I'm looking at you.
Young Woong?
Who knew you had become a "hero"?
I had no idea.
Why did you find me?
Are you here to apologize?
Apologize?
You should apologize to me.
You totally pulled one over on me.
First, I just wanted to stop you.
Now that I'm seeing your face,
I'm getting so angry.
What are you talking about?
What did I do to you?
Exactly.
You should have left the past
in the past...
and lived with your new name.
Why did you upload that
on social media?
Why did you anger my old man
who's working to serve this country?
When did I do that?
Right.
Forget it.
You don't need to know that.
Did you eat?
- Young Woong.
- You lost weight.
Hey, should I jog your memory?
Should I? Yes?
Does it hurt?
- Stay still.
- Don't move.
My alibi checks out now, right?
I can go, right?
You might be able
to dodge the murder charge,
but I can lock you up
with the assault charge.
It won't work even if you try.
No prosecution
if the victim doesn't press charges.
(Crimes can't be prosecuted
if the victims object.)
I'm sure you know that well.
Choi Min Ho still listens to me.
He told me that...
he could ruin my family's future
if he wanted.
I know too well
that he's not bluffing.
I experienced enough of that
in high school.
It could be different this time.
No.
I changed my name...
and went on a diet.
I passed the GED
and got into college.
I thought I was living a new life.
In the end, it's the same.
I'm bound to face misfortune
in this life.
Even if Se Rin told you only lies,
she was heartbroken by your past...
and wanted to make Ko Jae Young
kneel and get an apology from him.
I'm sure those were true.
Kim Se Rin, please!
Young Woong,
Ko Jae Young is looking for you.
I can't say for sure
about other things,
but he wants to hide
the crimes his son committed...
and hurt others
as collateral damage.
That kind of person can't be
the Minister of Education.
Open up!
Open it right now!
You jerks!
Hey!
I got it. Okay?
Let go of me.
Where's the video?
Who are you? What video?
I already deleted everything
on this phone.
It was about Ko Jae Young.
What's so important
about a bunch of kids playing?
What's all this fuss?
I would have given you
if you just asked.
That's all I have.
Are you sure
there aren't any more copies?
Your sister just underwent surgery.
If you want her to live a long life,
you must be sure.
You scumbag.
How dare you threaten me?
That should be enough
to cover the damages to your car.
If you don't squeak
and stay quiet...
until the hearing is over,
I'll give you some more.
Here.
Hey.
A gift.
What is it?
(Search and seizure warrant)
It's all thanks to the reporters.
When they were yapping about it,
they issued it quickly,
so we can catch the culprit.
Will we get anything
from Zian Clinic?
Yes, we will. Definitely.
Thanks.
This is from Ms. Lee.
(Zian Clinic)
She didn't want you to waste time
as you're busy,
so she sent this to you.
If she was inside the clinic
from the afternoon...
of Kim Se Rin's murder
until the next morning,
Lee Shin can't be the culprit.
Isn't that Bae Jung Tae?
That's the day of the murder.
What? Why is he here?
The drive to the crime scene
takes over an hour.
This rules him out as the culprit.
Hey, Bae Jung Tae knows her, too?
I can forgive a lot of things,
but I can't
when people go after my sister.
You can't do anything
if you don't have your daddy's help.
Should I make things entertaining
at his hearing as a surprise event?
Do what?
Yes, he got rid of all the videos
on Choi Min Ho.
But it turns out
you were pretty awful...
to kids other than Choi Min Ho.
My gosh.
Seriously.
Your daddy did not raise you right.
But he wants to be
the Minister of Education?
If you stab me in the back again,
I'll make you more famous
than your father. This is a warning.
Got it?
(Attorney Han)
Darn it!
Darn it.
You've heard, right?
You don't need to worry.
What about Bae Jung Tae?
Like his wish,
I just proved his alibi.
Now, we should observe...
how ironic...
fates can be.
Is it really taken care of?
You're not fooling me, right?
What is this?
Hey, Mr. Detective.
Bae Jung Tae? What is this photo?
Let's talk more about it in person.
I can only imagine...
how curious you must be
about that photo.
(Corporal Ji Hyeong Ju)
Seung Min, what brings you here?
My gosh, you didn't answer
your phone all day. I had no choice.
I had to come to see you.
I still have a few days
until the deadline.
That's why I'm here. If you went
past it, it would've been a mess.
What? Kim Se Rin?
Isn't she the college girl
from the manhole?
Will you incorporate this
into your story?
How do you know Se Rin?
Of course, I know.
Her information went viral.
People even know her name?
That's not the only thing.
Her schools, her hometown,
everything about her got exposed.
Look. There's a photo too.
(Name: Kim Se Rin, age: 20,
Residence: Royal Studio)
By the way, isn't she the one
who made a scene at your house?
People posted comments saying
that she was a nutjob.
- Then, were you...
- Seung Min.
I'm sorry, but could you leave?
What? But...
- Did I mess up?
- No, no.
I just thought of an idea. Please.
(Kim Se Rin)
Ms. Lee Shin?
Why do you need her number
all of a sudden?
My gosh, we don't need to thank her.
I'll take care of it.
You just focus on getting better.
I'm going to meet up
with Detective Ji Hyeong Ju.
I'll go to the hospital
as soon as I'm done.
What's this?
We're not some important people.
Unless we died from some incidents
that went viral,
how did Ms. Lee Shin...
know when and where we'd die?
- It was a heart attack.
- How did you know?
I asked the officers
at the district police station.
We didn't find any other traces
on the site.
I think she just missed her footing,
but we must investigate more.
This is his ID and wallet.
Okay.
(Cha Jeung Seok)
Was this Ms. So Hye In?
Yes, she passed away.
Name, Jang Jin Ho.
There wasn't any blood in the car.
After falling,
he probably tried to escape.
But he got swept away
in the current.
They already came to
a tentative conclusion.
(Kim Se Rin: Was it accidental
or premeditated?)
(Who? How? Murdered?)
He's early.
He sure came early.
Detective...
All of these incidents...
took place in the district
of Seoul Makang Police Station.
Could this be a coincidence?
(Kim Se Rin,
Who? How? Murdered?)
(365: Repeat the Year)
- I thought you trusted me.
- What in the world is going on?
Who's the culprit?
You should catch them yourself.
Did Hyeong Ju kill him?
Don't be ridiculous.
I saw everything.
This is getting quite interesting.
You are a key suspect.
Do you know anything
about their deaths?
What if they all got murdered
by the same person?
Do you think I can't kill you?
- Report this to the police.
- First...
Take your hands off of this case.
It's a serial killing.
Was it really you?