I'll do it too.
I'll be the person who stays...
for you.
(A Piece of Your Mind)
(Episode 8)
That's hot. Hot.
Store-bought seaweed tastes good.
I'm doing it because I want to eat it.
Want a beer?
Sure.
Where are the others?
Jin Soo won't be home until past midnight.
Min Jung goes to sleep as soon as her drama ends.
I don't know what she does during the day.
I haven't seen you in days, but you look tired.
I...
thought a little,
and I feel kind of pressured.
About what?
I feel like we'll have to get serious if we keep going like this.
The human psyche is a funny thing.
I didn't realize when it was just between us,
but now it's out in the open, it makes me think,
and I can't just love as I want.
Of course you can. What's the big deal?
But I can't.
Just how much am I supposed to think about?
Whether or not I'll marry this person,
whether or not he'll be a good father...
How can I predict that...
How can I predict that already and worry about it now?
If you like each other now, you keep loving them.
If you continue to like them, you get married.
Of course, you should think about the next stage.
What stage are we at now?
The state at which we think about the next stage.
What's with you and stages?
It's frustrating.
Isn't that only natural?
No.
Get to your point.
Don't beat around the bush.
Drop the concern about the future and stages and all that.
Tell me your point.
Let's break up.
This is all I thought about a few days ago.
Sorry. I just feel too pressured.
I'm home.
Are you enjoying some alone time?
I'll stop intruding then.
You're so noisy!
He was incredible.
Awesome.
Why are you here?
I live here.
Okay, I'm glad you're here. Let's talk. Sit.
The lease is up next month.
Renew it in my name for me.
You're leaving anyway.
- Who said that? - You did.
You said when you came that it was temporary.
You were only here because of Ji Soo.
Sorry.
It wasn't only because of that.
Are you going to stay?
Yes. I want to settle down here.
That's so out of the blue. Why?
I'm sleeping well.
Sure. You want to live where you've been living.
You don't need a reason. Let's live together.
No. It's uncomfortable.
You move out.
I'm speechless.
You know you'll do as I ask.
Are you okay living in Seoul?
Yes. I like my job.
I lifted up a musician who had hit rock bottom.
If he becomes more and more successful...
This is different from growing plants.
It's unbelievably worthwhile.
I think I like people in need.
- What? - Well,
I've noticed a few strange things about you.
You're...
He has a wife. He's married.
The thing is, his wife suddenly went on a trip one day.
She still hasn't come back.
That's what Mr. Kang says,
but who knows?
Maybe they already split up.
- Drop it. - Don't worry.
I'm not crazy enough to fall for a man like him.
I check every detail to see if he's free of trouble...
before I fall for someone.
But I haven't had this feeling in a long time.
I feel like I'm needed.
- When should I move my stuff out? - Take your time.
That's my uncle.
Here.
Thanks.
It's not the location either.
Are you going to work?
Good morning.
Eun Joo and that guy.
They broke up.
Eun Joo, I'm having lunch at home. Let's eat together.
Gosh.
You're here early.
I'm staying until this evening. Are you available?
Yes, I just need to step outside during lunchtime.
Will you play what we recorded yesterday?
Sure.
Where are you going, Seo Woo?
I'm going home. I'll come back after lunch.
- In the middle of work? - I need to go.
This is from yesterday, isn't it?
It's nice.
If you hadn't dragged me out of the car,
this wouldn't have existed.
Gosh.
You're really here.
I said let's have lunch together.
I'm so tired.
I only made one pack of noodles.
We can throw in some rice.
All right, then. I roasted some seaweed too.
I can finish two bowls of rice with just seaweed.
- Eun Joo. - What?
What's going on between you and Chang Sup?
He wants to end it.
Why that jerk...
Don't say that. These things happen all the time.
Are you okay?
I am. I'm not fazed at all.
What about work?
I came while working because I was worried about you.
Hurry up and eat then.
Can you come home early this evening?
I'm going to make refreshing small octopus stew.
I'm craving something energizing.
Sounds delicious.
Gosh, my stomach.
(Have a nice trip.)
Did you sleep well last night?
It wasn't because of the location.
So you couldn't sleep.
I'm going to find another reason.
What else could there be?
If we bring hands into her daily life,
will it help reduce her anxiety?
Most anxiety symptoms are caused by the increase of neurotransmitters.
Drug treatment is most important, isn't it?
Causes of anxiety...
are as diverse as people's appearances.
It might be better to conduct supportive therapy along with it.
Like how?
- Holding hands, for example. - Holding hands with whom?
The person whose hand she wants to hold.
As in, you want to build a hand?
- I'm for it. - No. We can use conditioning.
With a pattern.
It could be perceived as a human hand...
if a certain pattern and pressure are strong.
We'll build a model on the premise that she feels it via conditioning.
Like phantom limb syndrome.
Medically speaking, phantom limb syndrome is...
a person experiencing pain in a hand...
- that was severed. - It's similar.
- I see. - Approaching this...
as a problem in her brain rather than her hand...
She can feel like...
she's holding someone else's hand although no one's there.
- We can make a hand. - No.
Just the touch.
It may be effective for old patients with dementia if we combine this...
with a conversation program at nursing homes.
They feel great emotional stability...
just by holding someone's hand.
- Cappuccino for me. - Okay. One cappuccino.
Americanos for everyone else.
Send us more articles on anxiety.
Okay.
It might be able to make coffee...
according to my mood soon thanks to you guys.
That's our plan.
You need a hand to feel a touch.
Why are we making only the sense of touch?
Go ahead and try it outside.
It's moving fast. Nice speed.
It's working hard.
It's delicious.
- My gosh. - Good work.
It's time for Min Jung to post pictures on her social media page.
- She does it at 1pm all the time. - Really?
No.
Mr. Kang, why don't we take a short break?
I heard you got this plant as a gift.
I did.
Who gave it to you?
A friend of mine.
What kind of a friend?
I'm the only one who considers us friends.
She doesn't consider me one.
Why do you think it's just you?
Because I know how I feel.
I don't know how she feels.
She went somewhere far away,
so I have no way of knowing how she feels.
Mr. Kang, I don't think it's a bad idea...
to release a few pieces first before a full album.
Why is it so quiet?
He's back to...
Mr. Kang, it was nice just now.
Shall we continue?
Shouldn't we check the nerve reaction data?
I've requested them to collect the data.
I'll take care of the rest.
That's right.
What is he doing?
My gosh.
- Are you done? - Yes.
Good work.
I'm proud of you.
Are you going to stay longer?
No.
I guess you have trouble playing without Seo Woo.
We mix pretty well.
Hi, Eun Joo.
Yes, I'm coming.
I'm probably on my way.
Here?
Eun Joo, I'm coming.
You're on your way where?
Oh, gosh.
Did you lace the blanket with something?
It puts me to sleep.
Sleep some more.
It's okay.
I came to stay with you since I had some time,
but I have to go now.
You just got here.
Did you get some sleep?
I had a tiring day, so I should be able to sleep.
Something came up in the homestay, so I need to be with Eun Joo.
She's in the worst mood.
I'll come again.
I'm so popular these days.
Everyone needs me.
Mr. Kang wants me by his side when he plays.
You know he's married, right?
I do.
Why did you point out that he's married?
Don't tell me...
- That's not it. - Oh my gosh.
No way.
Has my 1 percent gone up to 20 percent?
I mean,
I feel like that guy Kang In Wook...
may be leading you and Soon Ho on...
It just went up another 5 percent. It's 25 percent now.
No, that's not...
25 percent...
Hi, Eun Joo.
Chang Sup keeps walking around, and I can't stand it.
He shouldn't come here now that we broke up.
Why did he eat the stew I made to cheer myself up?
I'm not okay. I'm not okay at all!
I haven't had dinner. I worked extremely hard.
I slept a little, but I'm still exhausted.
So keep it short.
I'm thinking.
It's not over between you two, is it?
I mean,
whether to keep living here or to move out.
I'm torn.
Didn't you think before breaking up with her?
Hey, I wanted to stop dating her,
not move out of the homestay.
After settling the situation...
What are you talking about?
I'm starving.
I'm too tired to even argue with you.
Have the leftover stew.
Eun Joo's small octopus stew is the best.
Get out. Don't think, and just move out.
Something came up in the homestay, so I need to be with Eun Joo.
She's in the worst mood.
I ate it all.
Ate what?
It's not the exhaustion.
- Thank you. - Thank you.
- Goodbye. - Thank you.
Why are you moving your stuff here?
Because it's my apartment.
No, it isn't.
I told you it would become mine.
Let's go.
How do I...
Come in.
Soon Ho.
- Soon Ho? - Yes.
I changed it all to my name.
It used to be another name.
Uncle is finally moving on.
I'm sure...
he hoped he'd see Ji Soo somehow at some point.
But it's over now.
So I thought he'd leave Seoul, but he's settling down.
But he's definitely different from before.
He doesn't have that vagabond vibe anymore.
The funny thing is,
I was kind of disappointed that he was over Ji Soo.
Why?
He was always cold about love,
and became a real mess whenever he got into a fight.
A part of me felt like we need people like him too.
A human air purifier. I think I supported him subconsciously.
Of all the things to support.
What was that?
You should support him moving on.
Family should help with things like that.
What? Did you become his fan too?
Sure, he is all that.
- Should I put this here? - Yes.
Ji Soo?
- What about the device? - I got rid of it.
Ji Soo.
- Seo Woo! - Yes?
Ha Won?
Let's go.
How many texts did Mr. Kang send?
I'm asking because I don't know,
but does he need you for rehearsals too?
No, not necessarily.
He keeps asking for you. It's weird.
Why did I take this?
Still.
Ji Soo...
Where are you?
Is that possible?
That would be awesome.
When you're nervous, it's so calming...
if someone holds your hand.
More so in hospitals.
It's nerve-wracking just getting a check-up.
It would be nice if someone would hold your hand.
That's it. We have to try it.
I wonder if you can feel it when no one's actually there.
Do this.
Close your eyes.
Don't open them.
Did you feel anything?
I'm really dense.
Open your eyes.
I'm going to do this...
to your hand.
Close your eyes again.
It's because you're aware. You were conditioned.
It felt like you touched me.
This is touching.
Are you listening to music?
It's nice.
I'm scared,
but it's beautiful.
The last song...
Ji Soo heard.
It isn't the location,
and it isn't fatigue.
I think I fell asleep...
because someone stayed with me.
Can you...
come stay with me now?
I want to see you.
I'll do that again.
Seo Woo?
Seo Woo.
Ji Soo.
If...
If by chance...
Ha Won forgets you,
I'll...
I'll remember you more.
You should've told me if you were stepping out.
Seo Woo.
I can't drop it,
but I dropped it.
Shape up, will you?
Something suddenly came up at the studio, so I couldn't go.
You're at the studio, right?
Yes.
It's fine, then.
I'll text you later. Sorry.
It's okay.
You can take your time.
Why are you sighing?
Eun Joo.
Even if I lock myself in my room, I hear Chang Sup.
I hear him walking, drinking water, opening the door, peeing...
I gave you half off for the room, so it's half mine.
Eun Joo.
The thing about love...
Shut it. Don't talk about love or life or garbage like that.
I don't want to hear it.
I have my physical tomorrow, so I'm drinking stuff to poop.
I have no energy.
Tell me why you were sighing.
Go on. Tell me.
I guess it's because things never went well for me,
but whenever things seem to be going well,
I think of 100 reasons why it can't work.
That's so you.
You talk about deflating things with such energy.
Tell me 1 of the 100 reasons.
I feel like...
I stole a love someone else was supposed to receive.
Hey. Are you dating Chang Sup?
Are you insane?
Eun Joo, your hair.
This? I used the gift certificate Soo Ji gave me.
The owner gained so much weight since I saw her last year.
When I mentioned that, she said I couldn't use the gift certificate.
I'm sure she was offended. But?
So I said I was dumped, and she felt bad for me.
She did it right away.
You did good. Good thinking.
What does he look like?
The guy.
The 100 reasons guy.
Hey, Won. Straighten your shoulders.
Straighten them like this.
Yes, that's right.
Try pushing your bangs back.
- My bangs? - That's right.
That's right.
You should let the light hit your face. Like me.
For photos for documentation... Smile with your mouth closed.
Okay. Good.
This isn't for a document.
Then what?
Why are you taking your picture if it isn't for a document?
Someone asked me to send a picture of me.
Who?
You always said you were busy, and I guess you were.
Who asked you for a selfie?
A selfie...
I don't have any pictures.
Then why are you looking?
Do you have to go?
I... I need to use the bathroom. Darn it.
I went to all the restaurants you told me to check out.
I finished the list of hot restaurants.
Mommy ate at all of them.
I'm done now.
These are 4 to 5 minutes pieces that I wrote.
Pick any one of them.
We can record what you choose.
Here.
I tried jotting it down.
The impromptu piece you played in the concert hall before.
You played it again yesterday too.
I liked it, so I had recorded it and written up the score.
It should've disappeared.
What do you mean?
This piece shouldn't exist.
This can really help someone...
when they're having a really tough time.
Music saves the world, is that it?
Yes.
It saved me for a few seconds.
At least for a few seconds. Definitely.
Give me that.
I'll play it.
An invisible touch that soothes anxiety.
I'm sure you'll figure out the technical matters,
but...
people wouldn't use it only for medical purposes.
Definitely not.
There's a greater chance it'll be used improperly.
You'll make people feel something that isn't there.
You're very persistent.
You're right.
I can't seem to get free from it.
I should though.
I won't do this one.
Are you sure you can decide that so quickly?
I haven't even started yet.
Thank you for everything.
That's not good.
It's not like I'm terminal.
A doctor shouldn't tell me what to do.
I came to say goodbye.
But I don't want to.
Where's Eunjoo Homestay?
- Does it really exist? - Thank you for your hard work.
Let's meet on a personal level.
We can eat together once or twice a month.
I don't have any friends either.
All I have are work and family.
I had no time for friends.
Sorry, but I don't have the time.
I'm leaving this city.
Okay, then.
I'll just have to chat with your device.
It even has your personality. All except for one.
What?
She's cheerful.
- Then she isn't me. - She's you exactly.
You've just hit bottom right now briefly.
Briefly...
Can I talk to her?
The cheerful Kim Min Jung?
It's against the rules.
The patient on whom the device is based...
can't talk to it during the testing stage.
I want to hear what nonsense...
the cheerful one says.
I know that.
We can just take Min Jung out.
We have to do it right now. That's the only way.
I'm in front of your office.
Come in.
How can I talk to myself sober?
Right?
It's not like it's therapy.
From this point on, it's a social interaction.
Since we're friends now, not doctor and patient.
So how about a drink?
He invented this device.
I can't do anything without his permission.
Pretend he's not here.
How can I, when he's here?
Look at him. He doesn't even talk.
He isn't here.
Okay, then.
- Cheers. - You too?
Just the toast.
I don't drink while I'm working.
He makes me uncomfortable.
Should I turn it on or not?
Okay.
I'm turning it on.
Here.
Min Jung?
Hello?
You're the one who called me, so talk.
Kim Min Jung.
Yes?
Why are you so cheerful?
Why?
What is with that tone, like you have no worries in the world?
Seriously.
Why are you...
You're shameless.
Why are you?
Oh my gosh.
Why do you live?
What's wrong?
You can't run to save your life.
Mom...
Mom.
No!
Eun Joo!
No, please!
No, please. Please no...
Wake up.
Please wake up. Mommy's here.
Mommy's here. Wake up.
Please no.
Please...
If only I had run a little faster...
If only... If only I had run a little faster...
If only I could've held her hand...
She was waiting to hold my hand...
If only I had run a little faster...
Thank you.
I went home once or twice a month.
I was too busy with work.
- Hello. - I have a reservation.
What name is the reservation under?
My daughter checked my Instagram as soon as she woke up.
The more likes I got, the happier she was.
She nagged if I didn't eat a proper meal.
Then the next day, I'd eat what she told me to,
and take a picture.
That's all I did for her.
I realized after my daughter died...
that without her,
everything was meaningless.
There was nothing to work hard for,
nothing to live for... Everything was meaningless.
I can't forgive myself.
If only I could've held her hand...
Didn't someone hold my hand earlier?
I felt like I could live.
Your bag.
Thank you.
- Have a nice day. - Have a nice day.
I came to visit someone.
Where are you going now? Do you want to go home together?
No, I have to go somewhere.
Can't you go with me just for today?
I don't want to go alone.
Go alone. Stop whining.
It wasn't a woman's hand.
What are you listening to?
- Mr. Kang. - Right.
How does it feel...
to stay in the studio with Mr. Kang all day long?
What do you mean?
I'm just curious.
You don't feel anything special, right?
No.
Okay, then.
I only work when I work.
I said okay.
I like someone.
When did you start dating?
I'm not dating anyone. I just like him, that's all.
Isn't that the same thing?
I see. Is it one-sided?
I like him,
and I think he thinks I'm a nice person.
It's similar, but it's completely different.
It's night and day.
It's not that extreme.
I don't think it's just one-sided.
If our dense Seo Woo is confused, it isn't one-sided.
Why do you think that?
How do you think that? Why? Even I didn't think that.
Just because. I'm just throwing it out there.
It's not like I can tell you to stop.
It's employee management.
You're always picking on me.
Are you mad?
(Before Dawn)
Hello?
Do you know the term "half-look"?
Half-look?
Do you look at only half?
When I was learning Korean,
I read Korean dictionaries and maps all the time.
It's a term I saw in the Korean dictionary.
When a married woman...
missed her mom,
she'd go halfway and look at her briefly.
That's what they called a "half-look".
That's an antiquated term.
No one says that these days.
Let's do a half-look.
Together.
You can walk 10 minutes,
and I'll drive 10 minutes.
The overpass will be the halfway point.
Let's do a half-look there.
I'm working, so I can't stay long.
That's what a half-look is.
Looking briefly and affectionately.
Hand.
Briefly...
and affectionately.
Okay.
You'll be busy tonight too...
I'm not busy.
See you later.
No, no. This wasn't it.
He asked me to stay.
Please stay.
I said I'd stay.
I have to stay.
Then I can just stay.
He asked for help, and I just have to help.
I can't go because I dropped the device?
Why are you creating drama in your head?
I cleaned up.
I cleaned.
You're good once you put your mind to it.
Did you sleep here?
I go back and forth.
It must be uncomfortable.
I'm used to sleeping a few hours here and there.
I'm here...
because you asked me to help you sleep.
So...
Let's set it up first.
What was I doing?
You were in the room.
That's right. I was in the room, and you were on the sofa.
Put your bag down.
The door was open that time.
We'll make it exactly the same.
Let's make it exactly the same.
What was the angle at which we saw each other?
You slept there, and I slept on the sofa.
Yes, that's right.
Okay, let's sleep then. Goodnight.
Then when do we eat this?
Where's that? That.
- "That"? - Yes, that.
The... That. The...
I don't have that, so let's just eat.
Okay.
Frying pan.
"That" was a frying pan.
There was a time when I didn't sleep for a month.
Why not?
Right before I left Oslo.
It may seem strange to others.
Not sleeping, not eating at mealtimes,
not caring if the living room and bedroom are indistinguishable,
not settling down in a place.
That's how I am, and I'm used to it.
It's the same blanket.
You said you slept well because of the blanket,
because it crinkled since it was new.
In the spring and fall, if it gets sunny out,
Eun Joo and I hang the blankets out in the sun.
I sleep the best on those nights.
I should hang a clothesline in the front yard.
Let's do that.
I'll leave once you fall asleep.
I need to go.
Things suddenly got busy at the homestay.
Timing is so...
It's working. Go to bed.
Go before I get sleepier.
I'll walk you home.
No one will use that blanket,
so come whenever you want to sleep well.
Since I can't go to the semi-basement.
I can hear the thoughts in your head.
It is what you're thinking.
You're right.
- Hey. - Yes?
Tell me 1 more of the 100 reasons why it can't happen.
(Epilogue)
See? You won't let me go.
You want me too much.
It's just for today. I only need you today.
I won't need you starting tomorrow.
I don't want to be alone today.
I'm scared.
Thumbs up.
(A Piece of Your Mind)
Out of the blue,
there are 100 reasons why you can't like him.
Was it intentional?
Stopping midway and looking only briefly.
Yes.
What was your daughter's name?
You know, a noose hanging from the ceiling.
What?
Ji Soo?
Someone was just here.
I'll make an exception and listen to you.
As long as no one dies.
What if someone did die?
I want to see you and I want to stay with you.
This is all new to me.