Medicine box.
Where is it? Seo Woo said she put it here.
Here it is.
What's this?
What is it?
Who's this?
"Original Score Number One".
She told you a million times that she was hurting,
but you ignored her.
What will you listen to now?
You have no right.
Ji Soo.
In Wook.
I went back and called out to her...
Enough.
Do you know what you've done?
Do you know what you took from me,
what you trampled on,
and what you crushed?
Do you know how I've lived each and every day,
and how I survived?
Do you know what you've done?
Don't force your own thoughts onto Seo Woo.
This is the decision that I made...
after struggling with it for a very long time.
I'm in pain because of his regret.
His tears hurt me.
I want to tell him,
"It's okay. You can stop struggling."
(I want to be a strength to In Wook)
I want to be a strength to In Wook.
Now that I've made this decision, I feel at peace.
Once enough time passes,
I'll be able to talk about this with a smile.
I'll contact you again when that time comes.
Take care of yourself, Ms. Moon.
Yours, Kim Ji Soo.
Ji Soo.
Guess who...
let Kang In Wook know what was in your heart, Ji Soo.
The one who suffered the most because of him.
It was Ha Won.
Ji Soo.
I relayed your earnest feelings to him.
Now,
rest in peace.
You aren't hurt anywhere.
Normal.
Well,
I have thick bones. I'm strong.
Min Jung is leaving tomorrow,
so I need to go.
Did you cry?
I told you. I don't cry.
Oh, right.
You said you never cry.
Of all people,
Ha Won,
this man saved Kang In Wook.
(A Piece of Your Mind)
You're going too far away.
There are plenty of nursing homes in Seoul too.
It's close to the sea.
I've wanted to live someplace near the sea.
You'll get over it quickly.
When my parents first moved to Geoje Island,
they said they were loving it, but not anymore.
At least I'll like it for a short while.
Aren't you scared of living in an unfamiliar place?
Yes, I'm scared. Why wouldn't I be?
Still, I've got to go.
I want to go and get through it.
I want to show myself...
that I'm not weak.
It's good to be brave, but...
Whatever.
- Hey. - Yes?
Why are you running a homestay when you used to hate it?
I insisted on doing it.
To work hard for five years,
earn a large sum of money, and live the way I wanted.
Five years have passed.
Right, it's way past five years.
My goal has changed.
Seo Woo.
I'm going to quit when she comes above ground.
She says she feels too guilty to live comfortably.
She feels at ease there.
She keeps telling me that she's okay,
but if she really is okay, she'll come above ground.
I'll make sure she gets out of there.
Or I won't be in peace.
I'm home.
- Hey. - Jin Soo.
Are you drinking without any food again?
We have no drinking foods.
That's why I bought some.
- What did you buy? - Sausages and...
Mom.
Give me a bit of strength.
Why do I feel so sad?
It's driving me crazy.
You were so rude.
The lease said I'd get that room.
- You were so mean. - I did nothing wrong.
- What... - Come on.
Hey.
She doesn't drink. She can't.
Seo Woo? Seo Woo!
What's wrong with you?
It's okay. Let me drink.
She can drink.
Why am I so sad?
Why do I keep crying?
Goodness.
Why are you doing this? Min Jung is leaving tomorrow.
I don't know. My heart aches so much.
(7:40am)
(2 missed calls)
Ji... Ji Soo?
Yes... Yes, it's me.
What...
How...
I heard In Wook's recording.
Didn't you play it?
That's...
What good timing. I wanted to ask you a favor.
Do you know how In Wook first told me that he liked me?
That's so random.
I don't know. Who is Kang In Wook anyway?
He said he watched me for 10 years alone.
He didn't leave Oslo because he liked seeing me.
I can't forget what he said and the look on his face.
He was so cute.
He liked Ji Soo for years.
He wants to be where you were,
hear what you heard,
and feel what you felt.
I really like looking at him like this.
It's an unrequited love.
Ji Soo's point of reaction is Mr. Kang's unrequited love.
I want to hear his voice.
- Please. - No.
I don't know who he is.
I don't even want to be close with him.
Not a conversation. It'll be too painful for him.
Let me listen by myself.
He isn't in any pain right now.
I'm hungover right now, so I can't really talk.
- I'll let you rest. - I'm...
dead, aren't I?
I booked a practice session.
Hello.
I didn't feel like greeting you, but I did it anyway.
I started a conversation.
Don't you have anything to say?
Do you think I'm doing this because I want to talk to you?
I'm sorry.
He spoke.
Piano in April.
How are your preparations going?
You're performing at such an amazing recital.
Why all of a sudden...
He spoke again.
Please play the piece you wrote.
"Number One".
I want to listen to it right now.
Well, Seo Woo.
I don't play something just because someone asks...
Please do it.
I want to hear his voice...
and his piano.
It'll be hard for him to talk with me since I'm dead.
Please.
Let me listen by myself.
Seo Woo.
Continue. I'm listening.
The longer, the better.
I'll listen just for five minutes.
I was...
wrong this whole time.
I was foolish.
So don't take what I said to heart.
Ha Won and Ji Soo...
Please talk as if Ji Soo were here.
I'll explain later.
Do as I say.
The device?
She knows that she's dead.
She asked me to let her hear your voice.
Please do that for her.
For Ji Soo...
I thought...
about Ji Soo as I wrote this piece.
And...
This one too.
When Ji Soo...
didn't know I existed.
When I had a crush on her.
And one day...
when she first looked at me.
Even after we got married,
I always...
thought about her when I played the piano.
I love her,
and I miss her.
Wasn't it hard conversing with me?
It feels like...
I'm talking on the phone with a friend who lives far away.
Do you think it'll stay that way?
Be honest with me.
I'm not so sure about that.
You really are honest.
Do me one last favor.
Will you...
get rid of me?
Goodbye, my early 20s.
(I'm so happy. It's exciting. Let's not forget today.)
We'll walk you to the bus stop.
Let's just part ways at the gate.
We'll walk you there.
Then I won't visit you.
Darn it.
Why isn't Seo Woo here yet?
Let's go to the bus stop together.
No, it's fine.
Let's say bye in front of Eunjoo Homestay.
See me off with a lighthearted "See you soon."
Like it's no big deal.
Like, "See you when you get back from the market."
She seems anxious.
Min Jung.
Let me give you a hug.
No.
Okay.
I'll get going.
I'm scared.
You'll come visit on your days off, right?
Text me the day before.
I'll cook something good. Eat with us!
I'll buy yummier food, so you have to come!
You have to!
I'm fine.
Tell Eun Joo I'm fine.
Come by now and then.
Come and rest, and eat some good food.
Don't cry like a fool.
Good luck with your relationship.
Thank you.
Don't worry!
Don't worry about a thing!
Be brave!
That's it. That's Eunjoo Homestay.
You've given me courage.
Eun Joo,
I'll be strong from now on.
Will you get rid of me?
I shouldn't be here.
- Get rid of me. - How...
could I...
If you can't, ask Won...
No.
He can't lose you again.
He just can't.
Yes, I think so too.
I will...
do it.
I'll get rid of you...
so you can't talk to anyone.
I know it'll be hard, but please do it for me.
I remember when I first met you.
When I was at my lowest.
I was walking up the hill carrying the plates,
and you were standing way up ahead.
That was the first time I realized what it means when they say...
someone glows.
Ms. Kim Ji Soo?
Way at the end of the road, glowing brightly.
I was so grateful...
and I didn't want them to break.
You were holding the door open.
I'm so grateful for you, Seo Woo.
Get rid of me...
and forget me.
Goodbye.
I... I can't do it right now.
What am I saying?
I can't look at you.
- Seo Woo. - I can't...
look at you right now.
Have a nice day.
(Before Dawn)
Are you happy to see me?
I bet you're very happy to see me.
We parted ways and were reunited after 35 minutes.
I guess we can part ways with a "Have a nice day."
You're not bothered by what Kang In Wook said, are you?
I'm not influenced by what other people say.
It doesn't bother me.
Your arm will go numb.
It's the perfect weight.
I'm falling asleep.
You smiled
And said to me
I want to fly
Seo Woo.
I'm okay.
I'm just...
very confused right now.
I think I'm weird too.
I feel like the person who saved Kang In Wook...
was you, Ha Won.
And that...
makes me so sad for you.
It's just so sad.
I shouldn't be here.
Get rid of me.
I will...
do it.
It's good for everyone.
It isn't good for just one person.
There's no reason to be sad.
I told you I'm weird.
Mr. Kang.
I understand.
How it feels to be caught between the two of them.
If I'm caught between Ji Soo and Ha Won,
they don't crush me meanly.
They crush me...
so hard that it's excruciating.
Try getting out briefly.
Then you'll see...
whether you were caught between them...
or next to them.
Are you not going to the studio anymore?
I'm not sure.
"Moon Studio when you're slumping."
It's true.
You got me out of mine.
I used up all my energy on that.
I have none left.
I'd like to apologize.
To whom?
I'm sure there are several.
To you...
and to Ha Won.
You can apologize to me now.
I'm sorry...
and thank you for getting me out.
Ha Won...
I'll tell him.
But if Uncle insists on seeing you face to face,
I'll let you know that too.
May I?
But if he says, "It's okay,"
it really is okay.
While you suspected...
Ji Soo and Ha Won's relationship for 10 years,
he figured out on his own...
how to overcome the tragedies that befell him.
He has his own methods.
It's not even all of it.
He protects just a small piece of what's important to him,
regains focus, and fulfills his dreams.
All while protecting himself.
Are you annoyed because I complimented Won?
No.
You have...
a great uncle.
(Piano in April, Kang In Wook's Piano Recital)
Come if you have time.
It's...
really nice here.
I'll see you in the studio.
"Moon Studio when you're slumping."
You should get out of yours too.
I'll go to Eunjoo Homestay today.
(I'll go to Eunjoo Homestay today)
Where are you?
At the office.
When are you done?
In half an hour.
I'll text you later.
I'm leaving now.
Do you go through the lobby when you leave the office?
No.
- Are you here? - No.
I'm in the house.
You're talking like you're here.
Which way do you go if you don't go through the lobby?
I have another walkway...
Why do you ask?
No reason in particular.
You must miss me.
You're right.
I want to see you from afar,
but you won't walk by.
I'm in the studio, so it's not like I can teleport over there.
Seo Woo.
Tell me.
Okay.
I'll tell you.
I have to.
I...
found out why I've been acting so strangely.
There is one thing I can't seem to find.
I can't get past it because...
I'm too afraid of being sad.
When I look... When I look at you,
I get too...
Why are you sad when you see me?
That's it. That's my problem.
You did nothing wrong.
The problem...
The problem is with me.
But we can't not see each other.
A short while.
It won't be for long. Just for a short while...
No.
Seo Woo.
Look at me.
No. Pretend I'm there.
Pretend I'm standing in front of you.
Pretend you're here.
Pretending you're here...
Let's take a brief... A very short break...
for a little while.
- Seo Woo. - While we're apart,
do something for me. Anything.
Do something...
that encourages you for me.
Put your fingers...
under your ear...
and feel your pulse.
Thump.
Remember this with every heartbeat.
That I love you a lot,
and I cherish you a lot.
Don't crumble just because you're sad.
I'll wait,
so...
make sure...
to call me.
I will.
I'll tell myself...
that what protects me beats inside of me.
I'll remember with every heartbeat.
Drink this and sleep well.
(Drink this and sleep well)
(From Kim Ji Soo)
(Piano in April, Kang In Wook's Piano Recital)
I'll do well,
Ji Soo.
(Pianist Kang In Wook)
(Wishing you a Fantastic Recital)
You did great, In Wook.
Ji Soo.
Here.
- She'll call. - I didn't ask.
You're so confident, it's sad.
I can't explain it,
but we can't break up.
Do we have the final test subject?
Isn't that Jin Hwan?
We decided not to do mine.
It's that engineer, right?
Right now, it is 17.5°C...
- and sunny. - Seo Woo?
It will be very dry.
It has been over 30 years.
Were you here all this time?
Let's see...
What a great sound.
Seo Woo, listen to this.
Do you know Seo Woo?
Searching for "a harmonium with a great sound".
Oh, my. It isn't Seo Woo.
It's just Seo Woo's voice.
This isn't Seo Woo yet.
Excuse me.
It hasn't reached the point of reaction.
What did she like?
Eunjoo Homestay.
Searching for information on "Eunjoo Homestay".
Grandma?
Hello.
Why are you so shocked?
You shouldn't touch that.
I learned how to turn it on and off.
I started studying acoustics.
I'll watch your practice today.
You'll watch it?
I'll watch with my eyes.
The line-up for the recital is insane.
- You'll have to practice hard. - Did you...
decide to come back to the studio?
Did I ever quit?
If I were going to quit because of something like that,
I shouldn't have started at all.
I'll study hard...
and assist Seo Woo when we record your next album.
It takes about two years to make an album, right?
I don't work with people who don't know music.
I'll have to study music as well.
I have my work cut out for me.
How about a bet to see whether you finish your album first...
or I finish my studies first?
I'm saying, let's do our best.
Hey. I did as Seo Woo said.
- But it won't work. - Why aren't you coming to visit?
Are you coming this week or not?
You're working yourself to death again, aren't you?
Okay, I'll go.
- Ask her for me. - Okay, hold on.
Seo Woo. She's asking...
if you can think of something else.
I don't know.
She doesn't know either.
- What could it be? - What?
What was that?
Sunset in Misiryeong.
I'm memorizing it.
Who's that?
We got cut off.
Hey you. Who's Before Dawn?
Searching...
Min Jung.
She's here.
She's... Excuse me.
Seo Woo's here. Do you want to talk to her?
Really?
Before Dawn.
Before Dawn puts Seo Woo together.
Makes sense.
Who's that?
Just someone.
This way.
Stay.
When Seo Woo was at her lowest...
Time can't erase the moment you first met them.
People like that tend to remain in my life for a long time.
The person who pulled her up.
It's me. Before Dawn.
Before Dawn.
Goodbye.
Thank you.
The thing you said you liked looking at...
You don't mean...
- Me? - We miss each other.
We want to be with each other.
We want to hold hands.
Please stay.
I'll get better.
I like 17°C the best.
It's the best for taking walks.
It's the perfect temperature to recover.
Why don't you live here?
Come here after work.
I'll be here when you return.
When I come, you'll be here.
The person who can say,
"I pulled Seo Woo up..."
"when she was at her lowest."
What's this?
Points of reaction are complicated,
but it can be explained by one thing.
Isn't it amazing?
Just as failure leads to success,
it's like the two sides of a coin.
It's alluring. It's intriguing.
Like the thunder.
Think about it again starting with that.
It's thundering.
Ji Soo used to get scared.
Piano.
How is it?
Should we add some pepper?
Should we? Okay.
Ji Soo. You should listen as you play.
Thunder.
The thunder is so loud.
Mom.
It's thundering.
Your mom plays the piano whenever it thunders...
so you won't get scared.
I got to know someone that precious.
Shouldn't I change somehow?
If I never met Seo Woo,
I never would've had the courage to even try.
- Eun Joo. - Hey.
I love the walk home.
I'm so glad I moved back.
- Did you eat? - Of course.
Good. Go in first.
I'll go in once Seo Woo comes.
She's been too down lately.
- Okay. - Okay.
(Please do not take. Eunjoo Homestay)
Seo Woo.
Me too.
Let's go home.
Hey.
When did you draw the heart?
- Heart? - Yes.
There's a heart?
- It wasn't you? - What?
It wasn't you?
What heart?
This.
No, that wasn't me.
- It wasn't? - No.
Who was it?
I think I know.
(Please do not take. Eunjoo Homestay)
Eun Joo. Do...
Do you have a hammer or something like that?
Why?
I need to get rid of something.
I think breaking it will be the least...
- Get rid of what? - Well...
So...
I was asked by someone.
Who asked you to do something so horrible?
Don't do it.
Look at you.
You're trembling already.
Don't listen to jerks who ask for bad favors.
It's not like that.
Don't do it.
You don't have to do it. Don't do it.
Did you eat yet?
I wanted to finish this the day I close down the homestay,
but let's eat it now.
Let's stop putting meaning behind eating certain foods,
and just eat them when we want.
If you think you're alone,
you'll become weak and controlled by people.
You're not alone.
Call out everyone who loved you, everyone who loves you now,
and everyone who will love you in the future.
Don't you feel secure then?
You can't become weak.
You, Han Seo Woo, think about Han Seo Woo the most.
You have yourself.
You're precious to yourself. So why are you doing this?
Why are you harming yourself when you're so precious?
Eat this, and be strong.
Give me the number of the person who asked you for the favor.
I'll give them a serious talking to.
They should destroy it themselves. Why are they doing this to you?
Don't do it.
I won't.
Come to think of it, I don't have to.
I must have lost my mind.
Hey. You can't eat this then.
No. These are tears of enlightenment.
Tears of joy.
Eat.
My precious Seo Woo.
I refuse your request to get rid of you.
In exchange, I'll put you someplace where no one can find you.
I also refuse your request to forget you.
I'm going to remember you.
It's your favorite weather.
Sprout, and grow healthy and strong.
You're saying bye to so many people recently.
I'm sure there's a meaning to it all.
Of course there is. A precious person came and left.
That's why Uncle left too.
Where?
He went there.
Courageously. While thinking of you.
Where is that?
I never knew he'd go there.
He didn't have to, but he insisted.
I was against it. I asked why he had to go.
Where did he go?
The place I wouldn't have been able to go to...
if I didn't have Ha Won.
I'm back.
Mom. Dad.
I think I know where.
I'm back.
You smiled
And said to me
I want to fly
Like a bird
(Han Seo Woo)
Hello?
What do you see?
The sky.
What are you looking at?
The night sky.
The front yard.
The clothesline.
You're at the house.
You sound better.
I recovered a little after coming here.
And I heard your voice right now only briefly, but I'm much better.
I can't even remember when I was sad.
Even the voice by itself is effective.
It's more than enough.
You'll be all better once you see me.
A full recovery.
I'll have to see you soon.
When can I see you?
Tomorrow.
See you tomorrow.
How nice.
Once I get on the plane, I'll be in Korea in half a day.
I'll be there in two hours.
I'll be there in 15 minutes.
You're here.
I'm back.
(Thank you for watching "A Piece of Your Mind")
(A Piece of Your Mind)
Did you see the moon?
- It's huge. - Right?
- Isn't it pretty? - It's super bright.