Only he knows...
the answer to the question I've asked all my life.
Only he knows.
I know.
I know how you feel, but...
Soon Ho.
Just one day tomorrow.
Leave him alone for just one day tomorrow.
How could you...
Please.
No.
How is this...
How is this happening?
(A Piece of Your Mind)
It's in Seo Woo's room.
If you can't find a mat, check if there's a bedsheet.
None of it is here. Come find it yourself.
Goodness.
And have a conscience.
Stop renting out the semi-basement.
Back when I lived here, your mom didn't rent it out.
Seo Woo insisted on using that room.
Goodness.
Min Jung, don't come out. Don't!
- I told you not to come out. - Why not?
- Were you crying? - No, I wasn't.
He seems even worse.
Why were you two crying?
His niece is causing us so much grief.
How much grief could a niece cause?
His niece must be adorable.
You can't win over your niece. There's no way.
This is good.
I was going to go for this distressed landlady.
I said I'm not distressed.
- Go where? - For a walk.
- At this hour? - Evening walks are the best.
I know the best place in this neighborhood.
- Join us. - Let's go.
- Let's go. - Goodness.
It'll cheer you up.
I'll show you the best spot.
I didn't know there was a place like this in our neighborhood.
When you ran out of the house,
your mom and I found you here.
She used to run out of the house all the time.
I hated the house.
I hated people frequenting there...
because it didn't feel like a home.
What? You said you were running the homestay to take a break.
That's the same thing.
This tiny thing was a disobedient brat.
She always talked back to her parents.
She never made eye contact with the tenants, calling us hobos.
What... I only remember good things about me though.
I envy your poor memory.
When I was at the homestay,
I came here whenever I felt troubled.
Looking up at the sky like this gave me such peace.
It's nice.
How nice.
(Eunjoo Homestay)
Let's go in.
Go inside.
Aren't you afraid?
Of knowing the exact situation.
Aren't you scared?
Not at all.
(Dressing Room, Kang In Wook)
(All tickets are sold out.)
"Sold out"?
I thought Mr. Choi was doing this.
If I were him, I would've yanked you away from the door,
barged in, and asked Mr. Kang everything I wanted.
My uncle and I aren't like that.
Right, I know what you two are like.
I would've opened the door if I were you.
I would've brought him a chair so they could talk alone.
You said you wouldn't come, but you're here.
That's good enough.
Thanks for coming.
You may not care, but the afternoon recital sold out.
Bye.
You're here.
All right, have a seat.
Oh, no.
What are you talking about? You're the main engineer today.
I know you went over the performance list...
and organized things all night despite your busy schedule...
because of my sudden request.
Of course.
Have a seat.
(3:50pm)
The tickets are sold out, right?
Was it a group reservation?
Why isn't anyone here?
Why isn't anyone here? It's almost time.
Do people usually show up right when it's about to start?
Isn't it a bit strange?
We're fully booked though.
There were no cancellations either.
What is it this time?
No, nothing.
I shouldn't be doing this here.
What should I do at a time like this?
There may be people in seats...
that we just can't see from here.
I'll go check.
Don't go in there. The recital is about to start.
Uncle.
Ms. Moon.
- Let go of me. - He wants to ask just one thing.
Let go.
He hasn't been able to ask anyone this whole time,
and he finally knows whom to ask.
Move.
Mr. Kang.
Kang In Wook.
Tell me exactly...
what you saw,
what you heard,
and what you did...
that day.
Move.
He has kept this question in his heart all his life.
He has to ask it.
Please leave them alone.
It snowed.
I saw your mom on my way home.
- Oh, I'm sorry. - No, it's okay.
Are you Korean?
You've been walking past here since two months ago, right?
You didn't answer, so I didn't think you were Korean.
Do you go to Eva Lawson High School?
Before I knew it, I was speaking in Korean.
Ha Won is coming this way right now.
Didn't the school make you take shelter?
It's going to snow more.
Where is your house?
Why don't you stay at my place?
Goodbye.
I shouldn't have said that to her.
I went back.
Ma'am!
Ha Won's mom!
Ma'am.
Ma'am!
Ha Won's mom!
I went back and called out to her...
But no matter how much I called out to her...
Two pairs of boots.
For Won and me.
She was bringing them for Won and me.
For me...
Enough.
(Dressing Room, Kang In Wook)
I thought it was...
because of the strong wind and snow.
But that wasn't the reason.
It was because of Kang In Wook.
I need to take revenge,
but I've never done it before, so I don't know how.
Should I break his fingers?
How should I do it?
Why does it feel like...
everything I do is in vain?
Hey.
Don't be sad.
Don't let everything lead to sadness.
Being sad when you should be angry or annoyed...
is bad for you.
It's okay to be angry. Be brave.
What was that?
Good work.
Bye.
What's going on?
I suddenly felt the urge to call.
You are amazing.
Soon Ho called. She told me to call you.
That you're having a really hard time.
What is it?
Tell me about my mom.
You wouldn't let me talk about her.
You were determined to forget her.
I thought I'd remember clearly even if I were determined,
but I'm afraid I really will forget her.
I want to hear about her.
Of course. She was such a beautiful person.
How could you forget such a person?
Ms. Im Su Ock...
was cheerful, strong, beautiful,
played the piano beautifully...
She couldn't cook though. Her snacks were not very good.
She said her cooking wouldn't improve...
because you ate everything well.
That's right.
Need help?
With what? I'm not doing anything.
Sit with me.
What should we have for breakfast?
Should I make sandwiches?
If you make something that you had never made for breakfast before,
would Chang Sup think it was special...
or your way of giving him the finger?
He'd like it because it's something new and different.
He's simple like that.
I've been taking this path for so many years.
I guess you wished...
someone would do this for you when things were tough.
Don't you feel like you're being supported?
Helping you maintain your balance.
I'm going to stay like this. I won't let go.
I know...
what I have to do...
to make myself happy.
I care so much about myself.
First, I go early in the morning.
There's no one in the building.
I open the door myself, air out the place,
make coffee,
and play music recorded the day before.
Then I hold my cup of coffee...
and take my first sip while looking out the window.
It's awesome.
What about you?
I'm thinking.
You have to research and put in the effort...
to figure out what you must do to make yourself happy.
It won't just fall on your lap.
Think hard about it.
Tell me another one of yours.
On my way home, I look back,
and there's a beautiful sunset.
I can picture it.
Another one.
When I go to work at the same time as usual,
but whereas it was dark yesterday, it's bright today.
The way the world knows to change with the seasons.
I like seeing that.
It's slightly different.
It's like playing "Red light, green light"...
with the world.
I thought of something that I like.
Listening to things you like.
Do you want to say something?
I don't like that many things.
What else is there?
Let's see.
The studio.
Listening to the best musicians perform before my very eyes...
using the best sound equipment.
I love it.
I'd like to see it too.
What? What's that?
It keeps lingering in my head, but I don't know what it is.
My mom used to play it.
Keep going.
It's very short.
I can find it.
I promise to find it and play it for you.
On the piano.
You played one for me too.
You have something to say.
Say it.
I won't forgive Kang In Wook.
Don't get your hands dirty.
I'll take care of it all.
That's not it.
Ms. Moon is so weird.
That's how she is.
"Are you okay?"
No,
I'm not okay.
You're right.
Right now,
it's all hazy, like I'm walking in a dense fog.
Weird, right?
I think so too.
It'll get better.
The world changes on its own.
Rely on it.
"It's 12°C today."
"Tomorrow, it'll be 17."
"I'll get better."
"It was cold today,"
"but tomorrow..."
"it'll be warm."
"I'll get better."
I like 17°C the best.
It's the best for taking walks.
It's the perfect temperature to recover.
I need to put up a clothesline in the front yard...
and take walks. I have so much to do.
That's nice.
(Eunjoo Homestay)
Are you leaving your shampoo?
No, I'm taking it.
There isn't much left.
If you want it so badly, I can leave it.
Okay.
Hey! Hey! Aren't you going to thank me?
Hold up!
- Jin Soo. - Thank you.
Yes. My favorite soup.
Is that the meaning behind this soup?
There's no meaning.
Why are you being like that?
Min Jung. Do you have another interview?
Yes. I have three today.
There's a lot of good food.
- It's the usual... - It's the usual...
It must be hard to get a new job.
That's right. So be thankful to your parents.
You run the homestay.
Awesome. I bet you'd be awesome.
Jin Soo, you be my witness.
I'm in.
I'll bum around in my room,
and take half the rent.
I'm out.
See? You don't want to do it either.
Exactly.
Think about why you're doing this.
Once you do,
if you question later why you're doing this,
you can tell yourself.
Chang Sup.
Are you moving back home?
So you remember.
No one seems to care.
No goodbyes.
They only talk about life.
Although it's the last time.
- You can finish. - "Last time"?
Are you dying tomorrow?
Watch what you say.
Are you moving back home?
It's a two-hour commute.
Bus, subway, then another bus...
Just wake up early.
You don't know how I feel.
This precious thing...
Thank you.
I gave Chang Sup two pieces of your mom's pickled vegetable.
It's his last breakfast.
Good thinking. He likes that.
You did very well.
Okay, good going, Uncle.
You should screen my calls if you're mad.
Good going.
I knew you'd be like this.
I came to drag you out.
Let's go. Get some sun, and let's go eat.
What's nearby?
Soon Ho.
Stop now.
Stop what?
You don't have to do this.
I have something to say to you. Let's go.
Many people who went to the recital posted online.
It was a humiliating recital, but you did it well.
You should be proud of yourself.
You prepared long and hard for it.
I'll put together the nice comments and send them to you.
Look through them and cheer up.
Is that everything you wanted to say?
Go see my uncle.
See him and lay down your burden.
I'll help you.
If I see him...
and apologize, will it be over?
Ask him in person.
"Will it be over if I apologize?"
Do you know what thought I keep having over and over?
I wonder...
if Ha Won and Ji Soo met.
Why are you thinking about that?
Right?
It makes no sense, but that's all I can think about.
Ji Soo went to that house in Wokin-dong.
No, she didn't go, but...
She didn't go there.
She never went there.
I see.
Stop thinking things like that.
Think only about what you did yesterday.
One, you gave a wonderful recital.
Two, my uncle.
If you are miserable right now, that should be why.
This is who I am.
This is why Ji Soo was miserable.
If I were supposed to change, I should've changed much sooner.
Your question doesn't deserve an answer,
but they did not meet.
And give your life, your all...
to free yourself from that thought.
I'll try.
I said to give your life, your all.
My uncle...
has nothing, has no one...
He was dumped by Ji Soo,
who was like family, whom he thought would be family forever.
He went through all sorts of hardships and heartbreaks,
but he works desperately to stay focused and protect himself.
He doesn't know how to abandon himself.
That's what it means to give your life, your all.
I watched him for 10 long years. No, 9 years.
I keep adding a year.
That's...
how my uncle...
spent the last nine years...
because of that one thing you said.
(From Kim Ji Soo)
Grandma. Tell Uncle to come home and eat.
He's having a hard time right now. He may die.
You call him.
Call him for me. I can't face him.
No, I won't.
Not now.
Call him anyway.
I'm early.
I thought the engineer was a woman.
I'm not an engineer.
I'm going up first.
But...
(28 Device - voice)
Voice?
100 test subjects.
I'm the 100th.
It'll be done after me.
Yes. The test.
Voice...
That's right.
A conversation device...
with that person's personality, emotions, and voice.
The studio is dry.
You're the manager, right? Is there any water?
Yes. I'll be right back.
What broke?
What is that?
My bag fell.
How does she know the house has good acoustics?
She has been there.
Well. To be exact, she wasn't there herself.
I must have lost my mind. I'm hearing things.
A large company uses our studio too.
They're collecting voices or something.
A conversation device...
with that person's personality, emotions, and voice.
Ji Soo.
Ji Soo's device.
Didn't you say a large company...
was collecting voices before?
That's what you told me when I said I was hearing voices.
You said a large company hired the studio...
Which company? Why?
This is important.
- This... - It is not important.
I thought you were going to apologize,
say you weren't thinking straight, and show repentance.
It was that day when I said I thought I had gone crazy.
- That day. I heard... - You really are crazy.
Soon Ho.
Just tell me which company.
Thank you.
The manager is super aloof.
Was the manager here?
That's how I got in because I came early.
Thank you.
(Ms. Moon)
(Seo Woo)
I wish someone would water me...
and give me sunlight.
When did you get a caretaker's license?
I was always preparing for the future.
I should've...
stayed by my daughter's side more instead.
What do you mean?
She loved how hard you worked.
She said so in her comments.
She loved how busy your life was.
She was so proud of you for being efficient...
and working hard.
She said every second of the day was precious to her,
and that it was how her mom lived too.
Your daughter has an awesome name.
I fought so much with my in-laws because of that.
- What? - They said no.
They said any name but that.
They hated the name.
What's wrong with Eun Joo?
Most of the Eun Joos out there...
are successful and happy.
- You gave her a great name. - Don't say her name.
You came to Eun Joo's house.
So you have to be happy.
Doubly happy for my daughter's sake.
Don't worry. I'll be four times as happy.
You'd better.
For the next week,
I'm going to be super nice.
I'll make sure you can never ever forget Eunjoo Homestay.
People forget so easily, don't they?
They act like this is the best place when they're here, but...
That won't be you though.
Don't try so hard. Once I leave, it'll be goodbye forever.
That's how I survive.
I'll make sure you can't forget.
Why are you telling me things you want to say to Chang Sup?
Wait and see. You will...
never be able to forget me.
Where?
Let's see.
Here?
There. Found it.
What is that?
We have stuff like that?
See? You do have stuff like this.
Do you want to exercise?
Here. Gosh.
Why couldn't you get that? Gosh.
- There. - Gosh.
There.
You need to move.
Gosh.
Get ready. Here it comes.
- This is boring. - It is?
Do you want to have fun? Was that it?
I'll give you fun. Goodness. I'll give you fun.
Here it comes.
Okay.
- What are you doing? - Watch carefully...
Jin Soo. Do you know how to play badminton?
Of course. I'm really good.
Don't be good. Be fun.
I don't know about fun, but I am really good.
- Try it. - Come at me.
Is this funny?
Hold on.
This is funny?
One more try.
Hold on.
How did it go backwards?
Uncle. Koreans get energy from rice.
(From Kim Ji Soo, To Moon Jung Sook)
I recently realized that you have two addresses.
I guess I was relieved but disappointed...
that you weren't reading my letters.
I'm sending one final letter.
This is the decision that I made...
after struggling with it for a very long time.
I'm in pain because of his regret.
His tears hurt me.
I want to tell him,
"It's okay. You can stop struggling."
I want to be a strength to In Wook.
Now that I've made this decision, I feel at peace.
Once enough time passes,
I'll be able to talk about this with a smile.
I'll contact you again when that time comes.
Take care of yourself, Ms. Moon.
Yours, Kim Ji Soo.
You need to connect with the device for the personality to surface.
You need to bring about a situation to share with the device.
The personality reacts according to the situation,
in which we can find the feelings.
Shouldn't we lead it systematically?
No.
You have to make it believe it has feelings.
We stimulate it...
to touch upon a nerve,
so feelings exist.
You seem tired, so one more.
The situation is brought upon by the device itself as well.
Each person has an earnest memory about feelings,
- so it must be random. - Jin Hwan.
Let's stop.
I'll let you rest.
Two pairs of boots.
For Won and me.
Mom.
(Han Seo Woo)
(Incorrect password)
I wanted to play the music, but it was locked.
I can do it alone if you're uncomfortable.
It's my job.
I should do it regardless.
Ji Soo...
When I found out that Ji Soo knew you,
I was nervous that you may know something about me.
I was nervous and miserable...
about little things and made Ji Soo suffer.
I feel like that was enough.
I'll work alone today.
I think that would be best.
Did...
Ji Soo come to the studio?
She did.
Why?
To see me.
Did she come just once?
Then did she...
I don't want to talk to you about Ji Soo.
It hurts too much.
Where is it?
Until Baekdu Mountain dries up and wears down.
The national anthem? Okay.
I think it is a ballad. It is,
but I don't think it's Kim Kwang Seok, right?
You say everything is Kim Kwang Seok.
Why must we find that song?
Won has been wondering about it all day long.
I keep hearing it too. It's driving me crazy.
You smiled.
And said to me.
Even the smallest things.
Make me cry.
- That's right. - Yes.
This is it.
Nice.
My patient loved this song.
Why does a doctor sing so well?
I want to go singing now.
Let's not go where we went last time.
Just sing instead.
No, no. I'm worse at singing.
My gosh.
I wondered who it was.
Let's go.
Seo Woo asked me to bring you.
You smiled.
And said to me.
I want to fly away.
Like a bird.
Bravo.
What about the second verse?
I want to hear it.
I wanted to do well.
I should've recorded it properly.
It was a very precious performance.
This?
Well,
you're worse than I am, but...
I think I'm better when you consider how much time I had to practice.
I can't agree with that.
I'll practice more and record it for you.
Take it to Oslo.
You should go with me.
I want to go...
somewhere neither of us has been before.
Seo Woo.
I love you.
Does that make you sad?
No.
I was fully charged instantly.
Let's go together.
Let's go to Oslo,
my hometown, everywhere.
Let's go together.
How nice.
I get sunlight and I watered myself.
No one else will do it for me. I'll do it myself.
(Soon Ho)
(3 missed calls)
Hey.
Grandma called, right?
I told her to.
It's not like I didn't worry about you at all.
You startled me.
I didn't think you'd pick up.
- Should I not? - That's not...
- Soon Ho. - Are you okay?
How could I be okay?
Sorry.
Tell me exactly what you're sorry for.
What's this? Are you playing hard to get?
You should repent properly.
"I'm sorry for this-and-this a reason."
I'm sorry for everything.
I must have been insane.
Are you sane again?
You know I can't think straight when I like someone.
You really are repenting, right?
That's right.
I'm the problem.
How could I do that to you?
Still,
I'm really glad I have you.
How could I have an uncle like you?
You're a bit excessive.
- Don't die before me. - Enough.
Whenever...
Grandma told me to meet people...
she wanted to sponsor,
I refused and didn't go.
They had the worst circumstances,
but they were all better than me, so I'd compare myself to them.
But for some reason, I went to see you.
Thinking back,
that was the best thing I've ever done.
- Uncle? - Soon Ho.
I mean...
You got dumped as soon as you came?
You hadn't seen her in years, so you came,
and she dumped you?
I'm tearing up.
What if I hadn't bought you gimbap that day?
You wouldn't be who you are today.
Not a chance.
Then...
I did one thing that was valuable, right?
Soon Ho.
You are...
my one and only precious family to me.
abundantly valuable.
Ji Soo.
Were you here all night?
Ji Soo's device.
Do you have it?
She brought the plant to the studio.
You recorded Ji Soo's voice.
Gave it to the company...
that made a device with her personality and emotions.
You tested it, which was why...
she knew Ha Won's house had good acoustics...
although she never went herself.
Whereas Ji Soo never went,
you heard Ji Soo's opinion.
Because you can talk to her.
Is that it?
If that is... If you have Ji Soo's device...
I don't.
Who said...
- you could take her voice... - Mr. Kang.
Let me talk to her.
Someone trying to forget her doesn't need it.
I don't have it.
Seo Woo!
Just give it to me.
I'm the only person qualified to have her device.
- I don't have it. - Yes, you do. Give it to me.
I don't. And get out.
You must understand how I feel.
You must know since you're caught between Ha Won and Ji Soo.
I do not.
Just once.
I want to listen to what she has to say just once.
What she really...
What she really thinks and feels.
I just want to listen.
She told you a million times that she was hurting,
but you ignored her.
What will you listen to now?
You have no right.
Let me give you a piece of advice.
No one can get between Moon Ha Won...
and Kim Ji Soo. Don't be mistaken.
I'm not mistaken.
I've seen, heard, and believed in so much.
I feel exactly, precisely what it is.
I don't distort it as I please like you.
I'm not like you.
(Soon Ho)
Where are you?
The recital ended long ago.
Why are you letting Kang In Wook be?
I said to do as you please once the recital was over.
Why? What's wrong?
He said no one can ever get between you and Ji Soo.
To Seo Woo.
Where is he?
(A Piece of Your Mind)
Have you any idea what you did?
We can't let her drink.
Give me some strength.
I love you a lot, and I cherish you a lot.
Will you please get rid of me?
See me off lightheartedly.
Like it's no big deal.
Don't you worry at all!
Be strong!
Let's take a very short break.
I'm back.