It isn't the location,
and it isn't fatigue.
I think I fell asleep...
because someone stayed with me.
I want to see you.
No one will use that blanket,
so come whenever you want to sleep well.
Since I can't go to the semi-basement.
I can hear the thoughts in your head.
It is what you're thinking.
You're right.
(A Piece of Your Mind)
(Episode 9)
You haven't given up, have you?
Are you going to say silly things again?
Don't. I'm totally at peace right now.
Good, and you know why.
It's all because of these guys.
There's definitely a reason.
One day, out of the blue, you wake up...
and there are 100 reasons why you shouldn't like him.
- How did you... - Keep listening.
Kang In Wook and Han Seo Woo focus only on work...
even if they're alone in a dark place.
It's incomprehensible to others.
Whether nothing happens or something does happen,
there's definitely a reason.
Think about it.
You'll have one silly, simple,
and useless reason come to mind.
You'll be here, right?
Mr. Kang doesn't need me for his rehearsal.
Please stay with him.
There has to be a reason.
I must put Ji Soo back in her place.
Mr. Kang.
I like your piece.
It's so good, that I hear it in my head before I fall asleep.
How did you write a piece like that?
If even someone like me likes it,
it means it's really good. Right?
Did you listen to it enough to have it stuck in your head?
It got stuck right away.
Do you mind if I listen here?
Suit yourself.
- Will you step aside a bit? - Pardon?
Okay.
You don't have to go that far.
Oh my gosh.
I'm here because Soon Ho asked me to fix the blinds.
Did she send you too?
No, that's...
You could just say yes.
Tell me.
You don't have time to see me,
so why do you come to see my apartment?
What's the difference between seeing me and seeing my place?
Did you do it on purpose?
Stop and turn back, and look only briefly.
Yes.
You can't lie.
- That's... - We miss each other.
We want to be with each other.
We want to hold hands.
It's my first time having it be mutual.
That's just my case.
Are you going to stay? I'll leave.
No.
Soon Ho, are you still there?
How are the plants you took from my place?
They're well. You know me.
I thought they were the only things my wife left behind.
She left an unexpected way out...
for me to escape.
Playing this song,
I feel like I can breathe.
My wife...
is gone from this world.
I got the results from my physical.
What does it say? Nothing's wrong, right?
The doctor said...
he had never seen such a clean and transparent colon before.
When I heard that,
I wondered why I was so stressed.
I felt all my stresses melt away.
It really bugged me to see him...
every morning and evening after breaking up.
Most people don't see each other after breaking up,
but we do.
It has its perks.
People usually break up not to see each other.
Office romances. They keep seeing each other after breaking up too.
They don't cook breakfast for the other.
- Should I kick him out? - Yes.
Aren't you his friend?
It's hard on you.
Breakups are hard for everyone.
- Not Chang Sup. - Darn you.
Anyway, I'm good for now.
What about you?
Tell me 1 more among the 100 reasons.
Why all of a sudden?
You'd better have 100.
I'm going to hear all 100.
Well, he...
What was that?
Tell me the 100 reasons. Tell me.
You don't have 100, do you? Why are you lying, you brat?
Tell me the 100 reasons.
The 100 reasons.
He kept telling me.
I need you, Seo Woo.
Stay with me.
To come. To stay with him.
- We miss each other. - That he misses me.
We want to be with each other. We want to hold hands.
It's my first time having it be mutual.
There's no reason why I shouldn't go.
This is clearly mutual.
- It's that thing. - That thing.
Take it.
It suddenly got cold.
That must be uncomfortable.
You'll strain your back and shoulders.
There's a way.
Doing this improves circulation in my legs and helps me fall asleep.
How did you know?
I could feel you staring at me.
Did it snow?
It's spring snow.
Everything sounds pretty with the word "spring" in it.
Spring snow, spring night, spring ache.
Spring ache?
Yes.
When you get so lonely in the spring that your body aches.
It's not exactly a word, but Eun Joo and I made it up.
I woke up at the sound of snow.
You heard the snow fall?
You can't hear it in Seoul.
You barely hear it in the dead quiet countryside...
when snow piles up on crocks outside.
I hear it from time to time ever since I was 18.
That's fascinating.
It's my first recording today.
I'm doing the official recording.
It snowed in secret. It's a good sigh.
Keep sweeping.
Now.
That side too.
Oh, gosh.
Are you okay?
It's nothing.
I'm afraid I'm making you even more nervous.
Didn't you hurt your hand?
I rarely get hurt.
You're the one I'm worried about.
Do you think I can do a good job?
Of course.
How's the pianist's condition?
I tried my best to maximize it,
but he chose the piece yesterday.
It'll go well.
With Kang In Wook's skills, it'll be a piece of cake.
Give me some of your Midas touch.
Shall we begin?
Okay.
That one sounded good.
Let's go with that.
Okay.
You were great.
You too.
Thank you for making sure this song doesn't disappear.
I'll send you the file and discuss with you before I upload it.
If you want to play it for someone, do it beforehand.
There's no such person.
I'm really tired right now.
Oh, okay.
Well...
It's a happy day. What's with the long faces?
- Good work. - Good job.
- All right. - Here.
Thank you.
- Gosh. - It's delicious.
You're right.
- Is it good? - Yes.
He's good at making other delivery food,
but not fried chicken.
I'm always so sad at nights when I crave chicken and beer.
Our chef isn't that good...
at making fried chicken and Pyongyang cold noodles.
Our lab will be perfect if those two issues are resolved.
Didn't he say he could make cold noodles?
He just wings it.
The noodles become stiff if you use too much pressure.
But if you use too little, they get brittle.
The pressure has to be perfect to get the right chewiness.
But it's so difficult.
I should donate a noodle-making machine or something.
- I'm against it. - Thanks.
I've even thought of where to place it. Hey, wipe your mouth.
But it takes up too much space.
The pressure should be pumped... Hey.
There's a design in your shed.
It's still there.
You haven't gotten rid of it?
Hold up, hold up.
Okay, that's good.
Hey. I'm off starting today.
Cheers.
- Sure. - Cheers.
- Take some time to relax. - I will.
The plant you wanted...
is Seo Woo's, so I can't give you that one.
But here.
What is this?
I bought it a few days ago.
I wanted to use it today, but I don't think I should.
A few days ago...
Before you told me about your wife.
Today is a happy day.
You're allowed to use them today.
But that's just my opinion. It's up to you.
Jin Soo, breakfast!
Why is a chair missing?
Ms. Kim took it.
I see.
No.
What's with him?
This is the emergency key when I was in that room.
Why?
Well... You know. A rope from the ceiling.
It's a common method.
Like in crime dramas. An inn, ceiling, chair...
- Shouldn't you open the door? - What are you talking about?
This isn't an inn. Don't be ridiculous.
- Oh, no. What do I do? - I'll open it.
- The key. Hurry. - Oh, no.
Oh, no.
No!
Oh my gosh.
What did you write there?
How could I remember? It was so many years ago.
You're the girl who used to live in this room?
The college kid Min Jung?
Who are you calling a kid?
You were just in middle school. You rude punk.
You aged so much. You look completely different.
I thought you were older than I was when I first saw you.
She said I was a rich girl because I was inheriting this homestay.
You have no idea how frustrated I was.
- I was right. - How so?
You won't do anything rash, right?
- Why would I? - What is this?
You wrote a boy's name and erased it.
Seo Joon Hee?
Yes, I remember. I was so silly back then.
There's another one. Cha... Cha Hyun Woo?
It was scratched out.
I should erase it if we broke up.
How many is that?
You should've erased it properly. This wasn't your ceiling.
I was popular.
"I'm so happy. It's exciting."
"Let's not forget today."
"May 2002."
- What day was that? - I don't know. I don't remember.
You said not to forget.
Whatever it was, it must have been exciting.
So that's where she was. The cheerful Min Jung.
Are you good?
If you add one more name there, it'll be the Big Dipper.
Welcome, college kid Min Jung,
- Why did you gain so much weight? - What's your problem?
That perm was so not like you. This is more like you.
- Should I write "Chang Sup" there? - Seriously...
Hold on.
Once you hit this, the piece will be uploaded, right?
- Hold on. - Done.
(Kang In Wook's "No. 1" has been registered)
(Han Seo Woo)
Mom, Dad.
I recorded this. It has been released too.
Isn't that so cool?
(I'm so happy. It's exciting.)
(Let's not forget today. May 2002)
What did you think of the piece?
It was nice. You recorded it after all.
How should I congratulate you?
What will you do?
I've never thought about something like this before.
Seo Woo.
- You two... - So...
He records in the middle of the night. He's Before Dawn.
Before Dawn.
Yes, hello.
I've heard a lot about you.
Do you know each other through work?
Well... I think there was confusion regarding when he had the studio.
Why don't you leave if you're done?
- Have a nice day. - You too.
But...
Be right back.
Why didn't you tell me you were close?
We're close.
Uncle.
Seo Woo.
I wanted to congratulate you on your first recording,
so I did in a tangible way instead of just empty words.
Check your bank account.
(You have received a payment from Moon Soon Ho.)
(Confirm)
(Transaction Details)
(Accept Payment)
130 percent increase.
Gosh. You scared me.
Congratulations.
You're our main sound engineer. I leveled you up.
Thank you.
How did you make this?
The frying pan made it.
Congratulations.
It has been an amazing day.
I was congratulated enough for a lifetime.
Can I really have everything?
Go on and eat.
It's delicious.
You said...
you could hear the snow now and then.
Since you were 18, was it?
Did something...
happen?
My mom...
I never talked about my mom,
so it's kind of hard.
It was a similar reason...
as your parents.
It was a blizzard.
That was all.
But I couldn't...
accept that explanation...
no matter how much I thought about it.
I kept waiting for it to snow.
To find...
a convincing explanation.
You said nature makes mistakes too, right? I had no idea.
Nature doesn't make mistakes.
That's just what I wanted to believe.
So that's why...
you heard the snow ever since you were 18.
I feel bad. I ruined the mood on your special day.
When I woke up in the morning
And looked at the neatly made bed
I used to get this thought
What if I disappeared
If I were to disappear
As if I had never been here
To begin with
If I keep living like this
There will be a reason why
I can't disappear
If I keep living like this
A reason why
I can never disappear
(I got a raise)
I got a raise.
I got you a red cardigan instead of red longjohns.
I'll pay 70 percent of rent now.
Make yourself pretty.
You'll realize what you want for yourself.
Do that for yourself, okay?
What do I want for myself?
Only I know?
Only I know.
Hey. My project was selected.
You know I've been working hard with ASMR.
Mine will be launched exclusively in an app.
He used to love eggs.
I'm reminded of Cha Hyun Woo.
What about Seo Joon Hee?
He was younger than me.
Do you need to go to the farm?
No, I don't.
That's where Hoon is. To clear his head for a couple of days.
Doesn't he know I'm in Seoul?
Why is he telling me to...
Hey. Tell him to clean the place while he's there.
Tell him to take his things in the shed.
He says he can't open the shed.
You go.
Okay.
Do you need anything at the house?
Cash. That house needs cash.
Hi.
Ma'am.
Did you hurt your arm?
Yes, up to my elbow.
I'm a bit flaky.
I won't be able to work for a short while.
But my last job was your debut.
So I'm very happy.
You should continue once it heals.
You and I are a team.
I did great, didn't I?
Of course. Your tuning is a work of art.
You said you decided to work here...
so that you could cry in the studio.
It's the perfect place to cry.
Is this your first time here?
My friend asked me to meet here.
I'll wait outside.
How old are you?
I'm a senior.
That's a tough age.
But it's still the best, isn't it?
You lived with your parents.
When you woke up, your mom was in the kitchen.
At night, your dad came home from work.
Your siblings lived all together.
It seems like a dream. I don't know how we all lived together.
My parents... There was a fire...
I'm okay most of the time, but now and then...
Excuse me.
Come inside.
Don't hold it in. You can cry in here.
It's such a good thing you went into this field.
You are really good.
Did you come all the way here to tell me that?
Naturally.
I wanted to compliment you.
Ji Soo, I wanted to say hi to you...
in the place that you like...
with the ambience that you like.
Ji Soo.
Ji Soo?
Did it break?
What broke?
What is it? What broke?
Are you alone?
Yes.
What is that?
Nothing.
I didn't know you were coming.
- I'll go. - Were you...
really alone?
There's no one here.
Someone was here.
Cash is the best.
Retail therapy is the best therapy.
Hi, babies.
Thanks, Uncle.
Oh, my. Mr. Kang.
I didn't know you came.
What's wrong?
I must have lost my mind.
I'm hearing things.
A large company uses our studio too.
They're collecting voices or something.
Anyway, that's what you heard.
What company does that?
It's confidential.
Anyway, it's nothing weird.
You're not crazy, okay?
To be honest, I hate listening to people's problems.
It's depressing.
But I'll make an exception just for you,
so vent all you want.
Kim Ji Soo.
(From Kim Ji Soo To Moon Jung Sook)
Here.
Since you like it right before the sun sets.
We're right on time.
Hoon.
Why aren't you answering me? I brought food.
Hey.
I'm doing well.
My husband and I weren't accustomed to life in Seoul,
but it's comforting knowing you're somewhere near.
I don't know anyone here.
Come to think of it,
I always live somewhere where I don't know anyone.
When I was in Oslo, I longed to be in Seoul,
but in Seoul, I miss Oslo.
Especially at this time of year.
The entire town was like a big Christmas tree.
Merry Christmas.
December 24, 2019.
PS.
Please forget what I said...
in my previous letter.
- Hey. - Is this the previous letter?
Yes. Well, that's not it.
I'd like to see you.
Here is my number. Please call me.
I feel like it'll all be okay if Won says it's okay.
Everything. All of it.
(I found out why Won's mom died. I'm tormented.)
I found out why Won's mom died.
I'd like to see you.
Here is my number. Please call me.
I feel like it'll all be okay if Won says it's okay.
Everything. All of it.
(I found out why Won's mom died. I'm tormented.)
I found out why Won's mom died.
Hey.
I looked through all of them.
Like I said, I'm sure I was mistaken...
(From Kim Ji Soo)
Ji Soo.
Guess where we are.
I get the feeling it's the shipping address.
Correct.
I found out why Won's mom died.
I'm tormented.
Please call me, Ms. Moon. I'd like to see you.
(Sincerely, Kim Ji Soo)
I feel relieved...
since you'll never read these.
I wanted to scream out loud somewhere.
I miss...
Won.
I feel like it'll all be okay if Won says it's okay.
(I feel like it'll all be okay if Won says it's okay)
Everything.
All of it.
What I regret most...
is telling her.
I collected videos of you from the past.
Videos?
Some are from your early 20s.
I'm going to make a personal homepage for you later.
- Are you that happy? - Yes.
It's super hard to get selected for "Piano in April".
It's your first time.
I'm so happy.
This is nice.
You've worked hard.
You had no connections.
You worked hard and made it on your own.
The world is acknowledging you.
Stop suffering inside now.
Suffering?
This is nothing.
This, which is lodged deep inside, is the problem.
What's that?
If I tell you,
will you be understanding?
Depends.
I don't want to say.
Tell me. I'm in a really good mood right now.
It's something that happened when I was young.
How young?
When I lived in Norway.
How bad could it be?
As long as no one died.
What if someone did die?
Look how shocked you are.
I wasn't shocked.
When we moved around in Europe,
I avoided Koreans so that I could adapt.
I was young and just didn't like it.
I never spoke Korean.
There was a Korean boy that I hated.
Why did you hate him?
No.
That doesn't matter. Sure, you could hate him.
So?
Sure, I could hate him.
That doesn't matter.
Correct.
It was snowing.
Hard.
- Gosh, I'm sorry. - It's okay.
Are you Korean?
You've been walking past here since two months ago, right?
You didn't answer, so I didn't think you were Korean.
Do you go to Eva Lawson High School?
Everyone was taking shelter in the school,
but before I knew it, I said...
Ha Won is coming this way right now.
So,
are you saying someone was in an accident because of a lie...
you told when you were a kid?
Why is that...
You shouldn't have told me.
This is nothing if you say it's nothing.
It was just an accident.
Why can't you...
If you'd just say it's okay...
How is that okay?
Ji Soo.
You can't do this. Back then, I...
Won...
How could you do that to Won?
Ji Soo. Why can't you take my side?
Why?
If you say it's okay,
I'll be able to breathe.
Why couldn't she take my side?
If only she had taken my side.
It's no big deal.
It's okay.
Play what you recorded with the piano tuner.
I'll know when I hear it.
There's a feeling of finality in a final piece. I'll find it.
Are you ready?
I can't wait.
The pianist is Kang In Wook.
I'm scared,
but it's beautiful.
You shouldn't have told me.
I found out why Won's mom died.
It wasn't the blizzard.
Why can't you take my side? Why? Why?
My husband was involved.
It's too much to bear on my own.
I want to tell the world,
but I can't.
That's why I'm writing you like this.
With the assurance that it will never be read.
Go with Ms. Moon.
She's more reliable than my mom.
I'll be relieved then.
It won't snow.
I can't leave.
Leave.
I'll stay behind and find out the reason.
Look at the ceiling.
It's soothing.
Got it.
I found out why I sold...
my dishes.
I found out the reason.
I found out...
the reason.
Not the blizzard. Maybe someone was involved.
An external factor.
She wasn't even in a shelter and died in a random place.
We questioned and argued it more than 1,000 times.
It looked like she went to pick you up...
That's what I couldn't understand.
She knew the rules for evacuation better than anyone.
Either the midway shelter or at the school.
She knew that better than anyone. Why would she go there?
Won.
I think Ji Soo found out something recently.
Ji Soo? If it were something you had to know,
wouldn't she have told you?
I'm sure she didn't because it wasn't worth telling you.
She wanted to see you.
She wrote you countless letters.
If she tried to tell me and not you, that means you didn't need to know.
I'm positive there was another reason.
I'll sound like an old fogy, but I'll say it anyway.
There are many things that make you miserable once you find out,
and many things that you're better off not knowing.
I'm not scared at all...
about what will happen afterward, or what will get better.
What I fear most is...
living without knowing something that I should know.
It's so cold.
It's nippy at night.
Won.
When I first met you...
in Boston...
Remember how it would snow up to our knees?
Right? But someone was standing in the middle of the street,
looking up at the sky like this.
With his neck bent all the way like it was about to snap.
But I looked closer,
and he was glaring at the sky.
Talk about intense.
Won.
Kim Ji Soo...
probably thought about it whenever it snowed too...
and realized recently...
that what happened to Won's mom wasn't purely because of the snow,
but another reason...
Very peacefully... She must have realized...
something...
I feel like perhaps she wanted to tell you that.
I do have an idea.
What?
The cause of Ji Soo's misery.
You worked so hard for years not to know about her husband.
I never said it was her husband.
Well, isn't that what you mean? You said you wouldn't find out.
Keep it that way.
What's up?
Hey, Soon Ho.
Yes?
Is Kim Ji Soo's husband not Korean?
Why do you care? That's what I want to know.
I thought Ji Soo and Ha Won were the only Koreans in Norway.
That's why they're so tight.
It was just the two of them.
Anyway, don't you dare ask Uncle things like that.
He left his cell phone.
He needs his phone.
- He left it intentionally. - Why?
He's shutting out the world.
Whatever. Let him be.
- Aren't you coming here? - Why would I?
I'm mad busy. Bye.
Why is she getting mad?
Hey, you.
Why are you loitering in front of my house? Move.
Why are you smiling?
I'm here to see Seo Woo.
Oh, 100 reasons...
Hello.
Come in.
She isn't picking up.
Didn't you call first?
I'll go to the studio.
Please tell her to come there.
I forgot my phone.
Have you had breakfast?
It's okay. My stomach isn't well.
No.
If I let you go without giving you at least water,
Seo Woo will have my head.
Come on.
When your stomach is bothering you,
nothing beats scorched rice.
It's nice.
Why did you come without making plans first?
I must have come because I wanted to see her.
You're not here to tell her something bad, are you?
I don't like Seo Woo being sad.
No.
When I see her,
I can stop thinking.
I feel at ease.
Seo Woo has that effect, doesn't she?
When I look at her, I feel encouraged.
I'm like that too.
But...
why does Seo Woo have so many reasons?
She said she liked someone, but 100 reasons stood in her way.
I asked her to tell me each one,
and they were all stupid.
Tell me just one.
She felt like someone else's misery was her happiness.
How stupid.
Right?
She's a tough cookie,
but she gets depressed when it counts.
You know how she's splat on her face at times.
She's all dejected.
"I don't know. I won't do it."
"Leave me alone."
Imagining 100 reasons...
and she withdraws herself.
Does it taste bad?
Why aren't you eating? You're hurting my feelings.
It's good.
Oh my gosh.
Something's up, isn't it?
What is it this time?
Tell me.
You're acting strange.
What...
Go home. Don't wander around.
You're going home, right?
- I came to see Seo Woo. - Seo Woo?
She's out recording Mr. Kang.
We're filming a music video. Cool, right?
We want to do as much PR as we can.
- Did you make an appointment? - No.
I just missed her.
Oh my gosh. Hey.
- Is that... Is that... - That's right.
I can't do this here.
It echoes too much.
Just... Just pretend to play.
We're doing this live because you insisted.
We'll edit the video to the music anyway,
so let's just do it.
It's not like it's classical music.
Ms. Moon considered the poster for the recital...
and wanted a location that would look nice.
That's why she chose this place.
So you haven't been here.
Even if that's why Soon Ho chose it, you should've checked it out.
Narrowing it down to locations we can use right away,
first is our studio,
second is Mr. Choi's studio.
We can check his schedule.
Or maybe somewhere you used to live?
Someone you're familiar with may be good too.
Home would be nice.
The apartment where I lived when I was four.
My aunt's house is in Oslo.
Does that work?
How will we find a house with good acoustics in time?
I do know of one.
My friend said it has good acoustics.
Never mind.
Second. Mr. Choi's studio.
Okay.
- You startled me. - Were you startled?
By this?
I was so startled earlier that I almost fainted.
- Did you hear? - What happened?
As you can see. The acoustics were bad enough,
but the director said, "It isn't classical music."
So we're filming in Mr. Choi's studio.
- I already arranged it. - No. It's not pretty there.
It's pretty here, but the acoustics are horrible.
You punk.
That's right.
That's why you were so arrogant toward me.
Seo Woo, you little...
(Hoon)
I said I won't come.
(Eun Joo)
Did you see the guy who wanted to see you?
(Phone)
(Before Dawn)
The phone is turned off.
This is a big mess.
All the plants at the entrance are dead.
There's no way.
- Send me a picture. - Come right away.
Look for yourself.
What... This punk. What's his problem?
I'm going now.
Let's go.
They're fine.
He lied to me.
Where is he?
How pretty.
Hoon, where are you?
- They're totally fine. - Hold up.
Soon Ho. Hold up.
You need to save me.
(My husband was involved)
What's this?
Ji Soo's husband killed Won's mom?
Oh my gosh. That psycho.
How could this be?
Where can I find this jerk?
I need to question him.
I'm against it.
Are you kidding me?
You can't do anything with this. It'll only torment Won.
Hoon. Let's say for argument's sake that Won catches that jerk.
Once he finds out what happened, he'll end it right there.
He's still Ji Soo's husband. He wouldn't do anything harsh.
He won't do anything harsh? He should.
Regardless, I don't care who he is. We have to catch him and finish him.
I'll take care of it.
Okay. Then rip it up. I trust you.
You rip it up.
It's your letter.
Seriously. Ji Soo has such a tough life.
(From Kim Ji Soo, To Moon Jung Sook)
I found out...
why I sold...
my dishes.
No. Never. She can never find out.
She can't find out what happens to her.
The more we talk, the more she finds out.
And if we're unlucky, she'll find out everything.
In the place that you like...
with the ambience that you like.
Since you like it right before the sun sets.
We're right on time.
The pianist is Kang In Wook.
What touched you, Ji Soo?
Won,
do you want to go to Norway?
You just have to say one thing.
If Won says it's okay.
Ji Soo said her husband made a mistake.
The cause of Ji Soo's misery.
You worked so hard for years not to know about her husband.
I never said it was her husband.
I found out why Won's mom died.
(A Piece of Your Mind)
Do you know about him?
I like him a lot.
Kim Ji Soo. That's my friend's name.
Should I just ruin it?
Don't hold it in. Scream and let it out.
I'll stay with you.
Do you want to live here?
I like this place because there's nothing here.
I guess you can't afford a frying pan.
I can fill it.
Why are things getting so complicated?
He's dying to know.
Ha Won and Kang In Wook can never meet.