(Episode 1)
Is there such a thing as being
fated to meet?
(Book store)
Do you have the book?
Excuse me. May I have the book?
(I Go to See the Body Every Week.)
I guess you are interested
in dead bodies?
It so happens that I'd ordered
this book.
It's a limited edition
with the author's signature.
I'd pre-ordered this book
to pick it up at three.
It's 3:15 p.m.
I really need this book.
Hey, there.
("The eye")
("The eye shall see for the last time.")
Would you like to buy my book?
You just scribbled in it.
I'll charge you for a used book.
A used book?
I'm fine if you don't want it.
By the way, I guess you have
a habit of pressing...
the fountain pen down when you write.
You'll break your pen soon
writing like that.
I guess it's better than spilling
coffee on your book.
I thought you weren't coming.
I'm sorry.
Why would my friend who is moving
away want this particular book?
Why is it that she's flying out just...
tomorrow morning?
It must be her fate to not have
the book.
It's her sad fate that she values
the writer's autograph...
over 100 million won.
- I'm sorry.
- It's okay.
Lovers never break up.
Though you may not know
when or where it will be.
We will meet again.
In the next life...
and the life after that.
(Episode 1, Heathcliff was in love.)
I envy you...
who is hoping for eternal love,
Ms. Jung Ha Eun.
Are you with us now?
We'll play your song request.
"When Love Passes By,"
by Lee Moon Sae.
Miss,
you shouldn't be carrying
that yellow umbrella.
Haven't you heard of a scumbag...
who only kills lasses with a yellow umbrella?
Lasses?
Don't get me wrong. I'm not a spy.
I defected to South Korea.
There are so many jerks who kill
lasses in South Korea.
We should bury those jerks
in the coal mine.
Aren't I right, Miss?
They will all be caught.
My boyfriend is a detective.
- What's happened here?
- How can this be?
She must have seen an evil being
with her own eyes.
Who could've stabbed someone
so recklessly?
Take a look, Detective Cha.
The culprit stabbed her
twice from the chest.
Once in the abdomen from this way.
Once from the other side.
And then stabbed like crazy here.
- Like...
- Will you please move over?
The body has been damaged.
But her face is untouched.
What does this mean, Detective Cha?
There are two guys.
One killed her.
The other one held
a funeral for her.
We have a clue.
The culprit has long hair.
Only a few men have long hair in Korea.
- Nine.
- Nine?
He waited 2 years
after killing 9 people.
Why did he start murdering again?
In Do,
can there be such a thing as
murder without a motive?
How can a man kill someone
for no reason?
(No Trespassing.
Under investigation.)
Get out!
Hey, you!
Don't take that!
Come here!
You there!
I said come!
Are you okay?
It's your girlfriend who has
a weak heart.
How come you're acting like this
every time?
Your heart is like a hard rock.
Let it go. Now!
Give me this!
Are the hearts of lovers connected?
At the same moment
that I feel pain in my heart,
his heart hurts as well.
It's not a heartache...
but as though...
his heart was stabbed with a knife.
He said it's here.
Right here.
(Old Future)
Geez, you startled me.
- My heart almost dropped.
- I'm sorry. Are you all right?
Try breathing. Can you breathe?
Breathe in, quickly.
Look at me.
Breathe out again now.
We've got to go to the hospital.
Your face turned blue.
I'm not a Smurf. Look who's talking.
Do you have to say
that your heart dropped?
Why can't I say it?
I do have heart disease.
It's genuine.
You can't use this.
Throw it away, right now.
Let's go.
It's not just a yellow umbrella.
- Didn't you see Dooly on it?
- Get in.
("Wuthering Heights"
by Emily Brontë)
"If all else perished, and he remained,"
"I should still continue to be."
"Whatever our souls are made of..."
"His and mine are the same."
Written by Emily Brontë.
"Wuthering Heights," page 123.
Come on.
Should I throw out the ladder too?
Hey.
It's on page 73. I've read it
countless times for you.
Is it?
Open it anyway, to page 123.
Why page 123?
You already marked page 73 so well.
(Become my bride, Ha Eun.)
I told you no one will buy the books
if you write on them.
I don't think the owner of
a used book store should say that.
I thought the scribblings were a part
of the book's history.
Also, that's not just a scribbling.
It's a proposal.
I waited a month for your answer.
Okay. Then...
I should scribble my answer too.
Look for it when I'm not around.
You'll have to scribble a lot.
I've written it everywhere.
They're in all the books in your store.
What?
Then, let me answer you now.
I'm not marrying you.
Sorry?
I don't believe in love.
"Love story" just released
its sequel.
And the main character loves
a different girl in the sequel.
Well...
If my heart beats...
for another year,
we could maybe get married.
You've been turning me down for
four years for that reason.
It's not going to work this time.
- Hey, Hyung Bin.
- Stop talking.
I already know what you're
going to say.
We're not meant to be married.
Then what are we?
Lovers.
Lovers who miss each other
even as they look at each other.
Lovers who can feel each other
no matter where they are.
A lover who will stay together
even after death.
That's what we are.
Then I don't want to be your lover.
I will be your lover forever.
You can get married to someone else.
I don't want you to embrace
this body.
I want to be embraced by your soul.
I don't.
I've never looked at any other woman
with these eyes.
I want to touch your face...
and go to sleep with you in my arms.
I want to see you go to sleep,
wake up, in pain,
and cry.
I want to see all of that
in my arms.
What if I die within your arms?
Would you be okay with that?
I'm happy,
just looking at you like this.
I'll be happy...
to be your husband when you die,
and when you die...
I'll keep on living, missing
this very moment.
Please stop.
I hate tragedies like this.
I hate how stuffy these are.
I can open a store with
all the gloves you bought me.
It's because I can't walk you home.
I've been called for an emergency.
Why? Is it the yellow umbrella?
He's so good at running
from officer Cha Hyung Bin.
I'll kill him if I catch him.
You know you should
never run, right?
Take the big roads,
the ones with street lights.
I know all about your shortcuts.
Don't take them.
- When you get home, lock...
- My gosh, your nagging never stops.
I'll have to run away.
That scream...
It was a woman, right?
You heard the dead woman's scream,
didn't you?
Did you see the face of the man
who returned the yellow umbrella?
Geez.
My aunt has an IQ
of a seven-year-old.
Little one, come here.
Do you want to play
a game with this man?
Do you see that sharp-looking man
like a razor blade?
He's not that much of a bad guy.
- It's fine.
- You aged on your own, haven't you?
Hey, who'll see you
as a 23-year-old?
I told you looking old is
my family's hereditary gene.
I will look just the same
when I'm old.
Watch me in 30 years, I'll still
have this exact face.
It's okay, come here.
Come here, sit.
Can you draw what you saw
in the mountains last night?
Let's just go eat.
Let's go.
Forget it.
Have some food before you leave.
Order fried rice for her,
I'll have a jjamppong.
I said forget about it.
(Yellow Umbrella Serial Murder Case)
(Criminal Affairs Division)
What is that man doing over there?
(Faithfulness,
sincerity, and service)
First of all,
why do you keep hanging
them in my house?
I'm hurt.
I can't paint as I did before.
That was it?
Is that why you started?
Because you couldn't paint anymore?
You must be going through a lot
because of me.
But don't worry.
I'm going to take a long break
this time.
It's all thanks to you.
Thanks to me?
When you put on socks...
on those pale white feet,
it seemed as if...
the dying Maria,
that dirty wench,
was like the Virgin Mary.
- What did you say?
- This girl looked...
like your mother who left you.
The previous girl looked...
like your stepmother
who did that to your eye.
Why are you dragging me into this?
You killed them
because you wanted to.
Shall I have a meal with my son?
(Suspect wanted)
You'll surely end up
committing murder.
You won't be able to stop
once you start it.
How could you...
do this to me?
Don't fight it. Accept it.
Make the evil on your side.
Receive inspiration
from the evil and paint like me.
You only inherited my blood
but not the talent.
You need to kill to become free.
That was the case for me.
Do I look like I enjoy killing?
I'm doing it
because I can't help it.
But once you start it,
you'll never be able to stop it.
The witch I killed this time had...
locked her father up
and starved him.
If she lived,
her father would've died.
Didn't I save an innocent man
by killing that witch?
I'm different from you.
You've never loved a woman.
Love? Are you...
in love with a woman?
While other kids used this
to cut colored papers,
your eyes were poked with this
by a woman.
And you're telling me...
that you love a woman?
Even if you don't kill her,
she's going to die anyway.
I can do it for you if you want.
Love?
Love...
(Episode 2)
Heathcliff was...
in love.
(Four years ago)
Move on.
(Rise, ten million workers! Rage!)
"The boy was called Heathcliff."
"Heathcliff seemed a sullen,
patient child."
"Hardened, perhaps,
to ill-treatment."
"Although his face is as dark as if
he's got it from an evil being."
"A ragged, black-haired child."
"Heathcliff was not haughty
to his savior."
"He just did not feel that he was
cared for..."
"even when he was."
You, in the end. It'll be hard
to hear from there.
Can you come to the front?
Is Heathcliff an evil being?
No, he isn't.
Heathcliff was in love.
"This endurance made..."
"old Earnshaw to always call him..."
"the poor fatherless child."
"He became furious
when he discovered his son..."
"persecuting the child."
"He took to Heathcliff strangely,"
"believing all he said."
"He liked him far above Cathy,"
"who was too mischievous..."
"and wayward for a favorite."
(Be my wife, Jung Ha Eun.)
This book was written by Tolstoy
when he was 70.
He writes that there's a deity
in every human soul...
so anyone can be resurrected
as someone new.
(Resurrection)
Can you picture Katyusha
and Nekhlyudov...
walking in Siberia?
(Katyusha)
Your homework for tomorrow
is to write a book report for this.
Yes, Miss.
(Resurrects eternally anew)
This book.
It's a present for you.
This one?
("Wuthering Heights")
You have a pretty smile.
Why do you hide your pretty eyes?
Don't be like that.
It's okay to show your other eye.
Show me...
your other eye.
It's not bad to be hurt.
The person who hurt you...
is the bad one.
What's your name?
It's Gong Ji Chul.
Gong Ji Chul.
In your next life,
I hope you're born in a place
where no one would hurt you.
Even if you die,
your soul can be reborn.
You can be born again.
I'm sorry, Mom.
Please open the door.
I won't do it again.
I made a mistake.
Open the door, please!
Mom!
I'm sorry, Mom.
I won't ever do it again.
Please open the door.
Mom!
Mom, open up, please.
I won't do it again.
I'm so sorry.
Please open the door.
Mom!
Please open!
I won't do it.
Open the door, please.
Mom!
Please open the door.
Please, Mom.
I'll never do it again. I'm sorry.
Mom!
Ji Chul, did you buy ice cream?
What about shrimp chips?
- Is it tasty?
- Yes.
Ji Chul,
my mom says I'm not her real son.
Not a real son?
Both of my parents are
blood type AB,
but I am blood type O.
They say it can't happen.
I think she's not my real mother.
What do you think, Ji Chul?
Where's my real mother?
You don't need a mother.
You can be born again.
So, you can...
pick your mom...
as someone you'd like.
Like you pick your ice cream.
Ji Chul, I can sing that song
you taught me well.
Do you?
Run and run, my robot
Fly and fly over, Taekwon V
Fists united with justice, Robot Taekwon
You're a brave and fearless friend
Stretch your arms straight
Fly in the sky toward the enemy
The wonderful fabulous
Hurray for Taekwon V
You are the matchless hero, Taekwon V
- What's going on?
- What happened?
My goodness, what is all this?
- What is it?
- What's happening?
Hey!
Here they come!
What is that?
What's wrong? Is he sick?
Sung Ho, it's me!
There was a robbery
and he got killed.
A robbery?
Step aside already.
Oh, dear.
My poor Sung Ho.
Why are you crying again?
I told you not to cry!
Die!
Why do you never listen to me?
I'm not your mother!
Ji Chul, help me.
I'm so scared.
- Ji Chul!
- Sung Ho.
Help me.
Ji Chul!
Kill them.
Kill them, I said.
Kill them all!
It's not bad to be hurt.
The person who hurt you...
is the bad one.
- Let me go!
- Let me get that scumbag!
I've seen you do it!
Next.
Hey.
Lift your head.
Next.
He's a junkie, take him in.
He told me he was a serial killer.
He must've killed them in his head
while he was high.
- Next.
- Go.
What do you know?
You think you know heavy metal?
Up in the sky!
- Up in the sky.
- Take him in! Next!
- Come here.
- Up in the sky!
- Get in there.
- Up in the sky.
- Stop it!
Stop!
Detective Cha! Someone called.
- Ms. Ha Eun is in hospital.
- When?
Detective Cha, do you know
which hospital she's in?
(Emergency room)
She's not in good shape.
She hasn't been taking care of
herself either.
At least...
someone found her and brought her
to the hospital in time.
I think she feels stuffy
with the oxygen mask.
She hates having something
over her body.
That's why she doesn't
even put on gloves.
Ha Eun.
Hang in there.
Why is she acting like this?
She hates the hospital smell. She
says it smells like formaldehyde.
We have a famous cardiologist...
from America visiting us.
Would you like to talk to him?
(Wards, restrooms, waiting room)
She has dilated cardiomyopathy.
It's a disease in her heart muscles.
There are not a lot of patients
who can have the transplant...
but fortunately,
Ms. Jung can live
with a heart transplant.
It will be the first transplant
in Korea,
but there are lots of successful case
studies in America.
I don't care how much
the operation will cost.
There is something more important
than money.
- What is it?
- It's the donor.
We need the donor to be brain  dead,
and their families need to
agree to the transplant as well.
Donor...
We can't guarantee...
when a donor will appear
at our hospital.
We'll wait.
Does she not have a guardian?
I'm her guardian.
She's stronger than most people.
Also,
I'll be by her side
until a donor shows up.
You need to stay by her side...
- every day, 24 hours.
- We're going to get married.
I'll protect her.
I'm going to be
by her side for 24 hours.
(Emergency room)
Ms. Jung is getting worse every time
she visits here.
Anyway, I didn't know hearts could
be transplanted like kidneys.
Isn't it amazing?
Mr. Min Young Ho in ICU is
brain dead.
I wonder if he agreed
to organ donation.
The doctor said the blood types
also have to match.
I heard Ms. Jung's blood type is AB.
And Mr. Min's blood type is O.
They can't have the transplant.
Also, his son...
Both of my parents are
blood type AB,
but I am blood type O.
They say it can't happen.
By the way, I envy Ms. Jung.
I can't believe there's a man
who will marry a dying woman.
Isn't it romantic?
Are you a family
of Mr. Min Young Ho?
Yes.
I heard from the professor.
You're his son, right?
Would you like to have
a cup of tea with me?
(Heart Surgeon, Ranton Smith)
What exactly...
does being brain-dead mean?
- Brain-dead?
- Please explain it to me.
Braindead means
your pupils don't dilate,
spontaneous respiration is
impossible,
and your brain stem reflexes
are missing.
Simply put,
you can't breathe on your own.
Is that so?
Excuse me for a moment.
(Cardiology)
I'm here at St. Peter's hospital.
She's made it through the night.
I'll return as soon as she's stable.
In your next life,
I hope you're born in a place
where no one would hurt you.
Don't die.
I'll get your heart.
I'm sorry.
The culprit has long hair.
Only a few men have long hair in Korea.
Are you awake?
Let's go home, Hyung Bin.
You know how much I hate
the smell of hospitals.
They smell like corpses.
Is it because it reminds you
of your parents?
I feel like throwing up.
Do it then,
let's go to the restroom.
I know already.
I need a heart transplant to live.
It's the same whether
I wait here or at home.
Let's just get out of here.
Hello.
Ha Eun!
You look healthier than I am.
Detective Joo.
Can you take him away?
You said you'd protect the country.
You're protecting me
like you protect the country.
Then why are you here crying
in front of me,
instead of catching bad guys?
That's such a turn-off.
Hey.
When did I cry?
That reminds me.
I'm here because someone reported on
the Yellow Umbrella Killer.
- A report?
- Yes.
Since you said you'd be here
for how long...
I brought the informant here.
I saw him
burning the yellow umbrella.
He had his face covered
with his hair like this.
His face I saw through flame
was somewhat...
haunted or possessed.
Where is the burning site?
I know who he is.
And I know where he lives.
I went for a visit to bring him
to my church.
I think he lives alone.
Lady.
You're in a cult, aren't you?
How could a person be possessed?
Then what am I possessed with?
Let me see.
You're possessed
by an old man's ghost!
- Satan, be gone!
- What the heck?
My name is Joo In Do!
It means I'm a guide!
- Geez.
- Guard this ward...
so Ha Eun doesn't leave the room.
Sure.
- Let's go.
- Okay.
Geez.
Come this way.
It was here.
He was burning yellow umbrellas
in the fire here.
- Where does he live?
- It's nearby.
It's right over there.
Brain death is...
a coma status that is unresponsive
to external stimuli...
with the inability
to breathe spontaneously...
and having two fixed dilated pupils.
Blood circulation may be normal.
Pure spinal reflex can
be maintained.
After six hours of examination...
Brain death is different
from cardiac death.
The brain may be dead
but the heart may still be beating.
Brain death is different
from cardiac death.
The brain may be dead...
but the heart may still beat.
I went to your house.
You were being followed
by an amateur detective.
Did you kill a person?
It must be because of you.
Didn't you think
you would be arrested someday?
I'm boarding on a ship today.
I'm leaving Korea.
This will be the last time
I see you.
That's a relief.
Ji Chul,
don't ever...
blame yourself...
in any situation.
It's not your fault.
That man up there has done
everything wrong.
The man up there?
No.
Everything is because of me.
I'm going to carry all the burden
with me.
I can never live...
proudly committing murder
like you...
while blaming someone else.
Hye Mi.
You take care of that kid
until the end.
The detective knows where he lives.
Find a place for Ji Chul to stay.
Yes, sir.
Gong Ji Chul.
(Gong Ji Chul)
("Old Future")
(Be my wife, Jung Ha Eun)
She's been throwing up.
I don't know
what made her stomach upset.
I just took her to the book store.
Please come often.
Okay.
Goodbye.
Both of my parents are blood type AB.
I heard Ms. Jung's blood type is AB.
I'd like to cut my hair.
I just closed.
What can I do?
I'll have to cut your hair.
Come over here.
You must have gotten
the eye disease.
Why do you look familiar?
Where have I seen you?
You're handsome.
Why do you look so gloomy?
How do you want me to cut it?
What's your blood type?
Why do you ask that so suddenly?
You seem to have
a good personality.
I'm curious about the blood types
of women like you.
I'm...
type AB.
How about you?
But...
why is Sung Ho's blood type O?
Was he really adopted?
Sung Ho?
He was a type B.
Ha Eun!
Taxi!
Are you okay?
Would you like to sit down?
- I'm fine.
- Are you sure?
Please stop the bus.
Sir, please stop the car.
Let's go.
Oh, no.
There's no telephone booth here.
You're such a weak coward.
You and that one
only knew how to cry.
- That one?
- Yes.
The kid you were playing with.
That one.
Why did you kill him?
What nonsense.
It was hard enough for me
and my child to survive.
Why do I have to feed and clothe
his ex-wife's child?
I wasn't related to him at all.
But the man who called himself
his father...
could not recognize his own child.
I told him his blood type was O,
and he believed the kid was born
by his wife and another man.
He stripped him naked, tied him up,
and beat him for hours.
Even I couldn't watch it.
Did you deceive him?
We would become happy...
if it disappeared.
What else could I do?
He was small but persistent.
It wouldn't die
even when we starved it.
It didn't die even
when we put it outside all night.
But that day,
I only pushed it once.
It...
just kept sleeping.
If I had only killed you earlier,
Sung Ho wouldn't have died.
It would've died anyway.
Don't call him "it!"
Sung Ho, it's me.
(Love Salon)
This is Love Salon.
Someone got hurt.
St. Peter's Hospital is nearby.
Please come quickly.
I think she's going to die.
Please hurry.
(Born Again)