(Episode 11)
(Gong Ji Chul)
I wanted to see her,
at least once.
Jun Ha Eun.
It's time for "Case Inside."
Today, we have with us the author
of "Secrets of a Murderer,"
and the attorney
at Gong Ji Chul's trial.
She's Jang Hye Mi, John Grisham
of Korea.
Welcome to the studio.
Would it be okay to refer to you
as the expert of Gong Ji Chul?
Not really. I've only written
a novel...
based on the scribblings on the wall
in his solitary confinement.
There's a poem here.
"A bone comes out of a birdcage."
"When it was separated from
the world and life, alive,"
"the bone would croak."
"Leaving there its robe
of feathers,"
"it walks out, whistling."
This was the poem he transcribed
on the day before he was executed.
I see. At the ending of your novel,
Gong Ji Chul is still alive
at the end.
Do you think he might still be alive
somewhere?
No one thinks that Jack the Ripper
or Zodiac Killer is alive,
but we still talk about them.
Gong Ji Chul is just like that.
Isn't that why...
someone would want to be noticed
by committing a copycat crime?
Do you think Gong Ji Chul
as a psychopath?
I...
have interviewed
many serial killers.
But Gong Ji Chul is not
a psychopath.
He's not a psychopath?
Gong Ji Chul had...
all the emotions a human being
could have.
He could even feel beauty.
He likes to read and loves music.
("Case Inside," KBC)
He was...
the same as ordinary people
in the beginning.
("Secrets of a Murderer")
("His wish was to live again.")
"I wanted to live."
I wanted to live.
That woman is alive.
(Resurrection)
Why is this thing buried here,
Father?
I assume you're aware of something.
Father!
That child thought of resurrection.
Who is that child?
Chun Jong Bum?
No, I'm not at school now.
I'm at the museum for remains.
I don't know what he's doing,
but he won't come out.
Why are you tying ribbons
on the tree?
It's a ritual in East Asia
that carries a wish of resurrection.
The body may have died,
but the soul will be a butterfly...
and fly away, they'd hoped.
In the national myths of Eurasia,
ribbons symbolized...
the border between this life
and the afterlife.
(The Archeology of Death Exhibition)
(Hosted by Korean Osteology Society,
Supervised by Seoyeon University)
The Altai natives hung ribbons
on sacred trees...
in this way and made a wish.
They wished their loved one could
resurrect back to life.
When I see your face...
at the museum of remains,
sometimes you're like
a whole different person.
Someone I don't know well.
But then...
someone I think I might know
so well.
Oh, Prosecutor Kim.
I'd like to ask you to accompany me
voluntarily.
We found the remains of a baby
at Sky Garden Cathedral today.
Remains?
If I accompanied you voluntarily,
would it be as a suspect
or testifier?
You'll know when you get there.
What is it?
It's nothing. Please don't worry,
Professor.
I'm asking you what this is about.
We should go. You can stay here,
Ms. Jung.
I feel so comfortable seeing you
here. We should've met here sooner.
Chun Jong Bum. Or...
shall I call you Chun Eun Woo?
You can call me as you wish.
The box that carried the child's
remains had your fingerprints.
You buried the box by yourself.
The priest gave testimony.
So do you think that I killed
the child?
You're not as imaginative
as you look.
Prosecutor Kim Su Hyuk.
Is that so?
Then let's hear what imagination
I need.
That child was Lim Hwa Young's.
- What?
- Check the DNA results.
DNA...
So you're saying...
The day she died...
she told me something
while she was drunk.
That she killed her own child
with her own hands.
- So?
- And I found the child...
who was buried in the mountains.
Then I moved the remains
to the cathedral.
Do you expect me to believe that?
I'm only telling you the facts.
It's up to you to believe it or not.
How did you know where
the child was buried?
How would I have known?
- I heard from Hwa Young.
- Whatever.
All right, let's say that's true.
Then why... Why did you do it?
You dug up a buried child...
then wrapped it up in a box...
and buried it again in
the cathedral. Why?
Did you form a meaningful
relationship with Hwa Young?
Or did she ask that as a last
favor before she died?
You killed her. Didn't you?
I felt bad for the child.
You felt bad?
I guess you came up with
some sort of a story.
But who would believe you?
You killed a woman when you were 15.
Do you want me to read
your criminal records again?
You killing that girl back then...
is also a fact, isn't it?
- I don't know about that.
- You don't know?
I have a question.
Why did you ring the neighbor's
bell before you killed Hwa Young?
The neighbor's bell?
I pressed a doorbell?
But what does that bell have
anything to do with the sock?
You pressed the bell then
waved the sock.
Someone like you wouldn't have
pressed that bell by accident.
Tell me why you set up a witness.
Sir.
The chief prosecutor has
called you in.
Jong Bum's fingerprints were found
on the remains of the child.
So I'm looking into that.
I don't care whether it's the DNA
or the fingerprints.
But you can make up evidence or
hide them. You're good at that.
But why did you do it this time?
Why?
Should we call a press conference
with the people...
you put up in jail
with fabricated warrants and proofs?
Su Hyuk.
Yes, sir.
Are you trying to be my enemy?
Why do people play the victim...
when they are the ones at fault?
That woman killed her own child
ten years ago...
yet tell me her dead child is
torturing her.
I'm going to throw this away.
So it can't...
torture me anymore.
I'm going to throw it away.
Watch me.
Goodbye.
I've done it.
You don't throw sins away.
You shouldn't let them fade
like old photographs.
You need to keep them...
in your heart.
Then...
blood must be repaid with blood.
If you set up a witness for me,
I guess you didn't get what
you wanted.
(Gong Ji Chul)
(If there's someone else you want to
kill, we can meet again.)
I think I'll find you before that.
Are you okay?
I guess you miss Su Hyuk a lot.
Why are you driving so recklessly?
- Hello.
- Where are you?
You know that place I like
near the practice room, right?
I'm on my way.
Can you change the music?
Do I have to listen to the violin
even here?
I hope you understand.
She's a violinist.
She hears the strings five times
louder than other people.
Okay, ma'am.
I guess your tastes don't change.
I like them young and tender.
How about you, Su Hyuk?
Does this fit your tastes?
I'm having them
because you like them.
I heard...
you're looking into the Gong Ji Chul
tribute murder cases.
Someone who would pay respect
to Ji Chul...
would only kill the targets that
Ji Chul would go for.
Su Hyuk, did you see my mom on
the television?
She's an expert on Gong Ji Chul.
So who's the target?
Someone who Gong Ji Chul would
want to kill.
I don't know.
Ji Chul couldn't kill
the woman he loved.
If he was still alive...
who would he want to kill?
A psychopath had someone he loved?
Of course.
His tragedy...
started when he was abandoned by
his mother.
It's quite unpleasant...
to refer to it as "tragedy."
There's one thing I agree with you.
Murder cannot be stopped
by one's own will.
Try observing the kid...
I mentioned last time.
Kid? What kid are you talking about?
Excuse me for a second.
We can make a bet.
He's going to commit murder
for sure.
I'm talking about Chun Jong Bum.
You make bets with people's lives.
I saw him for the first time
when he was 13.
He was very interested
in Gong Ji Chul.
So I gave him a book as a present.
You gave him a book
about serial killers...
to a 13-year-old boy.
I have a talent for identifying
psychopaths.
I know how to handle them.
No one in his home understands him.
He's going to come looking for me
someday.
I wanted him to be honest then.
So did he come to you?
No.
He had a stronger mentality
than I expected.
Just wait and see.
He'll make great success
in his own field.
Let's just hope it isn't murder.
Just wait and see.
He'll make great success
in his own field.
Let's just hope it isn't murder.
(The signature mark of Gong Ji Chul)
(Jang Hye Mi,
"Secrets of A Murderer")
(Gong Ji Chul and Jang Hye Mi)
Oh, my goodness.
She was talking about how she killed
her own baby with a pillow.
The tragedy of Gong Ji Chul...
started when he was abandoned by
his mother.
A person who gave
"Secrets of A Murderer..."
as a gift
and the one who read it.
A novelist who cherishes
Gong Ji Chul...
and someone who has become one
with him.
Instead of Gong Ji Chul,
he makes a judgment...
on the mother who abandoned
her baby.
He's going to commit murder
for sure.
I'm talking about Chun Jong Bum.
I felt pity...
for the baby.
I asked you what was going on.
Why does she keep him
beside her?
Is it good?
My heart!
I want to be your vampire tonight.
What are you talking about?
You don't look strong enough.
- Pardon?
- Uncle must've...
forgotten to take his medicine.
Dear Uncle Freak,
please be careful
who you're talking to.
Okay.
Just beat it
No one's want to be defeated
Have a good time.
"Everything is up to mind."
If we think it's the alcohol
that's inside the skull, it is.
If we think it's water,
then it's water indeed.
It means everything depends
on how you think.
Bottoms up.
Hey, aren't you drinking?
Why the long face?
What's going on?
What's that look
with the food in front of you?
(Chun Jong Bum)
Please excuse me.
Leave it. Hey!
- It's noisy there. Where are you?
- Where are you?
I'm on my way home.
Are you okay? You...
I know you're curious.
Ask me what you wanted to know.
Shall we take a walk?
I've decided not to be curious
about you.
- Are you listening?
- Go on.
You only need to think
about yourself from now on.
Only the present you matter to me.
I'm not going to believe
what others say about you.
I'll get mad at those who talk
about things I don't know about you.
I'm...
only going to believe
what you show me.
I'm going to hang up now.
Oh, right, my boss.
Hey!
How can you go home alone
while we're drinking?
Get back here right now.
I'm on my way.
I'm not going to believe
what others say about you.
I'll get mad at those who talk
about things I don't know about you.
I'm...
only going to believe
what you show me.
I'm only going to believe
This is my second atrium
and second ventricle.
The human heart contracts
around 60 to 70 times per minute.
It's about 100,000
on average per day.
If a person lives up to 70 years,
the heart contracts
2.6 million times.
The energy produced by the heart
in one hour is...
equivalent to lifting a person
of 75 kg...
to the top
of a three-floor building.
A heart failure rate is lower
than an ultra-precision machine.
Bovie.
A heart weighs 350 to 600 grams.
The heart is located...
at the center of the chest...
at the front.
It's shaped like a cone
between the two lungs.
It's a piece of muscle
as small as a fist.
The purpose of the heart is...
only to apply pressure
like a piston engine.
The blood
that enters the left ventricle...
through the bicuspid valve
from the left atrium is...
a muscle activity
of the left ventricle...
that opens the aorta valve.
It rises to the aorta
flowing throughout the body.
The human genes are still active
for 24 hours after death.
The heart still beats
even during brain death.
A heart is...
To me, a heart is a gift.
To me,
a heart is a machine.
(Episode 12)
If someone
with an organ transplant takes...
immunosuppressive drug
with grape fruit,
one can experience abnormalities
of heart beat, respiration,
and even end up in death.
Don't you know?
Because of the substance
in grape fruit,
the effects
of immunosuppressive drug will...
become five to ten times higher,
leading to severe side effects.
How did you know that I had
a heart transplant?
Few people would be unaware of that
as a medical student.
The article of your interview was
translated into five languages.
The first to get the transplant from
a death-row convict 18 years ago.
Oh, gosh.
By the way,
- I have a gift for you.
- A gift?
I'd figured you'd like old stones
since you like skulls so much.
It's an old stone that flew here
from the universe.
It's a necklace made with meteorite
fallen in Argentine 5,000 years ago.
It's been certified
by the observatory...
so it's got to be real.
It's shining
although it's just a stone.
It'll amaze you
because the color keeps changing.
Why don't you try it on?
He only dates girls
with surgery scars.
I want to ask you something.
What do you think about women
with surgery scars?
Surgery scars?
A medical student would
have nothing against that.
Isn't it done yet?
It's done now.
Are you feeling cold?
Why are you shivering?
Isn't it obvious?
I'm allowing someone to touch
my neck.
That's not it.
I mean I'm allowing someone to touch
my body. That's also not it.
I'll go now.
What are you doing?
It's 50 cm tall and assumed to be
less than 2 months old.
The gender is unverifiable.
The baby had to shut it's eyes
by the time...
it could meet it's mother's eyes.
Are you done now?
This baby didn't even start
to get teeth.
We got the DNA results
for this baby remains.
It's the biological child of Lim
from Pureun Studio Apartment.
And Chun Jong Bum is...
the suspect for the murder case
of Lim Hwa Young.
I could send you the records of the
case investigation if you'd like.
Did you say Chun Jong Bum?
Isn't it the most dangerous thing
to specify a suspect...
when you are under investigation?
Why are you...
giving him a chance?
You shoudn't do that to a guy like
Chun Jong Bum.
Sometimes beasts live among humans
and have the look of a human being.
They're hiding their instincts.
Those beasts will bite a person off
if there's the slightest chance.
Murder is what happens
within that chance,
not in a broad daylight.
I can no longer have
those beasts hurt my people...
after they get this chance.
That chance may seem to be little,
but my father...
Prosecutor,
why do you always lose your temper
before me?
I never lost my temper.
I'll ask you again.
Why are you always concerned
about me while you are angry?
- Concerned?
- You're being concerned about me.
Let's stop here.
Geez.
(Model demonstration)
Did you separate the bones
and flesh correctly?
You're the best at this job.
Did you handle the bones well?
Oh, Chun Jong Bum.
I'll be there soon. Bye.
I happened to overhear
your conversation, unwillingly.
Would my bones and flesh
be seperated now?
What brings you here?
- I live nearby.
- Oh, really? Where is it?
This is your house?
No, it's the rooftop house
of this building.
Lady Sabin!
When you're feeling lonely,
you can come and see me
When you're feeling blue,
When you're feeling lonely,
you can sing live at Body Check
Come to see me
It's good to see you again.
Did you say the kid's name was
Jong Bum?
Do you like salmon or something
else?
Hey. Put that knife down, right now.
I raised my child with this knife.
If you hold up a knife, looking
as you do,
who will think you're
a raw fish chef?
People will think you're a defect
and ex-convict...
going to kill your wife
who had an affair.
A defect?
An ex-convict?
A defect.
An ex-convict.
I didn't kill someone,
but it was attempted murder.
Why are you talking so much,
you pseudo-ex-convict...
who used to live off this girl.
I shall change the location
of your ribs...
in an extraordinary way.
A brother who murders
another brother...
- You're going to murder.
- What do you think, Sa Bin?
Between attempted murder...
and jerks who betray
their own people,
who is worse off?
- Should I be frank?
- Be honest with me.
I think it's neck and neck.
I should tear you two to shreds
and quarter you.
But I think playing
with people's minds is...
a bit more unlikeable, personally.
You're right.
- That's right.
- Why you...
Whatever.
Hey, Jong Bum.
What do you think?
Tell me who is more of a jerk.
- I want to ask you something.
- Go ahead.
Did you give up trying to murder
someone,
or did you fail to do it?
You must've made a plan
for your murder.
Didn't you feel despondent
after you'd given up?
Amen.
Everyone who can hear shall
hear him.
Jong Bum, you're like
a forensic psychologist.
You're my type of guy,
both the way you look...
and the way you talk.
Everyone who can hear shall
hear him.
You're pretending to know even when
you don't know, you jerk.
You jerk.
Help yourself.
Jong Bum, aren't you going to tell
me to come inside?
I came here because I missed you.
Don't you think you've done enough?
Look at this place.
How could you live here?
You really must be
a different breed from me.
I couldn't live a day in this place.
If Dad found out you came here,
he'll be really angry.
To me?
He'll be angry at you.
You should hang those in your room.
Don't you think?
Why?
Did you leave it
so you could return?
Drink it, brother.
If you don't drink your juice...
Mom would be disappointed in you.
His brother?
If I don't drink it, you would be
disappointed not mom.
Why don't you drink it?
You should have a taste
of something you made.
What?
You drank it even though you knew?
We can't become a family...
because you're spiteful like that.
I feel bad for you.
You even ate detergent...
just so you could stay at our house?
I don't have to drink it anymore.
Take all of it with you.
I guess we're not family anymore.
Who is it?
Hello.
I'm Jong Bum's little brother.
Jong Bum, I'll be going now.
Oh, right.
Mom told me to tell you to come
to the charity party this weekend.
My uncle told me to give it to you
because the heating here is bad...
due to construction.
Don't touch it.
I told you not to touch it.
Are you stupid?
You shouldn't have...
taken anything if you knew
someone meddled with it.
If you didn't want that...
you should have splashed
it in his face.
Your little brother is doing this
to you!
You should have at least told your
family. Who drinks this?
I'm warning you.
Don't come any closer.
Why did you do it?
Answer me. Why did you drink it
even though you knew?
- Because I needed to be there.
- There?
That was the only place
I could go to.
Go.
Why?
Because you were a juvenile criminal
or because you're a psychopath?
So...
is that why your family's doing
this to you?
Even though you can't feel...
my anger, sadness, or hardship...
you can analyze and predict them.
That's what people call
cold empathy.
All of your anger,
sadness, and hardship,
I can feel them.
That's...
what people call hot empathy.
So there is no one in this world...
who can't empathize
with another's pain.
Go away.
I'd go see that woman
even if I die.
I'm going to meet that woman
You don't look well.
What's wrong?
I have something on my mind.
Su Hyuk, your mate for this lifetime
is Sang Ah.
She's you're meant-to-be.
You have to protect her...
- if something bad happens to her.
- Did you two plan this?
A relationship so close that hurts
in the past life...
will just graze you
in the present life.
But a bad relationship
in your past life...
will come back to untie that knot.
So just...
be nice and loving to each other.
Su Hyuk, you heard her.
You need to be good to me.
So you're okay with us being bad
in the past life?
Here.
I started making string bracelets...
because of a female osteology
professor, who's a regular here,
but this is doing great as a hobby.
If this was a ring, I would have
today's date engraved on it.
Right, Mom? What a pity.
I will put the ring that the dead
couldn't let go even after death...
on his bride's finger.
- Where are you?
- In the autopsy room, why?
I'll be there.
Geez.
Hey, mister.
Why are you beating again?
Why?
You're disturbing my leisure time
on the weekends.
I'll leave right away
after I hand this to you.
This is...
We found six bodies related to the
Byun Sung Hoon case...
and he'll be put on trial soon.
You can return the ring to
its owner.
I'll be on my way.
Hey.
Since you're here already
let's go together.
We should return the ring together.
(Old Future)
Mister.
Do you use this stamp...
in this bookstore?
("Old Future")
Not anymore.
We used to use it a long time ago.
Then,
how long have you run
this book store?
It's been about 30 years.
After the former owner died,
his daughter died.
I took over after that.
A daughter?
You must've known
the daughter well.
She's already dead.
I went to her funeral too
30 years ago.
- She's dead.
- Yes.
I knew this would happen.
Did you think you'd meet her
if you came here without notice?
How can they look...
that much alike?
But it seems like
time has stopped here.
That's possible.
There haven't been...
any new books for 30 years.
I want to keep it that way...
until the day I die.
This book has been out of print
but here it is.
There are theses here too.
Oh, my goodness.
Go ahead and choose a book.
I'll buy you a book today.
Aren't you here
to look for the owner of the ring?
(Resurrection)
I'll take this.
It's raining.
The books will get wet.
Do you like the rain?
Everything that falls
from the sky is beautiful.
It's beautiful,
but the cherry blossom will fall.
Did you see the big cherry blossom
tree in front of the NFS?
I really wanted to take a picture
this spring.
That tree fades the latest.
Pardon?
I said that the tree fades
at the latest.
Do you like cherry blossoms?
Wait here while I get the car.
I got...
a heart transplant
from a death-row convict.
Maybe that's why my heart pounds
in fear whenever I see you.
But I get confused sometimes
whether my heart is pounding...
because of my feelings
or because of him.
Can I hold your hand just once?
I want to know whether it's pounding
because of me or him.
Frankly speaking,
my heart was pounding
since the first time I saw you.
Pardon?
Why? Wasn't it enough?
Can I do something else
if it's not enough?
You're a medical school professor.
Don't you have experiment ethics?
I'm a bit...
It's not like
there's something wrong with me,
but why does my heart pound
whenever I see you?
I've never felt my heart pounding
in my life...
because of a man.
I may have a strong sense
of experimentation.
(internal medicine)
It was the first day
I felt someone else's pain.
And...
This is crazy.
I've developed feelings
for this woman...
who has accepted my dark side.
(Born Again)
I see it.
You see other people's wounds,
but you don't seem to see yours.
I'm happy I didn't make you regret.
You shouldn't get hurt
because I like you.
Love? If you give it
yet you don't get it back,
your love becomes an obsession.
Cain became the first murderer
of the human race.
Oh, no. Prosecutor!