(Episode 5)
Start the on-site inspections
after the reporters get there.
He should be condemned
by the press first.
Yes, it's me.
I told you
my first lecture is today.
All right. I'll take it...
from there as soon
as my class is over.
His skull is missing,
so we don't have
the main item of the exhibition.
You'll have to bring your head
in case of an emergency.
But I...
My head?
Sir, please pull over here.
- Thank you.
- What is this?
Stop talking!
Come here. Give that to me.
Let me swap places
with this old woman.
What's this?
Who is this crazy wench?
Didn't you hear me?
I'll swap places.
Oh, well.
You'll be worth killing.
What's that jerk doing?
- Come here.
- Goodness.
- Hey!
- Gosh!
Heo Do Jin, 34 years old.
He committed school violence,
rode a motorbike, and arson at 15.
Mugging and injuring a man at 17.
Attempted murder of a part-timer
at an internet cafe at 19.
A criminal
with seven previous convictions.
Doesn't he ever consider
committing suicide?
Hey!
Come here.
- I just told you to come over.
- Why's he here?
What is he a leech? What a stalker.
- Why are you always after me?
- Oh, my gosh!
- Ma'am, are you all right? My gosh.
- My back hurts.
She won't be able to live
her life to the fullest.
Prosecutor, I don't think
Byun Sung Hoon is a serial killer.
I can't find any evidence no matter
how much I try.
He killed a friend of his family
and buried him alive at 13.
The DNA in his blood is
the evidence.
Tell him to wait for me. I'm coming.
(Meeting Your Past in the Future)
Prisoner number 3731.
The death-row convict,
Kim Seo Yeon has passed away.
But his heart is beating again...
in my heart.
(A Death Row-Convict's
Heart Transplanted...)
(to the Youngest Osteologist.)
You must be interested
in dead bodies.
What's this?
The syllabus is just a formality.
- Tell them about an autopsy.
- Would it be okay if I did?
Professor, here's a student
who got an A-plus from you.
You never gave me an A-plus.
That kid was the first in his major
in the Basic Science test.
I'd like him to be a researcher
under me, but that's unlikely.
You'll notice him the moment
you step inside the lecture room.
(Chun Jong Bum)
It's the point where archeology
and forensic medicine meet.
This is osteoarchaeology.
Bones are eternal evidence.
What we have here are the skulls
of a couple found 6,000 years ago...
in Valdaro village, Mantova
in north Italy.
Their teeth are strong...
so they are assumed to have been
man and woman between 18 and 20.
Do you see them hugging each other
in their death?
It's called the eternal embrace
of "Valdaro lovers."
("The eye shall see
for the last time.")
(University of Seoyeon)
Some say they might've committed
suicide together.
So you're looking
at the oldest lovers...
in the history of the world.
Yes, you over there.
Why do you think they are lovers?
What did you think, then?
It could've been murdered
then buried.
There are no external injuries
in the skull.
They used to bury people alive
with the dead 6,000 years ago.
The girl might've been buried alive,
embraced the body of the man,
then froze to death.
Isn't that a possibility?
Well...
Only the earth and worms would know
the truth.
But they are seeing eye to eye.
Don't you think they would've looked
at each other until their death?
You can feel that with your heart.
They could've loathed each other
until their death.
Why do you think that?
That's just my scenario.
I like how you thought
about a murder case looking at it.
That's forensic medicine.
The class is over for today.
Please apply if you want training
at the National Forensic Service.
Yes, Miss.
(Alarm)
Do you like hearing the music box?
Sorry?
I bought this for my nephew,
but maybe you might need it.
You cared about my hair,
not the lecture?
Not a very good attitude, is it?
Did you give that book
as a present to your friend?
- I'm done.
- Thanks to you, I did.
I'd like to see...
how an autopsy is conducted.
Are you Chun Jong Bum?
I guess it's you.
You need to be qualified
to attend an autopsy.
Is it okay if I tested you?
- Test me?
- I'd like to introduce you to him.
Can you come over to my office
after lunch?
He's 300 years older than you.
So you better behave.
(Welcome to the University of
Seoyeon College of Medicine!)
- Professor
- Professor.
Chun Jong Bum is so handsome,
isn't he?
Chun Jong Bum?
That guy over there.
Tada! He's a walking statue
of David.
He's in the second year of
medical school.
He's born with good genes, better
than being born with a silver spoon.
Anyone's heart would be pounding...
once they've seen him.
He would've been an Ardipithecus
4.4 million years ago.
Ardi... What?
It walked although its brain was
the size of a chimpanzee.
Female Ardipithecus would've fought
violently...
over a male Ardipithecus like him,
wouldn't they?
His father is the chief prosecutor,
a candidate for Attorney General.
His mother is said to be
the chief director of our school.
What secret of that perfect guy
would have?
Professor. I heard he is
a total psychopath.
And he murdered someone
for the first time at 15.
Come in.
- Don't just stand there, say hello.
- To who?
A warm and strong arm.
What is this...
- deja vu?
- You seem comfortable.
You must have done this a lot.
Let me down.
Mister.
How do you feel watching the world
for the first time in 300 years?
Do you recognize it?
Hanyang has changed a lot.
We still have a few palaces left.
Let's go for a visit once
the weather warms up.
If it's been 300 years, is it
from the Joseon dynasty?
Yes, we discovered the skull
in Andong.
A person isn't dead, just because
they are biologically dead.
A person is truly dead...
when everyone
who remembers he or she...
is biologically dead.
I'm the type who doesn't believe
in dignity after death.
Then why are you so interested in
the remains of people?
Because I understand you.
That remains are
an everlasting proof.
The flesh will rot and
the blood will dry...
but the bones remain.
It tells us silently...
how one person killed the other.
This one died of an illness.
Do you always look at everything
through a criminological view?
Because I want to be
a medical examiner like you.
- Hello?
- You're late.
It's almost three.
Listen well.
If you don't bring the Andong skull
to the exhibition hall by four...
you can say goodbye to your head!
Can't you wait for me until six?
This grave sinner has
another lecture.
Hey!
If you're busy, should I bring
the skull to its destination?
- Sorry?
- I ran errands for Professor Nam.
Really?
This is my errands app.
If you put in a formal request,
since this is a cultural heritage
the prices begin at 200 dollars.
Since I do attend your lectures...
I'll give you a discount.
200 dollars...
Okay, but if there are any issues
you'll repay me 5000 times that.
Since like you said, this is
a cultural heritage, right?
Then I'll have to charge you extra
for car fees.
Call me a cab.
Something comfortable and luxurious
for the heritage skull to ride in.
Okay?
Give me your phone.
I'll refuse.
I don't text my students.
I need to text my client
after the mission's been completed.
(Professor Jung Sa Bin)
(Name: PULSE)
Pulse.
A vibration as short as a heartbeat.
An electric current that flows
only for a short while.
That thing I felt...
from that person.
Did you give that book
as a present to your friend?
Thanks to you, I did.
I felt pain.
Please take a look over there too.
I told you.
I don't remember anything
because of the drugs I take.
- Can I talk to him in private?
- Okay, sir.
Let's go.
Why?
Were you too excited killing
to remember...
whether you killed 6 or 7 people?
That's good.
If you eat all of this,
a body will come out.
I'll talk.
I'll tell you everything.
I remember now.
Stand up.
Darn.
Wait.
It's not over there.
You might not know,
but your feet do.
Start digging.
I heard he is
a total psychopath.
And he murdered someone
for the first time at 15.
That's why Chun Jong Bum's
father sent him...
to America, cathedrals, and did
all sorts of things.
Come closer. This is very important.
Apparently, he only dates women
with surgery scars.
My friend So Hee's the daughter
of their driver...
and she dated Jong Bum...
because she had a scar from
her lymph nodes surgery.
I lived an empty life.
Hemorrhoids surgery is the only
kind of surgery I had!
What's wrong with you?
Give it to me.
There's only one coke.
"The eye shall see
for the last time."
"Arms, take your last embrace!"
"And lips, be sealed
with a righteous kiss..."
"and make a contract with death."
Shakespeare
in a Forensic Medicine book.
Is this his stream of consciousness?
(The Archeology of Death Exhibition)
I brought the Andong man
to the exhibit.
Send the money.
(The Archeology of Death Exhibition)
(Professor Jung Sa Bin)
(I brought the Andong man
to the exhibit. Send the money.)
The psychopath is crazy about money.
- Yes?
- Where are you?
I got a call
from the excavation team.
Can you go on a business trip
to Gangwon-do?
They found some remains
near the Donggang River.
I guess that remains came out
on a warm spring day.
Yes, I'll head there directly
from my office.
How are you getting there?
I'll take the train.
March 5, 2020. It's day 1021
of the bone autopsy.
I'm going to the excavation site.
I hope the remains
I find today will...
tell me the message
that they haven't spoken...
while they were buried.
There is a timing for each destiny.
When that time comes,
someone will find me...
and I will find that someone.
(Under Investigation)
This is a mummy
that was preserved by formalin.
It might have been saponified
underwater,
but the body did not rot at all.
It's interesting that only the face
was partially skeletonized...
and that it was tied
with a red rope.
The face has been shattered.
Apart from the skull,
the jawbone is still intact.
By the looks of the wisdom tooth,
it was in its mid to late 20s.
This was a male.
It was a strong male.
From the corrosion of the remains,
I think it's been buried
over 30 years.
"Wuthering Heights"?
The letters on the book are gone.
I don't even know
what "Wuthering Heights" is.
Just kill me.
I'd say my mother's a murderer
if that was done by me.
Of course, you got those dirty genes
from your mother.
There are many reporters out there,
so you can try your luck there.
- Bring him to the reporters.
- Yes, sir.
It's not me.
- What was your motive for murder?
- Are there any more victims?
Don't you feel sorry
for the victims?
It's not me!
I think he was stabbed several times
with a knife.
The wounds are deep.
Judging from the damages
done to the face,
I think someone was trying
to hide the victim's identity.
A crime of passion?
I don't think it was that.
Tying a dead person
with a red rope like this was...
one of the burial customs.
They might have given him a funeral.
This is Jung Sa Bin,
an expert on the bone autopsy.
He's in the excavation team of Seoul
Central District Prosecutors Office.
Prosecutor Kim Su Hyuk.
That fist won't be opened.
Professor Yoo tried it earlier.
Is that a ring?
That looks like a wedding band.
There's a number.
It looks like a date.
It's 830403.
"830403?"
Would it be a wedding date?
April 3, 1983.
It could've been the first day
he met the bride.
It could be a special date.
Let's do the detailed autopsy
as soon as possible.
After the police investigation,
please send the evidence to the NFS.
There's nothing else to identify him
because the criminal threw him...
after stripping him naked.
If this is a 30-year-old corpse,
it wasn't done by Byun Sung Hoon.
This is a corpse that died
when Byun Sung Hoon was eight.
Byun Sung Hoon was the one
who killed it.
This book was not here
in the first place.
In the end,
we also don't have evidence...
- Byun Sung Hoon didn't kill him.
- Here,
this bone is the eternal evidence.
Professor Yoo, let's move the bone.
Sure.
I can smell formalin from his face.
(Episode 6)
(Chun Seok Tae)
Is it you, Jong Bum?
Yes, Mom.
Are you sick?
You're sweating.
I ran all the way here. That's why.
I knew it.
Jon Bum has never caught
a common cold as a child.
My son has great genes.
I used to catch a cold in winter
just by washing with cold water.
I always had a runny nose too
due to allergic rhinitis.
Here.
What are you so happy about?
I would've been so happy...
if Jong Woo was half as handsome
as his brother.
Honey.
Look at how sharp his features are.
His skin is as smooth as marble.
He's fashionable, which he takes
after you.
Sure. You practically designed
his eyes, nose, and lips.
Visit your uncle in America
when the semester is over.
Don't think about coming back
whether it works out or not.
Stay there whatever happens.
What if he goes to the States?
Do you think he won't be
your son anymore,
once he's out of your sight?
Dad, please stop.
He's our family too.
He's not looking at you
how an older brother should.
How come you're not looking at me?
Are you afraid of me?
What did you say?
Jong Bum, go upstairs.
Now.
We need to talk.
Your biological father has...
an IQ in the top ten percentile
in Korea.
And his occupation is
in the top one percent.
He's either a great specialist
or a well-known CEO.
He may be a respected man in
a legal profession like your father.
Mom.
I've never thought
that I was unhappy.
No one abandoned me,
but I was chosen
through sperm donation.
I'm thankful to my father as well.
He has raised me.
You've never learned how to draw.
Yet you started drawing
a snowy field from the age of four.
You started drawing it
just as you woke up one day.
Jong Bum,
I adore you very much.
You shine
even if you just stayed still.
You've always excelled
at everything you do,
including academics, drawing,
sports, and music.
You've never had private tutoring
and even picked the medical school.
You loved drawing so much
but chose to go the medical school.
You know how to become
an object of envy.
The one percent of superior people
like you lead...
the ignorant 99 percent
of this world, Jong Bum.
Do you still not want the car?
It's my present for you.
I don't want the car.
Will you allow me to live alone
near the school?
Do you feel uncomfortable living
in this house?
- Do you want to leave?
- Do you feel comfortable...
with me living here?
Listen carefully, Jong Bum.
There's only one reason
why you might leave this house.
It's when I abandon you.
I will not...
abandon you
even if you committed murder.
But...
please don't fall behind.
If you do anything silly,
then I might have to abandon you.
Hot news.
The mummy of a young man was
discovered at Gangwon-do.
He was embalmed using formalin.
It was found at the site-inspection
of Byun Sung Hoon.
I thought he only killed girls,
but I guess he kills randomly.
Some say it's not Byun Sung Hoon
who killed him.
He was holding a book called
"Wuthering Heights."
Is this a message of the dying?
Who dies carrying a book?
It's a hint left by the murderer,
you jerk.
If feels like the warmth is
still here.
You must be happy to be out here
after living in water for 30 years.
You could take some rest today
since I untied the ropes.
What is your name?
You seem to around my age, and
I've seen too much of you already.
I don't know what happened
30 years ago,
but you must've been murdered
on the happiest day of your life.
That's the reason why you were not
decomposed, isn't it?
You might've bought a ring to give
to your beloved girlfriend,
and were on the way to give it
to her.
And you died even
before you'd met her.
Am I right?
I see now.
Mr. John Doe,
can you trust me?
I will find your face back to you.
I'll find your wife too.
If your bride is alive,
I'll find her and hand your ring
to her.
You're here like this...
because you weren't able to put
the ring on her finger.
When your wife receives your ring,
then,
you can leave...
in peace.
Hyung Bin!
Hyung Bin.
Did you have another nightmare?
Go back to sleep.
I really don't like this.
About what?
You getting up from bed before I do.
You always do that.
I thought we were going to share
one bed for the rest of our lives.
I don't like the way you talk
either. We're engaged...
yet you still don't feel
like you're mine.
I thought that's why you liked me.
I thought workaholic men
were also obsessed with women.
Anyone obsessed with
anything is weak-willed.
Why would they let
someone else control them?
Sorry. You can raid the fridge.
It's full of your favorites.
I thought I bought you a tie pin.
Why is it always that fountain pen?
(A Mummy Found in Donggang River)
(Social News)
You need to make sure the autopsy
report from the mummy is private.
Who's that person who did the
bone autopsy?
Make sure she's kept quiet.
We were too late. The remains became
bones in a single day...
and I don't know how they found out,
but the press is already here.
I'll be right there.
- Yes?
- Hello.
- It's me. Sung Hoon.
- Sung Hoon?
I guess you forgot my voice.
it's Byun Sung Hoon.
Will you put the person who gave
you the phone on the line?
Why?
I'm the one who wants to
talk to you.
Is that so? Then I'll be
right there.
- No.
- No?
I couldn't believe there was
a reporter who believed me.
I heard everything during
the on-site investigation.
It's a 30-year-old remain.
That mummy!
I know you're trying to blame
me for murdering that mummy.
I can't believe this.
Do you still think
I'm the serial killer?
Why? Because I was
a youth criminal?
I only killed one person!
You need to stop oppressing me.
That's why I'm falsely confessing...
that I killed over ten people!
This phone number of yours was...
told by this man beside me.
This man knew...
your phone number
and your home address.
I don't think...
you'll be able to
live your life to the fullest.
I'll see you at the trial.
Goodbye.
Mr. Ahn.
Track the phone contraband routes
in your facility.
Not through mails, but investigate
those with an external prescription.
Send over anyone that gets caught.
So you want to play?
All right, I'll play along.
Is this the remains found
in Donggang River?
Is this scientifically possible?
- Did Sung Hoon commit the crime?
- Please move out of the way.
Please give us a word.
Answer our questions!
Is it scientifically possible for
a mummy to turn to bones in a day?
Is there any possibility of bodies
switching in the NFS?
Were there past cases similar
to this?
Did Sung Hoon commit the crime?
Sung Hoon...
We will release the actual
cause of death after the autopsy.
I think you can come in now.
It's not cold here.
That's not a living person.
What do you want for
our late-night snack?
Sex, male. Height, around 184 cm.
Weight, around 75 kg.
He's of a robust build.
Judging from the bones, he seems
to be in his late 20s.
Time of death, around
30 to 35 years ago.
Estimated to be around
1984 to 1989.
There was a deep reverse cross wound
on his chest when discovered.
It was an upside-down cross.
Two amateur knife wounds on
his stomach.
But the critical wound is
determined...
to be the wound on his stomach.
The chest wound seems symbolic...
so it could be the criminal's
signature mark.
The knife went through the ribs...
and reached the spine.
How could anyone stab
someone like this?
The left side of the face is
completely smashed with a dull club.
Everything from the zygomatic bone
to the lower jaw is smashed.
The skull was also fractured
due to the impact.
Mr. John Doe,
what happened 30 years ago?
Tell me what happened.
Did you say hello to
Prosecutor Kim Su Hyuk?
He went into the observation room.
A prosecutor?
Did he just leave?
(Wuthering Heights)
What happened 30 years ago?
He's just amazing.
Let's go.
(A Corpse Was Skeletonized
in One Day After Excavation.)
(It was skeletonized on 6th...)
This remains discovered
by the Papyeong Yoon clan is...
also known as the Naju Lady Mummy.
They say her skin was
still elastic...
because it bounced back
when pressed.
If only the skeletal system
and cartilage tissue are intact,
it's enough to know
the cause of death.
What was the cause of death?
One side of the lady's stomach was
bulging out.
After CT and MRI scanning,
her womb was ruptured,
and the head of the fetus had
already reached the vaginal opening.
She passed away while giving birth.
Why didn't it rot?
They poured lime outside the tomb.
The lime hardened like cement...
and stopped the decomposition
of the corpse.
After how many days
was the body skeletonized?
She became an unwanted visitor...
to a medical school anatomy class
before she was skeletonized.
We don't have laws
on mummy preservation yet.
Can it be explained medically...
if a corpse is skeletonized
in just one day of excavation?
Pardon?
You must be interested
in the Donggang mummy.
I'll invite you to the autopsy room
if you're taking the NFS training.
With three internships, you might
get the chance to be the assistant.
But you have to be polite
towards the corpse.
I won't accept
if it's just plain curiosity.
When can I go to the autopsy room?
You look like you're going
on a date.
NFS autopsy is different
from anatomy.
They usually died of a tragic death.
You need to have the condolences
towards them.
Sure, I mean, I'll do that.
I don't believe in an afterlife,
but only in a near-death experience.
They say people see a panorama
of their life from childhood...
until the last moment
right before their death.
I heard they see...
another world like a hallucination.
You said you didn't believe
in an afterlife.
Humans are organisms,
so I guess it'll be explained
medically someday.
But...
I also have an X-file in my life
that cannot be explained medically.
An X-file?
I've never learned how to paint,
but I drew paintings...
that could be displayed in an
exhibition since I was four.
They were particular paintings.
What kind of paintings?
It was a village that was snowing,
a birch forest,
and a snowy landscape.
You're trying to say
that you're a genius, aren't you?
When can I visit
the Donggang mummy autopsy?
Were you serious about becoming
a medical examiner?
Yes.
All right. Call me in front of NFS
tomorrow at two o'clock.
- You must be distressed.
- Thank you for coming.
Please take a seat over there.
You're quite brave, Jong Bum.
Grandpa loved you so much.
Aren't you even a little bit sad?
He's just in shock.
Don't say that.
Jong Bum, let's go out.
Come.
- That kid isn't crying at all.
- You're right.
Is it because he's so little?
Jong Bum, tell me...
what's on your mind right now.
When we saw that dead puppy
in front of our house,
you didn't think it was pitiful.
You only said
you wanted to dissect it.
You just want to...
know more about Grandpa's body,
don't you?
You can tell me honestly.
You're curious
what's inside the body, right?
No.
It's not bad to have the urge
to dissect.
It's because you're a genius.
Do you know what a genius is?
You have the DNA...
of the upper one percent
of the top doctors.
My son is different indeed.
Other kids your age...
only know how to cry in funerals.
I'm curious.
Sure.
That's okay.
Grandpa was a pastor.
- Right.
- I want to know...
if there is
such a thing as a soul...
and if Grandpa will be resurrected.
I want to know how he'll look
when he resurrects.
What?
(Wuthering Heights)
This is the book...
that the red rope mummy loved.
(Chun Jong Bum)
Hello?
I'm on my way.
I'll be there in ten minutes.
Okay, I'll be out soon.
What's wrong with me?
Why?
(Protected, Permitted left-turn)
There is a timing for each destiny.
When that time comes,
someone will find me...
and I too find that someone.
(Born Again)
Haven't we met in the past?
Even if we live in different times,
we can still commune.
His copycat has popped out.
This is the sign of Gong Ji Chul.
Chief prosecutor Chun would gnash
his teeth about Gong Ji Chul.
He's the man that you hate the most.
A college student was wandering
around the medical school.
- I have a witness.
- I guess you snoop around behind.
We got crucial evidence.
Do you want to ruin a living person
because of a dead person?