(Episode 9)
Someone got hurt. Please come
quickly.
Sir, I was going to kill
just the passenger as a warning.
But Kim Su Hyuk got hurt instead.
- Who is the passenger?
- It's a woman, sir.
He died...
instead of a woman?
We did a CT scan, and there are no
injuries in his head, fortunately.
His injury is not bad compared
to the severity of the accident.
I'd say the lord has looked
over her.
When will he be recovering
his senses?
- Are you his family?
- No.
Are you his lover?
No, I'm not.
The person in the passenger seat
gets a serious injury...
or die in most cases like this.
He'd swerved in the direction of
the passenger seat...
knowing that the car would hit
the driver's side.
If you're not a family or a lover,
I wonder what it is that made him...
overcome his instinct to survive.
(Instinct)
This is the first time I'm observing
the funeral of an abandoned dog.
I'm worried because this area is
a redevelopment zone.
They wouldn't demolish
the cathedral, would they?
No one touched a handful of soil
in this place...
for the past 35 years.
From now on,
no one will abandon this dog again.
No one.
I brought it because it was hit by
a car.
- It's a puppy.
- What did you say?
Why would you bring the puppy here?
Let's take the puppy to the hospital
right now.
It died not having committed a sin,
like Jesus.
It's going to be born again
after three days.
This dog is not dead, it is dying.
Don't you...
want to save his life?
It would be better
to be born again...
than to die after being abandoned.
We pray in the name of the father,
the son, and the sacred being.
You always visit me even though
you don't believe in the lord.
I'll be going now.
Wait a minute.
I bought this on my way back from
a retreat as I was reminded of you.
Do you still collect meteorites?
Thank you, Father.
Jong Bum!
If you want to suppress
your instinct at a critical moment,
let that person carry an object
that you like.
Have him or her place it
where you can see it.
(Family Waiting Room)
Is there a guardian
for Mr. Kim Su Hyuk?
How are you feeling?
Are you all right?
Can I ask you why you did that?
You almost died.
You could've died, trying
to save me.
Don't be burdened.
I would've done the same thing
even if it weren't for you.
- Gosh.
- Let me see it.
The accident might've damaged
your eyes.
- I'm fine. Let me just...
- Geez, let me see.
How would you know when you've only
touched dead bodies?
Don't mind it. This happens often.
Is it both of your eyes
or just the left side?
This won't make me give up
the remains.
You'll be accompanying me to
the bookstore Old Future, won't you?
What's that?
Your eyes won't hurt if you were
kinder.
Try blinking your eyes.
Go ahead, blink them.
There's something I've
been meaning to ask you.
Why do you look at me in that way?
What about my eyes?
It's as if...
you're looking in the eyes
of your past lover.
What did you say?
Don't look at people that way.
They might take it the wrong way.
Hello?
No, the truck got in the way
so suddenly.
I'm fine,
but Prosecutor Kim got hurt a bit.
Yes.
I've got a lecture at the University
of Seoyeon tomorrow.
I'll come to the NFS right
after the class.
I'm really okay. Yes.
Prosecutor Kim?
You should be resting. Why would you
leave the hospital already?
What will you do if you get
a scar...
in that razor-sharp face of yours?
It's nothing.
The man who did this to you...
turned himself in right after
the accident.
Turned himself in?
I did some background check
on him as I felt leery.
He's a guy who works for Seo Tae Ha.
You know Seo Tae Ha,
the boss of Kennedy clan?
The Kennedy clan has close ties with
political, financial, legal circles.
I also did a background check
on Byun Sung Hoon's account.
I found records of Byun transferring
money to Seo several times.
So where is he now?
Seo Tae Ha is currently imprisoned
in Seobu Jail.
He must have hit it off
with Byun Sung Hoon there.
Seo Tae Ha might be young...
but he integrated...
five clans in Suwon, Pyeongtaek,
and Anyang.
He's a horrific guy.
But if...
Seo Tae Ha is
on Byun Sung Hoon's side...
things are becoming tougher now.
Shouldn't we be going around
the whole country...
looking for remains killed
by Byun Sung Hoon.
Track Chun Eun Woo...
I mean Chun Jong Bum, Detective Joo.
Report to me everything about
that man.
(Jang Hye Mi)
"To the highest place?"
I have a gift for you.
I'll put your painting
that I bought here.
I didn't think you still
had it with you.
This is...
the place...
where a genius artist I used to
look after lived.
It's a bit cold here,
will you be okay?
Thank you, I won't miss the rent.
When are you going to move in?
Soon.
(All is as willed by the lord!
Accept your destiny!)
This angle is so fresh.
It's like you're looking down
from above, like a deity.
That's not what I intended.
- A deity?
- But this facial expression...
How is it so lively?
It's as if you had it right before
your eyes.
It seems as though someone
is standing in front of the woman.
I want to paint the room.
Is that okay?
Whatever you want.
You liked the meteorites too.
Yes.
I don't know where the falling
meteorites come from...
but someone always finds them.
I'll get going.
I'm excited when a face is restored
on the dry bones like a flower.
(Gong Ji Chul)
(Lim Hwa Young deserves to die.
Don't you think it's time we meet?)
Did you watch them cook this?
Of course.
These are harp seals from Canada...
with wild ginseng, sea cucumber,
loach, and mountain yam...
boiled for two straight days.
You're putting them all at once?
Would it taste okay?
Is that the juice for Jong Bum?
The color changed.
It has a harp seal in it.
It's full of DHA so it's good
for your brain.
While I go visit your
grandfather in the US...
you need to give
your brother this juice. Okay?
I've been doing it
for a long time already.
You know he's the pride
of our family, right?
Sure.
Here, you can have this.
It's not bitter.
Are you going somewhere?
What's with you?
Mom told me to watch you drink this.
It's super expensive.
Give it to me. I'll drink it.
How are you sure that Jong Bum
is the real culprit?
Someone with the memory of murder
always murders again.
His first murder was when he was 15
years old. He held it in until now.
Keep an eye on him.
This is Jong Bum's family registry.
Father, Chief prosecutor
Chun Seok Tae.
Mother, President of Seo Yeon
Foundation, Heo Jin Kyung.
(Chun Jong Bum, Father, Chun Seok
Tae, Mother, Heo Jin Kyung)
Three days.
He lived with a corpse
for three days.
Why didn't you just come to
the office?
How are you feeling?
- I'm sorry for worrying you.
- What worries?
Do you have a suspect on
the Lim Hwa Young case?
We have a strong suspect.
Who is it?
Tell me.
It's your son, Chun Jong Bum.
He's a prime suspect.
What? Jong Bum?
He was the last person to be
seen with the victim.
The errand boy, Chun Jong Bum.
The person who visited the victim
during the time of her death...
was also just Jong Bum.
We already have a witness report.
There's no way.
You always talked about
your second son...
yet you never talked to me
about Jong Bum...
so I almost mistook him
for a bastard son.
How many people know?
I've already told everyone to
keep a tight mouth.
I will turn this into a private
investigation.
(Gong Ji Chul Tribute
Murder Case Report)
(Crime scene photos)
This is your fault.
I thought I told you to
live quietly.
Dad, I want to live with Jong Bum.
Why?
Why can't he live with us?
What did he do this time?
You're an adult now.
Let's not make it hard
for both of us.
Leave before your mother returns
from the US.
Dad.
Let's talk in the study.
What a moron.
Did you kill Lim Hwa Young?
Answer me.
Do you even want to listen
to my answer?
You know,
this is why I don't like you.
You want...
to look into people's minds.
It's nerve-wracking and unpleasant.
You were just like that
when you were 15.
Instead of answering me
whether you killed it or not,
you just looked at me
with those eyes.
Are you talking about that day?
Do you know how you looked at me...
when I was 15?
You only asked
if I killed it or not.
That was all you cared about.
Keep your distance from Jong Woo.
I'm not leaving Korea.
But instead, I'll live quietly...
where you won't see me.
Don't worry.
Thank you...
for raising me.
I don't quite remember it,
but...
there might have been...
happy moments I had in this house.
He looks just like him.
He doesn't look like
he's going on a trip.
Is he running away?
Hello?
Is this Detective Ju In Do?
Yes, who is this?
I'm Lim Hwa Young's neighbor
in Pureun studio apartment.
You gave me your number.
You told me to call you
if I remembered anything.
You were the lady who was in pain
because of your dimple surgery.
Is there anything...
that came into your mind?
Now that I think of it,
- it was around 1 a.m.
- I see.
At first, I thought
he got the wrong house.
I didn't see his face.
I only saw his hand.
Who is it?
I thought a crazy person followed
and pulled a prank on me.
Now that I think of it,
it was frightening.
- If Hwa Young died after that,
- What is that?
I think he might be the murderer.
What a lunatic.
He wore baby socks on his fingers
and forecasted a murder.
This is an insane psycho.
I thought she was making up stories
to seduce men,
but she kept talking nonsense.
Oh, my goodness.
It was about killing
her month-old child with a pillow.
The little one tried to survive...
and couldn't be killed
in one strike. It's just terrible.
Prosecutor?
That's the reason why
Chun Jong Bum visited Lim Hwa Young.
What is it?
- Baby socks.
- Pardon? Why?
(Chief Prosecutor Chun Seok Tae)
You've never called me at this hour.
- What's going on?
- Remove Chun Jong Bum...
from the list of suspects.
My son was with me...
on the day of the murder.
Do you want to see the reporters
rip me into pieces?
Is that what you want?
I apologize.
Su Hyuk, you said
you were one of my people.
Yes, sir.
- Su Hyuk.
- I'm listening.
I know your temper,
but don't take this personally.
Don't even take an interest
in my son.
Attacking my son is like
tugging on my weakness.
Do what you're good at.
Let's cover this up with that one.
Make a suspect for this case
and put him inside.
Isn't that possible?
I understand, sir.
I liked you the first time
I saw you...
because of your cold composure.
You were logical
when you beat people up.
You didn't even flinch
when a beautiful lady went to you.
Even when millions of dollars were
brought to you,
you spat at the money that was
unnecessary to your big picture...
I know you're a cruel but hot man.
I am in your big picture,
aren't I?
Then don't destroy
your big picture...
because of some petty emotions.
Petty emotions?
Lim Hwa Young.
Baby socks.
The baby's mother killed...
her baby and threw it away.
Chun Jong Bum.
He lived with a corpse...
for three days.
A cross.
A signature mark...
by Gong Ji Chul.
(March 10, 2020, Lim Hwa Young)
Don't destroy your big picture...
because of some petty emotions.
(Suspect Information, Chun Eun Woo)
(Episode 10)
You always stroke my head
from behind me.
- Is it a fetish?
- It's a habit.
- Get in the back, Prosecutor Kim.
- Why don't you sit in the back?
I can't trust someone to drive
the car.
Didn't your car get smashed
beyond repair?
- You can use Sang Ah's car for now.
- It's okay, Mother.
Sang Ah's recital is soon, so I want
to have her in the practice room.
Could you just escort her
after her practice is over?
There's someone I need to meet.
Is something on your mind?
You always go free diving
when there's something on your mind.
It's nothing. Don't worry.
By the way, I'm going to adopt
a cat.
Shall I get a Russian Blue or
a Chinchilla cat?
Choose one that you like less.
You throw away things you love
too much.
I turned it off because I don't want
to be interrupted.
It's been a while since we've seen
each other.
I don't want to be interrupted.
Did you just push me away?
We could get into an accident.
I could even die
if you only looked at me.
I don't want to die
in a car accident.
And someone like you got into
such an accident?
You were injured, trying to save
that woman.
That woman?
I heard it from the doctor
at the hospital.
She's a researcher at NFS.
I guess...
that researcher must be precious
to you?
So precious that you'd risk
your life.
(Jung Sa Bin, NFS)
Is he completely ignoring me?
He's such a formalin.
Hello, prisoner number 37321.
Mr. death-row convict...
has never gone on a date before?
His heart is pounding like crazy.
This is not a game of puzzle.
It's impossible to restore without
the cheekbone and nasal bone.
And even though I'm a professional
at engineering this,
what do you expect me to do
when the eyes and nose are accurate?
I'm not a creator who makes people
out of clay.
We don't have bone fragments...
but I brought a special DNA of his.
These genes account for less than
one percent of genes in Korea.
His father has the typical genes
of a Korean.
But I found the genes of a Siberian
on his mitochondria.
I guess someone in his mother's side
would've been a Russian.
- Try making his nose bigger.
- Okay.
Bigger or higher?
- Higher.
- Right.
That's enough.
- All right.
- Make the eyes a bit deeper.
- Deeper.
- Right.
Make his skin look like a Russian.
- Make the skin as white as snow?
- That's right.
Got that.
This...
looks pretty familiar.
I sent the notes of identification,
to Prosecutor Kim.
Will you send this report file
to Prosecutor Kim?
How did you send him the notes
of identification?
Are you really going to give
false testimony at the trial?
I'll tell you this.
Three years ago, I saw
the same thing as Prosecutor Kim...
and had the same feeling.
If this skull could be used
to save someone,
I'm more than willing to testify
in Prosecutor Kim's will.
Well, what is it you saw
three years ago?
Am I the only one missing out here?
Do you understand what she's saying?
I'm not sure.
But if it's finding the family
of the remains that you want,
you'll have many ways to do that.
An online group?
First, join the group.
Okay.
For 30 years,
this man has read
"Wuthering Heights."
Results from the restoration
of his remains suggest...
his face is...
similar to this image.
If the bereaved family
of this man in his twenties...
who went missing between 1985
and 1987...
is out there,
please call me at this number.
Unusual features.
He'd been keeping a wedding ring.
At the time he went missing
in 1987,
he seemed to have purchased
a book titled...
"Wuthering Heights"...
at an old bookstore called
"Old Future."
At the burial site of the body,
the book was found with him.
Please give me a call.
My number is 010-3109-313.
A cafe for the bereaved family
of the missing?
It doesn't say it's the remains
of the mummy from Donggang River.
But the fact that a wedding ring was
found with the body, along with...
"Wuthering Heights" shows this is
the mummy from Donggang River.
There are related news articles
being posted on the internet,
so the comments that report
about it are unbelievable.
Who's the person that posted
the face of the mummy on the cafe?
You can find out by giving a call.
Here's the number.
(Give me a call. 010-3109-313)
Is Jung Sa Bin there now?
Sa Bin said she'll be at her lab
at the University until late today.
What is it, Prosecutor?
Forma... I mean...
Prosecutor Kim. What brings
you here?
We need to talk.
- What is it about?
- Didn't you say you'll send...
the results of
the facial restoration to me first?
- Oh.
- Oh?
Didn't I tell you Byun Sung Hoon
will be out again without the skull?
Is that what you want?
Do you want to see Byun Sung Hoon
kill a person before your eyes?
It's the professor.
What's happened?
Who's the guy?
Why are you taking this so far?
And why are you taking this so far,
Prosecutor?
Byun Sung Hoon can get
the punishment he deserves.
Why do you want to fabricate a skull
he did not kill?
Let me explain it to you
in infantile terms.
It's because a criminal does not get
the punishment he deserves.
He'd commit the same crime again
after being released.
Had those jerks been locked up
in jail in the first place,
there will be no reason for us
to bring out or fabricate the skull.
- Do you understand now?
- What if he has a change of heart?
What if he doesn't commit
the same crime again?
What if he could live
a different life?
Get in the car first.
Hello, Prosecutor Kim Su Hyuk.
I'm glad you remember my name.
But I don't have time to
chat with you.
When did you two meet?
I guess he needs you to fabricate
some evidence.
Or...
do you have any personal
business with her?
There's nothing personal.
I do have personal business
with her.
So why don't you leave us?
Can you trust him?
You know he can kill someone with
the law by fabricating evidence...
in a murder case.
What did you say?
Hey, my book.
Whether it's official or personal,
I don't think Ms. Sa Bin...
will have anything to do with
a murder suspect like you.
A murder suspect?
Okay, let's talk somewhere else.
It's my business, I'll take care
of it. Don't worry.
Hey.
Take my advice
and don't get too close to him.
I'm a prosecutor. I only deal
with bad guys.
I can tell just from their eyes
where they've been,
whether they will stab someone in
the stomach or wear a location tag.
But do you know which kinds will
never be able to better themselves?
Psychopaths.
Here.
He's rotten up here.
Did you get that?
Why do you judge people and
give them a tag?
I met....
Jong Bum before you did.
So how much do you know about him?
Not much. But...
I will experience him myself.
Whether he's a good person
or a bad person...
I will decide that for myself.
Where do you live?
What?
I don't want to talk to someone
who will defend him. Get out.
Okay, I can't stand the smell
of formalin anyway.
You told me to get out.
I didn't say get out right here.
You have got to be kidding me.
Anger.
But it hurts.
You'll get into another accident
if you drive like this.
Stop thinking about other things
when you're driving.
Focus on the road.
I'll get off here.
I need to buy something here.
How old are you?
I'm 32. Why?
You don't seem to be the type
who listens to others.
I don't care if you want
to get yourself killed.
But what fault did the people
around you make?
It's my life.
Babe! I'm almost there.
You're here to pick me up?
Where would you be?
Mister, stop!
Why are you wandering around drunk
at times like this?
Wake up!
What? Wake up? Who are you
to tell me to wake up?
My dad said he can tell what was
in Ji Chul's eyes.
June 15th, 1988.
At the prison he was appointed in,
my dad met Ji Chul.
May 31st, 1988.
The day my mother
gave birth to me.
Five minutes before my dad heard
about my mom going to the hospital,
he picked the lottery of
Gong Ji Chul's executioner.
The executioner of Ji Chul...
Why did it have to be my dad?
Why?
Your father's symptoms
are getting worse.
He's been hearing things lately.
He seems to think that Gong Ji Chul
is still alive.
He's been hallucinating.
The Ji Chul in his hallucinations...
is coming for his daughter.
Dad.
Gong Ji Chul is dead.
You said you pressed the button.
He won't bother us. You nor me.
No.
He's...
coming.
He'll find you.
Dad!
Run.
You need to run away.
Please run away.
Execute.
One, two, three.
- One, two, three.
I pressed the button the fastest
out of the three guards.
Gong Ji Chul died by my hands.
He...
He just moved. He must be alive.
I know the first time can be hard.
It goes on for a few days after
you execute a prisoner.
The prosecutor told me...
that Jung Ha Eun,
that woman is still alive.
Can I see her just once?
What do you mean by resurrection?
No one can do that.
Why do you want to check so much?
I saw him move!
His looks were a waste in
the grave.
Why you... Hey!
- You have to run away!
- Dad.
It's fine.
You're fine.
You must run.
(Sincere Correction, Bright Future)
It's President Baek In Seo
behind Seo Tae Ha.
Are you the prosecutor
that uses harsh investigation...
during this age
of scientific investigation?
How unpleasant to hear.
You have illegal bonds collection,
extortion, assault,
drug smuggling,
and violation of the election law.
Are you trying to build your résumé?
How's life inside?
You look very comfortable.
Do you want to live there
for the rest of your life?
Finish with Byun Sung Hoon.
Then I'll get you out in five years.
Oh, no.
There's this old man I know,
and I'm going out next week.
You should talk with respect.
But thank you for your kindness,
Prosecutor Kim Su Hyuk.
What's the point of going outside?
I'll escort you back in.
You'll be in solitary confinement
from then on.
You won't have access to a phone,
layoff, and even special pardon.
I'll handle you myself.
I was not going to say this,
but have you heard
about the gangster who saved...
President Baek's life
multiple times?
President Baek must've sent
a New Year's gift to his son-in-law.
But he sent the wine back to me.
Here. Do you see it?
Geez. Even your handwriting looks
unlucky.
I still have a couple of cards
other than President Baek.
So you're planning to stick up
for Byun Sung Hoon?
Do you think I'm going to do that?
Your client, Oh Chang Soon, is...
accused as a second-time offender
of assault.
Do you want to see me making him
into a 13th-time offender?
I heard he had gout and arthritis
because of his old age.
Never mind.
I can just manipulate the remains
and make Oh Chang Soon...
the serial killer
instead of Byun Sung Hoon.
Do you know...
you have the blood of a killer
in your veins?
Worry about your own veins.
Sung Hoon.
This thread will go...
through your nostrils
and come out from your mouth.
You've done this.
This is a special service given
only for those who harass girls.
Swallow.
That's right.
Tell me all the seven spots...
you buried the corpses in.
If what you tell me today is wrong,
you'll suffer
the same thing tomorrow.
It was two today,
tomorrow it will be four.
If what you say tomorrow is wrong,
you'll get eight
the day after tomorrow.
Why are you doing this to me?
It's because I've got something
I want to protect too.
It'll double every day
until the day I get out.
Why aren't you answering?
You have no one in this jail.
Don't forget I hired your lawyer.
I'll tell you everything.
Please save me, Mom.
- Take it down.
- Yes.
I'm scared. Please help me, Mom.
Say it.
Let's move the remains.
Geez.
We've dug for half a day, and yet
we still haven't got anything.
We got it until the sixth one.
Byun Sung Hoon is playing us.
We still have one spot.
Let's move.
What's going on?
Byun Sung Hoon might've thrown
a corpse in this chapel.
What do you mean by that?
That's impossible. This is a church.
Father, a person has died.
Go up and look for it.
Prosecutor.
Byun Sung Hoon cuts his corpse
into pieces and throws them away.
He wouldn't have buried it here
when people are passing by.
We don't know that.
- Over here.
- Let's go.
Here!
- Yes.
- Start digging here.
(Born Again)
Do you think I killed that baby?
Why did you press on the bell
of Lim Hwa Young's neighbor?
Is Gong Ji Chul alive?
Before that,
I think I'm going to find you.
Gong Ji Chul didn't kill
the one he loved.
I wonder who it is
that you want to kill right now.
Don't come any closer.
Why do you get mad at me
and get worried afterward?
The ill fate of the previous lives
will meet to untie their knots.
I sometimes get confused
when I see you, Prosecutor Kim.