A person is hurt.
Please come quickly.
He's bleeding.
A person is dying.
I...
I started seeing his blood...
from that moment.
I've felt this since we got
the remains from Donggang River,
didn't we meet somewhere
in the past?
At 09:33 a.m. last Monday.
I saw you being held a hostage.
- At Mapo-gu.
- Me? At Mapo-gu?
I was negotiating with the attacker,
not being held hostage.
You were almost going to die.
Almost...
Well,
so you passed by me
even after seeing that, Prosecutor?
I was busy then.
I'm busy today too.
I see you're busy. But we should
introduce each other.
I am Jung Sa Bin,
Prosecutor Kim Su Hyuk.
I'll remember that, Ms. Jung Sa Bin.
That formalin.
That way. Wear a gown
and sterilize your hands.
The autopsy room is inside here.
I'll be waiting.
Okay.
- Who is that guy?
- My heart skipped a beat.
- I'm asking you. Who is he?
- What are you doing?
He's my student from school.
He's here for a training session.
A student?
It's the mummy that has been
skeletonized in a single day.
I wonder how he looked
when he was alive.
He is handsome,
in terms of phrenology.
He has a small face
and is about 184 cm tall.
He has wide shoulders,
just like a swimmer.
I don't know how his eyes, nose,
and lips would look like though.
Do you want to hear the story
behind him?
- Mr. John Doe...
- Mr. John Doe?
I decided to call him that.
Mr. John Doe passed away on his way
to the wedding hall...
carrying a ring for his bride.
(Mummy from Donggang River)
Are you all right?
Yes.
Professor, isn't today's autopsy
confidential?
I invited him over.
Since the mummy from Donggang is
an unprecedented case, medically.
The case has not been closed
for the remains.
Do you think it makes sense
to give public access?
Trainees can observe the autopsy
three times.
I'll call you next time. Sorry.
Is it okay if I see it from there?
- Please leave now.
- I will.
We'll say this is the woman murdered
by Byun Sung Hoon ten years ago.
Let's save the stab wounds
in the abdomen and chest,
but let's say the shattered
skulls are impossible to restore.
Sorry? What do you mean by that?
It's an unidentified body.
We should make use of that.
We need to maximize Sung Hoon's
crimes to put him in for life.
You will testify at his trial,
won't you, Professor Yoo?
- Pardon?
- That won't happen.
The purpose of our team is to do
a 3D restoration and identify them.
The family of this body still thinks
he is missing.
I thought we were on the same team,
Professor Yoo?
- Well...
- Are you trying to forge a record?
This is an insult to the body.
Do you want to go to jail
for damaging the remains?
Go to jail?
Why do you think Mr. John Doe met me
after his death?
It's to resolve an unfair incident.
He wants us to take him
to his loved ones.
Mr. John Doe or not,
his family would've given up on him
after 30 years.
Professor Yoo.
Get a confidential agreement
from this woman.
I'm a medical examiner,
not some woman.
Please keep Ms. Jung Sa Bin quiet.
I said it's a medical examiner.
Well, we'll see how it goes.
Mr. Kim Su Hyuk.
Send the facial restoration to me
only, and prepare for the testimony.
I'll be going now.
I guess you don't care
what I'm telling you.
I'm fine with that.
Give me back the book and ring
that belongs to Mr. John Doe.
It's his keepsake.
You should read that this time.
Goodness.
("Wuthering Heights")
Even the publication year has faded.
What's this?
It looks like a seal.
Is it from a bookstore?
If everything in this world
disappeared but you,
I'm going to keep on living.
Whatever our souls are made of,
your soul is the same as mine.
You are like me, more than I am.
- What are you doing?
- That's what I wanted to ask you.
Geez.
You threw this book away to me.
Here, I'll give it back.
You're so fickle.
Your mind changes every minute.
Give me that fountain pen too.
It's mine.
Let me give you a piece of advice.
Just pass by when you witness
a murder from now on.
You might be the one to get killed.
What a way to be concerned about me.
Why that...
Why is my heart beating over
that formalin guy?
Gosh, that startled me.
I'm sorry to have kept you waiting.
Where are you now?
I'm in front of the autopsy room.
I think I left my fountain pen
there.
Could you bring it over?
Why is everyone looking for
a fountain pen today?
Fountain pen...
Where could it be?
Here it is.
We'll say this is the woman murdered
by Byun Sung Hoon ten years ago.
Let's save the stab wounds
in the abdomen and chest,
but let's say the shattered
skulls are impossible to restore.
Sorry? What do you mean by that?
It's an unidentified body.
We should make use of that.
We need to maximize Sung Hoon's
crimes to put him in for life.
You will testify at his trial,
won't you, Professor Yoo?
(Pureun studio apartment errands)
(Pureun studio apartment)
Hello.
I sent you the money.
Thank you, always.
The ice hasn't melted at all.
Good job.
Cutie, wait.
Do you want to have a drink with me?
I'll give you your
three month's pay.
I get married in three weeks...
and I want my bachelorette party
with you.
I'll choose the place.
And only two hours from where we at.
Okay. Wait here.
I'm sorry, I know you're busy.
You don't have to be
so formal, ma'am.
I'll do that...
after you and Sang Ah are married.
I'm sure we still have more
to hide from each other.
- I'll have a flat white.
- Yes, ma'am.
(Secrets of a murderer)
Is the second edition already out?
But do people really need to know
the secrets of a murderer?
I don't think they were born
as a murderer.
A cobra isn't raised to be one.
It's born to be one.
If you don't tame it before
it raises its head...
it will spray poison on you.
Did you know...
that Gong Ji Chul is the person
in the book?
- Gong Ji Chul?
- Stop playing ignorant.
I know Chief prosecutor Chun
Seok Tae despises Gong Ji Chul.
You're close to him, aren't you?
I guess he's your target
for the day again.
I was always curious about
your relationship with him.
So?
What do you think it is?
I'll wait until you tell me.
Did you know?
Chief prosecutor Chun has...
a troublesome son.
- So what?
- Isn't it ironic?
Who would've thought that the son
of Chief prosecutor Chun,
who hung so many criminals
on the noose, was a young offender?
What a twist.
His wife got pregnant...
from a donated sperm
since she thought he was infertile.
I guess she picked the wrong seed.
Ma'am.
I'm sure you give me
all this information...
because you want me to do something.
But please don't try to control me.
I'm not easy and I'm also rude.
I don't play in
someone else's field.
I know...
that you play around with warrants.
But Su Hyuk...
you hate people who are ill here.
Chief prosecutor Chun's son is...
exactly that.
The kind of people
you hate the most.
I saw him when he was young.
I think his name was...
Why, of course.
Chief prosecutor Chun would've given
his son a new identity already.
A girl from Somang Alternative
School went missing for 40 days.
The perpetrator was Kim Jung Hoon,
18 years old.
He incarcerated a girl, gang-raped
her then burned her to death.
Onjin Elementary School
mutilation murder case.
The perpetrator was
Um Yoon Hee, 12 years old.
A game addict.
She kidnapped a kid with
accomplices then killed the kid.
A violence case against peers...
Digital sexual violence...
A murder of a female middle school
student, and abandoning the body.
Chun Eun Woo, 15 years old.
He pushed a girl to death, then
abandoned her body in the building.
He spent three days with
the dead body.
(Suspect information, Chun Eun Woo)
Why does he look familiar?
You need to empty all the bottles
in this restaurant today.
Otherwise, you won't be paid.
You really want the money,
don't you?
With your looks,
you can earn ten million dollars
just by sitting in this place.
Money...
I'm doing this because I like it.
Why do you like doing errands?
No one pays attention to me.
You're a weirdo.
Could you...
listen to my story for today?
- That's why I'm here.
- Sorry?
This is all you'll be drinking.
Go on. Tell me.
You really know how to make
a woman want to be drunk.
Chun Eun Woo, a kid with
the memories of murder.
(Suspect information, Chun Eun Woo)
(Prosecution Service)
What did you call me for, sir?
There was a murder case...
in Pureun Studio Apartment
at dawn today.
You should take that case,
Su Hyuk.
I'm working
on the Byun Sung Hoon case.
There's a murderer who is
on a different level from him.
He died 30 years ago...
because I hung him
on the gallows.
But...
his copycat has popped out.
Are you talking
about Gong Ji Chul?
I'll handle...
the rumors in the Prosecution Office
about the fake remains...
on Byun Sung Hoon.
Take the Pureun Studio Apartment
case instead.
I'll pair you up...
with a detective
who knew Gong Ji Chul.
(Do Not Enter)
He writes the victim's name and
date of death on a yellow umbrella.
That's the mark of Gong Ji Chul.
Geez.
You shouldn’t touch the crime scene
like that.
I saw this once in an on-the-spot
investigation 32 years ago.
It's just like him
from 32 years ago.
He killed people this way too.
Detective Cha Hyung Bin?
Aren't you Detective Cha?
- This can't be.
- Geez.
You're not a doppelganger.
How can you look just like him?
Were you drinking before coming
to the on-site inspection?
Do you take preservatives?
Are you a vampire
or were you frozen?
Detective Cha!
I'm Detective Kim Su Hyuk.
Kim Su Hyuk...
How can this be?
Even your voice is the same.
Start with the legwork on the
neighborhood including security.
He walks out alone
just like Detective Cha did.
The time of the murder is
around one at dawn today.
There's a scar on the neck.
It's a tattoo
to hide a surgical scar.
I think it might be
a thyroid surgery.
A surgical scar.
You were here.
The victim was said
to have worked in a hostess bar.
Her fellow worker next door said...
a medical school student
who was working errands...
came here quite often.
If it's a part-time errand boy,
his phone can be tracked.
Let's check the CCTV
of the maintenance office.
He's leaving on his own again.
It's an old studio apartment.
Maintenance is weak,
so the CCTV is only found
in the parking lot...
and the elevator only.
Anyone can enter without a pass.
So you mean...
though there are three people
in the elevator during the incident,
we cannot know for sure
how many people really entered...
aside from them?
I guess you can say that.
Have you seen the errand boy
who visited room 1808?
He must've come every day.
I know him very well.
I think he also came last night.
What time was it?
It was around one
in the morning.
It's the time
my granddaughter calls...
on her way home from the library.
Hello, there.
Be careful on your way home.
Sure.
- Do you remember his face?
- Of course.
He was very handsome
like a celebrity.
I remember him. He was good-looking.
He was quite tall too.
I'll find the face of my mummy.
O dry bones, listen to me.
Let's see the face.
I will attach tendons to you
and make flesh come upon you...
and cover you with skin.
I will put breath in you,
and you will come to life.
Even bones as small as dust are...
recognized by the program
and magnified with a digital method.
Let's take a look.
Here are the cheekbones
and the contour of the jawline.
- Should I sharpen the jaws?
- Yes, go ahead.
Could these eyes be the one?
Did he have double eyelids?
I got it. This is the one.
Oh, my goodness.
Was he a celebrity?
There isn't any handsome celebrity
in his 20s who went missing...
in the 1980s.
Do it again.
That's what I'm trying to say.
Is this even possible?
There are only 53 pieces of bones.
You can finish the symmetry...
with only half of the face.
More than half of the 53 pieces
are on the left side.
Let's try it again, okay?
Go find some more bones.
I'm not doing this before that.
And please, let me sleep.
Geez.
Don't you see the red light?
- The red light?
- This traffic light hasn't...
been showing the green light
for three months now.
You're a medical school professor.
You're not color-blind, are you?
I can't see only red.
I can't see blood nor organs,
so I'm destined to love bones only.
It's off now.
I have something to ask.
What is it?
If a body rots below the ground,
does the color of the soil change?
Pardon?
You go to excavation sites a lot.
I was curious.
I see.
When a body rots in the soil,
the soil does turn darker
than others.
For remains of the massacre
from bullets or cartridges,
the soil turns yellowish-brown.
Why do you ask?
What about the clothing?
Doesn't the clothing rot
when buried under the ground?
For example, silk.
If it's a basic soil,
silk will rot easily.
If it's acidic,
cotton will rot more easily.
Why?
I was curious.
I almost forgot.
When does the exhibition with
the Andong remains I delivered?
We're making preparations for it
tonight. Do you want an invitation?
You look like you need help.
I'll get there by myself.
See you during the lecture.
That's definitely an acidic soil
from the hills.
What am I thinking?
I'm Detective Joo, who called you.
Prosecutor.
Lim Hwa Young is said to have come
here all the time.
She remembers vividly
seeing her...
on the day of Lim Hwa Young's death.
Do you remember the man
who'd accompanied Lim Hwa Young?
I remember because the woman said
such odd things that day.
I remember the guy's face too.
But the woman was crying.
At first, I thought that a handsome
man was giving her a hard time.
She was crying?
- Ma'am.
- Yes.
- Could you give us soju?
- I'll be right there.
- Here.
- Okay.
It...
cried too much...
so I took it to the hospital.
The doctor said it was
biliary something.
What was it he said?
It cries all day long.
It wasn't like a human being,
but an object.
An object that shrieks loudly.
I just wish...
I didn't have that thing.
I'd be so much better off.
Biliary obstruction?
I don't know.
Maybe that's it.
I really don't know.
Why don't we...
just drink?
Cheers.
Is that why you killed him?
How did you kill him?
But...
I dressed him
in such good clothes...
when I let him go.
It was an expensive silk cloth.
In his next life,
I hope he won't have...
a wench like me as his mother.
I don't know if she made that up
to seduce the guy.
She was talking such nonsense.
Did they leave together?
- What was the time?
- Let me think.
It was around midnight.
Oh, I remember.
He took her out
when she was completely drunk.
I thought they were going
to a motel.
But he grabbed a cab for her.
We got the cellphone information
for Lim Hwa Young, Prosecutor.
I looked through
all her recent calls.
A man's phone number was
registered in a service app.
The numbers are 010 8960...
I called the number to ask
for a service.
- Who was it?
- You should check for yourself.
Namgung Ju Hye asked me
to give this to you.
Oh, thank you.
That'll be 50 dollars.
The guy at the autopsy room?
This flower means eternal love.
I bought it because it goes well
with the exhibition.
Jung Sa Bin?
Track the phone number
of the errand guy.
I'll check with the mobile operator.
It's not KR or LC.
It's SKP Telecommunication.
There's a record of registering
in May 2015.
His name is Chun Jong Bum.
Born on February 14, 1998.
Chun Jong Bum.
Are there any suspects
other than Chun Jong Bum?
The security at the victim's
studio apartment is poor,
so we'll searching now to see...
whether there were other suspects.
But Chun Jong Bum is
the most likely at the moment.
Track everything he did on the day
of the incident.
When you see the remains
for the first time,
I stare at it
just like you're doing.
I do that until I can picture
his face as a living man.
- Do you see it then?
- Sorry?
You said you can picture him
as a living man...
- when you see the remains.
- Of course, I can.
My friend is a talented graphic
designer who restores the remains.
I'm excited when a face is restored
on the dry bones like a flower.
Even if you restore it,
what meaning does finding out
the face...
of a dead person has?
You are meeting with someone's life.
Even if we live in different times,
when we face each other like this,
we can feel a connection.
What's written on it?
It's an ardent lover letter
of a wife...
to her husband, leaving this life.
I’m guessing she was a commoner
as it was written in Hangeul.
The name is...
Yeon Yi's mother.
It says that there were shoes
made from her hair at the grave.
What does it say?
Do you want to know?
- "Look here."
- Look here?
It's how they called each other
back in their times.
"Look here."
"Do others care and
love each other..."
"just as we do?"
"Didn't you say that we'd die
together after living together..."
"until our hairs turn white?"
"All you do is be over there..."
"but would you truly understand
how sad I feel?"
"Read this letter carefully,
show up in my dreams nicely,"
"and do everything you wished."
"Look here."
"I believe..."
"I'll see you in my dreams."
"Please sneak up on me
in my dreams tonight."
"I..."
"still have..."
"so much left to tell you.'
I have a disease where I cry
every time I hear the dead’s' tales.
I'll wrap up here. You should
go home too.
Oh, yes. I should.
Chun Jong Bum.
From March 9th to the 10th...
from 10 p.m. to 2 a.m.
Where were you?
Tell me where you were
during that time...
and give me contacts of those
who can prove your alibi.
I get that you're a prosecutor...
but at least tell me your name
before you start questioning me.
I'm investigating the Pureun
Studio Apartment murder case.
Lim Hwa Young.
You know her well, don't you?
Lim Hwa Young is the victim?
Why do you all react the same way?
I have a witness who saw you
going into her studio apartment.
I said goodbye to her around
midnight and went straight home.
Do errand boys have a drink with
the customers these days?
That was the errand for that day.
I wouldn't think you need the money
that badly.
Should I guess...
your true motive?
You're laughing?
A person just died, yet
you can crack laughter?
Hey!
You're Chun Eun Woo.
Aren't you?
You do so much using your
title as a prosecutor.
You must be busy.
Where did you find the time
to investigate me?
You should learn how to...
answer yes or no to questions.
I'm not the type to learn so easily.
What did it feel like to spend three
days with a corpse?
Gosh, you glaring me is terrifying.
It's just personal curiosity.
Why don't you give it a try?
You're a prosecutor after all.
There are tons of bodies in
the autopsy room.
Thanks for the advice.
I don't know if I'll feel
the same way as you though.
It's me, Sung Hoon.
Can we meet tomorrow afternoon?
Darn it.
(Seoul Seobu Police Station)
I'm sorry.
I couldn't sleep well.
Oh, did you?
You should talk to my lawyer
from now on.
He's a famous human right
activist and lawyer.
You don't know him?
There is only one body
that's assumed...
to be killed by my client right now.
It was an accidental murder too.
We have him buying the murder weapon
on camera and it's accidental?
My client...
bought that to fix his house.
Anyway,
I heard that you came up
with a scenario...
where my client killed seven people.
Wasn't the body from 30 years ago...
also fabricated by you?
My client told me...
that the body was buried
with a book.
Then you blamed it on my client.
Isn't this a classic case
of legal tyranny?
Do you have proof?
Bring me the body!
If I'm the murderer...
where's the body?
The body!
Do you understand?
Have you gone deaf?
It's a personal curiosity...
but your cat tattoo on your arm,
- who is it for?
- What?
A cat?
You only killed women taller
than you, isn't that right?
Then again... Most women
would be taller than you.
You scumbag.
I feel like you would have been
beaten around by women.
I used to know a guy back in school.
He was a big boy...
but he cried when the girls hit him.
He even gave them money.
But that guy went home...
and beat his dog and his sister.
Oh.
Is that why you started
murdering people?
Because a girl beat you?
Why you son of...
Find out who's paying for
Sung Hoon's lawyer fees.
I'll scare him a little.
It will push him to continue on.
Kim Su Hyuk.
He'll hurt himself even more
if he continues.
Really? How will you do it?
Are you going to cut him?
Or pull him out?
Or slash him?
Did you really kill seven people?
My mom always told me...
that I should become the first place
and it didn't matter in which field.
So I decided...
to win against Gong Ji Chul.
Crazy freak.
Why can't I see even one letter?
Not one single letter.
Geez.
This is a digital restoration method
that allows you...
to shoot various lights
on the records to make...
the volatile
and discolored records readable.
If it's a 30-year-old record,
the print may not come out,
but the ink would show up.
Wait. What is that?
I don't know. It looks like a seal.
I think we can find the identity
of the Donggang Mummy remains.
We found crucial evidence.
- Crucial evidence?
- You'll see if you come with me.
Where are you?
- Get in.
- All right.
Fasten your seat belt.
This is a seal of the bookstore
from the Donggang Mummy's book.
I looked up "Old Future."
There are only three places...
in Sillim-dong, Anam-dong,
and Cheonggyecheon.
You're not giving up, are you?
All right.
Did the Donggang Mummy live?
He died 30 years ago.
Do you want to hurt the living
because of the dead?
This is about the living murderer,
Byun Sung Hoon.
He's going to kill another person
if he comes out to the world.
I'm not interested in anything else.
I'm only interested in the remains
that I'm studying.
So...
do you think you can find
the real criminal...
if you find the identity
of the old mummy?
So the criminal would apologize?
Listen.
Have you ever lost someone you love?
I just want to keep the promise
I made to the mummy.
I am going to let his bride
wear the ring...
that he didn't give
up until he died.
Fine. Let's do it our own way then.
It was Byun Sung Hoon
who killed that mummy.
I'm going to say
Byun Sung Hoon killed...
all the future remains
that will be discovered.
I'm sorry, Please pull over.
I want to get off here.
Hey!
Wake up, Prosecutor Kim.
Don't die. Wake up.
Please wake up.
A person is hurt.
Please come quickly.
Where is this place?
A person is dying.
He's bleeding too much.
Blood...
I started seeing his blood...
from that moment.
If everything else disappeared
and only you were left in the world,
I'd still keep on living.
Whatever our souls are made of,
your soul is the same as mine.
It's on page 73.
You keep buying the same book.
(Wuthering Heights)
I'm going to propose
with these lines...
to ask her to be my bride.
So this is how he looks like...
with his eyes, nose, and lips.
This man doesn't know
I fell for him at first sight.
"Look here."
"Do others care and
love each other just as we do?"
"Didn't you say that we'd die
together after living together..."
"until our hairs turn white?"
"All you do is be over there..."
"but would you truly understand
how sad I feel?"
"Read this letter carefully,
show up in my dreams nicely,"
"and do everything you wished."
"Look here."
"I believe I'll see you
in my dreams."
"Please sneak up on me
in my dreams tonight."
"I still have so much left..."
"to tell you."
(Born Again)
Was it Kim Su Hyuk
instead of the girl?
Most get serious injuries
or even death.
He won't be abandoned
ever again.
A long time ago,
this is where a genius painter
I served had stayed.
He was young, but he's scary.
Prosecutor Kim almost died.
He almost died trying to save me.
He must've been special to you.
He said he could recognize
Gong Ji Chul's eyes.
He's coming.
Gong Ji Chul is dead.
Do you know a murderer's blood is
flowing through your veins?