(Episode 3)
Oh, no.
There's no telephone booth here.
(Love Salon)
There are guys like that.
Just looking at them makes you want
to bully them.
That's what I felt for Sung Ho.
He had the same look as you.
He called me Mom even
as he was bleeding.
Mom?
It's nothing, really.
But watching him beg made me
not want to be one.
Isn't this what happened to you?
You look like you've begged
growing up.
Why does it have to be me?
Kill your own mother, you punk!
Help!
Help me!
Somebody help me!
Go...
and beg Sung Ho to forgive you.
You will end up killing someone.
You can't stop it once
you've started it.
It's not bad...
to be hurt.
The person who hurt you...
is the bad one.
Brain death is different
from cardiac death.
The brain may be dead
but the heart may still be beating.
The brain may be dead...
Brain death.
Spontaneous respiration is
impossible...
and having two fixed dilated pupils.
A coma status that is...
unresponsive to external stimuli.
It is beating.
This is Love Salon.
Someone got hurt.
I think I heard a sound from here.
(Episode 2, Bad karma)
This is the police.
There's been a murder.
Hello?
I...
just saw his face.
Where are you at, ma'am?
Help me.
Doctor!
She fell asleep, Doctor.
It's been ten minutes
since she's been like this.
Around 15 minutes from now.
Please save her.
Come with me.
Stop RSC. Scalpel.
Hyung Bin.
This is Ha Eun.
I am outside now. If you want
to reach me...
- Hello?
- Is this Ha Eun's?
I'm calling from St. Peter's
hospital.
Did something happen to Ha Eun?
I can tell from your voice
that you are her guardian.
Ha Eun was rushed to
the emergency room just now.
(Restricted Area. Emergency Center)
Ha Eun!
Where were you? I couldn't find you
in the bookstore nor your house.
I'm alive, Hyung Bin.
I'm alive.
You held my hand
and didn't let me go.
You held so tightly that
the death messenger let me go.
He said he'll let me go to you.
Your hand?
- I did?
- You were holding my hand...
just until now.
Hyung Bin, I'm so surprised.
I'm weirdly okay now. Here, watch.
I don't feel nauseated
by the smell of the hospital.
I can't smell the formalin
of the corpse now.
It was the first time in my life.
I ran for 50 or 70 meters.
I was able to run
that distance today.
Yet I'm still alive,
just like a miracle.
You had to run?
Why did you have to run?
- Sorry?
- What made you run?
- Well...
- Tell me.
Reporting yellow umbrella serial
murder case. Over and out.
The name of the salon is
"Love Salon."
I got you. Over and out.
Listen to me, Ha Eun.
You can't act on your own from now.
Got it?
Wait for me in the hospital.
Don't go anywhere until I get here.
- I have to tell you...
- Please listen to me.
Will you take me
to the police station, Hyung Bin?
- To the police station?
- Yes.
I'll wait for you there.
That's okay, right?
- Thank you, Doctor.
- Sure.
Who was the man
who brought Ms. Jung...
to the emergency center?
- A man?
- He brought her...
in his arms with blood all over him.
What does he look like?
I've seen him before.
He's a guardian for a patient
in the intensive care unit.
So I've met him over a consultation.
He has a scar over his left eye.
Do you know his name?
It was written Gong Ji Chul
in the chart.
I'll leave you now.
You were holding my hand
just until now.
(Old Future)
He's after Ha Eun.
(Love Salon)
What happened?
December 14th, 1987, Yoon Jeong Hee.
She's the 11th victim.
Don't you think it could be
a copycat crime this time?
The killer has only used a knife
until the 10th murder.
He never used a club to hit
someone on the head.
If it was imitated, he would have
used a knife too.
What's going on?
That pen...
My daughter also has it!
- Oh, no.
- What's going on?
Oh, my goodness.
- This pen?
- Yes.
Buyeon Elementary School.
It's a commemorative pen
for its establishment.
It has a needle on the other end.
Could this be a clue?
Where is it located?
That school closed down
four years ago.
In Do, go check on Ha Eun
at the police station.
He's going alone again.
One.
Two.
Three.
Four, five, six,
seven, eight, nine,
and ten.
One killed and the other
gave them a funeral.
No.
One killed...
and the other painted a picture.
(Criminal Affairs Division)
The pain from the wound the woman
you loved gave...
can't even compare to the pain...
of having your eye pierced.
Then would your murderous instincts
leave that woman alone?
I'm different from you.
I don't care if she doesn't love me.
I will complete...
my love in my own way.
My first prophecy came true...
but you don't think
the next one will?
If you want to protect that woman...
don't drag her into your destiny.
I will never...
let her die.
I will...
save her no matter what.
save her.
(Keeping law and order.
Making a just world.)
The face of a murder you saw...
Was it this man?
Detective Cha!
Ha Eun saw the serial killer murder
the owner of the salon.
We finally have an eye witness.
I can't believe Ha Eun saw it.
- Go home.
- Detective Cha.
Hyung Bin, why are you doing this?
There are no eyewitnesses...
and Ha Eun didn't see anything.
Hyung Bin.
Ha Eun, look at me.
I'm no longer a policeman
protecting the public.
I'm only going to protect you.
That's all I will do.
If it means protecting you, I'm not
only going to hand in resignation,
but I can kill.
Is that something a detective
should say?
He's after you.
He?
Someone who's killed 11 women
is right by you.
- Did you know?
- What are you talking about?
Go home. I'll take you there.
You can't be alone
for a single moment now.
You know how to use this, right?
Contact me with this from now on.
Keep it on 24 hours.
- Got it?
- Copy that. Over and out.
- You can go now.
- Get in. I'm going to stand guard.
I can't go to sleep
with you outside now, can I?
Get inside already.
Copy that. Over and out.
Hurry and lock your windows.
Use this time to listen to it
and get some practice.
You say it's your favorite, but
you keep getting the notes wrong.
Here.
(Old Future)
(Dial 112 for criminal report
and 113 for a spy)
I can't believe him.
Where are you? Reply. Over and out.
I'm going to the bathhouse. I need
to clean myself. Over and out.
I won't be able to contact you
for an hour.
Gong Ji Chul.
What's going on?
What's happening?
Is he a spy?
- He's the police.
- He has a gun.
I will fire if you move.
Gong Ji Chul, you're under arrest
for the murder of ten women.
You murderer.
Get up.
All right, let's go.
- Oh, my goodness.
- What a scary world we live in.
Look at him.
Gong Ji Chul.
Hurry up.
What is this?
Are you here to read books?
It's not bad to be hurt.
The person who hurt you is...
the bad one.
In your next life,
I hope you're born in a place
where no one would hurt you.
You murderer!
Detective Cha is protecting
the witness right now.
Do you think he's the real criminal?
Gong Ji Chul is...
in denial of all crimes
except the salon incident.
People have no interest
in real criminal.
They want a sinner.
- You deserve to die.
- Oh, my goodness.
Stop that.
But I think
the evidence is insufficient.
The evidence...
Tell Detective Cha to persuade
the witness.
I'll hang him in jail.
I know people like him.
He'll hurt himself
if he doesn't commit a murder.
The reason he wants to die is...
that he couldn't kill anyone.
She's going to die anyway
even if you don't kill her.
I can send her off comfortably
if you want.
Is this woman...
your 12th murder target?
You were a middle school drop-out.
You couldn't have learned to paint.
Who is your accomplice
who painted this?
Gong In Woo, whom you say is
the real criminal,
has been pronounced dead
15 years ago.
Nor he has never married,
he doesn't have a son.
Who painted "Reading Mary"?
I went to that book store...
a lot.
- The "Old Future."
- What?
I can hear the music box
from the entrance.
There's a photo...
of Ha Eun's family on the counter.
She likes tangerines,
which is why she drinks
tangerine tea.
Since when...
have you been following Ha Eun?
I don't know.
I haven't really been counting.
But...
I went to that book store...
even before you met Jung Ha Eun.
I probably know her better
than you do.
I know the way she laughs,
the way she gets mad,
and the way she closes her eye...
when she eats a sour tangerine.
I also know how she looks...
when she looks at the man
she loves.
"Wuthering Heights."
You don't even know
if her favorite sentence is...
on page 73 or 123.
You...
You only know how to ask her
to marry you when she's dying...
but I guess you still want
to protect her.
All right.
You're right.
I don't know
when she's going to die.
She lost everything
in her parents' car accident.
She grew up like an orphan.
You know what an orphan is,
don't you?
There are no murderers
from the moment they are born.
Aren't you mad at the people...
who made you like this?
It's not yet too late.
A lot of criminals have repented
who are living new lives.
I'm not saying this as a detective.
I'm telling you
as Ha Eun's guardian.
Finish your ill-fated relationship
with Ha Eun.
Start a new life now.
A new life?
I would've liked that...
more than anything.
Put me in jail as much as you want.
I'll go to her even after I'm dead.
I'll go without a doubt.
You...
asked why.
It's because that's the reason
I'm still alive.
So you're telling me...
killing Ha Eun is the reason
you're still alive.
You're not the only one...
who can kill people.
You're dead to me
even by looking at her.
Do you understand?
(Holy Bible)
If everything in this world
disappeared but you,
I'm going to keep on living.
(If everything in this world...)
(disappeared but you, )
(I'm going to...)
(keep on living.)
Even if the body dies,
the soul...
- will reborn.
- Even if the body dies,
the soul will reborn.
You can be born again.
(Reborn)
(Cha Hyung Bin, I wish
I could be you just for once.)
(Episode 4)
As you may know,
it might become worse again.
It's okay, Doctor.
I realized now.
If I have a strong purpose,
my heart...
will become that much stronger.
I'm going to live,
whatever it takes me.
We'll have kids and I'll fuss
and fight with you.
Just by your side, forever.
Are you...
accepting my proposal?
What a timing.
May I recommend a wedding hall?
There is a place called...
Haebora Cathedral
over in Samcheon.
I'm good friends with the priest
there.
We appreciate it, Doctor.
Detective Cha, where are you?
Over and out.
- Wait a minute.
- Take it. I'll go to the restroom.
I am listening. Over and out.
Detective Cha is really my type.
What a shame.
He's getting married to Ms. Jung.
Have you seen it?
There was another man with Ms. Jung
in the emergency room.
Really?
Does that mean...
she has another man other than
Detective Cha?
It's not the first time
I've seen it.
He brought Ms. Jung last time,
in his arms.
What do you mean by that?
What does that mean?
Actually, the last time you were
here...
someone else brought you here.
He was with you in the ER
the whole time.
- What?
- If he's a murderer,
he wouldn't have taken me
to the hospital since I'm a witness.
- So?
- What I saw wasn't...
him killing Yoon Jeong Yi,
but how he looked after she'd died.
His eyes were...
filled with fright. It wasn't
the look of a murderer.
I can't believe that he's killed
11 people.
Ha Eun,
girls normally feel creepy
in a situation like this.
He committed murder
before your eyes.
He hung around you...
hiding in a corner like that
looking at you secretly.
What do you think
he had on his mind?
Look how he wrote the same message
that I'd written.
He confessed to me that he wrote it.
You really want to meet this man?
He peeked at me and imitated you.
It's scary and it gives me
the creeps.
But...
what if that was all? He might not
be a murderer.
Hyung Bin,
I'll meet him.
I will testify if he's the murderer.
Even if he were sentenced to death
with your testimony,
what would you do
if he broke out of jail?
You've seen how he kills a woman
right in front of your eyes.
If he tries to kill you,
you can't run away.
Do you think he's not aware
that you have heart disease?
Hyung Bin.
He's the kind of guy who can live
only when he commits a murder.
And this guy knows you.
That alone drives me insane.
Gosh, he really left.
Hey, Hyung Bin!
(Abiding by the law.
Real correction)
It's been a long time,
Gong Ji Chul.
It's been four years.
Since we last met at night school.
You're the same as ever.
You didn't kill Yoon Jeong Yi...
deliberately, did you?
Wasn't it an accident?
You're not a man who'd kill someone.
What kind of person...
would that be?
You read a book while you carried
bricks on your back.
Do you know how your eyes looked
as I read a book?
You only show one eye...
but you looked brighter than people...
who live with both eyes.
Did you hold my hand
in the emergency room...
that day?
When I fainted at the phone booth,
you brought me to the hospital.
It was you.
Do you...
believe me?
I do.
Anyone who ever calls me
a teacher...
has the possibility to start
a new life.
Tell me about what happened
that day.
Tell me everything.
Yoon Jeong Yi should die...
so someone else could live.
- That's why I killed her.
- What do you mean by that?
You killed her on purpose?
- Yes.
- It wasn't...
an accident?
So,
how do you feel now?
Do you regret it?
Even if the moment came again,
I would still...
have killed...
that woman.
Why?
- She's a bad woman.
- Is it allowed to kill a person...
if she's bad?
And...
you killed her so someone else
could live?
Does that make sense to you?
Who is it you have to save
by committing murder?
Who is it?
- Do you want to know?
- Do you think...
this person would appreciate it...
when someone died because
of that someone?
I would've been scared
and felt creepy.
Do you think this would justify
your murder?
Murdering is...
what beasts do.
You've chosen the path...
of a beast, not a human being.
If you don't regret making
that decision,
you are already...
a beast.
(Your last moment will be
a sacrifice, not revenge.)
(A sacrifice)
- I think that's her.
- It's her!
- It's the witness.
- That's her.
- Are you the witness?
- What do you think of this case?
Did you see it with your own eyes?
Is Gong Ji Chul the real criminal?
Tell us anything.
Is he who you saw?
I will ask you again.
Did you see the defendant kill...
Yoon Jeong Yi?
Yes, I did.
How did he kill her?
He hit her head...
with a wooden stick.
How can he do such a thing?
"Be my wife."
Why do you think...
the defendant scribbled this here?
It's...
because he'd always watched me
in the bookstore.
He seemed to have imitated
my boyfriend's proposal.
He's unbelievable.
Did you ever think he could
be foreshadowing a murder?
The pictures of 11 women
he'd murdered...
are all wearing...
white cloth like a bride.
Your Honor,
the defendant was abandoned
by his mother...
and was locked up, abused,
and emotionally abused growing up.
After counseling, we were able
to find out...
he'd been stabbed with scissors
all over his body by his stepmother...
and had even been sexually abused.
This is the picture that proves
he was abused by his stepmother.
Yoon Jeong Yi, the hairdresser,
worked late at night...
and had a relationship
with several men...
according to people
from the neighborhood.
How would
Yoon Jeong Yi have flirted...
with the defendant that day?
She's making things up.
When the hairdresser approached
him with these scissors...
what would have the defendant...
have in his mind?
What's happening there?
The defendant is suffering
from epilepsy.
He has been diagnosed with
a seizure...
when he's put under extremely
stressful situations.
In these cases, he won't remember...
anything he has done.
This isn't a murder.
He just had a problem
with his brain.
Please say something.
- How was the trial?
- Is Gong Ji Chul the murderer?
Did he really kill 11 women?
Please say something!
Ms. Jung Ha Eun?
- And you are?
- I'm Cha Hyung Bin.
Oh, detective Cha.
Ji Chul will be...
put in a psych ward first, then be
moved to a mental hospital.
A lot of men died while there.
He'll be taken care of within
a few weeks. So don't worry.
He'll get out for sure. We need
witness protection.
I'll have the police stand guard
in front of her house.
I'm sure you'll be next to her
24, 7 as well.
Please give us a word.
It's Gong Ji Chul!
Hurry, take a picture.
Stay still.
Do you...
believe me?
I do.
You are not...
a man who'd kill someone.
Detective Cha!
Here is the list...
of doctors and nurses
at the psych ward Ji Chul is in...
that you asked for.
In Do, please take Ha Eun
to the train station.
I heard Gangwon province has
a heavy snow warning.
Will she be okay?
Get there first. I'll follow
you soon.
I don't think the walkie talkie
works long distance.
I'll be waiting.
Let's go.
I saw many cases
of psychiatric studies...
in America.
If you don't remember the murders
you committed...
they shouldn't be considered
murder cases.
This country is so barbaric...
that they don't know anything.
What is...
my blood type?
It's type AB.
Why do you ask?
Gong Ji Chul escaped the psych ward
after attempting to kill his doctor.
Please put up a wanted alert.
And send an ambulance.
Ha Eun...
Ha Eun! Answer me!
Ha Eun. Come out.
Ha Eun!
Jung Ha Eun!
This is Father Andrew.
I think it was January 24th
or the 25th.
Excuse my old age.
If you get off Samchuk station...
and ask for Haebora Cathedral,
everyone should know.
I've finished the preparations
for the wedding.
Wait just for a while.
I'll give you my heart.
(Resurrection)
Today is January 25th, 1988.
The time is...
5:15 a.m.
I love you, Hyung Bin.
Never forget my voice
telling you this.
Even after 20, 30 years...
I hope you stay as a policeman.
I will still...
miss you even then.
The serial killer Gong Ji Chul is...
said to have escaped the psych
ward around midnight.
He bludgeoned the doctor...
and escaped by changing into
the doctor's clothes.
Halt.
I'm the police.
Stop!
- What is it?
- Get him!
Are you Ha Eun?
Welcome.
Where is Hyung Bin?
He'll be here soon, father.
Would you like to see the cathedral?
- It's where your wedding will be.
- Yes.
I swear to lord and Ha Eun's parents
who are resting in peace.
I, Cha Hyung Bin, will protect...
my bride Jung Ha Eun with my life...
to the end.
Hyung Bin.
I heard lovers are connected with
a red string...
as soon as they are born
into this world.
If you want to sever that tie...
one person must die.
Hyung Bin.
I will find you whether...
you're dead or alive.
So please...
promise me you'll find me too.
I accept...
Cha Hyung Bin...
as my husband.
Whether we are together or apart,
for eternal to eternal,
I vow...
to love Cha Hyung Bin...
and Cha Hyung Bin only.
Is this Haebora Cathedral?
Is this Father Andrew?
Yes, this is Cha Hyung Bin speaking.
Did Ha Eun arrive at the cathedral?
Cha Hyung Bin is...
with me right now.
Father.
Look at his face carefully...
if he has a scar on his left eye.
My vision is not so clear.
I can't see it well.
Was it Cha Hyung Bin...
on the phone?
Are you here...
to kill people?
Can people who committed suicide...
born again?
All men are...
sinners.
We can be forgiven by the lord.
Lord...
No.
I don't need him,
but I want her to forgive me.
No.
I want to ask her...
if I really can't become human.
I came to tell her...
that I don't want to become a beast.
I want to prove...
that her faith is not mistaken.
Jung Ha Eun...
was the first person...
who looked me straight in the eye.
She was the first one...
to call my name.
I am...
Gong Ji Chul.
I told you...
you'd be dead
if you looked at Ha Eun.
You'll escape
if I put you in jail again.
You'll never get over it...
until you kill Ha Eun.
Murder is the only way you have.
Please give me time...
for once.
Did you give them time
before you killed all those girls?
No!
Hyung Bin.
No.
Don't do this.
Hyung Bin.
You can never go to Ha Eun.
Ha Eun.
Please save Ha Eun.
I told you...
that souls will be reborn,
didn't I?
Gong Ji Chul,
listen to me.
You'll never...
be able to come back to life.
My plan to give her my heart...
became a failure.
I had hoped
that would be the last time...
and the end of my destiny
and soul.
Just like the curse...
of Jung Ha Eun,
I hoped my soul that was tarnished
as a murderer...
would not be resurrected.
I hoped again and again.
I'm done.
That was quick.
I have the habit of reading
only what I want to read.
("The Man You Cannot Meet
While Alive")
But don't you need
the notes you wrote in this book?
They say notes are
the history of the book.
The first person to read the book...
and the next person.
I look forward to who'd read next...
and become the history of the book.
(Born Again)
Are you Chun Jong Bum?
What is this...
- deja vu?
- It's been bothering me.
She won't be able to live
her life to the fullest.
They found some remains
near the Donggang River.
What happened 30 years ago?
I felt pain.