So this is what you did
with all my flowers.
It's pretty.
- It looks great here. Gosh.
- Yes.
- It's pretty.
But why did she put firewood here?
Don't be so tacky!
It's called interior decorating.
She did a good job.
Chef Moon wanted to thank everyone
for helping out,
so he prepared a special course meal.
Take your time and enjoy.
- All right.
- It's a soup made with trout.
- Enjoy.
[ - All right. ]
[ Trout? ]
Examining it culturally,
this is an extremely gourmet dish.
[ I thought trout was only for sashimi. ]
Who knew it could be made into a soup?
I know.
This trout is lucky to have come
to our village and meet Chef Moon
because it became such a gourmet dish.
[ Gosh, it looks so pretty too. ]
Goodness! And it's delicious!
But still, I think it's too little.
In the countryside,
we always serve huge portions and...
Bong-doo. Don't be so tacky.
Just enjoy what you get.
But still, instead of this white mush,
I'd rather have some good spicy broth.
Seung-mo! Don't you have that broth
you always make? Bring that over!
Not that. It's not finished yet.
Don't be so fussy. It's good enough!
- Wait a minute, okay?
[ - Okay. ]
Hey!
[ Here. ]
That hits the spot!
[ We always need to have some broth. ]
[ Yes. ]
That's good.
But this doesn't smell like the broth
my grandparents used to make.
You have such a great sense of smell,
Seol-a!
Isn't that right, Seung-mo?
[ Belle Ombre ]
What are we watching?
A fashion show.
Not just by anyone,
but by the famous Bella.
We had a Byeol-na fashion show, too.
That's fake. This is a real fashion show.
Are you talking about me?
What is this? A fashion show?
Make some space for me.
[ That hits the spot! ]
[ We always need to have some broth. ]
[ But this doesn't smell like the broth
my grandparents used to make. ]
What do I do?
She'll come.
Bella will come.
[ Belle Ombre ]
Don't these clothes look similar
to what Byeol-na made?
[ Is that so? ]
[ You're right. ]
The style is similar, but don't you think
her name is similar too?
She's Bella, and she's Byeol-na.
[ - Yes. ]
- You're right.
But still,
Byeol-na's clothes look much better.
[ - Right? ]
- I guess you have an eye for fashion.
That seems somewhat fake.
Is that so?
Anyway, the show is so grand.
Did you say Donghan is hosting that?
Yes.
[ It must be a huge company. ]
[ I know. ]
I don't know how we can win
against such a big company.
Mr. Kang. This is Moon Seung-mo.
[ Belle Ombre by Bella Y ]
- Ma'am.
- Follow me.
[ Ombre de Seoul ]
Sit here.
Ma'am!
Get on the stage for the finale.
Sorry?
This is the finale
of your fake Bella show.
Get it together and don't mess up.
This is Bella's show,
the world's most-renowned designer.
Yes, ma'am.
[ Belle Ombre by Bella Y ]
[ Bella! ]
Bella!
What was that? I was watching that!
My show is on!
I've been looking forward to this!
- Go on. Watch your show, Seol-a.
- Yes.
Bella!
[ Bella! ]
[ Belle Ombre by Bella Y ]
[ - Bella? ]
- What?
- Is that her?
- That's Bella?
- What?
- Bella?
Turn the lights off. Turn them off!
Turn the lights off this instance!
[ - What?
- Bella? ]
[ - Bella!
- Excuse me! ]
[ Look this way! ]
[ - You're so pretty, Bella!
- You're so pretty! ]
[ - I'm your fan!
- Look this way, Bella! ]
[ - You're so pretty!
- Look this way, please! ]
[ - Over here!
- I'm your fan! ]
Hurry up.
- We need to go to bed.
- That was great.
I'm exhausted.
- One moment.
- Yes?
- I have something to tell you all.
- What?
I've decided
to run the restaurant with Donghan.
Really?
I think that's the best way
to save our village at the moment.
What?
Then will those handsome guys return?
The handsome guys?
[ You've made the right decision. ]
We can't end up getting kicked out.
That's right. Since they invested in this,
they can't kick us out.
Yes, that would be a total family feud.
Right? It's Donghan Food and...
Donghan Inter... Donghan Interview...
- Donghan International.
- International!
Right, I knew it. Gosh.
[ - That's good news.
- Yes, that's great. ]
[ - Nicely done.
- Right. ]
[ - You've made a great decision.
- Exactly. ]
[ Ombre de Seoul ]
[ - What's going on?
- Did you know about it? ]
Are you crazy? Have you gone mad?
How dare you? How could you...
- Oh, no.
- What do we do?
Where are you now, Mr. Jung?
Convene the publicity team right away.
I need an explanation about this.
Why did Hyun-a come out from there?
Is she saying she's Bella?
Let's talk later.
I need to go somewhere tomorrow.
Where?
- To get some ssi-ganjang.
- "Ssi-ganjang"?
It doesn't feel right to open Pungcheonok
when I haven't been able to master
my parents' broth recipe.
That makes sense.
Do you know where to get it?
There is one more place
that has the same ssi-ganjang
my parents had.
Hey, you should've gone sooner.
Why wait until now?
I know, right?
What? That's odd.
Is something bothering you?
Yes. What?
No.
Oh, come on.
Let it all out to me.
Quit it.
You make sure Seol-a and Byeol-na...
What are you looking at?
I'm just going to the bathroom.
[ Go where? ]
I need to go to Jeolla Province
to get some ssi-ganjang.
Think of it as getting some fresh air.
Let's go on a day trip.
Just the two of us?
Yes.
What's this awkward situation?
What's so awkward about it?
I just wanted to thank you
for the interior design.
I wanted to buy you some clothes
and food. That was all.
If you don't like it, never mind.
I never said I didn't like the idea.
Chef Moon!
How dare you. How dare you!
What on earth were you thinking?
I don't know.
- What?
- I have no idea
why I did that.
You're really...
This won't do.
Let's have a press conference
tomorrow right away and...
Give Ms. Jang a ride to her place.
Mr. Lim.
I'd like to have a private conversation
with my daughter.
I hope you understand.
Hey, Lim Chul-yong!
Good job.
Pardon?
I told you this before.
If there's something you want,
you have to take it away.
Now, no matter what people say,
you are Bella.
Dad.
You've finally taken away
what you've been wanting.
It's me. Call around
as many reporters as you can
and set up a press conference tomorrow.
What's going on?
If you were paid,
aren't you supposed to bring some news?
Come on. It's only been a couple of days.
I've spread out all my men
throughout the nation.
I'll get back to you soon.
We don't have time!
You better bring me something
before tomorrow's press conference.
Or else, you'll have to return
every single penny.
Get out.
[ Not yet open ]
- Aren't you taking Seol-a with you?
- Don't wake her up.
Chef Moon and I are going on a date...
Goodness. Chef Moon.
Is this the smell of the wind or river?
You're so elated.
Of course I am. All I do is stay at home.
I'm finally out for once in a while.
We should go driving often.
- Hey...
- I wonder what kind of person I was.
How many people did I go out with?
What are you talking about?
It's just
a random thought that popped in my head.
I bet you didn't date a lot of people.
You probably were a noob.
The same goes for you too.
- Me?
- Yes.
You have no idea what's on a woman's mind.
What are you talking about? I was popular.
Is that so? Show me proof.
I'll believe in you if you do.
You'll regret saying that.
Did you not get enough sleep?
No. I had a fitful night's sleep.
I was too excited.
You never answered my calls.
Why did you call me?
How did you get rid of the burnt corpse
at the closed school?
Where's the ground bones?
What ground bones?
You're making my heart drop again.
Nobody died there.
[ Nobody died! ]
So she's alive?
[ Are you sure? ]
Hey.
She's not dead.
Well...
- We...
[ - No, it's okay. ]
I think things are better this way.
Pardon?
Things are getting interesting.
[ Business Background ]
[ Business Strategy ]
Firstly,
we'll receive the entire stock
of all produce needed
for our Gourmandism Business
from here, Nonyang.
Secondly, we'll set Chef Moon's restaurant
as the base of the Gourmandism Business
and lead the way in revitalizing
the regional economy,
also attracting tourists
from other regions.
Lastly, we will build a food warehouse
[ with a proper eco-friendly system ]
in Nonyang so it's not disadvantageous
to the local residents
and the environment.
Very nice.
Let's seal the deal right away
and push it forward.
Sounds great.
[ Sir. ]
The group urgently needs you.
[ What? Marriage? ]
[ Stop the car. Right now. ]
I know it doesn't make any sense.
I'm sorry.
If you don't like it...
I'm curious why you're doing this.
The thing is...
Seung-mo, your father and mother
consented to it today.
Now, you two have
the consent of both your parents
and can start... What is it called?
Right. You can start
a romantic relationship now.
Wait. Why do you look so upset?
[ If you don't like it, just drop it. ]
We wanted to tell you our family's secret
only because you were going to be
our daughter's husband.
- Am I wrong, honey?
- You are right.
Right?
So what do you say?
You should give me a clear answer now.
If you don't like it, drop it.
I will do as you say.
Of course you will.
Oh, my. I'm so happy!
I will get going, sir.
It would be nice to
have the wedding right away,
but you're a man who has a big dream
of learning all the recipes
of all head families in this country.
And you're about to start the journey now.
[ It will be disrespectful of us ]
[ if we can't wait for just a few months. ]
So until Seung-mo comes back,
I want you to stay right there
and wait for him.
[ Still, ]
I want you to at least let me know
when you will come back.
As I'm leaving without any promise,
I will come back without any notice.
Am I Chun-hyang or what?
Seung-mo!
Don't laugh like that.
It's a serious matter.
So you learned the recipe
and then ran away.
I didn't know you were
that kind of person.
It's just horrible to even imagine
that I have to marry someone by force.
Anyway, what I'm trying to say is,
if I go back to that family as a single,
I might not be able to leave the family.
Just for one day, right?
Not even one day.
Just half a day would do.
Please.
What do you think we should do
to make them believe that we are married?
[ It looks really nice on you. ]
Does it?
Come on and try it on.
Just buy anything you like.
No way.
We should buy something
that looks good on both of us.
We are buying wedding rings.
Open your hand.
Which one will look good
on Chef Moon's finger?
It should match
with your skin color and finger.
This one.
Try.
[ You must be so meant to be together. ]
Pardon?
The ring that suits her ring finger
suits your little finger.
[ We say those people
are meant to be together. ]
That's ridiculous.
Just buy anything you like.
- I would like to buy this one.
- Okay.
"Meant to be together".
- Byeol-na, how about this?
- No.
It's a bit...
What do you want me to wear?
It's a very conservative family.
Something neat and elegant.
You should have told me that.
[ How about this? ]
[ Do you not like this one either? ]
Hello?
You look great.
I like it.
Let's go with that one.
I would like to pay.
Are they excluding me?
I know Dad has always been like that,
but how could even Byeol-na do this to me?
Don't be like that.
You're a bigger person, so be generous.
Your father is out of his mind these days.
I just can't believe
he's doing this only to me.
You knew
he and Byeol-na were going to leave.
I'm the only one who is excluded!
These guys are crazy.
Look at me.
I'm the one who has
an outstanding appearance.
What's wrong with these jerks?
What's wrong, Da-mi? What happened...
Look at this. Can you believe it?
[ No one cares about me. ]
[ They just want to know where it is. ]
I'm the one that stands out
in the picture.
Am I not?
[ Really? ]
Gosh.
Okay. I'm coming right now.
Are all the reporters there?
Good.
Ms. Jang Sun-young.
Here's a letter of dismissal.
[ Press Conference ]
What are you saying?
I founded Belle Ombre.
You are dismissed
by the largest shareholder.
What?
- "The largest shareholder"?
- Why don't you take a look?
Bella?
Where's Lim Chul-yong?
[ As of today, you are deprived of
all your rights to the corporation. ]
[ Including the drafts
of Bella's personal designs ]
[ and the trademark rights, ]
[ our legal team have Bella notarize
all clauses regarding her rights. ]
[ Official Press Conference
on the Collaboration Fashion Show ]
Although it wasn't made public,
Bella and Ms. Jang
seems to have had serious conflicts.
This is also the reason
why Bella kept the mysterious concept.
Last night, she revealed
her face for the first time,
[ and I think it's not too much to say ]
that it was a performance
to announce her breakup
with Ms. Jang.
There you were.
She contacted me.
[ Donghan International, Press conference ]
What did she say? Where is she?
Let me come with you.
I get that you want to see her right away,
but why don't you leave it to us for now?
[ You might end up wasting your time. ]
Let us check her first.
We will get right back to you after that.
Okay, then.
Mr. Jin.
Please hurry. I don't have much time.
I will. Don't worry.
- Hello.
[ - Can we meet? ]
[ There's a lot I want to say to you. ]
How gorgeous.
Byeol-na, listen carefully.
You can eat any food they give you,
but don't drink their liquor.
- Why?
- It's a long story.
Anyway, what's our relationship?
- Married.
- And if they figure out it's a lie?
You will have to get married.
I want you to take this seriously.
Let's go.
He's back!
Seung-mo has finally come back!
Sir.
Even Lee Mong-ryong, that jerk,
had a conscience.
It wouldn't have been enough
even if you kneeled down in front of me.
And how dare you brought another woman?
I don't know what to say.
Forget it.
Are your parents all right?
Both my parents have passed away recently.
What?
What did you just say?
I'm sorry. I should have contacted you,
but I was too busy.
But how?
There was a fire.
My goodness!
They managed to escape at first,
but then they went back into the house
to bring the ssi-ganjang.
What's the big deal about ssi-ganjang?
Is that more precious than one's life?
I know it's a lot to ask,
but the reason I came back is...
Go ahead.
In this entire country,
you are the only one
who has the ssi-gangjang
that is like Pungcheonok's.
Are you saying you came
for our ssi-gangjang?
That's right. Please excuse me.
How did it go?
I'm not sure.
He doesn't say he would give it to me.
Anyhow, I learned a new thing about you.
What do you mean?
Of course, I'm talking
about your taste in women.
I didn't know you liked
that type of woman.
She's not my type.
Yes, she is. You looked cute together.
What are you doing?
Are you jealous or something?
Jealous? Why would I be jealous?
[ Don't be ridiculous. ]
Father, he's suspicious.
Did you feel that too?
I happened to hear them talk a bit.
Seung-mo talks to her with respect,
but that rude wench
talks down to her husband.
What kind of wife does that?
Right? You're right.
That skinny woman is
just not as pretty as you.
I can't understand him either.
He's really suspicious.
They don't look like a married couple.
Not once have I been wrong
about these things.
Then what do we do now?
What do you mean by that?
Of course we should reveal the truth.
We will make things back to normal.
Mi-nyeo, I think
we should prepare a feast.
No one can resist our family's liquor.
[ The next story is ]
[ about Bella, the world-famous designer. ]
[ Her face, which has been
hidden until now, is revealed, ]
[ and created a big buzz
in the fashion industry. ]
[ Designer Lim Hyun-a
turned out to be Bella ]
[ and the daughter
of the Managing Director ]
[ of Donghan International,
one of Korea's biggest fashion companies, ]
[ and it's making headlines. ]
[ The reason why she revealed her face ]
[ and the future collaboration plans ]
[ of Belle Ombre
and Donghan International... ]
[ Bella is dragging
the world's attention... ]
[ She's dragging everyone's attention. ]
After the collaboration show with Bella,
today...
Our stock price has risen
by 23.96 percent.
[ Especially the event ]
[ where Bella's face was revealed
at the launching show ]
and the fact that Bella is the daughter
of Managing Director Lim Chul-yong
are one of the favorable factors.
[ The stock market is excited about this. ]
[ Not only private investors
but also international investors ]
are competitively buying the stocks.
I'm thinking of organizing a board meeting
regarding merging Belle Ombre.
Okay.
That was amazing.
I didn't know Bella was your daughter.
I'm surprised.
Congratulations.
Thanks.
Right. Mr. Hong said
he would like to apologize to you.
Because he decided to work with us.
It seems that the county office
sealed the deal with them.
Don't you think we should make a move too?
We are just about to merge
with Belle Ombre.
We won't do anything
over such a trivial matter.
But...
Memorandum of understanding
is just a piece of paper.
It can easily be torn.
You have traveled a long way.
Hopefully this releases your fatigue.
Sorry, we have to get going early today.
So, you don't need my ssi-ganjang?
No, that's not it, sir.
Then have a drink with me.
I'm disappointed.
This is so good!
Where are your manners?
What did your parents teach you at home?
How dare you start drinking
when the elder hasn't eaten yet?
It's not my fault
that the drink is so enticing.
Have we met before?
Why are you talking so informally to me?
She lived abroad for a long time,
so she's not used to
the Korean culture yet.
So, a Western fox, I see.
What did you say? A Western fox?
Stop it!
Excuse me, may I take this call?
Sure, go ahead.
What does a Western fox mean?
That's our way of saying
that you're beautiful.
Then you can be a Western fox, too.
What did you just say?
You're beautiful, too.
Hello, Chef Moon.
I talked with Mr. Hong. It went well.
[ That's good to hear. ]
Does that mean that our village isn't
in danger of being demolished, then?
It's too early to say.
[ Mr. Lim won't let it go this easy. ]
Speaking of which,
can you open your restaurant faster?
[ When do you think you can open it? ]
My business permit should be out soon,
so it won't take long.
Sorry for rushing you. You already have
so much on your plate already.
[ I think we should hurry
when we have the momentum. ]
- I'll see you at the opening.
- Yes.
Have another drink.
Chef Moon, you try some as well.
It's absolutely delicious.
That's right.
We made this drink
when our Mi-nyeo was born.
It's as old as Mi-nyeo.
I was going to open it up
when she brings my son-in-law...
[ That's okay. ]
Who cares about who drinks it, anyway?
All right. I'll just have a drink.
Really? Sure.
You must be hungry
from coming all the way here,
so let's eat.
Thank you.
Why are you guys eating like that
when you're a married couple?
Sorry?
A husband has to tear the meat
[ and feed it to his wife. ]
Are you sure you guys are married?
You're right.
- Here.
- Good.
Hold on.
[ Sorry. ]
Here.
Sorry.
The bride seems to be quite shy.
- We're newlyweds.
[ - I see. ]
Congratulations, anyway.
Let's drink some more.
Cheers.
Where did you two meet?
- Us?
- Yes.
We met in Australia.
No, we met in the mountains.
Don't you remember?
You carried me on your back
down the mountain.
You guys are too young
to have Alzheimer's.
How come your memories are so different?
We met in Australia and in the mountains.
That's what happened.
Yes, sir.
Chef Moon,
I admit that your eyes are handsome.
Whenever you look at me with those eyes,
you have no idea how fast my heart beats.
It's not just the eyes!
His nose is perfect,
and his neck is so lean and long.
Hey, being handsome doesn't make someone
a good man.
Really?
The handsome ones lack
in the personality department, don't they?
A good man is all about the heart.
Our Chef Moon has a good heart.
He doesn't act like it,
but he's always looking out for me.
He's such a good man,
I know that.
I hope he meets a good woman,
falls in love, and gets married.
Honey, we're married.
She's drunk.
I'm going to put her to bed now.
- Byeol-na.
- Don't touch me.
You're making me blush.
Something is certainly off.
It seems like you're busted.
Are you sure you're married?
Of course, she's just drunk.
To be honest,
the ring is the only thing that proves
that you two are married.
Show us a photo or something.
You must've held a wedding, didn't you?
Where are your wedding photos?
People have smartphones
with all their photos in there these days.
Let me see some.
[ Bang Da-hoon ]
It's Seol-a!
Pick up already!
Goodness.
Seol-a!
[ Byeol-na? Do you want to talk to Seol-a? ]
- Let me talk to her!
[ - All right. ]
Seol-a! I miss you.
You want to talk to him?
Fine, go ahead.
[ Speaker phone ]
[ Dad, you're terrible. ]
[ How could you just leave me behind? ]
[ Take me the next time you go. ]
[ - How can you just leave me... ]
- I'm going to go and die!
Mi-nyeo! Where are you going?
[ - Dad! ]
- What do you mean, go and die?
Are you out of your mind?
[ - Mi-nyeo!
- Dad? Dad! ]
[ Are you listening to me? ]
Hello?
You think everything can go back to
how it was before
as long as we find Bella?
Will that be possible?
Even if the real Bella comes back,
you'll be the only one
who knows that she's Bella.
And who will believe someone
who got kicked out of the company?
People may not know how she looks like,
but there are people who can recognize her
just with Bella's clothes.
[ Belle Ombre ]
[ Okay, say that we found her. ]
Then what?
Then I'll have to take it back.
Belle Ombre that they took.
You think he'll let you have it back?
Chul-yong is no easy man.
But I can help you get it back.
Belle Ombre.
You know well who the real Bella is.
She's Hyo-myoung's daughter, so why?
That makes me want to see her even more.
[ We're not open yet.
What brings you here? ]
Is Mr. Moon Seung-mo here?
You're here to see Chef Moon?
He's out on a trip
and he said that he'll be back tonight,
but it seems like he'll be here tomorrow.
Well,
here.
That's Byeol-na!
You're right.
- Do you know her?
- She lives...
Who are you?
Someone is desperately looking for her.
Who is it?
Why are you looking at them like that?
You don't know them.
I'm just astonished at how chic she looks.
She almost looks like someone else.
Right.
They went out together this morning,
so they'll come back together.
Would you like to
leave your number with me?
No, I'll just come back another time.
- Thank you.
- Okay.
Goodbye.
What should we do?
Should we go back
since we've confirmed it?
Are you kidding me?
We're waiting here until she comes back.
Darn it.
Should we turn on the heater?
It's getting cold.
[ 22O 6100 ]
Who's out there at such a late hour?
Chef Moon,
are you asleep?
No.
Are my eyes that handsome?
When did I say that?
Earlier.
I don't know, I can't remember.
You're acting drunk
because you're embarrassed.
Chef Moon,
why do you like me?
When did I ever say that I like you?
If you don't like me, why did you jump
into the fire to save me?
How can I just watch?
That's not a good enough answer.
Close your eyes and go to sleep.
I don't know.
Ever since
I first met you in Australia,
[ I kept thinking of you, ]
[ worried for you,
and wanted to care for you. ]
[ That was how I felt. ]
I had no idea
that I'd see you again like this.
And we're living together now.
I'll be so happy for you
when your memories come back,
but to think that you'll have
to leave me someday,
it makes me sad
and hurts my heart.
After my wife passed away,
we've lost our tradition
as the head family.
Our ssi-ganjang of 200 years
has dried out like this,
[ and it doesn't mean anything
to me anymore. ]
So take this if you'd like.
Only soybeans grown domestically
can be used to make this ssi-ganjang.
But those soybeans are so rare to get.
Because it's such a special produce
that only a few kilograms
can be produced each year,
this ssi-ganjang is
that much special.
I don't have a hangover at all.
That liquor is always like that.
It makes us drink until the end,
but we don't have a hangover
after drinking it.
Just like the liquor at my home,
I don't hold any grudges.
I wish you two the best,
although Mi-nyeo won't be able
to do the same.
Thank you for everything, sir.
Let's go.
Sir, we'll have a happy life!
Don't worry about us!
Goodness.
What can you do with this empty pot?
There's someone
who can bring that back to life.
Really? How?
This person is the master of beans
who makes soy sauce
only with domestically-produced soybeans.
You'll see when you get there. Let's go.
- Do you want to eat anything?
- I do!
This, this, this, and that!
We'll take one of those.
I want this one, too.
We'll take this one as well.
It's delicious. You want a bite?
You can take this.
[ Bella! ]
[ - Bella!
- Look this way, please! ]
[ - I'm your fan!
- Look this way, Bella! ]
[ - You're so pretty, Bella!
- You're so pretty! ]
[ - Over here!
- I'm your fan! ]
[ - Bella!
- We love you. ]
[ That's right, ]
[ I'm Bella. ]
[ Belle Ombre ]
[ Mr. Jin Tae-soo ]
Is anyone home?
Sir, it's me, Seung-mo!
Sir!
I don't think anyone is inside.
Who are you?
This store is closed.
What do you mean?
They closed down a while ago.
Then what about the man
who owned the place?
[ Care Center ]
[ After his son died in an accident, ]
[ he began to go crazy ]
[ and eventually,
he couldn't recognize anyone. ]
[ Onjeong Care Center ]
Thanks.
Sir, you have a guest.
Hello, sir.
Do you remember me?
Sir?
It's me, Seung-mo.
Open your eyes, your son is here.
He's so handsome and tall, just like you.
- I'm not his son.
[ - I know. ]
He'll only open his eyes
when he hears that it's his son.
[ Who knows? Maybe his memory
will come back even just for a moment. ]
He recognizes people sometimes these days.
You came yesterday,
and you're here today, too.
Sir.
Seung-mo, promise me
that you'll come tomorrow as well.
Do you remember me?
I certainly do.
Is that your wife over there?
Yes, sir.
She's my wife.
Chef Moon,
that's...
Sir, do you remember her?
Seol-a!
Seol-a...
Our Seol-a,
where is she?
Seol-a.
Seung-mo!
[ Let's get out. ]
[ It's okay, come on out. ]
Come here. It's okay, Seol-a.
Here.
Seol-a, let's go.
[ Eccentric! Chef Moon ]
[ He's now sure that
she's not his daughter. ]
They're not related.
[ It's okay, come on out. ]
Seol-a.
When you're gone,
[ I don't think
I'll want to sleep nor eat. ]
- Why?
- I'll miss you.
Because I'm Bella.
Why should there be a reason
when Bella wants to show who she is?
[ - It's time to get things done.
- Sorry? ]
[ The more secrets you know,
the more at risk you are. ]
[ Do you have any idea
how much I've missed you? ]
[ What are you doing? Go run them over! ]
[ I have someone ]
[ that I want to protect now. ]