[ Episode 12 ]
[ Yu-jin! ]
Ms. Yoo Yu-jin, please come this way.
Don't do it.
I have to head inside.
Why are you trying to be the only one
to deal with it and sacrifice yourself?
Why?
Don't get me wrong.
I'm not sacrificing myself.
- It's what I want.
- Don't lie.
I...
I'm on my way from seeing Lim Chul-yong.
I heard everything.
You're so clueless about me.
I never do anything I don't want.
- Yu-jin...
- Seoha Village
and your parents' house.
Those are where
I was the happiest in my life.
And it's my grandfather's house too.
I wanted to protect it on my own.
No.
I won't let you.
To me,
you are
more valuable than the house.
Thank you so much.
For that.
I have something I want to tell you too.
To me,
you are more valuable
than the name "Bella".
I beg of you.
Please let me do this.
Hello everyone,
it is time for DBC News Interviews.
We invited a special guest today
who is the center of attention these days.
[ We prepared an interview
regarding the news ]
on the opening of Bella Boutique
we sent out yesterday.
Yesterday's star was Louis Bellemont,
and today's star is this person.
The person we know as "Bella Y"
[ is here with us at the studio today. ]
And the chairman of the famous
French fashion brand,
Louis Bellemont is also here
with us today.
[ Before we begin,
we would like to inform you that ]
[ we also have an upcoming interview
with Donghan International ]
[ and Lim Hyun-a. ]
I will now ask Ms. Yoo Yu-jin a question.
Why haven't you spoken up until now
throughout the whole incident,
and what made you request for an interview
at this point?
Well...
[ Why did you request for an interview? ]
[ Well... ]
Go on, Yu-jin.
Tell them everything.
I have been observing
the controversy until now,
and I wanted to settle it
through this interview.
I see.
However,
it must not have been an easy decision.
I am the one who made
the real Bella outfit
that was chosen at the opening
of the Bella Boutique yesterday.
Good job!
- Let's go, Bella!
- Way to go!
- Good job!
- Way to go, Bella!
Good job!
She said she made it, so it's over.
- That's right.
[ - Are you happy? ]
We're getting kicked out of the village.
Even if we do get kicked out,
I wish Bella would give those
Donghan jerks
a good beating this time.
- That's right.
- Yes.
Then are you saying that
you are the real Bella,
instead of the Bella Lim Hyun-a
we all know of?
It is true that I made the outfit.
But...
[ Name: Yoo Yu-jin ]
I am not Bella.
I am here to tell you this.
What?
Mother.
[ Mother. ]
Wait a minute. I will ask you once more.
[ You are saying that you did make
the outfit Chairman Louis chose, ]
but you are not Bella.
[ Is that correct? ]
Yes.
That is correct.
[ News Studio ]
You cannot enter, ma'am.
- Open the door. Open it!
- I'm sorry.
- Mother.
- Open the door!
- Mother!
- Open the door.
- Open it!
Mr. Jung.
Halt the
clothing industrial complex construction
at Seoha Village immediately.
[ Made the Outfit, but Not Bella ]
[ Bella ]
[ She was the swindler? ]
[ I feel bad for Lim Hyun-a. ]
What?
Why is she saying she's not Bella
when she is?
Right.
[ Why is she doing that? ]
Who knows?
Oh, no. There are so many nasty comments.
What is Bella going to do?
She'll be hurt if she sees this.
Wait, what is going on?
Even I don't know
how to interpret this as well.
Hello?
Yes. What?
Okay.
What is it?
- We're good.
- "We're good"?
- For what?
- They canceled the construction
of the clothing industrial complex!
- What?
I'm serious!
I just got the call
from the county office.
- Goodness.
- Yes!
[ - This is amazing!
- Does that mean... ]
The worst is past, right?
Goodness, you're right.
I was devastated,
[ but I'm so relieved now! ]
Yes!
[ We did it! ]
- Gosh.
- Goodness.
I don't know why,
but I'm feeling mixed emotions.
I'm happy,
but I feel sad for some reason.
Goodness, gracious.
Right?
Same for me too.
Why am I feeling this way?
What a coincidence to hear it as soon as
Bella was done with her interview.
Right?
You're right.
Goodness.
I apologize, Louis.
No need to say a word
when you made a fool of me like this.
The whole world will laugh at me
by tomorrow.
Don't ever think of seeing me again,
Madam Jang!
Louis!
You wench.
Stop it, ma'am.
Your mother ruined my life,
and now you're ruining it too?
Let's talk another time.
- Where do you think you're going?
- Mother.
Go back inside and tell them
you're the real Bella!
You are the real Bella!
Why did you have to lie? Why?
Mother, stop it.
Let go of me!
Mother, it's okay.
You go ahead. I'll wait here.
Are you out of your mind?
What were you thinking?
What's with that trunk?
Are you going to leave again?
What are you going to do
with Belle Ombre now?
You made a fool out of Chairman Louis.
Goodness, we're done in this industry.
You only care about yourself.
What?
My mom.
Did she die because of you?
What?
Were you
that jealous of my mom?
You...
What are you talking about?
- Did you...
- Yes.
I heard it from Lim Chul-yong.
[ Park Hyung-jun, Reporter ]
I also met with the reporter back then.
[ Why are you speechless? ]
Did my mom really die
because of you, Madam Jang?
No.
Yu-jin.
That's... That's not it.
I don't know what you heard from where,
but it's not true.
I was
going to tell you one day.
I'm sorry.
It was...
It was a mistake.
"A mistake"?
You're calling it a mistake
when someone died?
[ How can you ]
[ call it a mistake
when you betrayed the person ]
who trusted and relied on you the most?
How could you?
[ I just want to make sure
of one tiny detail. ]
I understand you'll be leaving
the country for good, right?
Excuse me?
We can't have two Bellas under one sky.
I'm sorry,
but that's none of your business.
You really don't listen.
Chef Moon must go through so much.
I'm saying many unfortunate events
will happen to him
if he goes out with someone
as stubborn as you.
I didn't expect you to be
this devious.
I guess you overestimated me.
I'm someone who can take measures
beyond your imaginations
to achieve what I want.
Yu-jin, do you need me at the lobby now?
Don't look for me.
[ Just forget about me. ]
[ Live a happy life. ]
Where are you now?
I'm going to go somewhere far away.
[ It's now hard for me
to stay in this country, ]
[ and I don't want to anymore. ]
[ I don't think I can handle ]
others' eyes on me.
[ If you stay with me, ]
[ you will be unhappy too. ]
[ I have been only receiving from you. ]
I'm happy I can finally
do something for you.
Thank you for everything.
[ I love you. ]
Yu-jin!
[ The Managing Director
of Donghan International, ]
[ Lim Chul-yong was inaugurated
as the new chairman of Donghan Group. ]
[ Donghan Group stated ]
[ that it was their best decision
in order to follow the teachings ]
[ of the late chairman, Han Dong-gil, ]
[ minimize the leadership vacuum ]
[ and maintain the business stable. ]
[ Chairman Lim Chul-yong ]
[ Are you busy? ]
Oh, hey.
[ Donghan Group ]
I heard you were transferred
to Donghan Food. Congratulations.
You shouldn't congratulate me.
You need to comfort me.
So this is what the leather couch
in the director's office feels like.
Come on.
My friend is a managing director
and a son-in-law of the chairman.
People around me are successful,
while I'm a mere manager
of the Food Business Division.
Not many people of our age
get to hold the manager's title.
[ You earned the title
with your competence. ]
You are not like me
who got here through connection.
Gosh.
Thanks for saying that.
By the way, I was surprised to see
your selection of the principal designer.
She earned her position.
Ms. Jang seemed pretty disappointed.
- Is that so?
- Yes.
Sir, may I have a word with you?
Sure. Excuse me.
[ Managing Director Kang Min-suk ]
[ Yoo Hyo-myoung had a daughter? ]
I guess I'm drunk. I'm talking too much.
Are you the only one who knows it?
Mr. Kang knows it too.
Is Min-suk her father?
How did you know? Did Mr. Kang tell you?
It's before Mr. Kang got married,
and Hyo-myoung said he didn't know
that he had a daughter.
Are you saying
he knew about her all along?
I guess that's why
he seems to feel really bad for her.
I thought that was perhaps
why he was so nice to Hyo-myoung.
I had no idea
he's the kind of person
who mixes personal feelings with business.
Now, let me get this straight.
He and Yoo Hyo-myoung
are in a relationship
and that's why he picked her
as the principal designer,
not you.
Please excuse me for a second.
[ You were right. ]
Women are
supposed to marry men
who love them more than they love men.
What's the point of saying that now?
I will kill him.
I wish he's dead!
I loved him so much.
How...
How could he betray me?
Tell me about it.
Is that what happiness is like?
How could he do that to a woman like you?
[ Mr. Kang Min-suk's Shocking Love Affair ]
[ Mr. Kang Has a Daughter out of Wedlock? ]
[ Ms. Yoo, the Secret Mistress ]
[ Mr. Kang Min-suk's Shocking Love Affair ]
What happened?
I don't know
how such articles are published.
- Could it be Ms. Jang?
- What?
I recently met her to comfort her
because she wasn't chosen
as the principal designer.
And she told me about
your relationship with Yoo Hyo-myoung.
She said you two had a daughter.
What?
What are you talking about? Is that true?
Did you not know about it?
Reporter Park.
[ Mr. Kang! ]
- Is it true?
- Please answer the question.
[ - Would you like to say a word?
- What's going on? ]
[ - How do you feel?
- Is the scandal real? ]
[ Mr. Kang! ]
[ Mr. Kang Min-suk
of Donghan International ]
[ and Ms. Yoo, a model and a designer,
were in a car chase, ]
[ fleeing from the reporters, ]
[ - and crashed into a 25-tonne truck. ]
- What the...
[ The two were severely injured ]
[ and were transferred to a hospital,
but passed. ]
It's me.
Make sure to keep the driver's mouth shut.
Don't cry.
You wanted this.
You said you wanted to kill him.
You said you wanted them dead.
I told you
I would do anything you want me to do.
What are you saying?
I was just angry, so...
What are you talking about?
You wanted it.
And I even killed my friend for you.
No...
No!
You're in this too.
I killed them
because that's what you wanted.
We are in this together.
We are destined to be together.
[ Chairman Lim Chul-yong ]
Yes, Reporter Park.
[ Congratulations, sir. ]
Well, thank you.
I heard you also got a promotion
and have become the head of the city desk.
[ It's all thanks to you. ]
Don't say that.
We're just helping each other.
[ Park Hyung-jun, Reporter ]
Hello.
[ It's been a long time, Ms. Jang. ]
You scumbag!
Looking at the situation,
it looks like
it's frustrating for you too.
[ You see, ]
I have got something
that you and Ms. Han Mi-young,
[ Lim Chul-yong's wife, ]
would love to hear.
What do you say? Aren't you curious?
I guess Chef Moon is
not coming today either.
Should we close the store again today?
Yoon-ja makes great gukbap.
How about we only sell gukbap today?
What?
She's right.
You can make gukbap, Yoon-ja.
What are you talking about? I can't.
Yes, you can.
Just give it a try.
I don't think your gukbap is
any worse than Chef Moon's.
Strictly speaking, that's not true.
What the...
It's definitely delicious though.
Why can't you speak more nicely?
So have you not heard
anything from Chef Moon yet?
[ Bang Da-hoon ]
Hey, Da-hoon.
- Hey!
- Goodness.
What happened?
[ Are you not coming today either? ]
I'm sorry.
I don't think I can today either.
Please tell the people for me.
Why did she do that yesterday?
Did she lie because of our village?
I mean, right after her interview,
we were told
that the construction was canceled.
Everyone said it was strange.
[ Hello? ]
You're not saying anything.
So I was right.
Hey, you're with her at the moment, right?
Dad, are you with Byeol-na now?
Please put her on the phone.
Tell her I miss her so much.
Seol-a.
Byeol-na isn't here at the moment,
so I can't put her on the phone.
I promise I will tell her
what you said. Okay?
I'll hang up.
Hello?
Did he hang up?
What does that mean?
Does that mean she lied at the interview
in order to save our village?
Seung-mo isn't saying much,
so I suppose so.
[ He's a horrible liar. ]
See? I told you something was off.
Goodness. What do we do?
Tell me about it.
[ Ms. Jang Sun-young ]
[ See you at the hotel's coffee shop. ]
Yu-jin?
If she didn't even contact you,
I guess she left for real.
May I ask
why Yu-jin left you,
Ms. Jang?
Yu-jin
believes her mother died because of me.
Actually,
she's right about it.
She did die because of me.
I'm sorry.
I shouldn't have said that.
Yu-jin must be having
a hard time at the moment.
The only way
I can apologize to Yu-jin is
to get Belle Ombre back
and give it back to her.
To do that,
I must take Lim Chul-yong down.
I just got a phone call from Mr. Jin.
He wanted a deal.
Excuse me?
[ I was right. ]
Lim Chul-yong hired Mr. Jin
to kill Yu-jin.
And he seems to have the evidence
to prove that.
What evidence are you talking about?
He said he would get back to me,
so I will see once I meet him.
Are you going to meet him yourself?
I should.
This is something I should solve myself.
It'll be dangerous.
Don't go alone on this one.
I'll find some people who can help.
[ Kang Min-suk ]
[ I'm finally here to see you at last. ]
[ When I was a kid, ]
[ I wondered why I didn't have a father
like everyone else. ]
[ I was also sad. ]
[ But that made me ]
[ that much curious about who my father
could be. ]
[ I'm finally getting to see you at last. ]
What kind of a father was he, Jun-su?
In my memories,
he was an incredible man.
He was a warm and compassionate person.
That's where you get that from.
Really?
When I see you next time,
do you mind
if I call you my sister?
I mind.
Call me Sister from now on.
- What?
- I'm leaving soon.
I don't know
when I'll get to see you next.
What?
I'm going now.
Thanks for bringing me to Father
before I have to leave.
Sister,
where are you heading to?
I don't know,
somewhere far.
- Yes, Chef Moon?
- Mr. Kang,
Ms. Jang would like to meet with us.
[ - Can you come with me? ]
- Why?
She apparently has the last weapon
that can tear down Mr. Lim.
Then we should definitely meet.
I guess Yu-jin doesn't know about that?
She doesn't seem like she does.
What? You met with Yu-jin?
Where is she right now?
She just left, saying that she was leaving
to somewhere far.
Enjoy your flight.
Chef Moon?
How could you just disappear like that?
Do you know how worried I was?
Why are you doing this?
Tell me!
When I saw you at the hotel,
I suddenly began to wonder
whether my existence is any good to you.
How can you be, when you just do
whatever you want all the time?
That's the kind of person I am.
I say what I want and do what I want.
You always have to have your way
and you're so much in trouble.
But
that's what I like about you.
I like you.
I...
Don't leave, Yu-jin.
Let's head to Seoha Village.
I'm not the only one
who's waiting for you.
Seol-a, Da-hoon,
and all the people in Seoha Village are
waiting for you.
[ I know you resent me. ]
It's not like I'm perfectly happy
with you,
but what's past is past.
I hope we can get back to being
on good terms again like before.
Like before?
[ When? ]
Before
you killed Kang Min-suk?
Or
after you used that
to threaten me into this marriage?
You're drunk.
Looking back,
I was too young
and too scared.
[ That's why ]
I married the man who killed my husband
and blamed
Yoo Hyo-myoung for everything.
What are you saying?
[ I thought I was the last target ]
for your greed.
I had no idea that you'd go to the extent
to hurt my father to steal his position.
Come on. You knew that he wasn't healthy.
That's nonsense.
You want to lose Jun-su, too?
Listen carefully.
This is my last warning.
If you try to pull off something
one more time,
Jun-su will end up
just like his own father.
[ Pungcheonok ]
Why is the light still on?
My back!
It's a relief that the restaurant is
still doing so well.
It's our day-off tomorrow,
so let's clean up quick and get some rest!
[ - Sounds great.
- Yes. ]
[ - Good. ]
- Wait. It's Seung-mo!
- What?
You're back!
Gosh. Chef Moon, you're back!
Chef Moon, we tried selling gukbap
by ourselves and... Gosh!
[ Look who that is! ]
It's Bella!
[ Bella! ]
Are you all better now?
Bella, you must've had a difficult time.
Your face was already small,
but it's even smaller now.
Seol-a.
I'm sorry.
Byeol-na!
Don't leave me again.
I'm going to live with you
for the rest of my life.
I'm sorry.
Please accept my apology.
[ Please? ]
Have you eaten anything?
Would you like some gukbap?
Eat a lot.
This is so good!
Yes.
You could run this place without me.
- What?
- That's nonsense.
We can't cook anything else.
[ You're being too kind. ]
You could totally learn to make
the other dishes.
- Don't you think?
- Anyone could be Chef Moon
if it just took a few days to learn
how to cook like him.
[ That's true. ]
- Indeed.
- How funny.
Bella,
I know you must've had a hard time
because of us.
- What?
[ - We know. ]
The construction stopped
as soon as your interview finished.
You think we wouldn't know?
Your life is the most important thing.
[ You don't need to think for old people
like us. ]
It breaks our hearts.
I'd like to apologize to you
[ on behalf of the county office. ]
What are you to represent
the county office like that?
Bring the county governor here tomorrow
and have him apologize to her properly.
You idiot!
I know he has no power whatsoever,
but don't you talk to him like that.
[ Fine! ]
[ Here. ]
Let's toast.
We should celebrate.
Grab a drink, everyone.
- Cheers!
This is great.
Didn't she just say politely?
What?
Seeing everyone here,
I feel
like I made the right choice.
That doesn't mean that you can live on
and just leave the precious name
Bella behind.
I'm not going to design clothes anymore,
which is why the name Bella
doesn't matter to me anymore.
And
I got a new name, Byeol-na.
Don't say that.
Bella and Belle Ombre were everything
to you.
Even if you say you don't want it back,
I'm going to get it back for you.
Don't you think you're trying too hard
to be cool these days?
I really appreciate the thought.
Just wait.
I'll get it back for you, really.
[ - I don't want to.
- Gun-woo. ]
I can't and I won't.
- Hey!
- To be honest,
I came out because I thought
that you had a new business idea.
We're not spies.
And since we're on the topic,
I was doing so well in Australia,
but I left and came to Korea for you.
Now, I can't even get severance pay.
And yet, you've called me here again
to take revenge on Mr. Lim?
- Hey.
- What?
I'm right.
It was already difficult
when he was a director.
But he's now Chairman Lim!
I don't want to be involved in this.
Gun-woo! Wait.
Let me go.
[ Sorry I'm late. ]
No worries, we just got here.
Hello.
Last night,
I had a talk with Ms. Han Mi-young.
She told me that she doesn't want
to be involved in any of this anymore
and that she wants me to leave you out
as well.
Are you going to be okay?
I think having the whole group taken away
hit her quite hard.
I'll have a talk with her.
Okay.
That'll make me feel a lot better.
Yes, ma'am.
[ When did you get here? ]
Just now.
What are you doing?
The cleaning lady will clean it all up,
no need to clean.
It's okay, I just want to do this.
What's wrong?
Mother?
Have some.
Jun-su.
Yes?
Can you not get involved in this
from now on?
Mother, I can't give up here.
I can't let my grandfather's company
end up in the hands of someone like him.
Please, I'm begging you.
I'll get going now.
Don't drink too much.
Jun-su.
[ Listen carefully. ]
I'll tell you why your father ended up
like that
[ and why he died. ]
I'll tell you everything.
I'll tell you why your father ended up
like that
[ and why he died. ]
I'll tell you everything.
[ What are you talking about? ]
You're saying
that my father didn't pass away
in an accident?
Why?
Why are you telling me this just now?
[ So that I'd stop? ]
Then you should've
kept it a secret from me until the end.
I'm sorry, Jun-su.
[ But ]
I can't lose you like that.
[ I was mistaken. ]
Lim Chul-yong is not
someone that we can battle.
I'm terrified because I don't know
what he's going to do next.
Jun-su,
I'm begging you.
Can you please stop here?
I
can't understand you.
And now,
you gave me a reason why I can't stop.
[ He wants to meet tonight. ]
[ Pungcheonok ]
Are you going to keep the restaurant open?
Actually...
I thought of closing it,
but seeing everyone yesterday,
I realized that I shouldn't.
Why?
[ It's a relief that the restaurant is
still doing so well. ]
[ A week passes by so quickly ]
when the business does so well.
Pungcheonok is owned by everyone
in this village.
It's not a restaurant that I can close
as I'd like.
Then I have a share in this too, right?
How much of a share do I get?
Just eat.
[ I'm meeting with Mr. Jin tonight. ]
[ I'll call you after. ]
He won't bring the police, would he?
- Have you been shot in the head?
- What?
If we get arrested, things are
going to get more difficult for them.
They won't hand us over.
This is Mr. Kang Jun-su.
You're Mr. Lim's son, right?
What an honor it is for you
to come out here yourself.
Let's cut the small talk.
Show me all the evidence.
[ I thought you made no mistakes. ]
[ You're the one who will be in trouble ]
[ if Sun-young finds out about Bella. ]
[ I think she's leaving for Paris tonight, ]
[ but I think it'd be best ]
[ if we just take care of everything
before she leaves. ]
[ How much do you need? ]
I have one more.
[ I didn't kill Bella. ]
[ It was ]
[ just an accident. ]
Tell me what you want.
Find me a safe way out of Korea
and give me 10 grand for my time abroad.
Give me some time.
I can't give you a lot of it.
Da-hoon, you can shower now.
I'm going to use the bathroom!
- Did you meet him?
- Yes.
Did you get the proof?
I confirmed the recordings
of Chul-yong directing murders
and Hyun-a implying
that she's not the real Bella.
That's good to hear.
I'll head to Seoul once I take care
of the restaurant business.
No, you should stay there
and take care of Yu-jin.
[ I'll take care of the things here. ]
I'd like to take revenge
on Chul-yong myself.
- What?
[ - It turns out, ]
my father and Yoo Hyo-myoung
didn't die in an accident 20 years ago.
Then what is it?
Chul-yong planned the murders
and made them look like an accident.
What?
My mom just told me about everything.
So, Yu-jin's mother...
[ Eccentric! Chef Moon ]
Are you hiding something from me?
Aren't you the one hiding everything?
[ I want to be with him. ]
[ It'd be nice if we could stay happy
together like this. ]
[ Chef Moon is very teasing. ]
That's how he snatched up her.
Are you hiding something from me?
[ Maybe he'll propose to you. ]
Dad, I'm Bella. I'm not Hyun-a.
I have a bad feeling about this.
Why did you do that? Why?
[ I don't like being exposed to danger. ]
[ It's not like he's not returning
for good. ]
I'll be back soon.
Okay.
[ Whoever you're waiting for isn't coming. ]