Byeol-na!
- Seung-mo!
- Chef Moon!
Chef Moon!
- Dad! No!
- No, Seol-a.
[ - No, you can't go in there.
- Dad! ]
Byeol-na!
Byeol-na. Wake up!
[ Byeol-na! ]
No!
What's going to happen to my dad?
What if he dies in the fire
just like my grandparents did?
No, Seol-a.
I'm sure your dad is going to be okay.
When isn't the fire department here
already? Are you sure you called them?
They'll be here!
It hasn't been long since we called.
Be patient.
Anyway, we can't go in there to check.
What are we going to do?
[ Seung-mo! ]
- Come on. Stop it. Not you too.
- Goodness.
Do you want to die too?
[ That's Seung-mo! ]
- Seung-mo!
[ - Chef Moon! ]
[ - Chef Moon!
- Chef Moon! ]
- Chef Moon!
- Chef Moon.
- The hospital.
What did you say?
- Get her to the hospital now.
- Okay.
- Right here!
- We're right here!
[ Right here! ]
[ Episode 5 ]
[ You ]
didn't tell me
that Jang Sun-young is back.
If you want me to be on your side,
you
must not hide anything from me.
[ It's over. ]
[ No Caller ID: It's over. ]
It's all over now.
Now, I just need Hyun-a to do her part.
Who are you?
Bella!
I'm sorry.
- I didn't mean to...
- You killed me.
[ Did you kill me to become me? ]
Is that why you've been plagiarizing
my designs?
No.
Stop pretending to be kind or innocent.
Why don't you be true to yourself now?
You're a fraud and murderer.
No. That's not true!
[ You're a fraud ]
- No. No, I'm not.
[ - and murderer. ]
No!
Let go of me!
[ There are no major external injuries
except for chemical inhalation. ]
[ You got her out quickly. She got lucky. ]
If she had been there a little longer,
she might not have made it alive.
Let's get her admitted
and observe her for a few days.
[ Okay. ]
- Okay.
- Thank you.
Thank you.
This is all thanks to you, Chef Moon.
Well done.
Come on. What did you just do?
What? I didn't do anything.
- Are you hurt?
- No.
- Hey!
- My gosh.
Goodness, Chef Moon. You're the one
who should be in the hospital.
- How did you put up with the pain?
- Doctor!
I'm fine. Go back home with Seol-a.
- I'll keep an eye on her.
- My gosh, you.
Okay. I'll bring you some clothes.
[ Let's go, Seol-a. ]
Dad, you must keep her safe
no matter what.
- Okay.
- We should go too.
Yes. Make sure
you get your injury treated.
Okay. Thank you. Bye.
Okay. Hey, let's go.
Officer Jo.
Can we talk?
Can you look into who this did to her
and why they tried to harm her?
I will.
Everything will be okay now.
Byeol-na.
You're up.
Where...
You're at a hospital.
What on earth happened to you yesterday?
Why did you go there?
By the way,
is there anything you remember?
A black van approached me,
asking for directions,
so I went up to them.
Where?
Then I was pulled into the van.
Stay still!
I can't remember anything from there.
I don't know.
I can't remember anything.
[ - I can't remember anything! ]
- It's okay, Byeol-na.
- No!
- Byeol-na!
- I can't remember anything!
Are you all right?
She needs some rest.
Do you mind stepping out?
- Not at all.
- Take a big breath.
One, two.
[ Just breathe slowly. Are you all right? ]
Yes, Officer Jo.
The kidnappers have been caught?
Yes,
did you get home safely last night?
It's nothing.
I was just wondering if you got in contact
with Moon Seung-mo yesterday.
[ No, why? ]
Something bad happened there
yesterday.
Something bad?
That's too bad.
By any chance, does what you do
have anything to do with him?
Mr. Park,
so what if I do?
- Sorry?
- Aren't we on the same side?
We talked about it yesterday.
Sir. Well...
You know that nothing comes for free.
[ Please take care of things for me. ]
[ And also,  ]
let's not talk for a while.
[ You know what I mean, right? ]
Hello? Mr. Jin.
It's him.
That's him?
[ He turned himself in,
saying that he set the school on fire. ]
What about the kidnapping part?
Did this old man also kidnap Byeol-na?
No, he's homeless.
He says he made a fire
because it was getting too cold.
He keeps saying that he had no idea
that there was someone inside.
Then what about the car?
Did you look into that?
We did find the black van,
[ but it was dumped on the highway
and the guys ran away. ]
[ Didn't you find anything inside? ]
[ Let me see it for myself, please! ]
What's with all the noise?
Who are you?
This is Mr. Moon Seung-mo,
the man who saved Byeol-na.
I see. Goodness,
you're a hero.
Chief is wanting
to award you the Brave Citizen Award.
- Congratulations.
- I don't need that.
What about the kidnappers?
Have you found them?
Kidnapping? What kidnapping?
Byeol-na told me that she was kidnapped
in a black van
and got dragged to the school.
You said you found the van!
It's the black van deserted on Highway 59.
The unregistered van, you know.
- That one?
- Yes.
What does that have anything to do
with kidnapping?
You're jumping to conclusions here.
There has never been such a case
in this district before.
If it's not kidnapping,
how did Byeol-na end up in a deserted
school on her way to the market?
We're going all "CSI" on this.
Do you think you're in a drama?
And how can we trust what she's saying?
She's out of her mind.
- What did you just say?
- Stop here.
[ I don't know
what else we'd be able to find,  ]
but we'll look into it and contact you
when we find something.
Take him back.
- Yes.
- Seriously...
Let's head out first.
- That man...
- Come on.
Dad.
Hyun-a.
This is a very important time for us.
What do you think you're doing?
Dad,
I don't think I can keep doing this.
What do you mean?
Living as Bella
is too painful to live.
Get it together!
We've already crossed the river.
Have you forgotten all the things
I've done for you?
Please, Dad.
I'm not Bella.
Please.
Hyun-a, you wanted to be like Bella.
That's why I did all of this.
Dad, I...
For the past 30 years,
I've done my best to serve Chairman Han,
because I wanted to be one of them.
So I endured all sorts of
degrading moments,
trying my best.
But he's still only using me.
You know
what I learned from that?
You have to take what you want
from others.
There's nothing wrong with that.
That's how the world works.
Understood?
Change up Hyun-a's security guards
to those guys.
Have them guard her 24 hours a day.
[ Yoo Byeol-na ]
Here!
Seol-a, wait for us!
Byeol-na!
Seol-a.
Byeol-na! Here!
Are you all right?
[ - Hello. ]
- Are you okay? What happened?
[ My goodness. ]
? Look how beautiful it is ?
[ Is this really the right time
to be humming? ]
The flowers are just so pretty.
Can we leave flowers in the hospital room?
I don't think it's allowed anymore.
What are you talking about?
Who visits the hospital without flowers?
What do you think?
You're right.
The flowers brighten up the room.
Byeol-na, what do you think?
Ta-da!
They're beautiful.
See? She likes them.
Fine.
It's a dangerous world out there.
How dare someone just kidnapped you
in broad daylight?
[ Exactly. You could've died. ]
It's a relief that you're fine.
You were so lucky.
That's right.
As long as you came out of
the fire pit alive and in one piece.
It wasn't just any fire.
- The entire building was on fire.
[ - Really? ]
It wasn't the whole building.
That's what it felt like.
I'm just saying. We couldn't go inside,
just not knowing what to do,
but Seung-mo jumped right inside.
[ Then what happened? ]
? And I will ?
? Save Yoo Byeol-na ?
He flew out of the fire
with Byeol-na in his arms.
- And?
- It was amazing,
even in the eyes of men like myself!
That's right! Dad was awesome!
- Right?
- He's awesome, indeed.
I think I'm falling in love with him
just hearing this story.
What are you talking about?
That's not what's important.
His back is burnt from the fire.
- That's right.
- Burnt? His back?
- Yes.
- What are you talking about?
Dad!
[ - Chef Moon!
- Are you all right? ]
It's just a very light burn.
[ My goodness. ]
I told you
to just bring her stuff here quietly.
How can I do that?
It's better if the whole village
is looking out for her. Isn't that right?
- That's right. We're family here.
[ - Have one. ]
Mr. Moon, please come
to the treatment room for your burn.
Oh, no. Is it serious?
[ That must hurt a lot. ]
Chef Moon has a nice body.
It's impressive.
Gosh, that stings. It must sting a lot.
- Oh, no. Goodness!
- Gosh!
- Gosh.
- Goodness.
- What are you guys doing there?
- Move. No, no.
- Leave now!
[ - I'm sorry. ]
- Go!
- I'm sorry.
Which course would you like today?
My skin feels chapped.
It must be because it's winter now.
Okay. I understand. Please come with me.
I must have forgotten my bag.
- Why don't I go get it for you?
- No, I'll get it myself.
[ I should sell Donghan Food's stocks. ]
[ - Why?
- Their oldest son came back ]
and is doing whatever he likes
with the company.
[ They're lucky
that they only have one son. ]
[ It's quite a mess at our company because
my children are fighting each other. ]
No, he's not the only child.
They have two children.
[ Don't you remember Mr. Lim's daughter? ]
[ I heard he hid her somewhere because
she has some kind of mental illness. ]
What are you talking about?
They have three children.
[ - What?
- You must have forgotten ]
[ since it's ancient history. ]
[ The late Kang Min-suk
had a daughter out of wedlock. ]
She's probably old enough
to be an adult now.
Right. That's right.
The illegitimate child.
[ I wonder what she's doing these days. ]
I wonder about that too.
I'm very curious
about what she's up to now.
If you hear about her,
you should let me know too.
Did everyone leave?
You told them to.
By the way,
- are you okay?
- This is nothing.
Anyway, how did you know where to find me?
Goodness.
This.
You're so sloppy.
You dropped this on the street.
Take it now.
[ How sloppy. ]
Officer Jo, any leads yet?
[ That's not why I called. ]
Reporters are going over there
to get an interview from Byeol-na.
- An interview?
[ - What should we do? ]
If this gets published in the newspaper,
they might come back.
Darn it.
- Did something happen?
- No, it's fine.
Try not to move for a second.
What?
Is anyone inside?
My gosh.
There's no story here. Let's go.
What? What are you talking about?
[ Can't you see? She has a flower
tucked behind her ear. ]
She really is crazy. Let's go.
Then, how are you going
to write that article?
There's no point. I'm sure the director
is going to kill the story.
[ Why would I waste my energy? ]
[ My gosh, the officer was right. ]
Take that out now.
No. What are you doing? I like it.
Suit yourself.
My gosh, he's so fickle.
Donghan Food's main project
is the old restaurant project.
It's one of our major businesses
as over 100 branches have opened up
in the metropolitan area and major cities.
I believe the hard work
and effort of the executives
who were in charge of this project
made this all possible.
But you didn't devise any plan
for the illegal activity,
executed by the Menu Development Team.
As I made it clear a while ago,
I will not allow our business to flourish
on such illegal grounds.
All right. Everyone,
get hands off the computers.
- Confiscate them.
[ - What? ]
- What are you doing?
- Go ahead.
[ - What are you doing? ]
- Hold on.
- You can't touch that.
[ - Hands off the computer. ]
It is truly unfortunate,
but for the sake of the company's future,
I am going to make a decision.
[ Announcement of Transfer ]
[ I'd like to show my gratitude ]
[ to Junior Managing Director Jung
and directors who were in charge ]
[ of the old restaurant project. ]
[ But sadly, they must empty their seats,
so I can lead the company ]
[ with honest and upstanding projects. ]
[ Director Choi Gun-woo ]
Hello, sir.
Let's go inside.
Is this the first decision you want
to make after your instatement?
Throwing out the employees
who have been showing good results
and replacing them with your people?
No.
It is true that their project
has been making profits for now.
They had been leading the business
by using improper means.
I believe that it'll be a risk
to the company in the long run,
which is why I made a difficult decision.
Mr. Kang.
What risk?
The biggest risk here is the fact
that you're trying to fire people
who have dedicated their lives to Donghan.
Chairman Han,
the executives are not immoral.
Although we violated some laws,
it was all for Donghan and was trivial.
That's your management principle,
isn't it?
You'll do anything for results.
What's wrong with that?
I can do anything for Donghan.
I can tell that you two both love Donghan.
Give it a try.
Give it a try your way.
But you'll have to be responsible
for the actions you're taking.
Yes.
Sounds good?
Yes, sir.
You two can stop now.
What was Bella like?
What?
I thought I knew all about her,
but I want to know more.
Who did Bella take from?
I was taught that you have to take
what you want from someone.
What are you saying?
Don't talk nonsense. Just do your job.
Sorry,
I guess I was kind of
not in the right mind
since this is my first big project.
Don't you ever get so delusional.
Lim Hyun-a, this isn't your project.
This is Bella's.
[ Nonyang General Hospital ]
[ A week passes by so quickly. ]
Is everything good?
All good.
Isn't staying there uncomfortable?
It's not bad. How's Seol-a?
She's beside me right now.
Dad! How's Byeol-na doing?
[ I've been reviewing ]
[ what Byeol-na taught me! ]
[ Seol-a! ]
[ Don't snatch the phone away
when adults are talking. ]
She's coming out tomorrow, right?
Should we go pick you guys up?
No, I'll take her.
Just have the house clean.
I'm always cleaning.
Dad, Uncle Da-hoon hasn't been cleaning!
The house is a mess.
[ You keep making messes everywhere! ]
[ No, Uncle Da-hoon did it! ]
[ - It was you!
- No, he was the one! ]
- It was you!
- No, it was you!
Bye now.
Hello?
What was that?
Where did she go?
Gosh.
What are you doing?
Are you applying cream on your burn?
I'll help you.
I can do it.
Give it to me, I'll do it for you.
I'm really fine.
Take your shirt off.
What?
What's there to be so embarrassed about?
What are you doing now? Hurry.
Come on.
You must've been in pain.
When I go into the kitchen to cook,
there are a lot of dangers waiting for me.
There are knives, fire,
hot water, hot oil, and more.
If I zone out for even just a moment,
I'd get hurt.
People think
that one becomes a good chef
with some special sense of smell or taste.
But that's not it.
Until you find your own dish,
you're in that danger,
getting injured, burnt,
and cut.
That's why you become patient.
Or else, you can't be a chef.
You're acting all tough.
Why go through so much pain?
Because I love it.
Because I love what I do.
That hurts!
I told you that I'd do it!
You should be thanking me!
Did I ask you to help me?
You did that on purpose, didn't you?
No!
Why are you whining when I helped you?
Whatever. I won't help you again.
[ Moon Seung-mo ]
Moon Seung-mo?
Yes, he's one of the most renowned chefs
in and out of Korea.
And he's perfect
for our premium Korean food project.
Is something bothering you?
Moon Seung-mo?
[ Moon Seung-mo ]
You know what I learned from that?
You have to take what you want
from others.
[ Don't you ever get so delusional. ]
This isn't your project.
This is Bella's.
[ I can see it clearly ]
[ now that I've looked into them. ]
[ They're not original. ]
[ They're plagiarized. ]
[ They say plagiarism is a talent as well. ]
[ I guess they're not
completely worthless. ]
[ Are you mentally unstable? ]
[ I have a friend who's a doctor ]
[ and he can be of help. ]
You'll feel well after you get some sleep.
Good night.
Hey,
We'll be framed as murderers
if we get caught, won't we?
What are you talking about?
We won't get caught.
You start working next week, right?
Yes, sir. Thank you for your concern.
I'll work harder.
I've almost finished studying the company.
How much have you found out
about the collaboration with Bella?
I found out that we will have to build
more lines at our existing factories
in order to secure the supply increase
due to the collaboration,
and that we need to prepare
in case there is a shortage.
That's not enough.
We need to build more factories,
and we need more warehouses
to prepare for traffic.
Sir...
[ I think it may be too much, considering
it's a one-time collaboration. ]
Why don't you consider a subcontractor?
Who says a collaboration with Bella
will end as a one-time deal?
Sorry?
- This is...
- It's the whole district of Nonyang.
That's where the new warehouse
will be built.
Why Nonyang, sir?
What are you thinking about?
Here.
Just...
I was wondering who I really am.
"Was I really a beggar
who stole someone's money?"
"Why was I at that school?"
Just those things.
Why are you acting all serious?
It doesn't suit you.
Who could have wanted to kill me?
What if they try again?
Why?
Do you want to be the damsel in distress?
When you get your memory back,
[ it might turn out to be nothing. ]
If they come back,
I'll just save you again.
I can't wait to go home and eat your food.
[ Hospital ]
Close the window. It's cold.
Seol-a!
Da-hoon!
Where is he?
- Where did they go?
- Wait.
I know where Painter is.
Where is he?
Welcome...
Gosh, look who's here!
[ It's Chef Moon and Byeol-na. ]
Are you back from the hospital?
Are you all better now?
Yes, ma'am.
Seung-mo.
Why didn't you tell me you were coming?
I wanted to welcome you back at home.
Gosh, you're making me worried
with your painting.
What do you mean?
You always got scammed
whenever you painted for a woman.
You lost your academy because...
No! It's not that this time!
[ Gosh, you surprised me. ]
What are you guys talking about?
Nothing, ma'am.
We met last time, didn't we?
I heard a lot about you from my mom.
I'm...
Gong Da-mi.
Hyo-sook.
She's my daughter, Gong Hyo-sook.
Da-mi, my foot.
Are you still doing that?
I paid the naming center 100 dollars
for that name.
Why do you keep calling yourself Da-mi?
Mom! I paid you back that 100 dollars.
- Hyo-sook?
- I said it's Da-mi.
I'm going to change my name.
To Gong Da-mi.
She ran away to Seoul with all my money,
saying she's going to take
modeling classes or something,
but she lost everything
and came back penniless.
Why would you say that to them?
You're embarrassing me.
Gosh, so you know that
you should be embarrassed?
But too bad. It's for a fact.
I'm going to make you pay for everything,
including interest.
Gosh, I'm leaving.
Hyo-sook!
I mean, Da-mi!
Where are they going?
They should be working!
Ms. Byung-chun, have you seen Seol-a?
Seol-a?
Bong-doo said
he was taking her to the market.
?Hey?
? What's wrong with my age? ?
? There's no age in love ?
Since I bought you snacks,
you have to learn Chinese from me
starting tomorrow.
[ - You promised, right? ]
- Sure. Okay.
[ Isn't that Yoon-ja? ]
Gosh, Chef Moon! Byeol-na.
Are you all better?
Yes, sir. But where's Seol-a?
I met Yoon-ja on the way,
and she said that Seol-a was too messy
and that she would bathe her,
so I dropped her off there.
- At Yoon-ja's place?
- Yes.
When will you be all grown up?
If you keep making a mess like this,
your dad will make a fuss about it.
Gosh, you...
Hurry up and take your shirt off.
- Am I that messy?
- Come on.
When did that happen? That's so strange.
You must have a hole in your chin.
Or maybe
you can't see well
because your eyes are bad!
I'm ticklish!
You should come to the bathhouse with me
in the afternoon.
That's what you have to do in winter.
I'm bribing you with my kiss.
You smart girl.
Very smart!
How are you?
I'm not fine.
What time is it?
I told you not to be late.
Yoon-ja was nagging me to bathe.
You bathed at Yoon-ja's place?
No wonder you're sparkling
even more today.
Good job. Let's get studying now.
I don't know what Bong-doo fed her,
but she was a mess, so I washed her up
before sending her out.
I think she said that she was heading
to the village hall.
Is that right?
She had yummy food without me?
Who am I?
I'm the head of
the women's society and the village.
[ So, Seol-a,  ]
you're under two groups
that I'm in charge of.
Then is it okay that you can't read?
People are going to criticize me,
saying I didn't take good care
of the village.
Is that okay or not?
- It's not okay.
- That's right.
That's why you need to focus and learn
how to read. Understood?
- Yes!
- Now,
I taught you how to read
the consonants.
I'm going to check if you remember.
Let's see if you remember. What's this?
- K!
[ - Good. What about this one? ]
[ - N!
- Good. What about this? ]
- T?
- Perfect!
What's this, on top of the ribbon?
- R?
- You're a genius!
- What about this?
- B.
[ Correct. What about this one? ]
[ - S!
- You're doing great. ]
[ What's this? ]
[ - W?
- That's right. ]
[ - What about this?
- J. ]
[ You're doing excellent.
This one is going to be hard. ]
I was so frustrated
because I'm so busy taking care of myself
and I wondered
why Seol-a had to come into my life.
That's why I got mad.
But...
I didn't do anything.
It wasn't me who has been
taking care of Seol-a.
It was the village people all along.
The entire village has been raising her.
You're thankful, aren't you?
Then why don't you do something
to express your gratitude?
Do what?
Well... Whatever
you do the best.
That's what you can do.
Where are you going?
Get in!
Where are we going?
[ I'm hungry. ]
[ These are good. ]
[ That's popular. ]
- These are good?
[ - Yes. ]
- Could I get some of this?
- Yes.
[ Here you go. ]
[ Try this one. ]
Hello.
Could I see some meat for making soup?
[ - For soup? ]
- Yes.
Are we having meat?
Try this. It's good.
I want some too.
Hello.
Could I get some garlic, please?
How much is this?
- I'll take these.
- All right. Just a second.
Yes.
I'm on my way.
No, it's nothing like a party.
It's just to have everyone together
since she came back home.
[ You want me to call everyone, right? ]
[ Okay. Leave that to me! ]
Leaving anything to you is
the most difficult thing I have to do.
Don't let it get too big.
It's a party!
A party?
Call everyone.
Seung-mo is cooking for everyone.
Call everyone!
- Really?
- Yes!
Grandpa, Chef Moon is holding
a party tonight.
- Are you home?
[ - A party! ]
- Are you free tonight?
- Chef Moon is throwing a party.
[ - Come quickly. ]
[ Get ready and come quickly. ]
Why is everyone on their phones?
What's going on?
Why is everyone so excited?
Seung-mo is holding a party
to thank everyone in the village.
- Really?
- Yes!
Is Dad and Byeol-na home now?
Of course! They've been waiting for you.
She's so excited.
I have to make a call to my honey as well.
He's throwing a party?
That's so extra of him.
Chef Moon likes to make a ruckus,
doesn't he?
Yes. I was heading home anyway.
Wait for me.
- Sir.
- Yes? What's up?
The county chief is looking for you.
Why would he be looking for me?
I don't know. Just go to his office.
[ County Chief Office ]
[ Come in. ]
Hello, I'm Hwang Jang-dan.
Hello.
- Come this way.
- Okay.
Greet them.
They're guests from Seoul.
You know Donghan Group, right?
That's where they're from.
Yes, sir.
Jang-dan, you're living
in Seoha Village, right?
Yes, sir.
Then you've got a lot of work to do
from now on.
[ Nonyang Warehouse Construction Map ]
Here.
It's good!
Oh, meat.
It's good, Chef Moon!
[ - There's so much food.
- I know. ]
- There's more coming.
- Gosh.
- Goodness!
- Oh, gosh.
[ Goodness. ]
It's not much, but I hope you enjoy it.
What do you mean? There's so much food.
Gosh, by the looks of it,
I guess you're feeling all better.
[ You rude thing. ]
How can you eat like that
when the elderly haven't started yet?
I know. She might finish everything.
- Hurry up and eat.
- Yes.
[ Go on. ]
I prepared a lot, so please don't rush.
I'm sorry I didn't introduce myself
properly until now.
I was a chef in Seoul.
We know that, of course.
Your mother used to brag about you
all the time.
She said you were our country's
world-class chef.
[ A world-class chef! Give him a hand! ]
Look at him being shy.
What's this party for, though?
Chef Moon is thanking you for
looking after Seol-a while we were away.
What? Then this is all thanks to Seol-a?
Gosh,
this little thing must be a lucky charm.
[ She's feeding us all this good food. ]
What are you all doing?
Why aren't you thanking her already?
- Yes, we should do that.
[ - Seol-a, my lady. ]
Thank you for the food.
- Thank you very much, Seol-a.
- Thank you.
It's no problem. Just eat up.
Gosh, look at you.
Anyway, look at all this.
I guess Chef Moon really is a chef,
after all.
I bet customers would rush in
from all over the country
if he opened a restaurant.
I'm a bit of an expert with food,
and his skills are too good
to be wasted in this tiny little village.
Yes, he's right.
Look at all this.
This isn't anything ordinary.
Eat up...
Gosh, Byeol-na. Slow down.
You're going to choke to death.
Goodness. Seriously.
[ Seung-mo! ]
Seung-mo!
What's that?
Ms. Pi told me to bring this over
from the village hall.
Gosh.
It's the karaoke machine.
We can't just sit around
and eat like animals.
We need to sing and digest the food.
Am I right?
- Cheers.
- Let's all have a drink.
- Cheers!
- Gosh.
All right. Thank you for your patience.
Now,
we will begin the party
you've all been waiting for!
- Hooray!
- Yes.
The first performance will be
from our village mascot, the cutie pie...
Please sit down, ma'am.
Please welcome our village mascot, Seol-a!
- A round of applause!
- Gosh, Seol-a!
- That's my girl!
- Seol-a, what number will it be?
- I don't need any music.
- What? No music?
Gosh, that little thing has some nerves.
She really is something.
- Let's watch.
- One, two, three, four!
?Hey?
[ Gosh, it's a trot song! ]
- ?What's wrong with my age? ?
- Gosh, she's so cute!
- ?There's no age in love ?
[ - Come on. ]
That's my girl!
? I have one heart ?
[ One heart! ]
? And I have one feeling ?
[ One feeling! ]
? You are my one true love ?
[ That's my girl! ]
? I'm tearing up ?
? What's wrong with my age? ?
[ You go, girl! ]
? It's the greatest age to love ?
- Goodness!
- Look at her!
- Please give her a big round of applause!
- Good job!
- You were great!
Who would like to go next?
- Me, me!
- What?
I'm going to sing my favorite song,
"Amor Fati".
- Not that song again!
- Not that song!
- I want to go first.
- What?
"You, Clouds, Rain" by Heize.
- Yes, you go next, Hyo-sook.
- All right, come on out.
Sing a pretty song for us.
[ Good job, Hyo-sook. ]
Your daughter is so pretty.
[ - She is, isn't she?
- Yes. ]
We're in trouble.
This is not the time for a party!
What's going on?
They're going to tear down
our whole village!
- What?
- What are you talking about?
What do you mean, "tear down"?
They're going to get rid of our village?
Honey, can't you make it simple for us?
Donghan Group made the difficult decision
to invest in Nonyang.
They've decided to build
a big factory and warehouse
in Seoha Village.
[ Nonyang Warehouse Construction Map ]
It's your village, so make sure
to get the consent of your neighbors
so we don't have to force anything.
[ This is all for our district.
You should do what you can, don't you? ]
Yes, sir.
So all the houses in our village,
starting from the mountain back there,
will be torn down!
"Torn down"? What is he talking about?
Who would build a factory?
You know, Donghan!
[ The big company in Seoul! Donghan Group! ]
- They're going to build a factory here!
- Donghan?
Donghan?
Donghan, you say?
[ Eccentric! Chef Moon ]
So you're saying,
they want to wipe out our village?
[ Here's to Donghan Group and Nonyang! ]
Mr. Lim! Mr. Lim!
[ Donghan Group is trying to
wipe out Seoha Village. ]
[ Are we just going to let that happen? ]
That's enough, all of you!
You think Moon Seung-mo is that great?
- He's the best.
- We have no hope.
Will an alternative plan work?
[ What's wrong, Chef Moon?
You look distracted. ]
[ What kind of fate is this? ]
I'm never letting them have their way.
I'll do my best to help.
What if Bella never comes back?
Are you crazy?
[ - Take care of it for me.
- What's this? ]
I found out who Bella is today.