[ Episode 13 ]
- What's this about?
- Sir.
The police are going to reinvestigate
the fire at Pungcheonok in Seoul.
What should I do?
What about that?
Will that be a problem for us?
No, it won't.
But I looked into this a little deeper.
And I found out this reinvestigation was
launched by Nonyang Police Station.
Nonyang?
Isn't that where Seoha Village is?
Yes.
Go home.
[ It turns out, ]
[ my father and Yoo Hyo-myoung ]
[ didn't die in an accident 20 years ago. ]
Then what is it?
Chul-yong planned the murders
and made them look like an accident.
[ My mom just told me about everything. ]
What?
So, he killed...
[ If I pushed forward with the construction
of the clothing industrial complex, ]
I would have regretted it.
I would have missed my chance
of witnessing such a great restaurant.
What brings you here?
It is my duty as a businessman
to visit the talented chef
[ who runs a good restaurant in person. ]
When I withdrew the plan to develop
the clothing industrial complex,
I thought I may have unintentionally
harmed the village,
so I was sorry about it.
And I wanted to make a good business offer
to you while paying the village a visit.
So here I am.
From what I've heard,
your gukbap is to die for.
I know it's late,
but could I try some before I go?
Please leave.
Gosh, I'm so disappointed.
I know it is very late to ask for food,
but I'm a customer, too.
Get out
right now.
Why?
Are you hiding something?
Don't you have more things
to hide than me?
That was Lim Chul-yong, wasn't it?
Do you think he figured out that I'm here?
What's wrong, Yu-jin?
Were you going to leave Korea
because of Lim Chul-yong?
Chef Moon.
What if people in our village get
in trouble because of me again?
Don't worry. That won't happen.
I should get my ducks in a row too.
What's your plan?
- Tell me about your plan too.
[ - Yu-jin. ]
I'll take care of this.
I'm just worried that
something might happen to you.
I don't want you or the village
to be in danger.
It's not a bad feeling.
Having someone worry about you.
- Aren't you hungry?
- What?
No, I'm okay.
You really changed.
You used to make a fuss
because you were hungry at this hour.
Come on.
Wait.
It's ready. Try it.
What's this?
Magical porridge
that gets rid of your anxiety.
Gosh, there's no such thing.
Wasn't I right?
Yes, Chef Moon.
Chairman Lim Chul-yong
just paid me a visit.
What?
I have a bad feeling about this.
I'll go with you
when you meet up with Mr. Jin.
So you'll continue
to cause trouble to the end?
Mom.
I kept my promise
to keep you safe.
So give me a compliment.
But
I'm going to stop making clothes.
I'm just exhausted.
But I hope you won't scold me for that.
I was still able to fulfill the dream
you couldn't.
Tell me that I can stop now
and I did a good job
if you can hear me now.
And
I'm not sure if I could stay here.
I want to stay with him.
Staying here in this village
and living a happy life
with the people here would be nice.
But I keep making things hard for them.
Please tell me
what I should do.
[ Byeol-na! ]
[ - My goodness, she's there.
- Over there. ]
[ - Gosh.
- Hey! ]
[ - She's over there.
- Byeol-na. ]
My goodness. Are you all right?
Where have you been? Goodness.
I was visiting my mom's grave.
- What?
- Her mom's grave.
- Were you at Hyo-myoung's grave?
But what are you doing this morning?
- What?
- Goodness.
What are you hiding?
- Well...
- We were just...
We were exercising.
- A morning workout.
- Yes!
- Everyone was exercising.
- Right.
- Right? We started working out.
- Yes.
[ That's right.
We worked out since morning. ]
- My gosh, my body aches now.
- Right.
You should have washed your face first.
What?
- I see.
[ - Right. ]
[ You can tell that we didn't, right?
We should've washed up. ]
Dad, wake up.
Dad! Wake up.
Seol-a, what's wrong?
Byeol-na is gone again.
- What?
[ - What? ]
I looked everywhere, but she's not here.
Ms. Pi!
Hey, Da-hoon.
What are you talking about?
Byeol-na is gone?
My gosh. Okay.
Okay. I got it. I'm on my way.
Honey, wake up. Byeol-na is gone again.
Someone must have kidnapped her.
Come out now.
- What?
[ - Oh, not again. ]
What?
Yes, Chul-nam.
I think Byeol-na got abducted again.
What? The police?
Yes. We must call them.
Didn't I say it was nothing?
What?
What happened to the guy
who talked about calling the police?
Be quiet.
I, the police officer,
will go to work now.
Yes. Go on. Hurry.
If we're late,
Chef Moon will give us an earful.
Let's hurry. Okay. Let's go.
- Chef Moon.
What are you doing here?
- Exercising.
- I'm examining.
- What?
No. Exercising!
I'm exercising.
Were you exercising this morning too?
Well, yes.
You've become very diligent
while I was away.
Right?
I guess.
Then, I can't be the only lazy one.
Starting tomorrow, I'll join you.
[ - Sure.
- Okay. ]
- Sounds great. Yes!
- Yes.
Let's hurry. We must open the restaurant.
[ - Bye. ]
- See you later.
That punk, Bang Da-hoon.
[ He called me up in the morning
and made a huge fuss. ]
[ That good-for-nothing. ]
Did you visit your mother?
Next time, tell me in advance,
so we can go together.
Okay.
Come to think of it,
I came back to Korea for my mom.
Thanks to that, I got to meet you.
Right. I forgot to
say something to my mom.
I forgot to thank her.
[ Byeol-na! ]
Why are you out here?
Did you cry?
I thought you were gone again,
so I got scared.
What happened?
What? Did something happen?
We're on our way back from our workout.
Let's go.
[ Mr. Kang Jun-su ]
[ I'm going to meet up with Mr. Jin
four days from today. ]
Da-hoon.
I need to talk to you.
You want to teach the elders how to cook?
Yes. I need to be in Seoul
four days from today.
Seeing how invested they are, I realized
I shouldn't close
the restaurant whenever I want.
You're right.
What is this about?
Why are you going to Seoul?
To take back the name, Bella,
and Belle Ombre
from Lim Chul-yong,
I need to see someone.
But I don't want Byeol-na to know.
But if you tell them
you'll teach them how to cook,
won't they think it's weird?
"Chef Moon,
where are you going without us?"
I'm sure they'll say that.
Then, Byeol-na will think it's odd too.
That's why I'm telling you this first.
Do you have any ideas?
Let's see.
Wait.
I'm getting back the inspiration
I have lost.
[ Great. I'll draw you a big picture. ]
It will be very smooth,
but elaborate at the same time.
No, don't do it. I don't need your help.
No, just trust me on this.
I'm Bang Da-hoon.
[ Anyway, ]
you need to teach the people
in the village how to cook
without raising any suspicions
from Byeol-na, right?
Hello, Da-hoon.
[ Mr. Hwang. ]
You told me that a while ago, a TV station
wanted to introduce Pungcheonok
on their channel.
Can I meet with them today?
Sure thing.
Actually, they did call me before.
This all worked out.
Isn't this place great?
Have a seat.
I didn't expect a place like this
around here.
I heard you wanted to suggest something
for the documentary.
- Yes, sir.
[ - We only need ]
some shots,
and the editing will do the rest.
And you expect it to get high ratings?
I have an amazing idea.
[ Documentary Project Proposal ]
The documentary project proposal.
What?
So what is that supposed to be?
I was wondering what you were doing,
slacking off from work.
What is that nonsense?
Now...
We're supposed to be on TV, right?
[ But, they didn't seem
too thrilled about it, ]
so I asked Mr. Hwang to introduce me
to the production staff
to settle it once and for all.
- Are we going camping?
- Yes.
So, the whole village will go camping,
and there, Chef Moon will teach us
how to cook.
It will be the story of the world's
best chef, Moon Seung-mo,
and his clumsy assistants
growing together.
[ And in the end, ]
they will be able to run the restaurant
without Seung-mo,
which will be the heartwarming...
If we run it without Dad,
what will he do?
What? Well...
He needs some rest.
[ Belle Ombre ]
Ma'am...
Please keep it down.
I'm here to check what the people think.
The value of your clothes soared
once again after that incident.
There are a lot of merchandisers
from foreign luxury brands,
and we're getting more interest
from VIP guests, as you can see.
[ Excuse me, could you help me out? ]
One moment, ma'am.
Isn't this so pretty?
But did you hear about that?
[ Belle Ombre and Donghan are merging. ]
What? Why?
- Belle Ombre is doing that?
- Yes.
Are they insane?
[ I heard it's because Bella's dad
is the chairman of Donghan. ]
But still,
if Belle Ombre merges with Donhan,
it won't be a luxury brand.
I know. It's a bit odd.
[ - It's pretty though, isn't it?
- Let's go. ]
[ Did you find Mr. Jin? ]
He must be determined this time, sir.
We couldn't find a trace at all.
How will you manage to be
the head of Donghan Food like that?
I'm sorry, sir. But...
Sir.
We were keeping an eye on Mr. Kang,
and we sensed something unusual.
Jun-su? What?
Mr. Kang and Choi Gun-woo
are meeting up with smugglers
and passport forgers.
- What?
[ - I'm guessing ]
it has to do with Mr. Jin.
That's what Jun-su is up to?
[ Sir, Ms. Lim Hyun-a is here to see you. ]
Tell her to wait.
What do you think you're doing?
I didn't want to wait.
Hyun-a!
Dad, I'm Bella. Not Hyun-a.
All right, Bella.
What brings you here all of a sudden?
Is something wrong?
Cancel the merger between Belle Ombre
and Donghan International.
- What?
- Just leave Belle Ombre to me.
[ I'll hold a solo fashion show soon ]
and show you myself.
Mine and Belle Ombre's value.
What are you doing, Seol-a?
Since you came back,
I wanted to wear this again,
but I noticed there was a rip.
I tried to keep it safe
since it's valuable, but...
I didn't know you could sew.
I have to try.
If I keep practicing,
I'll get better, won't I?
Give it here. I'll do it for you.
You don't have to...
Watch carefully.
Like this.
You go this much...
And come back.
You really seem like a different person
when you're sewing and making clothes.
There.
All done.
Gosh, you're so fast!
[ Seol-a. ]
We have to get up early tomorrow
to go camping, so go to bed.
Dad, look at this!
What is it?
Did Yu-jin do this for you?
Gosh, it would be amazing
if she made another one like this.
[ - Right, Seol-a? ]
- Yes.
That won't make me want to start again.
Is it because of Ms. Jang?
After you disappeared, I met Ms. Jang.
She looked really bad.
She said she was going to get back
Belle Ombre to return it to you
and apologize.
When I was having a hard time
after my mom died,
Madam Jang took me to Paris.
[ Keep the space! ]
[ It's getting crooked. Focus! ]
Pay attention!
[ What are you doing? Continue. ]
I spent every single day
studying fashion design
and faced my mom's death each day.
It was too much at first,
but I told myself it was for my mom.
I also thought the reason Madam Jang
was being so hard on me
was all for my mom.
[ But... ]
It was all
so that she could ease her own guilt.
I'm sure she thought she was repaying
for the betrayal on her friend,
who loved her like a sister,
through me, her daughter.
[ But she was using it as an excuse ]
to become the top again.
Through Belle Ombre.
I don't know much about her,
but I felt her sincere feelings
towards you.
[ Don't think of it so badly. ]
Let's stop talking about Madam Jang.
We need to get up early tomorrow.
I'd better get to bed.
Good night.
[ Yu-jin is with me at Seoha Village. ]
[ Don't worry about her. ]
[ That's good to hear. ]
[ Please take care of Yu-jin ]
[ until everything gets handled. ]
Auntie, my wrist hurts.
I can't do any more.
Why are you acting like a baby?
Snap out of it and get started.
What are you doing? Hurry up!
Mom...
Who are you looking for?
You don't have a mom!
You are alone in this world.
You exist alone!
Here. Get to work.
Get it together.
Start the machine.
And keep the distance.
Focus on the movement of the needle.
That's it. Good job.
Yu-jin.
You got accepted
to Antwerp.
Really?
Gosh. I knew you could do it!
Good job. Well done.
Yu-jin.
I'm sorry.
[ CHTV ]
Seung-mo.
Do you really think
we'll be able to run the restaurant
after a few days?
We need to make it happen.
What's taking them so long?
Hurry up and come out!
Aren't you cold, Hyo-sook?
What do you mean? Fashion is all about
going against the weather.
Gosh, style is all about looking cool.
Haven't you heard of "swag"?
Oh, is that why you're wearing
that pleated skirt in front of Bella?
There's no answer to fashion.
Just follow your own style.
That's right.
[ But you might catch a cold ]
if you stay out for too long.
It will be a long shoot.
Don't worry.
Gosh!
Hyo-sook, are you all right?
Hurry up and wear this. I'm good.
I said I'm all right!
Goodness.
- My gosh!
- Goodness!
Yoon-ja! Slow down!
- Gosh!
- Slow down!
Is everyone here?
Why didn't you bring your car?
Our car broke down.
If we're going to cook there,
we need all this.
Don't even bother.
She was even trying to load firewood here.
I had such a hard time stopping her.
[ But still,
we're going to need a fireplace ]
if we're going camping. Gosh.
Yoon-ja. Don't you worry about that.
This way!
- Hello!
- Come this way.
Over here.
- Hello!
- Stop here.
Goodness!
I knew you had good taste, Jang-dan!
Chef Moon's Cooking Camp! Load it up!
- Help me carry this.
- Okay.
Why did you bring a vacuum?
[ - Gosh.
- Careful. ]
[ Be careful! ]
This way.
[ I'm meeting the smuggler today. ]
What's this?
Are you hiding something from me?
Of course not.
Is it...
Because you're nervous?
Gosh, it's because
I have no idea where to start
in order to teach them cooking.
Why did that punk have to set this up?
What are you worried about?
You'll be there, anyway.
It's just a show.
Sure.
Still, they'll have to be able
to do it without me.
- Goodness!
- Here.
That's pretty! There you go.
Is it good? Take one for me too.
Lower it a bit more.
Have you been here before?
- It's my first time.
- Is it?
The camera is on here.
Wait a minute...
Right here.
It's not heavy.
- I feel much better.
- Yes.
Look, this is where we will sleep.
So we're sleeping here?
Sure. You're doing a good job.
I did this before.
[ We will be using this. ]
[ What is that? That's pretty. ]
- Right?
[ - Yes. ]
[ Sure. ]
[ Pull this side up a bit. ]
[ - Yes. Tie it there.
- Okay. ]
Mr. Choi?
[ Chef Moon's Cooking Camp ]
[ The smugglers are ready. ]
[ We have two days now. ]
How much money do we need?
I got the lawyer to retract
the Jaeil PE private equity fund,
but that's going to take some time.
I'll figure out a way. Let's get out.
Did my warning sound like a joke to you?
What are you talking about?
I haven't been doing anything
ever since you told me not to.
No, not you.
I meant Jun-su.
He's working very hard.
Did you not tell him
that he'll end up like his father?
Please, please don't do that.
He's your son, too.
That's why I came all the way here
to warn you.
What can I do for you?
I'll do anything.
Please don't hurt Jun-su.
[ Please, I'm begging you. ]
Go straight down this way.
Good.
I'm chopping the radish non-stop here.
How long do we need to do this for?
I know how filming works.
Do we really have to do it like this?
Seung-mo, can't we stop here?
Chef Moon, let's stop. This is pointless.
Keep your pace up and chop consistently.
Keep everything this size, all right?
I'm now going to start talking
about the menus.
It's not our main menu,
but a new one that you can make easily
at home.
Dad, is it made with the sausages here?
Yes.
Is cooking them really necessary?
They're good as they are.
Let's get working.
Please heat up your frying pan.
Okay.
Take a sausage and put it on the pan.
Next, pour in about 1cm of water.
You don't need any oil.
Just keep cooking the sausage
until the water has evaporated.
Once the water has evaporated,
cook the sausage until it's toasted.
Once the sausage is cooked,
turn off the heat
and transfer it to the other pan.
Like this.
Wipe your frying pan clean
to start working on the egg pilaf.
[ Yes, sir. ]
I can't help myself,
I'm going to try some of it.
This is hot.
[ It's delicious. ]
It's so juicy.
My goodness.
This is some intense training.
We've still got a long way to go.
We don't have time.
We can't run a restaurant like this.
I thought you said
that it's our restaurant.
We have to sell menus other than gukbap.
You think food is a joke to people?
When the flavors change even slightly,
restaurants fail just like that.
Fine.
But don't you think this is too much?
It's not like you're never coming back.
Where are you going?
I have to prepare for a class
after dinner.
Take it easy!
We're on a camping trip,
for goodness' sake!
What is it?
I don't have a lot of time.
Jun-su,
let me know if you need help
with anything.
I was being too weak.
[ I just want to help, ]
so let me know
if you need anything.
Mother,
actually,
I'm retracting my private equity fund
[ to collect enough money to pay Mr. Jin, ]
but I don't think I can make it
by the deadline.
How much do you need?
I'll help you out.
Thank you.
No worries.
[ When and where ]
is this exchange happening?
[ - I think I did quite a good job.
- It's driving me crazy. ]
[ This is... ]
I told you, we can't use the fish
if you prepare it like this.
Do it again.
Seriously?
- Show me.
- This is really good.
That's spot-on.
Chef Moon,
don't you think we're working too hard?
It's just our first day.
And I mean that both for yourself
and for the rest of the village people.
We have to work hard. Pass me the knife.
- I'll do it.
I told you, you shouldn't do that.
[ Are you okay? ]
- I'm fine.
- Chef Moon...
Let me just go wash my hand up.
[ - What's wrong?
- You should hold it with your hand. ]
Why are you doing this?
- What do you mean?
- It's weird.
We all thought we were just going camping.
You're hurt and people overworked
because you...
What?
They have to learn how to cook, too.
If the restaurant belongs to everyone
and not just me,
everyone needs to do their part.
That's what everyone has been doing now.
[ Yoon-ja prepares ingredients, ]
- Are they fighting?
[ - Ms. Byung-chun cleans, ]
[ Ms. Pi tidies everything up, ]
Bong-doo takes care of parking,
and Chul-nam is on the finances.
Everyone is doing their best...
[ Maybe Chul-nam messed up
on the finances. ]
[ My goodness. ]
- What do we do?
- Is this all my fault?
- Yes, it's all your fault.
- Darn you.
[ Byeol-na, don't be too disheartened. ]
[ He must be feeling extra pressured ]
[ because he's taking
on his parents' restaurant name. ]
[ You're right. Don't be too sad. ]
[ But Chef Moon was too harsh for sure. ]
[ He's too by-the-books. ]
[ Donghan ]
[ Han Mi-young ]
[ Two days later at 11 pm, ]
[ Pyeongtaek Port Distribution Facility. ]
Motherly love,
indeed.
Give me the money first.
See it for yourself.
It's perfect.
It's really dark.
How are you taking photos?
Wait.
I'd like to meet tomorrow instead.
What do you mean?
Someone is following us.
[ You've been busted? ]
[ Don't worry too much. ]
[ But I'm meeting up with him
tomorrow instead. ]
- Tomorrow?
[ - Yes. ]
[ And ]
you're going to have to meet Mr. Jin
[ since they're following me. ]
All right, then.
Good work, everyone!
It was nothing.
Let's eat.
[ - We're doing great.
- We are. ]
Chef is an artist.
- You're right.
- Lower your voice.
[ Absolutely. ]
[ He didn't mean it, don't worry. ]
We planned for a series of classic blue,
the color of the year.
[ - We... ]
- That's too cliche.
[ We used a variety of classic blue... ]
Get out.
- Sorry?
- Don't come back again.
- What?
- Ma'am,
the planning team took the whole night
to prepare this.
Ms. Seo,
do you not want to come back
from the next meeting on as well?
I'm sorry.
It's not a Donghan International show,
it's a Bella show.
I don't want to see anyone else
for this meeting
except for Ms. Seo from the next meeting.
I'm going to work on the designs,
so get a new team for the next meeting.
I said, I'm going to work on my designs.
Yes, ma'am.
Let's head out.
Is this all? Goodness.
Give me that.
Good work, everyone.
We'll continue filming at the restaurant
in the afternoon.
- What?
You're coming to the restaurant?
My goodness.
Producer,
I don't think we can film today.
[ Sorry? ]
We can't delay our schedule.
I'm sorry.
That's okay.
[ Sure. ]
- Chef Moon!
- Thank you!
- You're the best.
- Chef Moon!
[ - Let's go!
- Chef Moon! ]
I was going to quit
if we were filming today, too!
Same here.
Chef Moon really knows
how to treat people.
That's how he got her, after all.
[ - Get in the car. ]
- All right.
This is too heavy.
My goodness.
What do we do?
NFS has handed us over all the information
on the cases
that Mr. Oh Jung-tae is involved in.
What do we do?
How did you get all of that?
"All of that"?
[ Tell me more. ]
I'll write up a good report for you.
You know that your sentence is reduced
if you come clean, right?
Right?
I don't know. I don't know anything!
You don't? All right.
[ If all of that ends up on your record, ]
[ that'll be 5, 10, ]
15 years.
Seems like you'll be in jail
until you turn into an old man.
I'm leaving now.
I'm really leaving now.
Hold on.
They want to meet at 9 pm tonight.
I'll send you the location.
[ Okay. ]
I should've been more careful.
I apologize.
[ That's okay, don't worry about it.
I'll let you know when I get there. ]
Okay.
[ What? ]
[ What do you think? ]
[ I'm exhausted. ]
[ Let's get some rest. ]
Seung-mo,
what are you doing?
[ Why are you packing already? ]
Isn't it tomorrow?
We're meeting up tonight.
What?
[ Officer Jo ]
Yes, Officer Jo.
Seung-mo!
Dad, where are you going?
Byeol-na, what's wrong with him?
Where is he going?
He got a call from Officer Jo
and he ran out like that.
What about Soon-mi?
Seung-mo!
Dad, where are you going?
Byeol-na, what's wrong with him?
Where is he going?
He got a call from Officer Jo
and he ran out like that.
What about Soon-mi?
What do you mean?
The fire at Pungcheonok in Seoul
wasn't an accident?
Remember Oh Jung-tae,
the man arrested the last time?
He's a terrible man.
When he got arrested,
all the unresolved cases related to him
were being investigated all over again,
and
one of those was
the fire accident at Pungcheonok in Seoul.
Are you saying that he started the fire?
He just confessed.
Where is he?
Why?
I don't know.
I did just as I was told.
I had no idea that people would die.
Who told you to do it?
I don't know anything,
only Mr. Jin knows.
Mr. Jin?
Sir.
Why?
We can't get in touch
with one of our spies since last night.
What?
[ Chef Moon! ]
Where are you going?
You can train us tonight.
We're all ready to be trained.
I have
something to tell you.
I won't be
- able to...
- We have something for you.
Are you still not done with it?
I'm coming!
What's this?
We prepared a lunchbox
with the recipes you taught us.
We can't guarantee you
that it'll taste good.
It'd be weird if it tasted good.
Hey, we did just as we were taught.
If it's bad, that's all your fault.
Why are you giving this to me?
We noticed that you haven't been eating
since yesterday.
We heard that you're going to Seoul today.
Have some of this and have a safe trip.
They kept asking me where you were going.
It has something to do
with your parents, right?
- Sorry?
[ - We asked ]
Soon-mi what was going on.
We don't know what it is,
but it seems like it's not for us to know.
Good luck.
Yes, sir.
Close them up before dust gets in.
Close them up.
- Careful.
- Close them up.
Put them in here.
Yu-jin...
I'm disappointed.
How could you keep it a secret
even from me?
Yu-jin.
I knew something was up
because you've been weird since yesterday.
I'm sorry, Yu-jin.
I'm sorry.
I understand. It's about your parents.
But
promise me
to never hide anything from now on.
I'll be back soon.
Okay.
Mr. Kang, I'm on my way now.
[ Okay, I'll be waiting. ]
[ Hello, there. ]
- Gun-woo?
- Come this way.
Chef Moon.
[ Passport ]
I'll be back.
Chef Moon,
take care.
- I'm here now.
[ - What about Mr. Jin? ]
I don't see him yet.
- I'll wait here.
[ - Be careful. ]
Will do.
Is that Mr. Jin?
[ Eccentric! Chef Moon ]
- He died last night.
- You pig!
You want to go and get Belle Ombre back?
Help me just this once.
Why are you so greedy
when you're so incapable?
You think you'll get away with this?
[ I want to see you ]
get back on your feet again.
[ I'll give you Belle Ombre. ]
What's wrong, Dad?
[ Do what you want to do. ]
I'm going to get back whatever was
taken away from Yu-jin.
And I will get my revenge, too.