[ So you're saying, ]
Mr. Hong, the county governor,
teamed up with Donghan
and they want to wipe out our village?
[ Don't say it like that. ]
- It's a win-win for both sides.
[ - "Win-win"? ]
Are you taking the governor's side
as a fellow civil servant?
I'm not saying this
because my daughter is the police,
but we do have to consider it
from their perspective.
It's not the time for chit-chat.
This is a serious problem,
so let's share our thoughts.
What else is there to say?
I oppose it. We all oppose it!
Yes, we oppose it.
[ I don't know what I did so wrong
in my past life. ]
Why do I have to get kicked out
of my house again?
[ After getting married in Nonyang, ]
I lost all my ancestors' land
because of the flood,
and I couldn't say a word
because I was poor and uneducated.
That's right.
Our property was submerged.
We had practically nothing to eat
and we still had to share that.
[ Our whole family had to live scattered. ]
And you want us to go through that again?
What do you mean, "submerged"?
[ It was about 30 years ago. ]
They were trying to build
a big dam over here,
and the whole of upstream Nonyang
was flooded with water.
[ I came back to a lake
when I was discharged from the military. ]
Have you all forgotten?
The reason why
we're all able to live like this?
It's all thanks to Byung-soo, isn't it?
Are you at that again?
What are you talking about?
We should never forget our roots.
[ And your dead father, too. ]
Those people fed us for nothing
[ and sold their land
to put a roof above our heads ]
[ just because they felt bad for us! ]
You shouldn't be talking like that
in this house, at the least!
What's wrong?
I don't know.
It's just so sad to hear this story.
[ Goodness. ]
Just look at her.
Byeol-na is not even from around here,
and she's this upset.
[ We can't just sit around. ]
We can't just sit around when
they're trying to wipe out our village!
Let me fill your glass, sir.
As you know, Mr. Hong,
timing is important in business.
[ Of course, sir. ]
[ Excuse me for saying this, ]
but if you can't show us results
within three months,
we will have to invest somewhere else.
[ Gosh, what are you saying? ]
It's all for the good of our district.
Who would take charge if I don't?
You can trust me.
Now, here's to Donghan Group and Nonyang!
Cheers.
[ Learning Korean Letters ]
Try not to move for a second.
What?
[ Learning Korean Letters ]
[ Byeol-na! Are you asleep? ]
Gosh.
Why is she sleeping with Seol-a's book?
[ Learning Korean Letters ]
What the...
What's wrong with me?
[ Donghan International ]
[ Donghan International's Collaboration
With World-class Fashion Designer Bella ]
[ Donghan Food's Lim Chul-yong Appointed
New Head of Donghan International ]
"Donghan Food".
The lawsuit regarding the restaurant
took place before I was instated,
so I don't know the details of the case.
[ "Lim Chul-yong". ]
"Managing Director Lim Chul-yong"?
[ - The receiver cannot be reached. ]
- Darn it.
[ Please leave a message after the beep. ]
[ Mr. Jin Tae-soo ]
[ You know that nothing comes for free. ]
[ Please take care of things for me. ]
[ Police ]
Go on in.
[ What are you doing? ]
[ Look at you. ]
- You're here, Mr. Park?
- I said, what are you doing?
Well, I...
I was just walking past,
and I felt a dark presence.
- I was checking to see if any...
- You must be out of your mind.
You focus on your own work.
You're only a constable.
You're just supposed to alert Finance
Office if there's an abandoned car!
I couldn't reach the owner, so...
You're driving me nuts.
That's why you're supposed to alert them!
Do it first thing tomorrow.
- I'm off duty tomorrow.
- Are you joking with me?
Do it yourself. I'm going to check on it.
Do you understand?
Yes, sir.
Gosh, you're driving me crazy!
He must have anger issues or something.
[ 24-Hour Sauna ]
[ So, you're saying
we should organize a task force? ]
That's it. That's what I'm saying.
Then we need a chief, don't we?
Of course, we do.
I already work two posts,
so it might be a bit challenging,
[ but if you trust my performance
and experience ]
and insist that I must do it,
then I guess I don't have any choice...
[ Give your recommendation. ]
- What?
- If you think someone can do a good job,
[ recommend someone. ]
If you think you'll do a good job,
you can go for it too.
That's how we should do it.
Oh, yes. Right.
It's just mere formality.
[ But we're living in a democratic world, ]
so let's do it as Da-hoon says.
Is there anyone you'd like to recommend?
- Go ahead.
- You do it.
- Yoon-ja.
- What?
Don't you have anyone to recommend?
Right.
Ms. Pi would be a good fit, wouldn't it?
[ She's the head of the women's society ]
[ and the village. ]
Oh, goodness.
What do you think, Ms. Byung-chun?
Oh, right.
She should be the one in charge.
She likes being in charge.
Oh, goodness.
I don't like being in charge. No way.
Since everyone is wanting me to do it,
I'll do it with a sense of duty
as I'm the head of
the women's society and the village.
What about Seung-mo?
What?
Seung-mo may be stuck here
in the countryside,
but he's very famous.
He has won the gold medal
at the World Chef Championship
and he's been the main chef
every time the president
went on an overseas trip
to cook his dinners.
- He received a presidential citation.
[ - Oh, I see. ]
You're saying he's
outrageously competent, right?
Right. He knows a lot
of reporters in Seoul too.
And he knows many higher-ups
in the diplomatic field as well.
I think we'll be in good hands
if he ever becomes the chief.
Really?
I didn't know Chef Moon was
such an amazing person.
You're way too kind.
Hey, I don't know anything
about this village. Why would I do it?
Painter has a good point.
How about we go fresh with a new face?
Right.
I've done many demonstrations
when I was young and this is what I know.
It's a battle of wits eventually.
Being the head of such a small village
wouldn't do.
This is a totally different matter
to deal with. Of course.
Excuse me?
Are you saying my face is old
and that I'm stupid right now?
Ms. Pi, you should do it.
[ I've just moved in, ]
[ and I don't know much about the village. ]
Let's vote.
- Excuse me?
- Let's vote.
Democracy is all about voting.
[ - Okay. ]
- Yes. Let's do it.
That's a good idea.
Ms. Pi, you never disappoint us.
[ - That's a great idea.
- Let's do it. ]
[ Moon Seung-mo: 12, Pi Gon-sook: 1 ]
[ What? Did Ms. Pi vote for herself? ]
I didn't.
I didn't vote for me.
Would you shut it, you brat?
Can't I share my two cents?
Da-mi. Da-mi!
[ Okay, Chef Moon. ]
I hope you do your best for our village.
If you have any questions,
contact me anytime you want.
Chef Moon, how do you feel?
I...
I'll go and get some sikhye.
Sikhye?
Dad, take me too.
Is he treating us?
I want some more sikhye too.
- I'll see you later.
- Okay.
- Can I have some seaweed soup?
- Goodness.
Don't be so downhearted, Ms. Pi.
Square your shoulders. Wait for me.
Have you heard?
As soon as the redevelopment plan
of Seoha Village was spread,
the land value increased already.
According to my uncle
who works as a real estate agent,
our land value will soar
at least five times
once the redevelopment is done.
- That's good.
- Awesome.
Don't you know about Anjoong?
My sister-in-law got married in Anjoong.
That city was gentrified
and she's now driving a BMW.
- A BMW?
- Really?
I guess we'll only have
sunny days ahead of us.
[ - Right.
- I'm so excited. ]
What?
What did you just say?
Say it again.
I said, say it again!
[ What's wrong with you? ]
[ Why did you have to talk about ]
[ World Chef Championship ]
[ and cooking dinners for the president? ]
[ How could you be so slow-witted? ]
Why did you have to recommend me
at that moment?
You know a lot of higher-ups.
It's good if you could help out
the village.
And the adults are against it.
We should help our neighbors!
Then you should do it, why me?
My dad told me to never be the leader.
Darn you.
Something happened at the sauna.
Come on!
What is it again?
- Goodness.
- What's going on?
[ They're from Sangcheon Village. ]
What are you doing here?
This is ridiculous.
Do you know what they were talking about?
Goodness, what?
If they build factories,
your land value will increase?
Consider yourself dead today,
you're dead meat.
Bring it on. Bring it on!
We didn't say anything wrong.
What's the matter with you?
What?
I'm going to teach you a lesson today.
What kind of lesson?
- Goodness.
- Are you mad?
How dare you point at someone
older than you?
- Yes, I'm mad.
- Why you...
- Take this!
- Gosh!
- Do something.
- Go!
- What did you say?
- Come on.
- Come over here!
- What did you say?
- Take that.
- How dare you, get out!
- Let go.
- Mom!
[ - Get away! ]
Let go!
Why you brat!
- Get out!
- Move!
Nosebleed!
[ Nosebleed! ]
Hyo-sook!
Hyo-sook is not breathing.
[ CPR! ]
[ Resident's Companion,
Trusty Nonyang Police ]
This one?
It's fine.
You can't reach the owner, right?
Right.
If we can't contact the owner,
he must've bought it from shark loans.
What will happen to this car?
What do you think?
We should sell it by public auction.
You checked the inside, right?
Last time, there was a fish
or something inside
and we almost died cleaning that.
I'll double-check.
- Okay. Please do.
- Yes.
What's this?
It's blood.
All the other chefs are
incredible as well,
but I believe Chef Moon Seung-mo
is the right man
for our premium Korean food project.
What do you think, Ms. Song?
He's the only chef who's capable
of presenting all types of Korean food
across the nation.
We were considering him
since the very beginning of this project.
Marketing team?
His wide experience in foreign stages
will also be of great help
when launching in the global market.
Moon Seung-mo is that outstanding?
I told you. He's the best.
Since you're here,
- I'll be honest with you.
- Okay.
To me, it's a tempting offer.
I'm glad you think so.
There aren't many chefs in Korea
who can pull off such a business...
Is there a problem?
This seems to be Chef Moon's work.
Are you in touch with Chef Moon Seung-mo?
No.
If Chef Moon is in this,
it will be game over.
I'm glad he is not. Please try it.
[ One bulgogi and two bibimbap! ]
[ Gourmandism ]
By the way,
Chef Moon is certainly out of this, right?
- Pardon?
[ - I mean, if Chef Moon is in this too, ]
there's no reason for us to do it.
Is there something important
to talk about?
It is something important.
As I told you before, I came to Seoul.
So are you going to treat me a drink?
Of course I will.
As a matter of fact,
the company I'm working for now is
preparing a premium Korean food project.
And I need your help. That's why I'm here.
[ Gourmandism ]
- "Premium Korean food project"?
- Yes.
Please take a look inside.
[ I'm sure you will love it. ]
[ Donghan Food ]
Mr. Choi.
Yes?
I'm sorry
but I can't work with Donghan. Sorry.
Excuse me?
[ Yes. ]
We are planning to advertise
this show extensively
[ so everyone in Korea will know about it. ]
[ Don't worry about the cost. ]
Just make sure to publish
as many advertisements as possible.
[ All right. Thank you. ]
It seems that you are advertising the show
more intensively than usual.
So Bella sees it and comes back.
What if she doesn't?
What?
What if Bella never comes back?
Are you out of your mind?
How dare you say nonsense like that?
Bella will definitely come back.
The show is just around the corner.
Why don't you focus on your work?
Yes. This is Jang Sun-young.
Yes. There is a person that I must find.
I need to find the person in secret.
Oh, I see.
Okay. I will call you back.
Excuse me.
Are you
- looking for somebody?
- Pardon?
I think I can help you.
Actually, finding people is my specialty.
This is unpleasant.
I didn't know you were an eavesdropper.
It's not a nice habit to have.
If you change your mind later, call me.
Hey, how am I supposed to trust you?
Seeing that you tag along with Lim Hyun-a,
you must be one of Lim Chul-yong's people.
We are freelancers.
We don't work for certain people.
We work for those who make a better offer.
Well, then.
[ Jin Tae-soo ]
Down there is the entrance
of Seoha Village.
Donghan International plans to build
a clothing manufacturing factory
and a general warehouse.
[ The total land is 336,528m². ]
[ We will combine the dispersed warehouses ]
[ and move them to a bigger place. ]
After the project is completed, not only
the increase of Nonyang's population
but also a revitalization
of the domestic market is expected.
[ This will be the biggest facility
in this region, sir. ]
Don't worry. Nonyang will take care of it.
Make sure to take good care
of the residents' complaints.
- Mr. Hwang.
- Yes.
- Is everything going all right?
- Yes, sir.
The preparation for today's briefing
is going smoothly.
Good. Thanks.
Now, shall we?
This way.
You're making me dizzy.
Why are you so restless
like a dog that has a call of nature?
She's right. Stay still, will you?
You're distracting me.
Do you have any idea how amazing this is?
Why won't Mom call me?
May I ask what is so amazing?
What a frustrating man you are.
[ Seoha Teahouse ]
Depending on the result
of the briefing today,
I might end up going to Seoul.
How isn't that amazing?
[ You're right. ]
It is truly amazing indeed.
How annoying.
But I like here better than Seoul.
Now we are going to start
the briefing about the development
of Seoha Village and Mount Bongu
in Nonyang.
The county governor, the Managing Director
of Donghan International, Lim Chul-yong,
[ and the Junior Managing Director,
Jung Gwang-su, joined us today. ]
This is cool.
Thanks for coming.
[ The construction of Donghan's
clothing industrial complex ]
will be the biggest development project
in our region.
As Mount Bongu and Seoha Village are
within the development area,
for the construction
of the clothing industrial complex,
they will have to be moved...
[ What? ]
Are you saying you will sweep us away?
All residents of Seoha Village are
against this project.
He's right.
One's property rights must be protected.
This one-sided project is just absurd.
He's right. We are against this.
[ - I don't want this. ]
- Hey, the Subsection Chief is talking.
Who do you think you are to interrupt him?
He's the chief
of our village's task force.
[ "Chief"? ]
[ Now that you mention it, ]
it's not something
that you can be against.
It's the county office's decision.
It's not something you can go against.
He's right. Plus, this isn't only
Seoha Village's matter.
This is a matter
of the entire residents of Nonyang.
[ - You must hear ]
- Goodness.
[ other villagers' opinions too. ]
Every resident in Sangcheon Village
supports this project.
[ - That's right!
- We do support the project. ]
My goodness. Look at them applauding.
- Stop applauding.
[ - Goodness. ]
Seeing her talking all nonsense,
I regret that I didn't crush him
the other day.
Look who's talking!
What the...
Do you want a piece of me?
Bring it on if that's what you want.
- We didn't start this! You started it!
[ - Be quiet. ]
[ - This is unbelievable. ]
- Goodness.
Just stop already!
Sit down.
The villagers of Seoha Village
will lose their hometown
once the construction begins.
So their opinions should matter the most.
Our chief is one smooth talker.
- He sure is.
- What?
- That's just absurd.
All residents of Nonyang
have the right to make the decision.
- That's true.
- See?
- Don't be ridiculous!
- No way!
- What are you talking about?
- That's just nonsense!
- Our opinion matters the most!
[ - She's right! ]
[ - Don't be ridiculous!
- I can't believe this! ]
[ - Seriously!
- What's with all the mess? ]
[ - This is insane!
- Stop yelling! ]
[ - Wait!
- How dare you point your finger at me! ]
[ This is just ridiculous! ]
[ Stop the nonsense! ]
[ Sir! Mr. Lim Chul-yong! ]
Mr. Lim Chul-yong!
Let's talk.
Get off of me.
Just for a second, sir.
Mr. Lim Chul-yong!
Stop it. Gosh.
Darn it.
Where are you going?
[ So he's the chief of the opposition? ]
That's right, sir.
The villagers seemed to like him.
It might make things rather easier.
Pardon?
You remember how we disassembled
the labor union before.
Try to win him over.
Yes, sir. I will do some research.
[ Hue Sleep Clinic ]
It's not my fault.
[ I didn't kill her. I really didn't. ]
I didn't kill Bella.
"I didn't kill Bella"?
[ 596 hours left ]
I didn't kill Bella.
It was
just an accident.
[ An accident. ]
"Bella"?
She should be back before the show.
Come on, Bella. What happened to you?
Bella. What on earth...
[ Belle Ombre ]
[ December 17, 2019, Seoul Design Plaza,
Exclusive Live D-10 ]
I would like to have the same one.
So why did you want to meet me?
You must be worried
as the show is coming up.
You don't look as happy as before.
You have changed a lot.
You never worried about others.
I want to know and hear a lot of things,
but today, I will ask you
only one question.
I asked Mr. Lim about it,
but he wouldn't give me a clear answer.
Bella. Who is she?
I told you before.
The contract says it's confidential.
So I can't tell you.
[ The girl ]
you took to France with you 20 years ago.
It's her, right?
I'm not sure what you're talking about.
So it's her.
You weren't a talented designer,
but I guess you were a talented mother.
This is offending.
There's no reason
that I should be hearing this.
Ms. Jang. You can't seem
to keep your face straight right now.
[ So stop trying. ]
I never heard what you said.
About the girl...
It's embarrassing for me too,
so I won't talk about it elsewhere.
Don't worry and good luck
with the show preparation.
What on earth is up with Lim Chul-yong?
[ Jin Tae-soo ]
Jin Tae-soo.
Mr. Jin.
Mr. Jin?
This is Jang Sun-young.
Can we meet?
[ JS Security ]
I had no idea you used to be a cop.
Including my seniors and juniors,
I have a lot of friends in the police.
Finding a person is a piece of cake.
This is
a personal request.
I don't want Mr. Lim to know about this.
I don't care how much it costs.
Please find her.
[ Do you have other information? ]
I think it will be hard to find her
just with a picture.
Yoo Yu-jin.
She's 34 years old this year.
About a couple of months ago,
she called me and said she'd fly to Korea.
And I haven't heard
anything from her since.
She has lived in France for 20 years,
so she probably knows
next to nothing about Korea.
Which is why it was hard to find her.
I visited the place she used to live
when she was young,
but I guess it has been too long.
The house is now owned by someone else.
May I ask
your relationship with her?
She's...
like my daughter.
[ Virtual aerial view ]
[ Direction of the project ]
- You came back late.
- I had some drink.
Something interesting happened.
Today, I learned who Bella was.
What?
You will also be surprised
to know who she is.
You don't know who she is, do you?
What do you mean?
As I said before,
I can't be
on the same team
with someone who deceives me.
I want you to keep that in mind.
[ Bella ]
[ Donghan International, Bella ]
A collaboration with dead Bella?
She's asking me to find Bella
not knowing if she's dead or not?
I got a big one.
What is Doctor Choi saying?
It's just a checkup.
To be honest,
I'm not sure how much longer
I can enjoy times like this,
which is why I called you.
Grandpa, don't say that.
- Jun-su,
- Yes?
I'm sure you had a nice life in the US,
sorry for calling you back to
Korea like this.
And thanks for coming back.
I told you, I came back
because I wanted to.
If you keep saying that,
I'm going to go back.
You kid!
Fishing is
a lot like running a business.
Those who catch fish well
try their best to catch whatever it is,
whether it's a big fish or a small fish.
It goes the same for running a business.
Even just the slightest bit of ego
telling me that I've done enough
can push me down to the ground in failure.
Of course, there are
lessons to learn from failing.
But now is
the time you need to succeed.
That's why I'm nagging you like this.
Chul-yong is
not an easy opponent.
Yes.
I'll remember that.
Just for a second, sir.
[ Mr. Lim Chul-yong! ]
[ The company I'm working for now is
preparing a premium Korean food project. ]
[ And I need your help.
That's why I'm here. ]
Chef Moon, what's wrong?
Hey.
You look worried.
My parents
had Pungcheonok passed down to them,
and have operated the place
to maintain its 80-year tradition.
And all I have left is just a signboard.
Yes.
The company that took away Pungcheonok
from my parents is
Donghan.
And they're now trying
to take this house away, too.
That's ridiculous!
How can they do such a thing?
I know.
It's an ill-fated relationship.
Since we've come to this point,
I'm never letting them have their way.
I'll help you as much as I can.
They better watch out.
Everyone, Donghan Group is trying
to take over our village!
- They're sweeping it away!
[ - Please sign in it! ]
- Please take one.
[ - Please. ]
Take this. Thanks.
No, thank you.
Please, just one.
Is signing a petition so difficult?
It's so cold and people are even colder.
It's a cold world.
It's been a while! Here, sign this for me.
You're doing good work.
Do you just go around during your
work hours, talking to people?
How do you know everyone?
It's nice to know lots of people.
I don't know anyone, so I'm no help.
Chef Moon, I thought you were famous!
Why doesn't anyone here know you?
I don't know. Maybe I should've made
more appearances on TV.
It's so cold, can't we just start
from inside the market?
- It's too cold, isn't it?
[ - Yes! ]
Everyone, let's start
from inside the market.
- I know a lot of people in there.
- Sounds good.
Let's start from the inside.
Let's head in. It's too cold.
- Let's go!
- Let's head inside.
[ Come in. ]
Where did Hyo-sook go?
- Go ahead with the development!
Everyone, this is
where all the stores are.
Let's divide and have our petition signed.
Understood?
- Yes!
- Let's go!
- Go ahead with the development!
Look there. Come here.
Hello!
[ - Could you sign this for us? ]
- Thanks so much!
Where should I go next?
- Hey there!
[ - Here. ]
[ Hello. ]
- Hey, do you mind signing this for me?
- Let me try this.
[ Hello! ]
[ Down with the warehouse development! ]
Where is Da-hoon? I don't see him at all.
I don't know.
All right. Do I sign in here?
You!
Ms. Byung-chun! Hyo-sook is in red!
What?
You! Stop right there!
[ You! ]
Stop right there!
[ What do you think you're doing? ]
- You're dead!
- Bang Da-hoon!
- Stop right there.
- Da-hoon!
Stop!
- I can't stand them anymore.
- How could they...
- Stop there!
- You!
- How dare you?
- Come here.
[ - Fight me.
- How could you? ]
My goodness.
I'm going to die from the frustration.
- How can you be so mindless?
- Calm down.
How can I calm down?
Sure, I get Hyo-sook.
But Da-hoon, I knew you were crazy,
but have you gone out of your mind?
[ No need to ask. ]
I knew it when they started
hanging out every day.
Let's have them sit here like this
until tomorrow.
Until tomorrow? Please!
Put your hands down
and I'll kill you both with my own hands.
Understood?
- Yes, ma'am.
Stop it.
Put your hands down and stand up.
I have nothing to say.
She's not my daughter, she's my enemy.
[ Calm down. ]
We've got quite some signatures
on our petition, so we still have hope.
The next part is what matters.
Chef Moon, this won't do at all.
You've seen it all earlier
how hard those two worked
to get their petition signed.
Their side has so many more signatures
than ours. It's incomparable.
In my opinion,
we're completely defeated.
We need to find a new way.
Then let's each try to come up
with something.
I'll head to Seoul and meet up
with some news reporters tomorrow.
All right.
Don't you think
we'd leave a bad impression
if we just show up like this?
You wanted to meet him.
I know him,
and he doesn't change his mind so easily.
[ If we don't show up like this,
we'll never see him again. ]
Especially you.
What did I do?
[ Seoha Village ]
Chef Moon!
Chef, are you there?
What should we do?
I don't think he's home.
[ The faceless genius designer ]
[ Nonyang Construction ]
What are you doing in my field?
We're here to measure the ground.
Don't mind us and do your job.
Who gave you permission
to measure my land?
The county office gave us permission.
The county office, my foot.
It's my land, not theirs!
You're a part of those people trying
to take our village, aren't you?
[ And you want me not to mind you? ]
Sure.
I'm going to beat you guys up,
so why don't you try to do your job, too?
- Goodness!
- Come here.
Are you drunk?
Are you trying to scare us with that?
- Let's go.
- I'm just defending myself.
Fine, bring it on.
Goodness. My back!
My neck! Gosh.
You think a clueless old man like you
can fight us?
Demolishing the village
and building a factory is good.
Why are you interrupting us?
- My neck!
[ - Hey! ]
What do you think you're doing?
- Goodness.
- How dare you
- beat up an old man like this?
- You're going to kill me!
- Are you okay?
- My goodness!
- Gosh!
- Everyone!
[ - Help! ]
- You crazy woman!
Everyone!
- Help! Anyone?
- Hey! You crazy woman! Let go of me!
Are you all right?
You crazy woman,
are you drunk, too?
What do you think you're doing?
What are you doing? Let me go! Gosh.
Assistant Manager Kim Il-seob
from Nonyang Construction.
I called the police.
Stop it if you don't want to go to prison.
Who are you?
Come on.
Even if it's your request,
[ it's such a small village thing, ]
so it's going to get cut.
Isn't there anything you can do?
Maybe if you do an exclusive interview
with us, things will be different.
I'll do it.
Okay, I'll make up a story then.
Could you hold on for a second?
[ Da-hoon ]
Yes, Da-hoon?
Please contact me
if you need a witness or help.
I'll help you to the best of my abilities.
[ Kang Jun-su ]
Donghan?
Yes.
[ Emergency center ]
- Are you okay?
- Yes.
I'm fine... Gosh.
Lie down.
You're back!
Yes. Where's Byeol-na?
Right there.
Had it not been for that man,
[ Byeol-na would've gotten hurt, too. ]
[ The men would've beaten
all of us to death. ]
[ Chef Moon! ]
Mr. Choi? What brings you here?
I came here to see you
but ended up here.
Why don't you say hi?
Mr. Kang!
Chef Moon, you're back!
Are you all right?
Yes, all thanks to them.
But Bong-doo is...
We meet again.
Right.
Bong-doo, you'll be moved to a ward.
- Please be gentle.
- Bong-doo.
Chef Moon,
do you mind sparing a minute for me?
Please.
Thankfully, the police are
being very cooperative.
I don't think there will be anything
for you to worry about.
First of all, thank you.
It would've been a disaster
if it weren't for you.
I did what I had to.
But
the reason we're here is
that we want to have you
as the directing chef for this project.
That's why we came to Nonyang.
I understand that you may not want to
because of what happened with Pungcheonok.
But Mr. Kang has nothing to do with that.
Mr. Kang Jun-su,
how are you related to the managing
director of Donghan International,
who wants to build a factory here
while hurting people?
[ Lim Chul-yong. ]
He was the one who proceeded
with the Pungcheonok case too, right?
Well...
It's okay.
Mr. Lim Chul-yong is
someone that I need to overcome.
Chef Moon, just have a look look
at the project plan.
It's a great business plan.
[ We can do everything as you'd like. ]
Can you just look over...
Thank you for today.
Chef Moon?
Chef!
Hold on.
Mr. Choi, I'm sorry, but...
When we were in Australia,
you promised that you'd help me out
once in Korea.
You haven't forgotten, have you?
This is it.
I'm not telling you to decide right now.
Just please take a look at it
and give me a call when you do.
Gun-woo,
do you know anything else
about what Mr. Lim is doing here?
Well... I don't.
[ Nonyang County Office ]
Why did you make such a mess?
That old man was getting on my nerves.
That's your excuse?
You can't even train
your employees properly?
What a headache.
Sorry.
I'll take care of it
as the representative
of Nonyang Construction.
If you mess up one more time, you're done.
Yes, sir.
What are you going to do
about Seoha Village?
What else is there to do?
If we have to, we'll get an approval
from the board of county
and force the eviction.
What? Bong-doo?
All right, I'll visit him later.
I knew there'd be a disaster!
I can't agree with this,
but I can't disagree either.
- What am I supposed to do?
[ - Are you really going to do this? ]
[ As long as I proceed with
this Donghan project, ]
I could be appointed
as the provincial governor.
Stupid people are ruining everything!
Darn it.
[ You should lower your voice. ]
- Take a look at this.
- What is this?
"Promoting local produce"?
You think we have time for this?
This has been prepared for a long time.
Tell the Director of Culture and Tourism
to wait.
Yes, sir.
He's going to leave us with nothing
and become a provincial governor?
[ Department of Culture and Tourism ]
Gosh. What happened?
Are you all right? What do we do?
Hey there.
Hi.
Some men came and made a mess
at my field today.
Careful!
They were from the construction company.
Officer Jo caught them.
- Such heinous people!
[ - Goodness. ]
They've been in and out of jail
so many times.
- That's terrible.
- Indeed.
See? Those people you sided with
made him like this. Are you happy now?
Don't put it that way.
Sorry, sir.
Bong-doo, I'm not one of them.
You better apologize properly.
- Stop smacking me!
- Please.
Be quiet! Seriously.
What are you going to do?
Are you just going to let this go?
I've contacted the Jo Family Club,
so they should be all heading
to the county office now.
Good job.
I'll head to the county office
and talk to the county governor.
- Good idea.
- Byeol-na, stay here with Seol-a.
No, let me come with you.
Painter, watch Seol-a.
- What?
- I'll go with you!
I'm the one who has strings to pull.
Everyone,
we shouldn't just stay here
like this, either.
- Let's go!
- That's right!
We'll be back.
We'll stay here,
looking back on what we've done!
Come back safely!
Look. This is Nonyang County Office.
It's big, isn't it?
This is where my husband works
as the subsection chief.
- Subsection Chief?
- Yes, it's a powerful position.
- It's not food.
[ - Chef Moon! ]
- Honey!
Come and have a talk with me.
Honey, I'm here.
Head inside, it's cold.
He's worrying for us.
Let's head inside. It's cold.
Let's go inside. This way.
Chef Moon, I have something to show you.
Take a look at this.
Come on.
[ Kind People, Good Nonyang ]
Sir, we're in trouble.
What's up?
The entier Jo family is here,
demanding to have a meeting with you.
What?
This won't be good for
the upcoming appointment.
You know how powerful they are
in this region.
Why Jo family of all people?
I think you should flee
for the time being.
That's right. Tell them
that I'm on a work trip.
Okay. This way.
This is not proper.
- This shouldn't happen here!
- Right.
It's the home of politeness and manners,
Chungcheong Province!
That's right!
How dare young men
- beat up an old man in broad daylight?
- Sir.
Get out of my way!
- We can't just let this one slide.
- Please.
- Right.
- Get out!
- Sir...
- Get the county governor here.
Get the county governor here!
[ - Come on.
- Bring him. ]
[ - Bring him right now.
- Please calm down. ]
- Let's go.
[ - How could they? ]
[ Bring him here! ]
- Sir, hold on.
- What?
[ Kind People, Good Nonyang ]
[ Nonyang County Office ]
Goodness. Thank you!
- Come here.
- Thanks for coming.
We can't even go out!
Lock the doors!
- Lock all of them!
- Yes, sir.
- Where should we go?
- Let's head upstairs.
- Upstairs?
- Come with me.
We're not here to exercise violence.
Let us meet the county governor.
He's on a business trip right now.
- Make an appointment and come...
- We'll wait here, then.
Call him.
The entire Seoha Village people are here,
waiting to meet him.
Call him. Come on.
- You can do it.
- Go and check first.
- Check!
[ - Yes, sir. ]
Hello.
What?
I thought he wasn't here. Here he is!
- Look at that!
- He's right there!
[ He was running away
from us all this time! ]
[ How dare a young man be so rude? ]
- Look at him.
- How dare he?
Yes, sir.
Yes.
The county governor is inside.
- What?
- How dare you lie to us?
- You lied to us!
[ You shouldn't lie like that. ]
- Let's head inside.
- Let's go.
Get out of the way.
Look, Mr. Hong.
We've supported you during your election
[ and elected you to serve us. ]
How could you do this?
How dare your people beat up
an old man in broad daylight?
And we came to meet you,
but you didn't even come out.
Instead, you were too busy finding a way
to run away from us. Despicable.
- Sir!
- Be careful.
Sir, please calm down.
It's not what you think it is.
[ We're going to do whatever we can ]
[ to punish the men
for what happened yesterday. ]
But the Seoha Village takeover is
for the county and the village.
I had no choice.
If it's for the betterment
of the county and the village,
then is it okay to proceed
without our permission?
- That's right.
[ - Please calm down. ]
Mr. Hong gave it a lot of thought
before making the decision.
Every year, the population is decreasing,
and jobs are disappearing.
How else can we develop the county...
Is that what you need?
An alternative plan?
What plan?
What happened?
We looked into it,
and I don't think we can get him
on our side.
Why?
The chief of the village is
- the son of Pungcheonok.
- Pungcheonok?
You know, the burnt restaurant.
I do have a plan.
I'll open a restaurant in my name
in Seoha Village, Nonyang.
What did he just say?
[ What? ]
[ Eccentric! Chef Moon ]
Why are you so worried
even before opening the restaurant?
[ I'll take care of the interior design. ]
[ What do you think? ]
[ It's beautiful! ]
[ - Byeol-na, you're the best. ]
- The best!
[ How is there such a hip place
in this middle-of-nowhere village? ]
[ No wonder you're so proud of yourself. ]
[ What a masterpiece.
No wonder you're so picky. ]
Bits and pieces of my memories
are coming back.
Bella, you always came back
before the show.
I present to you, Designer Yoo Byeol-na!
Ms. Jang!
This is the finale
of your fake Bella show.
Thank you!
[ Why are you so full of surprises? ]