[ Episode 10 ]
Go on in and get some rest.
I'll stay here.
I heard you've gone against my words
and proceeded with the business.
Mother, if you're still upset with me...
The village you're running
your business in
is the hometown of your father's mistress.
- What?
- I know.
You may not see what the problem is.
It's been more than 20 years now.
No, Mother.
I had no idea.
I guess I thought
I'd be able to forget about that time
if that village disappeared.
That's why I didn't like
you running your business there.
Just do whatever you please, Jun-su.
Mother.
I don't want to be so foolish
to hold you a victim of my past anymore.
However,
promise me that you will be successful.
Okay.
Should we go and eat?
Your grandfather will wake up.
He's not that weak.
He would be outraged to find out
that we were waiting by his side.
Yes, Mother. Let's go.
I'll take that.
What do you want to eat?
[ They have left, sir. ]
[ VIP, Patient Han Dong-gil ]
[ Pungcheonok ]
[ Why do you do this before every show? ]
Bella! The finale dress! Hurry.
Good job.
[ Designer brands are rushing
to sign with Bella. ]
Something urgent came up in Korea.
[ Managing Director Lim Chul-yong ]
[ of Donghan International
purchased the land. ]
[ Sign with Donghan. ]
[ Why should I? ]
[ After all, I know all
of Bella's secrets. ]
Bella,
I'm Lim Hyun-a, Lim Chul-yong's daughter.
[ Was that you who stole the dress? ]
Are you insane? Stop the car!
Bella?
Yu-jin!
[ Yoo Yu-jin! ]
Madam Jang.
Yes.
That's me.
Yu-jin!
What happened to you?
Do you know how worried I was?
What do we do? Sun-young is here.
[ Just run them over! ]
[ Byeol-na! ]
Don't even think of coming back alive
if you lose her.
Yes, sir.
Darn it!
Byeol-na, are you all right?
[ What's going on? ]
- What's that sound?
- What was that?
[ - What?
- Who is that? ]
- Oh my gosh!
- Who's there?
- Go!
- What is that?
- Goodness!
- Damn it!
Go away!
- No...
- Why, you!
- Oh, no!
- Goodness!
- What do we do?
- Oh, no!
- Gosh!
No!
[ - Goodness!
- Get up! ]
- I'm scared!
- Get up!
[ - Oh, no! ]
- Gosh.
- Get him!
- Goodness!
- Darn it!
[ - Chef Moon! ]
[ Darn it, you! ]
- That's my friend!
- Jin Tae-soo...
[ - You! ]
- That bastard!
[ - Get up.
- Come on. ]
[ - My goodness!
- Look at him! ]
[ Soon-mi! Come over to Pungcheonok! ]
[ Someone has a knife out here! ]
[ Hurry up! ]
[ Chef Moon is hurt! Yes, call 911! ]
[ It's so scary. ]
[ I know, right? ]
One moment.
- I'm sorry. Excuse me.
- You may not enter, sir.
- What's going on?
- I'm sorry.
Who are you?
I'm the patient's guardian. Please move.
I'm sorry, sir.
At 8:58 pm, Chairman Han Dong-gil
had passed away.
What?
Move. Move!
Let go! Move!
[ Before Chairman Han passed away, ]
he left a will saying
he would like to inherit
the entire shares and management rights
to Managing Director Lim Chul-yong,
over here.
Who are you? Are you insane?
My grandfather was unconscious
after the surgery.
[ And you're saying he suddenly
woke up and left a will? ]
Do you expect me to believe that?
As the shareholders of Donghan Group,
I, Hong Dae-gon,
and Na Gyung-hun are the witnesses.
[ We were there. ]
As the family of the deceased,
[ my heart is breaking. ]
For our entire company,
I will gladly honor
Chairman Han Dong-gil's last will.
Lim Chul-yong...
Lim Chul-yong, you bastard.
[ Hey. ]
Are you still working on
the bloodstain test
I asked from the fake registered car?
I told you. I'll contact you
once I get the results.
I'm going to send you
a DNA sample right now.
How much longer will it take
for you to run a lab test
and compare the two?
Are you okay?
Were you hurt in any way?
Goodness.
What is going on?
Do you know how hard
I've been looking for you?
It's fine. Everything's fine.
Now that I've found you.
Goodness, gracious.
Dad, are you okay?
Yes, I'm fine.
Seol-a, you also get scars
when you fall down, right?
This is just like that. So don't worry.
[ Seung-mo. ]
According to Hyo-sook,
that lady who came for Byeol-na is a very
famous person in the fashion industry.
- Is that true?
- Yes.
[ Chef Moon Seung-mo ]
I can't believe Bella had lost her memory.
Anyway,
thank you so much for everything
you have done for her.
I'd like to pay you
as an act of appreciation.
No, thank you.
But I'd like to ask why
you need to go to Seoul
with Byeol-na at this late hour.
I'm sorry, but I cannot allow this.
[ May I ask ]
in what relationship
the two of you are in?
I'm...
Actually, I'm in no relations
with the Yu-jin who has found her memory.
So you don't have to worry about us.
I'll be honest with you
since you're telling me that.
The man who got arrested earlier.
He's a worker at a security company
I had requested to find Yu-jin.
What?
Why did he...
I guess he had another client.
The conditions to kill her
must've been more appealing
than to find her.
Can you think of someone
who would possibly do that?
Lim Chul-yong
of Donghan International.
Mr. Lim Chul-yong?
If he's behind this,
why is he trying to kill Yu-jin?
It'll take all night to explain that.
This place will be too dangerous to stay
once they find out
that their plans have fallen short.
We have to leave here now...
Leaving at this late hour
sounds more dangerous.
Anyway, since the hours are
too late right now,
why don't you sleep here for tonight
and head out tomorrow after breakfast?
[ How many times
do I have to repeat myself? ]
I did it by myself!
Gosh, if you keep lying,
you're going to be in big trouble.
Goodness.
I know your boss ordered you to do it.
I'm talking about that man
who's your senior, Mr. Park.
Hey, that's extreme speculation.
[ Goodness. ]
Do you have evidence? I know you don't.
Evidence?
Of course, I do.
[ When are you going to attack? ]
[ At night when people are gone
and they close the restaurant. ]
[ Should I stab her
and burn her like last time? ]
[ They closed the restaurant.
I'll call you again later. ]
Goodness.
You were going to stab her
and burn her? How scary is that?
Are you still going to play dumb on me?
Are you?
Gosh, how come I'm not hearing
anything from him?
Hey, call him.
He might be working right now. What if...
Gosh.
[ Oh Jung-tae ]
[ Mr. Jin ]
How did it go?
Where are you?
What? Who are you?
[ Me? ]
We've met once before.
[ We've met at Mr. Park's desk last time. ]
I'm Officer Jo
from Nonyang Police Station.
I'm going to the village today
to see my father.
I can guide you there.
Darn it!
- Turn off the phone, hurry!
- Excuse me?
Jung-tae got caught.
- Really?
- Yes!
I'll take care of things here.
You go out and get the car!
How did you end up being here?
What's your relationship with...
I'd like to ask that question to you.
How did things end up like this?
What?
I put on a show
without even knowing about it.
I was just trying to save you
and Belle Ombre.
- It was inevitable.
- And that's how
you lost Belle Ombre?
To that fake?
Do you know what your flaw is?
You're too desperate.
That's why you're always
being dragged around.
Belle Ombre isn't going to disappear
by not doing one show.
How could you be so impatient
and think of doing a show with that fake?
I'm baffled.
What about you?
Can't you think of it as a consequence
of not keeping in touch?
You should've told me
why you were going to Korea
and whom you were meeting.
Why do you always have to do things
so selfishly?
Forget it.
Goodness.
So my boutique
is opening this weekend?
Yes.
Why do you ask? What are you going to do?
What do you think?
I have to get back
Belle Ombre.
[ Sorry I left without saying goodbye. ]
[ Thank you for everything, Chef Moon. ]
[ I thought I wouldn't be able to leave
if I had seen your face. ]
[ So I'm saying goodbye
through the letter instead. ]
[ This place was my grandfather's place. ]
[ Maybe that's why it was so cozy here. ]
[ I think I will never be able to forget ]
[ the time I have spent with you. ]
[ Chef Moon. ]
[ I wish ]
[ we can meet again ]
[ after much time has passed. ]
[ Please say goodbye for me
to the people in the village. ]
[ I'm... ]
[ I'm sorry. ]
This is so good!
Pace yourself.
Drinks should be enjoyed
and appreciated, too.
This is just my second glass.
- You don't drink well, do you?
- Me?
Just take care of yourself after.
I don't plan on looking out for you.
- Fine.
[ So you're saying, you're in love? ]
[ Don't say that in front of your dad,
okay? ]
- Great work, Byeol-na.
- Right?
I'm telling you, I'm this good.
I'm sorry, Mom.
[ I was so nearby, ]
but I couldn't remember.
Mom.
No matter what happens,
I will protect you.
[ - Yu-jin. ]
- Yes?
- What are you doing?
- I was just drawing
you and me on a stage.
- Really?
- Yes.
Tell everyone
that they should be prepared.
I'm going to meet every one of them
one by one.
[ Good morning. ]
- Good morning.
- You are up early.
Are you wearing matching clothes?
I went downtown last night with Mom
and bought these.
- So put these on.
- Why?
They are really expensive.
Be careful not to spill kimchi juice
on it. That will be a disaster.
She's right.
You've got to show respect
to Designer Bella's clothing.
Are these clothes so great?
Come to think of it, she's right.
We must treat these clothes better.
The famous designer, Bella, made it.
We must treat them nicely.
[ It's beautiful. ]
[ She's right. ]
So we have been hanging out
with a world-famous designer, Bella.
- Yes.
[ - What do you mean by, "hang out"? ]
I even got
special lessons
from the famous designer, Bella.
[ - Goodness. ]
- Gosh.
Is Bella still asleep?
The sun is high up.
Why haven't you come to work yet?
Should I go and bring her?
- Yes.
- Go ahead.
Bella went to Seoul.
- What?
She left.
[ What did you say? ]
What did you just say?
Is she not coming back?
[ How could she leave like that
without saying anything? ]
She wouldn't do that to me.
I want to go to her.
[ You're not going anywhere! ]
I'm going to go find her.
Seol-a.
She got her memories back
and found her real family.
You should be happy for her.
But we are her family.
[ We are her family too. ]
How could she leave like that
without saying anything?
- Seol-a.
- This is just unfair!
She's right.
Even if she got her memories back,
[ it's just rude that she left
without saying goodbye to us. ]
What a cold woman.
It's not like we were going to stop her.
[ Come on. Don't be like that. ]
Of course she can't walk around
the whole village in the early morning
and tell everyone that she's leaving.
It's okay.
[ Deepest condolences for your loss ]
[ Prime Minister ]
[ Minister of Foreign Affairs ]
[ Belle Ombre, Bella ]
[ Junga Group ]
- Did you hear from Jin Tae-soo yet?
- Not yet, sir.
Is the preparation of Bella Boutique
going all right?
Yes, sir. It's going smoothly.
It'd better be good.
We need to impress
the shareholders with that.
We must show them
who is leading Donghan
and who is lining their pockets.
I suppose that's why you decided to hold
the shareholders' meeting
after the Bella Boutique opening.
Let's finish up
both the appointment of the chairman
and the merger with Bella Ombre
at the meeting.
Yes, sir.
You will be the chairman.
Watch your mouth.
[ Hyun-a ]
[ Belle Ombre ]
Bella Boutique looks nice.
Focus on the launch of the boutique.
I'll look forward to the opening ceremony.
[ Opening Soon ]
[ Belle Ombre, Bella ]
[ Bella, Bella ]
Sir, I think you need to come in urgently.
I'm sorry for your loss.
Thank you...
for coming.
Of course I should come.
You have been looking for me,
but you don't seem so happy to see me.
Sir, that woman...
Find Jin Tae-soo right now.
Yes, sir.
Finally, you two met.
It's all thanks to you.
Please get in.
It's not bad.
Then we will proceed with it.
Okay.
Oh, right.
This coat is the limited edition
prepared for the opening ceremony.
Since it's a limited edition,
we will receive reservations
on a first-come-first-serve basis.
And there will also be your signing event
that will be like a celeb party.
[ The marketing team will
send you the schedule. ]
Okay.
Can I have a look inside too?
Sure. This way.
Hello. How may I help you?
The store is not officially open yet.
I'm not a customer, so don't mind me.
[ This is it? ]
The finale work from the fake gala show.
It's the design you decided to ditch
three years ago.
"Bella Boutique"...
Then it needs to have
proper Bella's design.
It's been a while, Hyun-a.
[ Ms. Seo, can I have a word with you? ]
Yes, ma'am.
What's with the face?
You look like you saw someone
who has come back to life.
Do you have any idea
what it is like to live
as someone who is not yourself?
I have done it, so I know what it's like.
It's quite painful
when you wake up from the dream.
I mean it.
I will teach you what it's like soon.
Could you put it here?
Okay.
- Let me do it.
- Thanks.
Is there anything else
I can help you with?
This should be enough for the work.
That's a relief.
Just to be safe,
we've hired private security guards
to guard you two at all times.
We'll make sure that you're safe here,
[ so don't worry too much. ]
[ Thank you for all of this. ]
[ Well, it was Mr. Kang
and Ms. Han's orders, ]
[ so don't feel too overwhelmed. ]
[ I hear that she lost her memory
and got it back just now? ]
[ I guess that's why she was at Chef Moon's
all along. ]
What kind
of a person is this Chef Moon Seung-mo?
He's one of the greatest chefs in Korea.
He's currently working with Donghan Food.
I see.
Give me a call anytime
if you need anything.
- Thank you so much.
- Bye then.
Let's go.
[ Bella. ]
Do you think we can pull it through?
We've got less than four days.
Why? Are you worried
that my taste is gone?
That's not what I'm saying.
I'm talking about your health.
Don't worry about it. You can get going.
And this.
If you need anything, just call me.
I'll always be ready next door.
Sure.
[ Let's hold a press conference
with Bella. ]
Bella is terrified of press conferences
and she has a trauma of camera flash.
I don't think that's a good idea.
- Then...
[ - We'll win it in her way. ]
In her way?
When Hyun-a opens the fake Bella Boutique,
we're planning on revealing
both Bella's and Hyun-a's clothes.
And we'll prove who's the fake one?
But
is there anyone who can actually identify
between the two?
I'll bring someone if there's none.
There's Louis.
You mean Chairman Louis from France?
You can do that?
Yes.
He has been like that since last night.
Exactly.
Stop cleaning!
[ My eyes hurt from seeing everything
sparkling clean. ]
And get some sleep, too.
I'm fine.
I'm going to go and clean up the yard.
Dad, stop cleaning!
- Chef Moon.
- Hello.
He looks like he stayed up all night.
Yes. It looks like he's going to fall ill.
He hasn't slept
since Byeol-na left.
And he has been like that
since very early in the morning.
That's what lovesick is.
What? Lovesick?
She hasn't been eating anything.
It has been two days,
you can't just only drink water.
Hello?
Could we get some dinner room service?
Can you cook fish for us?
[ Deep-fried toppings ]
[ Great Pupil ]
You had goji juice?
That's not enough.
All right.
You couldn't stomach any food
by the best chefs in town,
but you liked the mung bean porridge?
Had it not been the porridge,
my last show would've been a disaster.
Right.
[ Mung bean porridge ]
Darn it.
I want to see if she'll eat
some mung bean porridge,
but all porridge shops are closed
and I can't find anything online.
No worries.
I'll see what I can do.
You...
Hold on.
Let me call you back.
Bye.
[ Chef Moon! ]
[ Chef Moon, where are you? I'm starving. ]
Did you not hear me? I'm starving!
You went to Seoul to take care
of something. Why are you already back?
Cut the small talk, you're just doing it
to stall time.
Chef Moon,
I want to eat the bibimbap you make.
No, maybe bulgogi.
I think I want japchae, too.
I want pajeon, too! Cook them all for me.
[ Mr. Choi Gun-woo ]
Hello, Mr. Choi.
Seung-mo!
Where are you going out this late?
I have to go somewhere.
Where?
It might take a while,
so just go to sleep without me.
What about the restaurant?
We're closed for tomorrow.
Right.
Drive safe, Dad!
I'll be back soon.
Drive safe.
What a master plan this late at night.
I'm sorry to have you go through
all this trouble.
No worries.
A close friend of mine owns the place.
If Bella hasn't eaten anything,
of course I'd help.
We're a team now.
Thank you.
Let's head inside.
Ms. Jang...
Actually...
I see.
I knew it was you as soon
as I saw the porridge.
I knew you cooked it.
I guess I'm busted.
Had I not lost my memories,
the time we spent together
wouldn't have happened.
[ I'm anorexic, so I can't eat properly, ]
and I'm very sensitive,
so I can never live
with other people like that,
especially in a tiny village like that.
The person that you knew was
Yoo Byeol-na.
That's not Yoo Yu-jin.
Had you gotten to know Yu-jin first,
I would've broken your heart
multiple times.
See?
You're hurt now.
I'm glad that I got to know
Byeol-na first, then.
I'm fine,
[ so Byeol-na, ]
no, Yu-jin,
I'm just happy
that your memory came back.
Thank you for the porridge.
Pungcheonok is closed today.
Is that you, Mr. Hwang?
- What?
- Haven't you heard?
Are you deaf?
Mr. Hong is with the provincial governor
and they're on their way there!
- Gosh, Da-hoon!
- What do we do?
- We need to hurry!
- What should we do first?
What do you need us to do first?
Let me help!
I don't know...
- Say something!
- Why don't we...
Wait!
Let's get changed first.
- That's a great idea.
- Let's go!
Welcome to
- Pungcheonok!
[ - Thank you. ]
- Sir.
This is the famous restaurant
that I've been telling you about.
Pungcheonok, that's a great name.
- We're ready to order.
- Yes, sir.
Can someone take the order here?
[ Everything on the menu is good. ]
The chef here is a world-renowned chef.
Then we'll have to see how good he is.
[ - We'll go with a course meal.
- I knew it. ]
That's an excellent choice.
I'll need at least 30 minutes
to get there,
so until then, start with the appetizer
and take as much time as you can.
This is omija.
Omija is an excellent fruit
with five flavors and scents,
perfect for
health and wellness trends nowadays.
They're best grown in cool weather.
Sorry, I'm getting nervous.
This is a salad made
with apples from Jungnyeong.
They're very sweet as they've been grown
high up in the mountains.
And the salad dressing is
a house special sauce,
so you'll be amazed at the flavors.
Here.
This is
pickled garlic
[ made with garlic grown here in Nonyang. ]
Let me tell you a secret.
This garlic isn't just a vegetable,
but a medicine.
[ You know how in the old tales, ]
the bear becomes human
after eating garlic?
That garlic is from Nonyang!
Quick!
Please prepare the broth.
Mushroom, shrimp, tofu, green onion,
deodeok, and tteok-galbi. Let's go.
Yes, Chef.
- Please keep stirring it.
- Yes, Chef.
- Let's go.
[ - Good work! ]
- Good work, Chef Moon.
Finally!
This looks scrumptious.
- Enjoy!
- Yes.
Let's dig in.
Yes!
Gosh.
They're really enjoying it.
Get home safely.
The food was excellent.
Let's go.
Chef Moon, I'll give whatever support
that I can,
so please do your best.
Thank you, sir.
- Good work.
- Let's head inside.
- Let's go.
Officer Jo?
I just got a call
from National Forensic Service
and the blood found
in the fake registered car
[ matches with Oh Jung-tae's DNA, ]
[ the man who was caught
in front of your house. ]
That means
that Mr. Jin, Mr. Park's senior,
and Jung-tae are on one team.
[ I found it out. ]
- Mr. Jin?
[ - Yes! ]
I've requested the police in Seoul
to investigate the matter further,
so they'll get caught for sure.
Don't worry.
[ Donghan ]
[ What do you mean? ]
[ There's a broadcasting company here
that we haven't invited. ]
Who called them?
I asked about it,
and apparently, Ms. Han did.
What is happening?
Things aren't looking good.
Chairman Louis is coming from France
and he called a broadcasting company
to the boutique.
But the bigger issue is
that there are two outfits
being displayed for the opening.
Explain properly!
Well,
the reason Sun-young called
Chairman Louis here is...
- Find a way to stop him from coming.
- But there's no way.
Find a way no matter what!
Figure out how we can contact Louis.
Yes, sir. Yes.
If you don't, you're fired.
Yes, sir.
[ Belle Ombre's boutique opening ceremony
will be broadcast live soon. ]
[ Madam Jang ]
It's starting now.
[ Belle Ombre's boutique opening ceremony
will be broadcast live soon. ]
[ Eccentric! Chef Moon ]
What do I do?
[ One has been made by fake Bella, ]
[ and the other has been made
by Bella herself. ]
Byeol-na must be going through a lot.
- Hello?
[ - It's me, Chef Moon. ]
[ Byeol-na! ]
[ You'll be on my side
whatever choice I make, right? ]
How can you do this?
[ Can you let me in on your revenge plan? ]
[ Find her weakness. ]
[ Do you want to just elope with me? ]