[ Nonyang County Office ]
[ Sir, ]
you're running for provincial governor
in the upcoming election.
- What?
[ - What? Provincial governor? ]
[ - Provincial governor?
- Unbelievable. ]
- What's going on?
- He's running for office?
- How could he do that?
- He should quit his job now.
- You seem to know a lot.
[ - Unbelievable. ]
Right here in Seoha Village, Nonyang,
I'll open up a restaurant that can
complete your plan for the local business.
[ - A restaurant? ]
- That's right. A restaurant.
- That's great.
- He'll cook with our produce
and sell food at the restaurant.
- That's it.
- He's so smart.
I'll cook with only the local produce
from appetizers to desserts.
And I'll develop a signature dish
that will put Nonyang on the map.
- That's a great idea.
- I like that idea.
- Right.
- Great.
[ How did he come up
with such a good idea? ]
[ Goodness. ]
So let's say
that you open up a restaurant.
Seoha Village is located
in the remotest area of Nonyang.
It doesn't matter
how famous you are as a chef.
I doubt anyone would go there to eat.
How could you say such a thing?
You're being too harsh with your words!
Besides, as long as the food is good,
people from Seoul will come.
People from abroad might even come!
- Aren't I right?
[ - That's right. ]
[ As I am the man
with the most connections in Nonyang, ]
if I make some calls, I bet...
One, two, three, four...
I wouldn't be able to count
all the customers with my own fingers.
That's right. I'm the head
of the women's society and the village.
[ - Right. ]
- And who's my husband?
And he's the subsection chief
of this county.
Honey. Right?
Yes.
Well, you know...
Anyway, tons of people
will dine at the restaurant!
- Right.
- Yes.
[ - Exactly.
- Yes. ]
[ - Right.
- So many people will come.
- Exactly.
[ If the food is good, ]
[ - people will be coming from everywhere.
- My gosh. ]
Give us a chance, sir.
Give our village a chance.
Well, suit yourself.
[ - What does that mean?
- What? ]
- What's he saying?
- We can do whatever we want?
[ - My goodness. ]
- This is amazing.
- Honey, we can do it?
[ - My goodness. ]
Oh, my.
- Chef Moon.
- You're the best.
[ - You're the best, Chef Moon.
- You're so smart. ]
[ Kind People, Good Nonyang ]
Who is that man? Why is he so confident?
I just looked him up.
He is indeed a famous chef.
- Really?
- Yes.
He's not on TV,
so not that many people know him.
But he's the best chef
in the culinary world.
- I should have gotten his autograph.
- What?
Nothing, sir.
It's just a restaurant.
Yes. Right.
Handle this as quickly as you can,
so it doesn't affect the development
- of the clothing industrial complex.
- Yes, sir.
By the way,
how did he know that I was planning
to run for provincial governor?
[ Right. What was that called? ]
The local business?
How did you come up with such an idea?
Exactly.
You said you were a famous chef.
You seem to know everything.
That was...
You should tell them yourself.
What?
Actually,
I should take all the credit for that.
[ What are you talking about? ]
- Listen.
- Okay.
Here's how it happened.
[ Okay. ]
[ "Promoting local produce"? ]
You think we have time for this?
This has been prepared for a long time.
Tell the Director of Culture and Tourism
to wait.
Yes, sir.
[ I got a hint from
what the county governor said. ]
[ I secretly snuck
into Department of Culture and Tourism. ]
[ As this was a top-secret document
which was very important to our county, ]
[ the security was airtight. ]
[ What was that called? It was like
"Mission: Impossible" or "The Matrix". ]
[ You know what I'm talking about, right? ]
[ Tourism Business ]
[ It was a life-threatening crisis. ]
[ I used my swift movements. ]
[ Local Business Promoting Local Produce ]
That's how
we were able to get this document.
Things at the office are quite dynamic.
When I went there to take care of
my business, it was never like that.
My gosh, don't be so rash with your words.
Chul-nam, you're
a family of a civil servant.
You're not the civil servant.
There are things we cannot just share
with the civilians.
So you contributed this time.
You and your bragging.
What are you talking about? Stop.
My husband was able to get
his hands on this important intel
and passed it along to Chef Moon. Right?
Then, you should compliment
and say nice things about what he did.
Look at him. He's getting all jealous.
I wasn't jealous!
Then, when Chef Moon
opens up a restaurant,
we just have to bring customers to him.
That's right. Yes.
Well, about what I said earlier...
Psychologically speaking,
I had to bluff about my connections
at that moment, so that was just a bluff.
Darn it. My gosh.
Why worry when we haven't opened
the restaurant yet?
After opening the restaurant...
My gosh, you could be so simple-minded.
Where is he going to open it?
[ In terms of geopolitics, ]
location is the most important factor
when running a business.
I'll open the restaurant at my home.
At home?
Given the location of his house,
that's not a bad spot.
- Right. Yes.
[ - Yes. ]
Chef Moon, will you be able
to handle everything on your own?
Shouldn't we help you out? Right?
[ Of course. ]
We can come together as a group
and help him out.
[ - Right.
- That's right. ]
In that case, Chef Moon,
come to the county office tomorrow.
I'll get everything ready
to change the purpose of your house.
Okay.
[ Clothing Industrial Complex ]
[ - Is this it?
- Yes. ]
He's planning to build
[ a huge complex for clothing factories
and a warehouse in Seoha Village. ]
And the entire village including
Chef Moon's house is subject to the plan.
Chef Moon must be in a tight spot.
- Get ready for a business trip.
- Pardon?
Do you have a plan in mind?
I think I have a good chance
to go up against Mr. Lim.
What happened?
We looked into it,
and I don't think we can get him
on our side.
Why?
The chief of the village is
the son of Pungcheonok.
Pungcheonok?
You know, the burnt restaurant.
How is that relevant to us?
It is irrelevant.
Mr. Jung, you'd better get a grip.
- I'm sorry.
- If he can't be on our side,
you must have come up
with a way to fix that.
Are you just going to give me
this useless report?
Go back down there and handle it.
If you can't resolve this,
don't think about coming back.
Yes, sir.
[ Chef Moon Seung-mo ]
[ "Gourmandism" ]
- What's that sound?
[ - "Business"? ]
"Gourmandism Business".
What are you doing?
I'm glad you're here.
How do you read this part?
What? That's P.
P? Like when you say "dog"?
No, that's not "D". It's "P".
All right. Read from the top.
"Gourmandism"
- "Business Plan".
[ - "Business Plan". ]
By the way, what is this?
Where did you get this?
The handsome man left this.
It was on Dad's desk.
[ What handsome man? ]
Why do you have that?
It didn't look like you were reading it.
So I'll keep this.
This isn't for you. Give me that.
Dad. That's mine. Give it back now.
The handsome man gave it to us.
Why do you keep calling him that?
Seol-a, did you hurt your eyes?
Why? He was handsome.
[ As if. ]
Besides, he's way too old.
He's an old man for her.
If he's handsome, he might look young.
Are you siding with him
because he helped you out that day?
I saved you two times...
Dad!
My gosh, why did she take it from my room?
[ Locally specialized restaurant ]
[ It's hard to serve different variations
of Korean dishes. ]
Darn it. Why does it
have to be Donghan Food of all places?
Yes, Mr. Hwang.
Should I head over there now?
[ They won't approve the change. ]
What? They won't approve it?
No, they won't. Your house is
an old house and must be preserved,
so they won't change
the use of your residence.
Who's behind this?
Who do you think?
It's the county governor.
[ We need to get approval
from him to change the use of it. ]
You're the managing director
of Donghan Food?
- Yes.
- What brings you here?
I heard there will be a clothing
industrial complex in Nonyang.
I see. I didn't do anything for it.
It's all thanks to your company.
And I also heard the residents
of the village are strongly against it.
Yes. Well, as for that matter,
I already took care of it.
Pardon?
A famous chef from Seoul
lives in that village.
He stood our way
claiming he'll open a restaurant.
But today, I didn't approve of his request
to change the use of his residence.
A restaurant?
Yes.
I want you to approve his request
to open a restaurant.
Pardon?
Donghan Food is planning
to make a very big investment
in the restaurant he will open.
Pardon?
[ Nonyang County Office ]
I can't believe I had to come
to this rural town again.
Wait. Isn't that Mr. Kang's car?
He doesn't have any businesses here.
Did I see it wrong?
It's cold.
[ Nonyang County Office ]
[ A restaurant? ]
So are you telling me
because of a mere restaurant,
there will be a problem in setting up
the clothing industrial complex?
My gosh, don't be so extreme about it.
To get everything in order,
I already told you that it would take
at least three months.
I'm just asking you
to give me that much time.
Sir.
If you keep this up,
we might change our mind
and move it somewhere else.
Come on.
Then, I have no choice.
What could I do?
What? What could...
What?
I don't know why
he's suddenly changing his side.
[ Managing Director Lim Chul-yong ]
[ Go back down there and handle it. ]
If you can't resolve this,
don't think about coming back.
What am I supposed to do?
[ Will this work? ]
It's not a losing game for us.
We can keep an eye on the restaurant
for three months.
We'll side with the one
that gives us a better deal.
By the way, this sure is interesting.
Pardon?
It's Donghan International
versus Donghan Food.
Are you playing with me right now?
I mean, earlier, he didn't approve
your request to change the use.
But now, he said you could.
I don't know what's going on either.
Well, anyway, isn't this a good thing?
You just need to focus
on opening up your restaurant.
[ Chef Moon,
please don't be upset about it. ]
[ Who is it? ]
You can't just pop out of nowhere
without a warning.
Hello, we meet again.
Is Chef Moon inside?
What?
What is it?
Watch out.
Chef Moon is out right now.
Really?
Well, if you don't mind,
could we wait here until he comes back?
Sure.
Thank you.
By the way, haven't we met before?
We met at the hospital.
No, not just there.
Where was it?
[ What's this about? ]
[ Gosh. ]
Goodness.
It's hot, so be careful.
Thank you.
[ Why are you serving us tea? ]
What if you spill it? It's hot.
And what are you wearing at home?
Be quiet.
This is my usual outfit at home.
Don't act like
you've never seen it before.
When have you worn that at home?
Dad.
Then, I'll leave you to it.
Just like any other day,
I'll go into my room
and read my book quietly.
I had no idea that you had
such an adorable daughter like her.
Mr. Choi, if this is
about the premium Korean food project...
I heard that you're preparing
to open a restaurant.
How did you know?
Please allow us to invest
in your restaurant,
and participate in our project in return.
- What?
- If you agree to the term,
this will be a great win-win
situation for everyone.
Did you stop by the county office
before coming here?
We did meet with the county governor
to prepare for our business.
I see.
I guess people at Donghan
always do as they please.
- What?
[ - Kicking people out as they please ]
and helping them out as they please.
When a deed is unwanted,
it's all considered rude.
Hey, they only want to help!
What's wrong with you?
[ We don't have much, anyway. ]
I think there's been a misunderstanding.
We only wanted to help.
Isn't it time for the meeting?
Excuse me.
I have to get to another appointment.
[ Seung-mo... ]
I'm sorry you had to come so far for this.
Why are they here?
Thanks.
Thank you all for gathering today.
I wanted to talk about how
we will be setting up the restaurant,
so you can feel free to speak your mind.
Chef Moon? I have a question.
Why are those lads here?
They are my guests.
- What?
- They are your guests?
Yes, that handsome man over there
is the savior who saved us and Bong-doo.
What's wrong?
We are here because we want to invest
in Chef Moon's restaurant,
so you don't have to worry about us.
[ - "Invest"? ]
- Are you sure you're interested?
Well, it's all up to Chef Moon,
but yes, we are interested in doing so.
Isn't it a good thing if a big company
wants to make an investment?
But he keeps playing hard to get!
He must have other plans, then.
- I guess he trusts us a lot.
[ - What? ]
[ - Well, we are quite trustworthy. ]
- Be quiet, everyone!
Here.
I made the blueprints
for remodeling Chef Moon's house.
[ What do you think? ]
[ What is it? ]
- Let me see.
- What's this?
My goodness,
Byeol-na has a talent for drawing.
[ Byeol-na sure is eccentric! ]
How did you come up with these drawings?
Chef Moon, is this what you wanted?
I think this is really great.
It doesn't require much construction.
We could finish this together
within a short time.
Do you like it? Then I'll take care
of the interior decorating.
Hey.
- Yes?
- You be my assistant.
[ What? ]
- Okay.
- Then I want to be your assistant too.
- Me too, Byeol-na!
- Sure, okay.
Then Byeol-na will do
the interior decorating.
Then what should we do?
I have a special favor to ask of you.
Come up with a menu
using Nonyang's local produce.
This is the most important task.
I don't know if I will be of any help.
Yoon-ja,
you're such a good cook.
Don't be so modest.
Excuse me. What should we do?
What?
- Us?
- You be quiet.
[ - Over there. ]
- Okay.
I've never done any work like this.
It's all thanks to you.
There's still tons. Hurry up.
"Seoha Village".
"An old house".
This must be it.
Darn it.
- Why?
- This.
That really is Mr. Kang!
What is he doing here?
This collection in Seoul
is Bella's first collaboration show
in Korea,
so she chose Seoul as the theme
to show the harmony
between the East and the West
and the modern and the retro sentiment,
and expressed the unique image of Seoul
through fashion.
A powerful tailored suit
[ and blazer. Feminine lace ]
and a ruffled skirt.
By using these bold contrasts,
she is uniquely showing off
her colors through
a mix of solid patterns.
[ Donghan ]
How much do you forecast in sales?
Don't you think your company
should be handling that?
I'm sure you have dozens of workers
in this building
who were hired to calculate that.
I'm a businessman, not an artist.
I'm only asking since it's hard
for me to tell with just the concept,
so don't take it personally.
Well...
I'm sure Bella's name-value alone
will easily exceed
Donghan's current sales,
so no need to worry.
[ Junior Managing Director Jung Gwang-su ]
Then I will trust your words.
Yes?
[ Yes. ]
Jun-su?
I guess you did well this time.
You may return.
"Sales"? You've got to be kidding me.
How dare he.
Who does he think Bella is? How vulgar.
Bella...
Ma'am, please check the clothing.
Tell them to come in.
I don't think this is the original design
for the collar.
It's hard to get it right
unless it's Bella, ma'am.
Are you kidding me?
I'm sorry, ma'am.
The finishing touch is different.
The fold shouldn't show any backstitches.
It may seem like nothing,
but that's what makes Bella different.
All right?
Hey.
Hey, Hyun-a.
[ Are you listening? ]
It's all done.
[ Is that all right? ]
I fixed the collar
according to your feedback.
This is enough.
[ This is enough ]
for your part.
Finish it off.
You said you know
who Bella is, didn't you?
But she's not who you think she is.
I never deceived you,
but how can I win your trust?
Did you call me over
to make these useless excuses?
- What's this?
- A gift for you.
[ That mountain ]
is where Yoo Hyo-myoung is buried.
What are you playing at?
I'm going to clear it out
as a gift for you.
and build Donghan's clothing
industrial complex.
It's all for you.
But...
Someone is trying to get in the way.
Your son, Jun-su.
[ Put that in the center. Here. ]
Where in the center?
The center over there!
- No.
- Gosh, it's not in line!
This way.
[ - This way. ]
- Okay.
Wait, stop. There.
Bring the one outside as well.
Gosh, I'm out of water. Let's go, Seol-a.
Jun-su. Will they even notice us?
I don't know.
Let's just keep trying.
Come on.
[ Mother ]
Goodness.
They only handle wild fish.
This guy was swimming
in the Namhan River this morning. Right?
Of course. You know it well.
[ Goodness. ]
Is that a mandarin fish?
[ - Yes. ]
- That guy is the pride of Nonyang.
Would you like to see this?
[ - Of course!
- Okay. ]
Did you collect these
from the mountains yourself?
They smell amazing.
The land is great here,
so they taste great.
I only sell them to my neighbors,
but people come in
from all over Seoul for them.
Pick out the best ones for us.
All right.
He's the chef from our village.
He's a chef.
- He's a chef?
- Yes.
Did you make this yourself?
Sure. It's not that hard.
[ It takes nothing. ]
It's too good for that.
You need to dip it in this. Here.
- Is it good?
- Yes.
Wait a minute.
Seoha Village
used to be known for mung beans.
We were all poor,
so we always made porridge and jelly
with these mung beans.
You said your mother was from around here,
didn't you?
Then she must have made some good
mung bean porridge.
Is that so? My mom made
really good mung bean porridge.
That's the first dish
I learned to cook from her.
Is that so?
Will these be of any help, though?
It's just mung bean jelly.
Of course!
I'll make a really good dish with this.
All right.
Don't you think these windows
look a bit empty?
My heart is even more empty.
What's wrong?
The handsome guy is gone.
I'm not getting any inspiration.
Inspiration...
Wait a minute.
This is it. This should be just right.
- Painter!
- Gosh, you surprised me!
What's so urgent?
It's very urgent.
- Follow me, Painter.
- What?
- Hurry up!
- Gosh...
Wait up, Byeol-na!
Welcome!
- Painter, take those three.
- Okay.
You take these.
Let's go.
What are you doing? Follow me.
What's with her? Is she a thief?
Hey!
Gosh, those two guys made things easier.
What are you going to do with all this?
[ I have no clue. Gosh. ]
Do you even know how to use that?
[ - By the looks of it, ]
- Yes.
I think she does.
What?
I think she knows how to use it very well.
Bingo.
Bingo. Of course you do.
All right. You guys take care.
Then I'll bring this back.
You guys can walk...
All right.
Let's go. Okay.
[ I'm going. ]
Painter! Try harder!
How can a man be so weak?
What? One moment.
- Run!
[ Run, Da-hoon! ]
This is so fun!
[ Learning Korean Letters ]
Hey, that's not it.
We're only putting one.
Yes, ma'am.
- Shall we see, then?
- Yes.
- Look.
- Okay.
[ - Here.
- Goodness. ]
What do you think?
- It's beautiful.
[ - It's so pretty. ]
- Byeol-na, you're the best!
- You're the best!
Shall we get started now?
What?
All of this?
Done.
[ It's beautiful. ]
No wonder she's so proud of herself.
What a masterpiece.
No wonder he's so picky.
I shouldn't.
Mother.
[ - Is this why? ]
- Mother, what do you mean?
This is your dream that you want to make
come true for him?
- Sorry?
- Your dream was to get in the way
of Donghan International's
clothing industrial complex?
Mother,
- I don't know what you've heard from...
[ - Jun-su. ]
I know you don't like Chul-yong,
[ but I cannot accept you affecting ]
the company due to your personal feelings,
both as your mother
and as an entrepreneur.
- I...
- Don't do it!
Don't get in the way of establishing
the clothing industrial complex.
Mother, please. Just hear me out.
[ No. ]
You listen to me.
Or else,
I'll have no other option
but to kick you out.
To make...
Who were you
before you came here?
[ Belle Ombre ]
Since this is Bella's first show in Korea,
we have to get everything perfect.
How is the timeline going?
Here is the timeline so far.
- Okay.
- You just need to approve it by today.
- The rehearsal is in the afternoon?
[ - Yes. ]
Okay, let's get started.
Byeol-na, you made all of this
by yourself?
[ My goodness. ]
I used to be a seamstress
back in the days,
and as an expert,
I can say that she is no amateur at this.
Look at this. This is hemming at its best.
You're too kind.
Beautiful.
You made all of this using blankets?
I think I'm a genius.
I felt like I could do it,
so I gave it a try, and I did it.
They're too good to just wear
in the restaurant.
Has your memory not come back yet?
No, but bits and pieces are coming back.
Really?
[ - Well,
- Yes. ]
[ I have a memory of sewing something... ]
like a lunatic!
You must've worked at a sewing factory
at the Guro Industrial Complex.
Where is that?
Is that a place for geniuses like myself?
Of course. People there are so good
at sewing.
I was a genius all along!
These are really beautiful. Right, Mom?
Absolutely.
She doesn't even know who she is,
[ - yet she's so talented. ]
- Wear this.
What about you? I plastered money on you
to study in Seoul and what can you do?
Plaster money?
You sure know how
to make people feel terrible.
Are we just going to look at these?
Why don't we try them on?
Hold on.
Okay. Fix this part.
I think we should change the orders.
This dangling thing looks messy. Go.
[ Good. ]
How is this?
Good.
Yoon-ja!
[ Look at that! ]
What is it?
[ Gosh, Gon-sook. ]
- Look.
[ - Look at you. ]
[ - You look like a model.
- You look like you belong in Seoul. ]
That's my daughter.
She should go to Seoul.
[ - Beautiful!
- Absolutely. ]
You look great.
- Seol-a!
- Absolutely adorable!
You're so cute.
Goodness. Look.
You look great.
Good job, you all.
- Come on, Dad!
[ - Seung-mo, come on. ]
- No.
- Chef Moon!
Chef Moon!
[ He's going to do it. ]
- You look good!
- Give him a round of applause.
[ That was amazing, Chef Moon. ]
Don't do this. I'll kill you.
I present to you, Designer Yoo Byeol-na!
Yoo Byeol-na!
- Thank you!
[ - Byeol-na! ]
What an incredible talent you have.
We don't need Donghan's
clothing industrial complex here,
we need to build Byeol-na a store instead.
[ - That's right!
- That's right! ]
Lights off.
Turn on the backlight after three seconds.
Three, two, one. On.
[ Belle Ombre ]
Okay. Please turn the lights back on.
Let's end it off here.
- Good work.
- Good work, ma'am.
[ Belle Ombre ]
[ By Bella Y ]
Can we really do a Bella show
with these fake Bella clothes?
Bella, you'd always be out and about
but came back right before the show.
You'll do that this time, right?
Bella...
[ Mr. Jin Tae-soo ]
Yes, Mr. Jin? Any news for me?
Hello.
There's no news yet.
So I'm thinking
maybe we should start searching
the entire country.
That requires quite some money,
so what do you think?
How much do you need?
I'll text you.
Yes.
What are you going to do?
If we get some money in,
we should at least send her
a scorched corpse or something.
Yes, sir.
Where does Da-mi live?
- What?
- Da-mi. You know, Gong Da-mi.
I hear she lives here.
You've come to the wrong village.
Wait, did you say that it was Ms. Gong?
I think I do know who she is.
Where does she live?
Over there.
You're Hyo-sook?
You told me it was Gong Da-mi.
Don't you know nicknames?
Just shut it and get ready to take photos.
Fine.
Do you really think that we can get
some nice photos here?
This is too rural for my taste.
Don't worry.
There's a very fancy place.
[ You look great! Great! ]
There. Okay.
That looks amazing!
- Gosh.
- Nice butt. Good pose.
How is there such a hip place
in this middle-of-nowhere village?
? The backdrop is surely amazing ?
- Next pose.
- Hyo-sook, you're doing great!
What's with all the noise?
Is Hyo-sook holding in her poop?
She looks like she's about
to poop in her pants.
That's not it.
Frowning doesn't make you a model.
You have to put your soul into it.
Feel the space.
Breathe, and look at the sky.
Feel the wind
and the colors of the windows.
Pour whatever you're feeling
right into the camera.
Smile more and hold your arms out.
Feel the whole space with your body.
One, two.
That's perfect. Stay still.
One more time.
[ One. ]
It's a little too dark here.
What are you doing?
Getting ready to take some better photos.
Straighten the back.
Keep your posture straight.
Don't forget.
One, two.
- You're doing great.
- Looks great.
[ Beautiful. ]
[ What are you all doing? ]
Are you okay?
Byeol-na, are you all right?
What are you doing in my property
without permission?
Get out.
I gave them permission.
It's a good way to get some exposure!
Get out!
Darn it!
Byeol-na.
What's up with your dad?
He may be your friend,
but wasn't that too much?
I can still smell the washcloth
on your face!
Don't you insult my dad!
You have no idea
how much Da-hoon messes up.
When did I ever do such a thing?
[ Seoha Teahouse ]
Look. What do you think?
I look pretty.
This place is just as hip
as the hippest neighborhood in Seoul.
- Who designed the place?
- The lady back at the house.
Really?
She's something else.
I wonder
why she was acting all weird.
Me too.
How are you feeling?
I'm all right.
Why are you so full of surprises?
Were you worried about me?
Not at all.
Where did everyone else go?
I got rid of them all.
What?
I wanted to show them something at night.
I had no idea
my yard could look like this.
Great work, Byeol-na.
Right?
I'm telling you, I'm this good.
Don't you think we can just open
the restaurant right now?
- Why don't we?
- Really?
[ Belle Ombre ]
[ Ombre de Seoul ]
[ Belle Ombre X Donghan International ]
What are we watching?
A fashion show.
Not just by anyone,
but by the famous Bella.
We had a Byeol-na fashion show, too.
That's fake. This is a real fashion show.
Are you talking about me?
What is this? A fashion show?
Make some space for me.
What do I do?
She'll come.
Bella will come.
- Ma'am.
- Follow me.
[ Ombre de Seoul ]
Sit here.
Ma'am!
Get on the stage for the finale.
Sorry?
This is the finale
of your fake Bella show.
Get it together and don't mess up.
This is Bella's show,
the world's most-renowned designer.
Yes, ma'am.
[ Belle Ombre by Bella Y ]
Bella!
[ Bella! ]
[ Eccentric! Chef Moon ]
[ Chef Moon, why do you like me? ]
Did I say that I like you?
[ You're too clueless about women. ]
Don't these clothes look similar
to what Byeol-na made?
You've finally taken it away.
[ That's right, I'm Bella. ]
What kind of a person was I?
[ Ever since I first saw you, ]
[ I keep thinking of you
and wanting to take care of you. ]
I've got a call.
I got so excited,
I couldn't sleep last night.
[ What? ]
[ You have a problem you can't talk about? ]
[ When Byeol-na's memory comes back ]
[ and she leaves... ]
[ I think my heart will hurt.
It makes me sad. ]