[ Episode 9 ]
Seung-mo!
[ Let's get out. ]
[ It's okay, come on out. ]
Come here. It's okay, Seol-a. Here.
[ Seol-a. ]
Yes?
Seol-a, if something happens to me,
you have to go find him.
He's your father.
He runs a big restaurant in Seoul.
My father?
[ Star Chef's Restaurant ]
Seol-a.
Aren't you hungry?
When will my grandpa go to the hospital?
I think he should go pretty soon.
I have a favor to ask you.
You will help me, right?
[ Take me to my father in Seoul. ]
[ Rice Soup Restaurant, Pungcheonok ]
[ Hello? ]
What? Ms. Park is in critical condition?
I'll try to get back as soon as possible.
But I can't go right now.
Thank you.
Seol-a, let's go.
I'm teaching you everything that I know
because I have accepted you as my son.
Did you get that?
Thank you, sir.
- Put one more log in there.
- Yes, sir.
It's good. It came out nicely.
Now, wrap it up.
Yes, sir.
Come this way.
Where are you going?
Just come with me.
[ It's just as it was before. ]
[ What's this, Chef Moon? ]
The soy sauce made
with domestically produced beans.
The soy sauce you were looking for?
Really?
- This is great news!
- Yes!
[ We found it at last! ]
- What are you doing? Keep up.
- Hurry.
[ This way. ]
[ Jang Sun-young ]
But why isn't that girl calling
Ms. Jang Sun-young?
[ She's perfectly healthy. ]
But Ms. Jang is
desperately trying to find her.
[ Mr. Park ]
Hey, Mr. Park. It's me.
That woman lost her memory.
She was found at the mountain.
And she's only staying there
because she has no place to go.
She doesn't even know who she is.
I'm certain of it.
Thank you.
I'll buy you another drink soon.
She lost her memory?
You'll make tofu?
Now? Why?
That will be Seol-a's grandpa's dinner.
How will you make that from scratch?
No one has cooked here for a long time.
Let's buy it on our way...
[ The Whole World Is Crazy
About Chef Moon Seung-mo ]
Is that you, Chef Moon?
[ I really want to cook the tofu
he taught me. ]
Get some rest inside if you're tired.
[ I can cook it alone. ]
No, I'll do it with Seol-a.
I'll help you.
We can finish quickly that way.
- What are you doing, Painter?
- I'm milling.
My gosh, try harder.
- I'm trying already.
[ - Faster! ]
[ Goodness. ]
You just need to gently break
the clumps on the surface.
Okay.
Gently.
- Isn't this hard?
- No, it's fun.
By the way,
how can you tell if this is cooked?
By smelling it.
If it's undercooked,
it smells like fresh beans.
And if it's overcooked,
you can smell it burning.
This is why Seol-a had
the sharpest sense of smell!
That's right. Her sense of smell
almost makes her a superhero.
It's all cooked now.
All right.
Now.
Don't press on it hard like that.
You have to press on it gently like this.
Press gently.
- Did you get it?
- Gently?
Okay. Gently.
Tofu seemed like such a simple ingredient,
but it's really hard to make one.
- Nothing comes easy in life.
[ - That's right. ]
If people enjoy the food
as much as you and Seol-a do,
it makes the chef happy.
Well, it's because
you make such good food.
- Right?
- That's true.
What is this awkward vibe?
Something happened yesterday, right?
- Try it.
[ - Okay. ]
You too, Seol-a. Try it.
Okay.
- Me too.
[ - How can the tofu ]
be so savory and soft?
It's because my grandpa
is the master of beans.
[ He was busy making tofu all the time ]
that he didn't take care of his health.
To be honest, I used to hate tofu.
What are those rings?
- It's nothing.
Stop lying. Those are matching rings!
No, they are not. It's a long story.
Stop making a fuss. And let's get going.
He has to eat his dinner. Let's go.
You must be jealous. Isn't this beautiful?
Grandpa, is it good?
Yes. It's good.
Where's my son?
Seung-mo is my son.
That's right. He's right here.
- My father.
- Who are you?
Seung-mo is my son.
It's okay.
My grandpa sometimes recognizes people,
and sometimes, he doesn't.
Grandpa, have more tofu.
Okay. This is so good.
He can't recognize you at all.
This is awful.
- Stay here.
- What?
Okay.
Yes, Mr. Hwang.
My gosh, Chef Moon. Where are you?
[ All of your family is gone, too! ]
What on earth is going on?
It's nothing. We'll come back tonight.
I called because I need your help.
- Okay.
[ - Do you know if there's a nursing home ]
for dementia patients near Seoha Village?
I need to take care of someone.
I'll look into that,
so don't worry about that.
Okay. I'll see you in the village.
[ Constable Jo Soon-mi ]
[ A black van, Chef Moon's house ]
[ 22O 6100 ]
[ What are you doing? ]
Nothing. My gosh, you didn't go home yet?
- Aren't you going home?
- I should.
Don't turn on all the lights
when it's just you.
Okay.
This is Jo Soon-mi
from Investigation Support Team.
I need you to look
into a license plate number.
It's 22O 6100.
[ My goodness. Where have you been? ]
If you're leaving town,
you should have informed us in advance.
I left to get some ssi-ganjang.
I should have told you before I left.
I'm sorry for making you worry.
- My gosh.
- All right.
He called me.
Why are you giving him a hard time?
By the way, what's ssi-ganjang?
You treat it like it's some kind of gold.
[ Is it absolutely necessary? ]
How are you a civil servant
when you don't know anything?
The soy sauce determines the flavor.
And among all types of soy sauce,
it's called ssi-ganjang.
Goodness.
You must be so happy to be a know-it-all.
Only a single man who cooks
for himself would know.
How would I know all that?
I had to leave
because without ssi-ganjang,
I can't make the broth from Pungcheonok.
I'll cook
under my parents' restaurant's sign
[ and to keep the pride of our village. ]
I didn't think I should settle for less.
- Well done.
[ - Yes, that's great. ]
That's enough interrogating.
Help us move this.
- Move what?
- We have to move that.
- All right. Let's see.
- What is it?
- Which one is it?
- Is it that?
- Is that ssi-ganjang?
- Yes.
Mr. Lim, the media
is going crazy these days.
You should have told us
if you had such good news like this one.
Thanks to Mr. Lim, I scored a good one.
The graph for the stock rise
is just perfect.
I doubt that you're treating us
to just this drink to celebrate.
I'm sure all of you already know
that my daughter is Bella.
Thanks to that, we're all smiling here.
And did you know that my daughter
chose me as her legal guardian?
Well, I wasn't aware of that.
[ Shareholder Written Resolution ]
[ Instate Han Dong-gil
as Honorary Chairman. ]
Bella established Belle Ombre
all on her own in France.
I'm sure you know her brand itself
became a symbol of luxury.
I can
leave the company at any minute
with my daughter.
And if Bella and I set up
a fashion company in Korea,
we would be competing against Donghan.
And if that happens,
I will do everything I can
to win the fight.
Whatever decision you make,
I will accept your decision
with the utmost respect.
[ Shareholder Na Gyung-hun ]
[ Shareholder Hong Dae-gon ]
Seol-a, say hello
to your grandpa and grandma.
Tell them that you will listen to your dad
[ and grow up to be a fine lady. ]
- "Dad"?
And I'm going to bring your grandpa
to a nursing home
near our home.
You and I will go and visit him often.
Don't worry.
Everyone, pay them your respect.
Others have elementary schoolers
at your age.
You're still single
and keep wandering off to other countries.
How can you say that?
Your son is being a patriot
by spreading Korean cuisine
in other countries.
- You're being too harsh.
- Gosh.
Before you become a patriot,
why don't you think of your parents first?
I can't let this be.
Get married this year.
Or go and bring me a grandchild.
I'll raise the kid. Okay?
[ Mom, Father. ]
[ There's someone I want to protect. ]
[ You would've liked her. ]
[ And I'll raise Seol-a well ]
[ and carry on the legacy of Pungcheonok. ]
[ You can trust me. ]
Didn't you say you were close
to Chef Moon's parents?
Why didn't you stay with him?
I'm not that tactless.
That was the first time Seung-mo accepted
that he was Seol-a's dad.
I thought they would need some time alone.
- I guess you really aren't that tactless.
- What did you say?
By the way,
why did he accept it?
He knows for sure now
that she isn't his daughter.
They're not related at all.
You may not be tactless,
but you sure are thoughtless.
What?
You don't have to be related by blood
to be family.
People can become family
when they find a companion
they can rely on.
Can't you tell?
I can't tell him at all.
How did you two even end up
getting matching rings?
I won't know unless you tell me.
Why? Is that not allowed?
Does that mean
you two are actually dating?
That's a secret.
You're driving me crazy!
I'm not sure if this will be of any help,
but I found something unusual, sir.
What is it?
[ Kang Min-suk's Shocking Scandal ]
It's an article from 22 years ago.
It was quite scandalous back then.
Oh, yes. I remember.
"The head of Donghan International,
Kang Min-suk".
What about it?
[ Two people died in that car accident. ]
[ There was a woman in her 30s
in the car with him. ]
We found something incredible.
She's Yoo Hyo-myoung.
- "Yoo Hyo-myoung"?
[ - Yes, sir. ]
It turns out she was Yoo Yu-jin's mom.
[ Han Mi-young Marries Lim Chul-yong ]
Kang Min-suk and Yoo Hyo-myoung died,
and Lim Chul-yong married into
the Donghan family.
And now he killed Bella
and turned his daughter into Bella?
Hey.
I think you guys did a great job.
Sorry?
Jung-tae, you go back to Nonyang
and stay there until I call you.
And Joo-hyuk, put this together for me.
Yes, sir.
Now I can finally bring some sense
into Lim Chul-yong.
Last night, some strangers came
and asked for you and Byeol-na.
- Me and Byeol-na?
- Yes!
They even showed me some pictures
and they looked like Byeol-na.
It must have been her family, right?
Well... Isn't that a good thing?
But the thing is,
they seemed somewhat suspicious.
[ - Sir!
- Over here! ]
- Please give us a word!
- Do you admit to having an affair?
[ - Is it true?
- Please tell us the truth! ]
[ - Do you admit to having an affair?
- What is your relationship? ]
Mom!
What's going on, Byeol-na?
What's wrong? Did you have a nightmare?
What was it?
I don't know.
I just feel scared,
but I don't remember it.
I think it's a dream of my childhood.
It got scary all of a sudden, but...
Anyway, I don't remember clearly.
It could mean that
your memory is coming back,
so think of it positively.
But...
I'm not sure
if having my memory back
is actually a good thing.
I'm just so happy these days
that it's making me feel uneasy.
What are you talking about?
Your family would be so disappointed
to hear that.
"Family"?
I must have a family, right?
Of course.
By the way,
how did you get such a beautiful idea?
What do you mean?
You decided to become a dad for Seol-a
and take her in as your family.
Seol-a's grandfather
thought of me as a son
and taught me all his secret recipes.
If there's one way I can repay him,
it's by taking her in
as my daughter.
That's what came to my mind.
I see.
My parents and the people
of this village taught me that
living with the people you care for
is what makes up a family.
Really?
Then...
What about me?
You're a good person,
- but...
- But what?
You care for me,
but don't consider me family?
That's not it.
You'll have to leave one day.
Whatever. Forget it.
So you're saying
I'm not part of the family.
I really feel comfortable
and familiar with
having you around.
I don't like
"comfortable" and "familiar".
What I'm trying to say is,
now I feel so empty and alone
when you're not around...
"Empty"? "Alone"?
And I don't think I would be able to
fall asleep or eat.
- Why?
- I think I'll miss you.
And long for you.
I'm thirsty.
[ - On television?
- Yes, ma'am. ]
Due to the rumors on
the merger and acquisition with Donghan,
stock prices are fluctuating, and
reporters are pouring questions at us.
I thought you could do an interview
and announce the next plans
for Belle Ombre.
"Next plans", meaning...
[ With the designs from the show, ]
we will be opening a Bella boutique
at one of Donghan's stores.
"A Bella boutique"?
So you're asking the world's
best designer, Bella,
to advertise a store on television?
Well, that's not what I meant...
All right.
But tell them
I want the questions beforehand,
and I'm only going to answer
what I want to.
Yes, ma'am.
Table number four, one rice soup.
How many times do I have to tell you?
Two rice soups, one soju!
Even Seol-a can get...
Just let me and...
I'll do it.
I used to be amazing with an abacus
as a child.
"Abacus"? What's that?
An abacus. The calculating...
How am I supposed to explain this?
Move over. I'll give it a try.
Yes, you try.
Table number four,
two rice soups, one soju.
[ That's 20 dollars. ]
Will it be cash or credit?
See? Even Seol-a can do it.
Let's see that again.
Table number four, two rice soups.
Are they all out of their minds?
What is it?
Just look at this!
No one cares about my pretty self.
They keep messaging me,
but they only want the address here!
I don't know what you're trying to say,
but why don't you post the address, then?
Then they won't ask.
Come on!
Insects live off of dewdrops,
Pengsoo lives off of tuna,
and I live off of attention.
- Gosh.
- Goodness, you.
I give you that attention.
Stop that.
You two are driving me nuts.
It was nice when you were in Seoul
because you didn't pester me.
Mother,
please don't be too harsh to Hyo-sook.
Since when am I your mother?
Gosh, it must be nice to have
a new dependable son.
Am I right? Goodness!
Goodness.
Chef Moon, are you free?
Let's take a picture.
Everyone else is ready.
I'll be right out.
Hurry up, okay?
[ Pungcheonok ]
What is that?
That's the old sign that used to hang
at his parent's store.
Goodness.
So that's why he needed that ssi-ganjang.
Come on now, let's take a picture.
- Yes.
- Let's do that.
- Make sure the sign is showing.
- Look at the camera.
- Come on, lower down. Where?
- Yes, okay.
One, two, three!
Pungcheonok!
You were much more appealing
when you were a hidden weapon.
But you know,
you should have been discreet
when you drew out that weapon.
I heard you were meeting
the stockholders behind my back.
You should have kept them quite
if you were going to do such a thing.
That's what I was intending.
What?
You need to hear it for yourself
in order to realize that
your end has come.
[ Please think of it ]
as words from a business partner,
not a son-in-law.
"Business partner"?
The times have changed.
You need to hand over the administration
to a business professional like me
and take a step back
as a leader of the past.
I want you to enjoy
the rest of your life in peace.
Those are
my words as a son-in-law,
not a business partner.
Chul-yong... Why, you...
Did you think that I wouldn't know
your current physical state?
What?
Dr. Choi showed me your chart.
I couldn't bear to keep watching
your health
cause a threat to the company.
[ Your greed has become ugly, ]
and I can't let it risk the lives
of our thousands of employees.
Make your decision.
Why, you...
Hello?
Is this 911?
[ We start business tomorrow. ]
Thank you all for helping me out.
In return for your support
and with my parents' recipe,
I will do my best.
Bravo!
Come up and say a word.
I understand that you must hate
just the sound of Donghan itself.
Donghan Food will work hard
to not disappoint Chef Moon
and everyone else,
who have given me a chance
to work with you here.
Don't forget about the county office.
Since I'm the person in charge
of the office,
I'll make sure to serve you
the best that I can.
Don't worry about things.
In light of that, I've prepared a toast
on behalf of the county governor here.
Hey!
He should come here
if he wants to say something.
- Why did you just do that?
- Come here.
I have to sort something out here.
What's my position?
- What?
- Your position?
I'm the brain of the village,
and that deserves to be recognized.
So, let's get that out of the way first.
Sure, what would you like to be?
Anything above Jang-dan is good
since I'm a founding member.
Nonsense!
Chul-nam, that's not
what positions are like.
You have to climb your way up
from the bottom.
- That's what you have to do.
- That's right.
Becoming a subsection chief is
no easy work.
Look at you.
What's above Subsection Chief?
I believe it's Manager.
Manager? That sounds nice.
I want to be General Manager Jo,
or else I'm going on a strike.
- Sure, you can be General Manager Jo.
[ - What? ]
See? He is so magnanimous.
Start calling me General Manager Jo
from now on.
I won't respond if you call me Chul-nam.
Then what am I?
I'm older and wiser
than Chul-nam here.
So, what am I?
What about Distribution Director?
Is that above General Manager?
Yes, that's above General Manager.
Sure, I'll be Distribution Director.
Wait! Who am I?
I'm the head of the women's society
and the village.
[ That being said, ]
I'll be the Operations Director, then.
Then I want to
be Senior Managing Director!
- Gosh.
- Then I'll be President!
Then I'll be the CEO!
Everyone, not everyone can have titles.
Who's going to work if everyone is
Manager and above?
Exactly my point!
[ But it's nice that everyone has a title. ]
[ - That's right. ]
- Yes, Mother.
[ This is nice. ]
What? Grandfather?
[ Seoul Medical Center ]
Father!
Are you all right?
Father?
Father!
Father... Father.
[ Please wake up. ]
Father!
I'm going now!
What took you so long?
The ritual ceremony is already over.
I've got a lot of people to serve
as a police officer.
My goodness. I'm so full.
Soon-mi, what took you so long?
- Did you just get off from work?
- Hello.
- I'm sorry.
No worries.
- Head inside and have some food.
- Yes.
Good night.
Good work tonight.
Good work. See you around.
- Let's go.
- Get some rest.
You can go, I'll be home soon.
Get home safely.
Chef Moon,
a couple of nights ago,
I saw some suspicious people
come out of your house.
Yes, they came looking for Byeol-na.
Da-hoon said that they even brought
a photo of her, which is very suspicious.
- What about them?
- They came to look for Byeol-na?
The last time I saw them,
they were looking for you.
When?
This middle-aged man with white hair was
looking for your house,
and I told you that
because he was so suspicious.
Don't you remember?
By any chance,
did someone visit your house?
Yes, someone visited me just now.
Right? It was a middle-aged person
with white hair?
Yes, it was a middle-aged woman
with white hair.
A woman?
But it was a man.
I remember.
- That's who came?
- I'm sure.
The man used to be a senior
to Mr. Park in the past...
and he operates
a security company in Seoul.
A security company?
I've kept my eyes on him
because he looked so suspicious.
He had his car parked here
and was watching your house all night.
Da-hoon also said that
they looked suspicious.
Do you have the company's
contact information?
I thought you might ask,
so I wrote down the license plate number.
Hold on.
I was saying...
[ Operation Room ]
What took you so long?
I'm sorry.
No worries.
What happened?
Dr. Choi is saying
that his blood pressure shot up
and his stitches from the surgery before
got undone.
There are news reporters outside.
Are you in your right mind?
I told you to make sure
that nobody finds out about this!
Well...
I'm sorry, sir.
We'll keep the funeral minimal.
Funeral?
Are you insane?
Are you saying that he died?
Or...
- is that what you're hoping for?
- No, I was just...
Apologize immediately.
Stop it, all of you.
The publicity team can handle the press.
[ You don't need to stay here. ]
You can go.
- Honey...
- I want you out, too.
It's really time to congratulate you now.
Let's hold an executive meeting
so that we can decide on the successor.
I agree.
He's still in surgery.
Please refrain yourself
from making such comments.
Yes, sir.
You can go now.
Take care.
Let's get going now.
Good work.
- Thank you.
- Watch your face.
Don't make it so obvious.
And make sure to expose
Chairman Han's health issues.
Yes, sir.
Hello!
How can I get to Pungcheonok?
Pungcheonok?
Go straight and you'll find a big house
on your left.
- That's Pungcheonok.
- Thank you.
Let's go.
How do they even know?
It's just the opening day.
[ Excuse me, ]
how can I get to Pungcheonok?
Go straight and you'll find a big house
on your left.
That's Pungcheonok.
[ - Thank you. ]
- Bye.
This is the place, right?
It is!
It is! Look at the windows!
- They're beautiful.
- Amazing.
Can we take photos here?
Go ahead.
Take as many as you'd like.
Welcome! Welcome.
Come this way.
[ Follow me. ]
You must've come after seeing my post.
You must be followers of mine.
It's me. Take a good look.
Take as many photos as you'd like.
Do you have back problems?
You must've come a long way for photos.
- Yes.
- Enjoy your meal
and take lots of photos.
As a food connoisseur myself,
this place is incredible
for both the food and the mood.
Let's take some photos after we eat.
We've got a good seat over there.
Please seat yourself at that table.
Here.
An order for table number three.
Order for table number six!
One tteok-galbi and one trout soup
for table number three.
There are also two bowls of rice soup
and one tteok-galbi.
- Is the soup ready?
- Yes.
Please hurry up on getting
the vegetables ready.
[ Can you pass me some spinach
for the soup? ]
- Spinach?
[ - Yes, lots of it. ]
Table number three.
Amazing.
- Amazing.
- Enjoy.
- It looks so good!
- Come this way.
Here's your table.
[ This is amazing. ]
Let's eat!
[ - It's delicious.
- Absolutely delicious. ]
It's so good!
- That's incredible.
[ - This is so smooth. ]
[ Pungcheonok Parking Lot ]
Right that way.
What's happening?
It's exactly what it looks like.
The restaurant is a huge hit!
There's no parking available up there.
Come this way.
[ Pungcheonok Parking Lot ]
Yes, Mr. Hong.
The restaurant is an absolute hit.
Really?
All right.
What an amazing meal. Let's come again.
- Thank you!
- Welcome.
- It's so nice here.
- It is incredible.
[ - Take care.
- Thank you. ]
[ - It's beautiful in here.
- Absolutely. ]
[ Two bowls of rice soup
for the corner table! ]
[ Look at that. ]
[ Thank you. ]
[ - Enjoy.
- Enjoy. ]
[ Coming right up! ]
This is so good.
This is some gourmet food.
Right? We've got a hit restaurant
here in Nonyang now.
[ Two bowls of soup for the corner table! ]
Look at that!
I didn't expect so many people
right from the opening.
How did this happen?
Seung-mo was known for being
a talented chef without a restaurant,
[ - and people ]
- Wear your sunglasses.
[ got curious
when they heard about this place. ]
- I see.
- What did you just say?
Your influence on social media
also took a huge part, of course.
- Right.
[ - What are you talking about? ]
The amazing interior design is bringing
all of these people in, don't you think?
- Sure.
[ - Hello? ]
- Coming!
- Byeol-na and social media.
That brought these people
all the way here,
to eat and enjoy the place!
That's incredible, I should thank them.
Thank you, enjoy your food.
Thank you, enjoy. Thank you.
[ - Thank you!
- Bye. ]
[ Coming right up! ]
I thought it might be you.
It's you, indeed! Hold on.
Mr. Hwang, no need.
[ - Just wait. ]
- Mr. Hwang.
Hello!
The county governor of Nonyang has
made a visit himself!
[ Han Mi-young ]
Hello.
We couldn't find Bella.
[ I'm going back to Paris tonight. ]
[ I'll look for ways to find her there. ]
I figured that you'd be busy,
so this is my goodbye to you.
Come visit me
before you leave for the airport.
I have something to tell you.
Dr. Choi is saying that tonight and
tomorrow will determine everything.
He says it's unlikely
that he'll be conscious again.
I hope he dies in peace.
I booked a shareholders' meeting
next week.
Get the legal team
and the shareholders ready.
Don't worry, I got it.
And Mr. Lim, once everything
is sorted out,
will you hand Donghan Food over to me
as we promised?
Is this really the right time for that?
I'm just giving you a reminder.
Get going now.
[ Untitled ]
[ I need to talk to you about real Bella. ]
[ Just the two of us. ]
I'm sorry for making you come out
when you must be so busy.
I thought you made no mistakes.
I thought so.
This was my very first mistake.
But life is full of surprises.
Had it not been for my mistake,
I wouldn't have gotten to meet with you.
Think about it.
Why did Bella not contact Sun-young
when she was alive all along?
That's what made me so curious.
It turns out, her memory is gone.
- What?
- Which is why
we have another chance.
If you give me the chance
to make up for my mistake,
I'll get everything done and be gone.
Everything?
After all, you're the one
who will be in trouble
if Sun-young finds out about Bella.
I think she's leaving for Paris tonight,
but I think it'd be best
if we just take care of everything
before she leaves.
[ Yes, sir. ]
I think it's time to end things
with Jin Tae-soo.
[ - Sorry? ]
- I told you
that the more you know,
the more at risk you become.
Excuse me,
didn't I see you in Australia?
You're from the pop-up restaurant.
Yes, I was the manager there.
What a surprise.
Bye now.
The lady who came with you
to the restaurant,
why
is she there?
What did you just say?
I saw her recently.
What? When?
Where?
Well,
there's an old house in Nonyang.
Did you just say an old house in Nonyang?
Yes.
Please excuse me.
But...
- Hello?
- Hello, Chef Moon.
What's the name of the lady
who lives at your house?
We saw her back in Australia.
- Byeol-na?
- Yes, Byeol-na.
After you rushed back to Korea,
[ a woman came to the restaurant
with Byeol-na ]
and she has white hair.
I ran into her just now,
and as soon as she heard about her,
she left for Nonyang.
Thank you. Okay.
It's unfortunate that Madam Jang won't be
working with me anymore,
but I believe that I can't go forward
if I don't step out of my comfort zone.
The same goes
for Donghan's conservative style,
which you have mentioned earlier.
I want to change that.
No,
I want to be the one to change that.
I've always sought after something new
and that's what gives me energy.
But there's one thing that doesn't change.
The country where you were born.
How does it feel to be
back in your home country?
Cut on Camera Two. Get Camera Three ready.
[ I think that explains it all. ]
[ Let's talk about something else. ]
- Let me know when it's all done.
- Okay.
[ How does it feel to be
back in your home country? ]
Goodness!
You scared me!
What are you watching?
You should be cleaning.
Let me be.
My role model Bella is on TV right now.
Bella? You mean me?
Not funny at all.
I'm exhausted.
So, who is this Bella?
Why do you respect her so much?
You want to watch it with me?
This was your first fashion show in Korea.
It was broadcasted live as well.
How was that?
I'd like to hear about your future plans
as well.
I've always missed Korea
during my time in France.
That's why I've always wanted to come back
and do a show here.
I'm so happy that I got to do
exactly that.
I'm opening Bella Boutique
in Cheongdam-dong
to communicate more with my fans.
I'd like to communicate with more people.
You're making an exclusive announcement
[ on our show
about Bella Boutique's opening. ]
Yes, I'll invite you for the opening.
Thank you.
And there was an even more famous part
to the show that became a huge issue.
Let's watch it again.
[ Belle Ombre ]
[ - Bella!
- Bella! ]
[ Mysterious Designer Bella Y ]
[ Belle Ombre ]
[ - Donghan...
- Bella. ]
[ Stop the car! ]
Byeol-na! Are you okay?
Byeol-na!
Are you okay?
[ - That caught everyone by surprise. ]
- Byeol-na.
[ What made you choose
to reveal your face? ]
[ Because I'm Bella. ]
[ Why should there be a reason
when Bella wants to show who she is? ]
Are you okay?
- Byeol-na, are you all right?
- Byeol-na.
- What's wrong?
Are you okay?
What's happening?
[ Why do you do this before every show? ]
Bella! The finale dress! Hurry.
Good job.
[ Designer brands are rushing ]
[ - to sign with Bella...
- The new landlord is ]
[ moving your mother's grave... ]
Something urgent came up in Korea.
[ Managing Director Lim Chul-yong ]
[ of Donghan International
purchased the land. ]
[ Sign with Donghan. ]
[ Why should I? ]
[ After all, I know all
of Bella's secrets. ]
Bella,
I'm Lim Hyun-a, Lim Chul-yong's daughter.
[ Was that you who stole the dress? ]
Are you insane? Stop the car!
Byeol-na!
Are you okay?
[ Madam Jang ]
[ Pungcheonok ]
Bella?
Yu-jin!
[ Yoo Yu-jin! ]
Madam Jang.
Yes.
That's me.
Yu-jin!
What happened to you?
Do you know how worried I was?
What do we do? Sun-young is here.
[ Just run them over! ]
[ Eccentric! Chef Moon ]
Why are they trying to kill Yu-jin?
Lim Chul-yong.
[ He has announced that all wealth
and authority will be ]
[ handed over to Mr. Lim. ]
[ Chef Moon, ]
[ we'll meet again
after time passes, right? ]
Tell them to get ready.
[ I'm going to go meet them one by one. ]
You've looked so hard for me,
but you don't seem too happy to see me.
Smile.
You look like you've just seen
a dead person come back alive.