(Episode 15)
Man, Jeong Hoon.
I thought you
already left by yourself.
You'll probably figure it out soon,
so I'll spill the truth first.
What is it?
I installed...
a location tracking app
on your phone.
It was just in case
anything happens to you.
Thankfully, the passcode
for your phone was the same.
I'll delete it now.
But please don't disappear
all of a sudden.
Are you
still that concerned about me?
Once I die, you'll only have...
memories of how you were
worried and concerned about me.
Did you just figure that out?
I guess your conscience says
that you're actually sorry for me.
Ever since Seo Yeon passed away,
I only had this thought on my mind.
"I will never make
another painful memory..."
"with another person."
That was the only goal I had.
Don't I sound like a fool?
Why didn't I want to make
more good memories?
My mother lived her life...
trying to give me
only good memories.
I don't want to live my life
making everyone worried like a kid.
I never thought of it
as you making me worried.
Don't say that.
Then will you just sit around
if I break down like you did?
That's what friends do.
Exactly.
I take back asking you
to fix my disease.
You can just be a friend
from now on.
You don't have to be
my doctor or guardian.
Goodness, what is this?
Ha Jin, Ha Kyung.
Girls!
Hey, are you two okay?
Was everything all right?
What about Ha Jin? Where is she?
What's wrong? Is something going on?
Someone spray-painted
the security cameras black.
Are you sure everything is okay?
Why is the door locked?
Ha Jin! Ha Jin!
Ha Jin!
Open the door!
Are you in there?
Ha Jin! Answer me!
- Ha Jin!
- Are you in there?
- Answer us!
- Ha Jin!
- Darn it, why won't this open?
- Are you in there?
- Ha Jin! Are you there?
- Ha Jin!
- My gosh.
- Why are they making a fuss?
- Ha Jin!
Ha Jin! Ha Jin!
Ha Jin!
Ha Jin, open the door!
Ha Jin! Ha Jin!
Ha Jin!
Open the door!
Are you in there? Ha Jin!
(Ha Jin, you're mine.)
What is all this?
Ha Jin, open up!
- You're in there, right?
- Darn it!
Break it open!
Ha Jin, are you okay?
My goodness, what is that?
Darn it.
It's not just tough for you.
It's tough for everyone.
Everyone gets sad
when they lose someone they love...
because of their memories...
Not you.
You forgot everything.
You forgot everything, and you live
as if nothing had happened.
So stop talking
as if you know everything.
(Director Choi)
(This is your last chance. Call me
as soon as you see this message.)
Hello, ma'am.
What's wrong with you?
What were you thinking?
I'm sorry for not calling.
Are you okay?
You seem better.
Sit down.
You know your leave
is until tomorrow, right?
Will you be able to work
starting in two days?
I want...
to work again.
But I can't promise you
that I'm fully recovered.
Come back to work.
The news is all that you have.
What else can you do?
Remember how I said...
I can't gamble with this?
But I realized that I already was.
Appointing you as the anchor
of "Lee Jeong Hoon's News Live"...
was a gamble for me.
The others said no, but I insisted.
So if I were to let you go
in order to save face,
what would that make me?
Let me be cool for once.
You can do it.
So come back.
The envelope and the photos?
Yes, I want to check
everything that was sent.
I believe Jeong Hoon has it.
I'll look for it.
But why all of a sudden?
Is something wrong?
Yes, something's wrong.
What? Jeong Hoon!
What's your deal?
You're alive and well,
yet you refused to pick up my calls
or text back.
Are you that upset
that I'm doing fine?
You know that's not what I meant.
I was worried sick.
Have you been well?
Of course.
By the way, did you hear
about Ha Jin?
Hear what?
(I'm always watching you.)
Hello, Anchor Lee.
Where are you? Are you home?
Yes, I am.
Where are you?
I'm on my way to your house.
I'll be there soon.
You're coming here?
Hey.
Are you okay?
Yes.
I'm sorry
for leaving first yesterday.
I know I promised to stay with you.
Don't be sorry.
You should be worried
about yourself instead.
(Don't get the wrong idea.
Ha Jin loves me.)
(Get ready. We'll meet soon.)
Did you report to the police?
No, not yet.
We don't want the media
to be talking about this right now.
Ms. Park is speaking with a lawyer.
May I look around your room?
The stalker could've installed
cameras or listening devices.
Sure. It's upstairs.
I didn't know it was this serious.
Why would someone do this?
Don't worry too much.
You'll be fine.
I'll make sure of that.
Okay. Thanks.
(Medication)
I don't see anything in particular.
But I think it's best
to hire someone to take a look.
Okay.
By the way, are you sick?
I saw your medication.
I had come down with a flu.
I'm all better now.
I'm sorry...
about that day
and yesterday as well.
Please don't take to heart
what I said to you at my house.
I just vented my anger on you.
I didn't mean any of it.
Okay. I'll just think that
you were drunk and rambling.
If you're truly sorry,
don't ever drink again.
You have a terrible drinking habit.
Let's go. Where's Ha Jin?
She's upstairs. Anchor Lee is here.
He is?
Oh, my. Hello, sir.
- Hello.
Ha Jin, have you packed everything?
I'm still packing.
Just pack the things you need.
- Okay.
- Are you going somewhere?
We're going to a hotel.
We don't want to stay here anymore.
Don't you think it'd be dangerous
since there are many strangers?
Is there anywhere else you could go?
My parents live too far away,
and I don't want to worry them.
We're looking for a place
she can move into right away.
I won't be staying there for long,
so you don't have to worry.
I'll look into it.
Give me some time.
Where?
Father, I got this herbal tea
as a gift recently.
Try it. It's really fragrant.
Okay.
So what brings you here?
I don't think you're here to see me.
How's Jeong Hoon?
Good. He's hanging in there.
Professor Kim called me.
I heard Jeong Hoon
received therapy recently.
What? Oh, about that...
What in the world is going on?
I heard
you asked Prof. Kim yourself.
Did you volunteer
to be his doctor...
so that you can keep everything
from me?
Is this your way of telling me
to back off?
It's not like that.
Then why didn't you tell me
about this?
After that incident,
Jeong Hoon has not once gone there.
If he went,
he must have had a reason for it.
You don't need to worry about that.
Does this...
have to do with that woman,
Yeo Ha Jin?
Is their relationship serious?
Is it truly possible for him
to love another woman...
with all the memories
he has about Seo Yeon?
Why aren't you answering me?
You must know.
I don't know
about his feelings that deeply.
Yeo Ha Jin.
Her name sounded familiar,
so I tried to remember
where I heard her name from.
She was your patient in the past.
The one who caused a problem because
you overprescribed sleeping pills.
Isn't she the patient?
If you can't find out
through Jeong Hoon,
try to keep an eye on him
through her.
You still have a good relationship
with her, right?
From what I know, she still came
for therapy after that incident.
Dad,
you're not interested
in my feelings...
or my emotions, right?
What on earth are you talking about?
You're well aware how hard
that incident had been on me.
How could you bring that up
so casually as if it's nothing?
Until when will you whine
like a baby?
This is why I don't acknowledge you
as a fellow doctor.
Instead of overcoming
such incidents, you keep whining.
You can't even control
your feelings. You're not a doctor.
Which unit are you going to?
We're going to Unit 701.
I was informed you were coming.
- This way, please.
- Okay.
Getting access to this budding
as visitors is difficult.
So you don't have to worry
while you stay here.
My gosh, this place looks great.
Are you sure we can stay here?
What about the person living here?
This place has been vacant
because of work.
This was supposed to be vacant
for some time anyway.
Feel free to stay here.
By the way,
how do you know the person?
Well...
We are close like family.
Thank you for going out
of your way to help.
You should go back in.
Call me if there's a problem.
Okay.
Then, you won't suddenly disappear
into thin air again, right?
You can go anywhere
or someplace far.
But if you are going anywhere,
just tell me.
Then, I'll know where you are
and wait for you.
I can't go even if I want to now.
Why not?
Because of me?
I have to be back
on the news program.
Are you going back?
When are you starting?
In two days.
My leave of absence ends tomorrow.
That's great!
I wanted to see you lead the news.
I'll call you once I get home.
Get home safe.
Go back in.
Ha Jin.
I'm certain that the owner
of this place is a man.
There's a razor in the bathroom.
Really?
The place is really clean.
And the interior design is chic.
I wonder who owns this house.
Is it Anchor Lee?
Does he have two houses?
Come on. No way.
Then, how could he get a house
like this on such short notice?
Ha Jin.
It's about Anchor Lee.
I think he has feelings for you.
Do you think so?
He was worried about you, so he got
a house like this right away.
To call it a fake relationship,
he's way too affectionate, isn't he?
You think so too, right?
Goodness. Look at you smiling.
Should we continue this romantic
feeling with some music?
I saw some records earlier.
Okay. Put on a good one.
Okay. I'll put on something great.
Ha Jin. I found
the photo of the owner!
Who?
Who is it? Who's the owner?
I guess this was when he was young.
That can't be Anchor Lee, right?
Seeing how he has such a common
face, I don't think it's him.
He looks familiar. Who is this?
Who am I to you?
I'm your only junior reporter,
Jo Il Kwon.
Of course, I ought to help you out.
I'm the best, right?
Yes. Thank you.
You don't look grateful at all.
Thank you so much.
Happy?
Can you feel my gratitude now?
If you're really grateful,
write me some coupons.
What coupons?
10 coupons to get a pass?
Okay. I'll give you 20 coupons.
Really? Then, I get 20 free passes
when you want to scold me.
You can't say anything later.
Okay, I got it.
And as for the house,
I said it was a close...
I just said it was a friend
of mine's house. Just so you know.
Okay. After hearing
what happened, I was worried.
I'm glad.
Then, I'm going to get some sleep.
Where's my room?
Why would you sleep here?
Then, where do I sleep?
There are a lot of places.
So many rooms are available
at nearby hotels.
I thought I was staying
with you for the time being.
With me?
Why?
Just stay at a comfortable place.
I'm sure staying with me
must be uncomfortable for you.
Here.
Well, you didn't have to.
You can't scold me
for how much I spend...
on the hotels. Okay?
Okay. Fine.
Go and get some rest.
Okay. All right. Good night.
My goodness. Hold on.
Where did I put my glasses?
Hold on. Where are they?
Did I put them here?
What's this?
(Dad)
Hey, where are you now?
I'm in the office.
Hey, you're here.
My gosh. I thought you...
What? Are you already regretting it?
No, I'm not. I was just checking
if you came to work.
How are you feeling?
Fine. I'm okay.
I'm glad to hear that.
My gosh. I can feel your affection
toward him in your voice.
Are you that happy
to see him at work?
Why do you keep talking nonsense?
What's up with your outfit?
What? What's wrong with my outfit?
Clothes are good
as long as they are clean.
Forget it.
Just focus on preparing the news.
It's been a while
since you worked together.
Stay focused to the end.
Okay?
- Do a good job.
- Okay.
People might think he was gone
for a year or something.
Why is she making a fuss?
You're feeling okay, right?
My gosh. Yes. I'm perfectly fine.
I'm okay.
Okay. You look fine.
Well,
what do you think about my voice?
Why are you asking me that
all of a sudden?
You know,
I do the countdown for you.
I thought if it was distracting.
That never crossed my mind.
Really?
Okay.
You should have just called him.
Did you have to come
all the way here?
I wanted to give him moral support
for coming back to work.
Since I'm here, I can research
about live news. It's great.
Research, my foot.
I can see right through you.
You're worried about him.
Should I get him some coffee?
No. It's better to visit him
as if it's any other day, right?
- What is it?
- I don't think...
you should be worried
about other people now.
Despite what happened,
you're still worried about him,
so I guess you like him a lot.
You know,
I just thought he needs me now.
I'll call you after I'm done.
Okay.
Wait, my phone. I must have left it.
Is this really you, my sister?
Can you go up alone?
Of course. Hurry up and go.
I'm going up.
- I'll call you.
- Okay.
Which floor was it?
- The fourth floor!
- The fourth floor.
The doors are closing.
("To You, Whom I Remember")
Where is he?
Is he already at the studio?
Hello.
By any chance,
do you know where Anchor Lee is?
Well, he was there just now.
I'll call him. Thank you.
He even left his phone here.
Where did he go?
My son, congratulations
on becoming a reporter.
This is your most treasured pen.
You're right. Very much.
When I hold this in my hand,
I get a lot of great ideas.
I hope you write a lot
of great articles with this pen.
Ta-da.
Congratulations on your return.
Please make great news
that refreshes our hearts.
What brings you here at this hour?
What's with that face?
You seem like you're happy
to see me, but you kind of don't.
Thank you for the water.
Anyway, are you here alone?
Where's Ha Kyung?
We came together,
but she left her phone at home.
I see.
Right, how are you doing?
Are you doing okay?
I'm doing fine thanks to you.
I'm glad.
If it's okay with you,
will you wait until I'm done?
I'll take you home.
Okay. Sounds great.
Jeong Hoon,
why do you look so serious?
Are you nervous
because it has been too long?
Me? No way.
I think you're the one
who's nervous.
If you can throw jokes,
I shouldn't have to worry.
We have a lot of stories,
so keep up the pace.
Okay, 10 seconds
to the opening jingle.
("Lee Jeong Hoon's News Live")
That's all for tonight.
Have a great night.
(Episode 16)
- Great work.
("Lee Jeong Hoon's News Live")
Great job.
You look the coolest
when you read the news.
Thank you.
I'll get changed quickly.
Okay.
Goodness,
it's so nice to see you, Ha Jin.
- Hello.
- Gosh.
You two always look great together.
Right, this is great. Jeong Hoon and
I are going out to eat something.
You should come with us.
We're going out to eat something?
- Why?
- What do you mean, "Why?"
We're celebrating your return.
It's my treat.
Okay, let's go!
- Ha Jin, let's go.
- Okay.
Let's go.
There it is.
Ha Jin, I found my phone.
Call me when you're done.
Okay. But I'm at a wine bar
with Anchor Lee.
A wine bar?
Okay. I'll wait nearby.
You jerk!
It's me! Jo Il Kwon! Jo Il Kwon!
It's me, Report Jo!
Reporter Jo?
Has it been you all along?
No, it's not like that.
This is my house!
My house! This is my house.
This is my house.
This is your house?
Yes. Jeong Hoon asked me to use it.
That's why I was away.
Can you put that down?
Were you the one
who sent those photos?
What photos?
I'm sorry I hit you.
I thought you were the stalker.
What were you doing?
I had to organize some stuff
in a hurry.
What did you have to organize
so suddenly?
Stuff related to my girlfriend.
She was cheating on me.
"Cheating"?
She's a wench!
Don't you love the vibe here?
Yes, it's nice.
Since you can't drink alcohol,
just sip on your water.
Ha Jin, can you drink
another glass of wine?
I'd love to.
You said you were going to treat me
to something delicious.
Were you talking
about this wine bar?
Their cheese is delicious. Try it.
Or do you want me to treat you
to something tastier?
Is something wrong?
No. Why?
You're not acting
like your usual self.
Let's just say...
I've finally become grateful
for the things around me.
You'll know once you become my age.
Excuse me.
Hello?
Let's get up.
- What?
- Hurry.
What? Are you going to the toilet?
It's over there.
No, I'm not.
Now that I'm back, cheers!
Cheers.
What a ridiculous woman.
And she slapped you?
I knew she was an odd one
ever since you said...
she couldn't finish
a single sushi set.
Calm down and drink that.
So what will you do?
Did you take your revenge?
No, I couldn't do anything.
She chose him over me.
I was speechless.
She wants a man
whom she can count on.
Gosh, and what?
She can count on that guy?
He's an MMA fighter.
I see.
Ha Kyung.
Do I not look dependable?
Do I look weak?
Yes.
I see.
So what? Are you going
to sit there and do nothing?
Then should I take my revenge?
Of course.
Strong men seem to be
her ideal type.
Fighting isn't about strength.
It's about skills.
What do you say?
Do you want my help?
Your help?
Do you not trust me?
No, it's not like that.
Sure, you can help me.
You're so trustworthy. You sure are.
Skills like this one?
This is amazing.
You twisted my arm earlier as well.
Come on, wait a minute.
This was the arm you twisted.
Wait. It hurts.
We'll begin starting next week.
What?
I don't care.
You keep saying okay
and wanting to hang up.
But what are you okay about?
I just miss you...
so terribly.
So hurry up and come here.
He's very cute toward his wife.
I don't know.
If you don't come here,
I won't go home tonight.
Jeong Hoon, call her over.
She'll probably listen to you.
You guys are always so close.
Am I an outcast or what?
It's me.
Oh, you're almost here?
Please hurry.
Are you close with his wife?
You know her as well.
I do?
Is she a celebrity?
- Director Choi.
- Hello.
What kind of humiliation is this?
Please wake up, Team Manager Kim!
It's my beautiful wife!
"Wife"?
I'm truly sorry about this.
Let me apologize on his behalf.
That's fine.
Get up.
Get up right now.
Why would you volunteer
as a third wheel...
and cause a scene?
- I was...
- Gosh.
just welcoming him back.
Goodness.
And I just missed you terribly.
That's enough.
Get in the taxi. Go.
I'm truly sorry.
Hurry!
Get in. Gosh.
Ha Jin, I'm so sorry. Bye.
- Wait...
- Get in there.
- Goodbye.
Please forget about tonight.
See you tomorrow.
Go home safely.
So the young man...
she met at a church was him.
Yes.
What didn't you tell me
that they were a couple?
It wasn't intentional.
I didn't have the chance to...
My car is parked
at the broadcasting station.
It'd be better for you
to take a cab, right?
It's okay. It's not that far.
Let's take a walk.
I've never been here before.
It's a totally different scenery.
It's empty and quiet.
When is the read-through?
I'm not sure, but I'm guessing
around the end of this month.
But I'm worried...
because my news tutor seems
to have forgotten about me.
I think I'll become a laughingstock.
When are you free?
I'll help you.
Really? I'm free starting today...
Be careful.
I completely forgot...
that I should always be on alert
when I'm around you.
You're making me nervous again.
Why?
I'm worried you'll say goodbye again
like last time.
That time, you were nice to me
at first and then said...
you didn't want to see me again.
But I'm not going
to listen to you anymore.
You see, I want you to be happy.
That's why I'm not going
to say goodbye.
All right.
(Director Ji Hyun Geun)
Hello, sir. It's Ha Kyung.
Why are you picking up her phone?
She's filming at the moment.
Okay. I'll call back later.
Wait.
The filming just started,
so it'll take some time.
Can you tell me what this is about?
I'm in front of your house
because I have a gift for her.
You're in front of our house?
Tell me when she'll be done,
and I'll stop by then.
I'm sorry, but she'll be filming
all night today.
If you don't want to leave it there,
you can drop it off at the office.
There's no need for that.
Just tell her to call me
once she's done.
It's okay if she's late.
I'll be waiting.
All right.
Don't hold your breath, you scumbag.
What's his deal?
Why is he in front of the house?
How dare she tell me what to do?
Did I get a call?
You were talking to someone.
Yes, Director Ji called.
Why did he call?
It's nothing.
I told him that you were
busy filming, so don't worry.
Okay.
Let's spam his number.
He'll call my number if it's urgent.
It could've been him.
He could've sneaked in and left
those photos and the letter.
I'm bound to run
into both him and Chul again.
I don't know how I can face them.
You don't have to face them. Don't.
Don't even answer their calls
for the time being.
I blocked his number.
Yes, Ms. Park.
How's the place you're staying at?
How about the security?
We can trust it, right?
Yes. I'm so relieved to hear that.
Yes. Okay.
Okay.
Ms. Park.
Hey, Chul.
I checked the schedule.
I'm with Se Min next month too.
Does it mean I can't work
with Ha Jin anymore?
My gosh, it's not that.
It's just for the time being.
Did I do something wrong?
It's not like I was bad at my job
or did anything wrong.
Why am I getting kicked out?
My gosh,
you're not getting kicked out.
Chul, don't get so worked up.
Ha Kyung told you
to kick me out, right?
Are you suspecting me?
That I'm Ha Jin's stalker?
- You...
- How could you?
It's not me. Okay?
It's not me!
Darn it.
Darn it!
Park Soo Chang?
Get out.
You sent Soo Chang's memory card
to get it fixed. Is it done yet?
Not yet. After deleting the photos,
he saved other files
in the same memory card.
I was told it would take some time.
Let me check on that now.
Okay. I'm on my way to work.
How much of it did they recover?
I brought everything
they recovered so far.
They recovered about 80 percent.
What?
These are all photos of Ha Jin.
My gosh, he took
her photos like a stalker.
Call the newspaper agency
he works in.
Ask them if he's in the office
and call me.
Okay, I will.
(Information:
10th floor, Censorship Board)
Why are you attacking me
out of nowhere?
You know what? I've treated you
with respect since you're my senior.
Do you think I'm a joke?
Is tailing me your way
of showing your respect?
What are you talking about?
You're the one
who's attacking me at my work.
Check that first.
What is it?
You secretly tailed her,
broke into her house,
and sent me a threatening letter.
That was you, wasn't it?
My gosh. What are you talking about?
I just took them,
so I can publish articles.
You know
I'm in the entertainment section.
I'm not here to listen
to your excuses.
I came here to warn you.
Starting now, I'll do everything
I can to stop you.
I can put you in jail
or bury you in our society.
But before that,
I'll do what's easiest.
I'm going to get you fired.
My gosh, what on earth
is he saying? Jeong Hoon.
It's not me. I didn't stalk Ha Jin.
Besides...
You know what?
I'm really sorry I tailed you.
Let's be honest here.
You don't have to get
so worked up over this.
Some people say that
you two aren't really dating.
You call yourself a reporter,
but you can't tell it's a rumor?
That's why I don't want you
to do anything.
Burying an incompetent reporter
like you is nothing to me.
Jeong Hoon. Hold on.
My gosh. This is driving me crazy.
Okay, Jeong Hoon.
I just got money from that stalker.
And I took Ha Jin's photos
and sold them to him for money.
I'm telling the truth.
What are you talking about?
I just did whatever
that jerk asked me to do.
Right, this. I...
These are the messages
from that jerk.
(Black Sugar)
(Returned home at 5 p.m.
after a movie schedule.)
Well,
this is an encrypted messenger
that can't be traced.
And I got paid
with virtual currency too.
You can't track him with this.
Do you expect me to believe this?
I'm telling the truth.
This is the truth, Jeong Hoon.
Okay. I've never met
the guy in person.
But one time, I observed him
from afar. I didn't see his face.
He messaged me
and told me to pull out.
But I didn't leave.
I stayed there and kept watch.
He was on a motorcycle.
It was a black motorcycle.
He must've wanted to hide something
because he covered his plate number.
What a surprise.
Why do you want to go out?
We've been cooped up inside.
We ought to get
some sunlight and all.
You're right.
I looked it up online.
There's an amazing cake shop
around the corner.
It's really good.
Don't make me run after the cake.
Well, you get a pass today.
We're outside now. Put on your mask.
Can I have two pieces of cake?
I get 2 pieces, and you get 1.
I knew it.
Here's our coffee.
That's so pretty!
I have to take photos.
Don't upload them
on your social media.
Of course, I won't.
Look. What do you think?
So beautiful. Can I eat now?
- Attack!
My gosh, this is great.
It's been so long since
we had time to enjoy ourselves.
Look what we have to put up with
because of that crazy stalker.
Right.
We can't stay at that place forever.
I'm worried.
Ms. Park is looking for a house
with airtight security.
- Hang in there a bit longer.
- Okay.
Oh, right. I found out who owns
the place we're staying at.
In 1, 2...
Whose house is it?
You know him too.
Hey, isn't that Yeo Ha Jin?
- What?
- Yeo Ha Jin.
She's so pretty in person!
Should I pretend to take your photo
and take her photo instead?
One...
In 1, 2.
- Let me see.
- Hey.
- It's her.
- I'll upload it on my social media.
- Hey, what should I say?
- Awesome.
Who said fans could never see
their stars in person?
I crushed that myth today!
My star, Ha Jin, is so beautiful!
Hashtag, Yeo Ha Jin in person,
Hashtag, the best cafe,
Hashtag, Cafe Baba,
Hashtag, Yeo Ha Jin.
Ha Jin, where are you now?
He was on a motorcycle.
It was a black motorcycle.
He must've wanted
to hide something...
because he covered his plate number.
I'm hungry.
Anchor Lee!
Ha Jin!
Yeong!
Ha Jin.
Stay with me. Are you okay?
Ha Kyung, are you okay?
I'm fine.
Oh no.
We better get her to the hospital.
Wait here. I'll get the car.
Oh no.
- Does it hurt a lot?
- Yes.
I didn't have to get hospitalized.
I just hurt my shoulder a little,
that's all.
The doctor said we should see
how you're doing in a day.
It won't be too late to go home
after he says you're totally fine.
Are you all right?
You must've been surprised.
Don't worry about me.
You need to get well soon.
We received a report.
Are you Ms. Yeo Ha Kyung?
Yes.
Let me ask you a few questions.
We'll get the security footage of
the scene and start investigating.
Yes, please look into it.
Yes. And by any chance,
is there anyone
who could have done this?
No, I'm not sure.
Okay. I'll give you a call.
Yes.
Are you cold? Do you want water?
Are you hungry?
Do you want me to
order some tteokbokki?
Just go.
Anchor Lee is here. You need to go.
I'm not leaving.
No, I'm telling you to go.
You can't sleep here,
and I can't go to sleep
if I have you here.
Should I go home with you?
Anchor Lee,
may I ask you for a favor?
I don't feel comfortable
leaving her alone in that house.
Could you stay with her?
Sure, I will.
Are you sure
you'll be okay by yourself?
Of course.
I'll call you
when my test results are in.
You can come then.
Let's do that. Okay?
Go now so that I can rest.
Come on, I'm going to rest. Go.
I'm okay now. You should go.
I promised I'll be with you.
And you don't look okay right now.
You're right.
I'm not all right.
That motorcycle driver is
my stalker, isn't he?
You knew, didn't you?
That's why you ran over.
I really don't know
what will happen now.
If you're troubled, just say so.
Don't be troubled all alone.
I'm here to help.
Ha Jin.
Ha Jin, is something wrong?
I'll come in for a moment.
Ha Jin.
Wake up, Ha Jin. Are you okay?
Anchor Lee.
What's wrong?
Did you have a nightmare?
The dream was really familiar.
It felt really odd
as if I had experienced it.
Wait here.
I'll bring something warm.
Don't go.
I'm not going anywhere.
It'll take only a minute.
Is that okay?
Hello?
It's me.
You know me, don't you?
How did you find...
Are you with her right now?
Yeo Ha Jin.
What?
Make sure you protect her...
if you don't want to lose her.
(Find Me in Your Memory)
Who is he?
He already knew where we'll be?
If I mention your stalker
on the news,
it'll provoke him even more.
How's Moon Seong Ho?
Well, it's kind of weird.
You don't have to know
every single thing...
that happens to Jeong Hoon.
Is it because of Yeo Ha Jin?
Really? You really like
that woman, Yeo Ha Jin?
Are you leaving?
I told you that I'm not leaving.
It's great to see you smile.
Don't you feel bad for Seo Yeon?
Are you with Ha Jin?
Anchor Lee, Ha Jin is...