- Anchor Lee!
- Tell us something!
- Say something!
- Anchor Lee!
Hey, Lee Jeong Hoon!
I picked up a huge scoop.
Don't you want to know what it is?
Man, he really gets on my nerves.
Let's see how long you can
keep your head up high.
What's the big scoop?
- Tell us.
- What's the huge scoop?
- May we talk for a moment?
- Tell us.
Wait!
Jeong Hoon, we need to talk.
Come here.
Did you know about this book too?
No, not at all.
I haven't seen it until now.
I knew it. You wouldn't give consent
to publish something like this.
The author is
apparently your doctor.
How can he write this book
without saying a word to you?
Is this Yoo Sung Hyuk
really your doctor?
Yes, he is.
This is too awful.
Mr. Kim came in with this,
so I gave it a read.
All he did was
replace your name with an initial.
But the person's age, occupation,
and the current situation...
all point to you.
Did you see everyone
who swarmed in at the lobby?
- Yes.
- They're already publishing...
millions of articles
speculating you as this man.
This book is liable
if you didn't know about this.
You need to meet your doctor...
and check on the situation.
- Okay.
- Right.
How's your stab? Is it all right?
Yes, I'm fine.
I forgot to ask
in the midst of this chaos.
What?
Hey, can you tell me?
I'm sure you know
since you're close to him.
- Is it really him?
- What's with you?
Does he suffer from hyperthymesia?
What's with you? I don't know.
You really don't?
Yes, I don't. I really don't.
Man, in that case,
I'll ask him when he gets here.
Why? There's no need to ask him.
Just because. I'm curious.
Why are you getting angry?
Don't ask him anything.
Hey, listen to this kid.
He just got out of the hospital
after an operation.
Don't ask him such a question.
Hey, you're still doing that.
- Jeong Hoon.
- Hey.
Hello.
Hey, you're here.
Hey, you know...
How are you feeling?
Oh, yes. I'm fine.
Okay. I'm glad.
Are you sure you're okay?
I saw Park Soo Chang in the lobby.
- When did he get out?
- It has been a few days.
He must have hired a good lawyer.
He got out on probation.
What has he been up to?
Have you heard anything?
I haven't really heard anything.
But he can't work
in this field anyway.
No one will hire him.
His days as a reporter is over,
so I'm sure he'll do something else.
All right.
Let me know if you hear anything.
Okay, I will.
- Ha Kyung.
- Yes?
Do we have any food ingredients?
You know, like ham and eggs.
- To do what?
- To make a lunch box...
for me and Anchor Lee.
Why do you want your perfectly
good relationship to fall in peril?
Hey, we won't fall in peril
for making a lunch box.
Back then,
it was my first time trying.
Don't you think he'll be touched
when I make a lunch box for him?
Yes, I think he'll show
a big reaction in another way.
Gosh, what if he gets
too touched and cries?
I don't have enough time
to make that again.
Okay, try your best.
It's not for me anyway.
Even if I don't try hard,
it should be pretty delicious.
Wait, why are there
so many articles on Anchor Lee?
About what?
("Is Anchor Lee Suffering
From Hyperthymesia?")
Apparently, there's a book
about him.
A book?
It's called
"The Man Who Cannot Forget".
Excuse me.
How may I help you?
I've disclosed information
about my patient...
whom I had been treating
for a long time.
I've violated the medical law.
So you're a doctor,
and you're turning yourself in...
for disclosing
your patient's personal information?
That's correct.
I met his new lover...
and told her about his illness.
He will always have her
in his heart.
Will you be okay with that?
Will their love endure...
this complicated
and frightening illness?
Will he truly be able
to break free...
from his past and love someone else?
Although I'm skeptical,
I do wish them the best...
and close this book.
Do you have time?
How are you feeling?
Shouldn't you still be resting?
If you were that worried,
you should've visited me
at the hospital.
You must've been in a rush,
seeing how
you just left the fruit basket.
I saw Ha Jin there, so I didn't want
to ruin it for you guys.
Did you guys talk it out?
Yes. I think so.
I'm glad.
You should be happy
that everything has worked out.
I'm sorry.
I'm talking about my father's book.
I tried to dissuade him
and even threatened him.
I tried my best.
You knew?
I should've told you in advance...
and thought of a solution together.
I'm sorry.
To be honest, I'm quite flustered...
and upset as well.
But you shouldn't be sorry
about this.
It's just an illness I have.
I was never planning
to keep it a secret forever.
But now that everyone
has found out, I'm a bit scared...
about how they'll react.
That's why we should
take care of this.
Don't hold yourself back for us.
What do you mean?
I went to the police station.
I turned myself in and told them...
that I had disclosed
your information.
Why would you do that?
My father wanted to see
how you were doing...
and asked me to send your results
every time you had your checkup.
I had no idea he was planning this.
Disclosing a patient's information
is a violation.
We'll be penalized.
And that book won't get sold.
You want me to sue you?
If you don't, I'll charge my father.
Tae Eun.
I'm sure he knew
you'd be soft like this.
That's why he did the unthinkable.
And that's why I want
to fix this even more.
If something happens to you
because of this,
I won't be able to stand it.
So please do that.
I'll be going now.
Do you want some coffee?
Okay.
What they said about Anchor Lee
is true, right?
Did you already know
about his illness?
Ha Kyung.
How could a doctor disclose
his patient's information?
It's about Anchor Lee.
He had no right to do that.
I hope people won't think badly
about him.
I'm worried...
they'll be judgmental
when they know nothing about him.
He did nothing wrong.
Don't worry too much.
You know how people forget easily.
They'll lose interest soon.
I really hope so.
I don't want him to hurt anymore.
Guess where I am.
Did you wait for a long time?
No. You did well today.
Did you miss me?
Of course. I missed you so much.
How about you?
Me too. That's why I hurried over.
How do you feel?
Does the wound hurt?
Do you have a fever?
I'm doing fine, and it doesn't hurt.
You don't seem to be having a fever.
Are you sure you're okay?
I'm positive.
Okay. You've passed.
We can go on a picnic.
A picnic?
Going on a picnic is the best way
to get some fresh air.
We just need to walk a bit more.
We're almost there.
I've never gone on a picnic
at this hour before.
The time doesn't matter.
What matters
is whom you're going with.
I packed a lunchbox and a mat.
Don't tell me you made that.
Of course, I did.
Why? Are you afraid
you'd feel extremely touched?
I'm touched and scared.
It's going to be delicious.
You're doing it again.
It's dangerous.
Walk properly.
It's not dangerous
if you're holding onto me.
I know you'll be holding onto me
in the future as well.
There. Sit down.
Can I finally see what you've made?
Oh, right. I almost forgot.
Since it's late,
I just made some simple stuff.
I gave it my all,
so you better finish it.
Ta-da.
I see.
That's it?
It looks nice.
There are various shapes,
and they look unique.
Is this a dolphin?
Bingo.
This must be your feelings
toward me.
You're right. It's a heart.
A heart. And...
Is this a rabbit?
Isn't it obvious?
You're right.
I was really passionate
about making the rabbits.
You may have been too passionate
and cut off an ear.
You're right.
Isn't it good?
It is.
Did you read the book?
Did you plan all of this
to cheer me up?
Yes.
Why didn't you tell me
that you met with Professor Yoo?
You must've been very surprised.
The things he said
didn't matter one bit to me.
You said you were happy.
That's good enough for me.
What about now?
Are you still happy?
Yes, I am.
That's good enough for me too.
I'm glad.
I'm not sure if this will help,
but people forget things
more easily than you think.
So I hope you won't be
in too much pain.
Okay.
Isn't it uncomfortable to sit here?
It may not be good for your wound.
Hold on.
Lie down.
Lie down?
Going on a picnic at 1 a.m.
isn't that bad, right?
Didn't I do a fantastic job
planning this date?
This is part of our date too.
The last part of our date.
It's nice.
I especially like the last part.
I heard from Anchor Lee.
He told me that you're trying...
your best to fix the situation
regarding the book.
I'm worried that
you might get hurt from this too.
You don't have to worry about me.
I'm okay.
But please take good care
of Jeong Hoon.
This must be hard for him to bear.
This is the same as getting
betrayed by a trusted friend.
I will.
And I want to apologize
to you as well.
Whatever my father told you,
don't let that get to you.
Why do you keep apologizing?
It's not even your fault.
Actually, I asked you to see me
because I had something to tell you.
What is it?
Do you remember
what you told me the other day?
You said you didn't want
to make the same mistake again.
That's been on my mind.
What happened in the past...
was neither your mistake
nor responsibility.
It was my decision.
So you don't need to be sorry
about what happened.
I am always grateful to you.
I was grateful back then
and still am.
I wanted to tell you this.
Thank you for saying that.
(Professor Yoo Sung Hyuk)
Yes.
- What is this about?
- Are you Professor Yoo Sung Hyuk?
We're the police.
You have been sued
for a violation of disclosing...
a patient's medical record
and breaking the medical law.
Come with us.
(Medical License)
Do you know where I was just now?
It was you who pressed
charges against me.
Did they take your statement?
This is on a whole new level
of embarrassing your own father.
How dare you talk to the university
and worsen the situation?
I thought you would only stop
if I took extreme measures.
Jeong Hoon didn't do anything.
Who are you to go around
and throw dirt on my name?
Why are you so anxious
to bring down your own father?
I didn't bring you down.
You did it to yourself.
You brought this upon yourself.
Are you out of your mind?
More than anything,
you were wrong.
How was I wrong?
It looks like Jeong Hoon found
a way to live in the present...
while keeping his past with him.
It was you...
who couldn't accept that
and stayed in the past.
What on earth are you talking about?
Do you even know
what you're jabbering about now?
If you're done, please leave.
I need to wrap things up here.
("Lee Jeong Hoon,
Is He Really a Gentle Tyrant?")
This must be the revenge
Park Soo Chang prepared for me.
I knew that he was a jerk.
I had no idea he was a scumbag.
I'm sure he'll talk about the book.
Is this okay?
Perhaps, we should stop him.
I could make it worse...
if I make my move rashly.
Let's watch his show today.
Hello.
I was fired from my job a while ago.
I'm Reporter Park Soo Chang
of "Real Entertainment".
It turns out that a lot of people
were waiting for my show.
Thank you so much.
The question I got
the most from you guys was...
if the main character of "The Man
Who Cannot Forget", H,
was truly Anchor Lee.
That was the question.
Talking about what everyone
already knows won't be fun.
I like putting "first"
or "exclusive" on my articles.
I prepared to share something new.
Here's what I prepared.
(The 29th Yearbook)
This is it.
This is the yearbook
of Yeo Ha Jin's high school.
All right. Take a look.
Right here. Do you see her name?
"Yeo Ha Jin".
Let's take a look
at the group photo.
She always took photos
with this girl.
She must be her best friend,
but when I looked at her name,
it sounded quite familiar.
I thought about
where I heard her name from.
And I remembered a name.
It was...
Sadly, she died
in a tragic incident.
It was Anchor Lee's first love. Yes.
She used to be
Yeo Ha Jin's best friend.
Everyone, how does this make sense?
The woman he loved died.
But he fell in love
with the woman's best friend again.
Do you think it's possible?
I don't think I can do it.
Why don't I read your opinions?
"I didn't peg him
to be a piece of trash."
Everyone has
a similar opinion with me.
Ethically, this can't be. You know.
That's why I was very shocked after
reading about their relationship.
Seo Yeon and Ha Jin
were really close.
Yeo Ha Jin recently played a role
in a morning soap opera...
I heard they've been friends
ever since they were kids.
Doesn't that mean
she already knew about him...
when her friend dated him?
No way.
Then, when her friend was alive,
did they have a fling or something?
Just the thought creeps me out.
My gosh. I'm more disappointed
in Lee Jeong Hoon.
I didn't think he was such a jerk.
Is this too much?
They might think this doesn't
suit my role as a teacher.
Come on. It's not a shoot.
It's just a meeting with a director.
Why not?
You look pretty.
- I do?
- Yes.
I should put on a different pair.
If you ask me one more time,
I'll kill you.
Gosh.
Goodness.
Ms. Park, did something happen?
The production company
just called me...
to cancel the meeting.
How could they be so rude?
I'm sure something urgent came up.
Did they reschedule?
They didn't even say that.
That's why I'm angrier.
Out of the blue, they just said
it'd be best if we didn't meet.
Hold on.
What is it? You're worrying me.
Has he lost his mind?
- What is it?
- It was Anchor Lee's first love.
She used to be
Yeo Ha Jin's best friend.
Everyone.
Why did you watch that?
I said you would only get mad.
Why is Reporter Park
going such length to torture us?
We were the victims.
That scumbag doesn't need a reason.
He's just a scumbag.
Did you talk to Anchor Lee about it?
We talked on the phone earlier.
But he only asked me
where I was and hung up.
Things must be hectic for him too.
He already has a lot on his plate
with the publication.
How come we never have
an uneventful day?
I agree.
Hold on.
- Don't open it, Ha Jin.
- Wait.
- It's Ha Jin.
- It's Yeo Ha Jin.
Is it true you were a close friend
of Anchor Lee's first love?
Were you really friends
with the woman...
from "The Man Who Cannot Forget"?
What did Anchor Lee say
about today's news?
- Say something.
- Say a word.
- Answer our questions.
- Ms. Yeo!
- That's Anchor Lee!
- What?
- That's Anchor Lee.
- It's Lee Jeong Hoon.
- It's Jeong Hoon.
- He's coming here.
- Say something.
- Jeong Hoon.
- Answer our questions.
- Is everything true?
- Say something.
- Is it true?
- Please say something.
- Jeong Hoon.
- Come here.
- Say something.
- Can you answer our questions?
- Is it true?
- Anything for today's news?
- Is it all true?
- Please say something.
- What was your relationship?
- Don't avoid us. Answer it!
- Come on, answer our questions.
- Hold on.
- Anchor Lee!
- Say something.
Please tell us what's going on.
Guys!
Why don't we talk?
You must've been caught off guard.
Is your wound okay?
Are you overworking yourself?
I'm okay now. I'm good as new.
But how did you know?
There were reporters
in front of my house too.
I'm glad I got here in time.
My gosh.
This makes me realize that
there are so many reporters...
covering entertainment in Korea.
I'm a reporter too.
Right.
Why don't you sit down and wait?
I'll come down
after I change my outfit quickly.
Okay.
I'll get rid of these reporters
and stop by the office.
Tell Anchor Lee to stay home
until I come back.
(Ha Kyung)
All right, thanks.
(All right, thanks.)
Your feet are cold, aren't they?
Wear these.
- What are these?
- Slippers.
Are... Are these
the only ones you have?
You're a guest,
so I'm giving you my favorites.
They're new.
I want something
a little more simple.
Those are the simplest ones.
Thank you, I guess.
Did you eat dinner?
No, I was really busy.
That's great. My dinner plans
got canceled, so I haven't eaten.
Do you want to make something?
"Make something"?
Are you going to cook?
It takes me a while to cook,
but I'm a good cook when I try.
I know you're good when you put
your heart and soul into it.
But I'm way too hungry
to wait a long time,
so let's eat something simple.
What a relief.
Something simple sounds good.
Do you need help?
Can you get stuff from that cabinet?
What are all these?
This is the cabinet for
everything that's delicious.
I can only eat these
when Ha Kyung gives them to me.
Your manager is very strict.
Okay.
I'm not taking anything out
with my hands.
What do you want?
Bread!
Bread.
And chocolate jam.
Chocolate jam.
And popcorn.
And cookies too, right below.
Are you sure you can eat everything?
The only thing Ha Kyung and I
have in common is our stomach.
This is a piece of cake.
Anchor Lee, open your mouth.
My mouth?
Isn't this delicious?
It tastes exactly like
how I imagined it would be.
Anchor Lee, open your mouth.
Again?
I think I'm all done.
No way.
You have to keep having a bite...
to be my accomplice.
Are you really going to
finish everything?
I forgot to bring
something very important.
This is yours, this is mine.
Mine, thanks.
Let's make a toast.
- Cheers.
Take it off.
You said it was your first...
Let's keep doing things
the way we did today.
Things will be
pretty rough for a while.
It might take
much longer than we thought,
and it might be
much harder than we expected.
But like today,
let's bear through.
I'll do that.
I'll be even better.
Just like today.
Anchor Lee,
you can just do everything
as you did today.
I'll do that.
(Episode 30)
- Hello?
- Hey, it's me.
Why are you calling me this early?
Me?
I'm on my way to the airport.
The airport? Why?
I'm leaving
to volunteer as a doctor.
I've been thinking about this
for a while,
but I finally got
a great opportunity.
Volunteering as a doctor?
What are you talking about?
What about your clinic?
I already closed it last week.
And you're telling me this now?
On your way to the airport,
over the phone?
I forgot to tell you.
Everything was decided in a flash,
so I've been out of it.
Right, let me say this just in case.
I'm not leaving because of you,
so don't take this the wrong way.
You don't mean that much
in my life anyway.
Don't be so hard on yourself.
How can you joke around right now?
Then should I be crying?
I'm not running away.
For the first time, I seriously
thought about what I wanted to do,
then made this decision.
So I mean it. Don't worry about me.
It's a relief
if that's really the case.
But why didn't you tell me before?
What is...
I couldn't even say goodbye.
What is this?
It's not like I'm leaving for good.
I do feel a little bad
for leaving...
when your life is hectic.
So you don't know
when you'll be back?
I'll decide...
once I get there.
Okay, then. Be careful.
And report to me
as soon as you get there.
Okay. I'll call you again.
(I took part in a campaign
for abandoned animals.)
You make a living with your image
as the nation's first love.
How can you do that?
Are you happy dating
your dead friend's boyfriend?
Yeo Ha Jin, stop being
so fake, okay?
I'm getting chills.
How can you do that?
They're still the same.
Ha Kyung.
Hey, Ha Kyung.
I had to do something,
so I'm at the office.
Make sure you eat breakfast.
I'll call you in the afternoon
once I'm done with work.
She said she didn't have
any plans today.
What is this? Hey!
You! Hey, you jerk!
Hey! Who are you?
Hey!
Goodness.
Ha Jin.
- Hello.
- Hey, Chul.
Ms. Park told me that
you've been working hard lately.
Gosh, that's the least I could do...
to pay you back.
Yes, keep working hard.
I'm keeping my eyes on you.
Okay. Do you want some coffee?
Or chocolate?
Chocolate. And don't tell Ha Kyung.
Okay.
Director, this is not
what you told me last time.
We were going to make a draft
of the contract for discussion.
Doesn't that mean
we're pretty much in contract?
The least you could've done is
tell me about this beforehand.
No, it's not like
we violated the contract.
You can't suddenly demand penalty.
You can't keep changing
your statement like this.
This is making me very flustered.
What do you mean,
she caused controversy?
Do you think
she's a criminal or something?
What is going on?
Ha Jin.
What penalty charge?
What contract?
Ha Jin.
Let's talk inside.
Please be honest with me.
I have the right to know.
You're right.
There's nothing I can hide.
Since Reporter Park's
did that live broadcast,
the public started to criticize you.
We have no work at the moment.
No one's been offering us work.
What about that drama
we had a meeting for?
They just called and backed out.
We're trying to persuade them,
but I don't think it'll work out.
Same with the penalty charge
for the advertisement.
If we do that,
the other places
will demand theirs as well.
As of now, I don't know
what we should do.
I didn't know it'd be this bad.
It's not like
you did something terrible.
Does she deserve all this hate?
That stalker is the bad guy.
I don't understand...
why she should take the blame
just because she's a celebrity.
Is there absolutely no work?
I don't need to be the female lead.
I can play a villainess.
I'm willing to do anything.
Everyone is hesitant
about hiring you,
so I don't think it'll work.
If that doesn't work,
we could go abroad.
"Abroad"?
Yes. It's not a big role.
But it's a nice character.
How far have you guys talked?
First of all,
they suggested having a meeting.
You need to try out
for the audition.
I had been postponing that offer...
because your schedule was so hectic.
Should I tell them that
we'd like to try it out?
You want to switch the news anchor?
What do you mean?
I'm sure you know what I mean.
After Jeong Hoon became
the news anchor,
we've been at the top
when it came to news quality,
viewer ratings, and credibility.
It'd be ridiculous
to swap him for someone else.
Everyone is against him.
Our viewer ratings
have been dropping for a week now.
Our viewers have been bombarding
the bulletin board for a long time.
We need to replace him
if we want to save the news.
So what if the ratings went down?
After all, he's the one
who raised the ratings.
And this will all subside
after some time.
- So please...
- I don't want to hear it.
I'm not going to change my mind.
I just want you
to do as you're told.
Then you'll have to fire me as well.
You...
Do they not clean the machine?
The coffee tastes terrible.
It's probably because
you're troubled. It's tasty for me.
Why aren't you troubled?
Aren't we on the same news team?
Do I look like a pushover to you?
Why are you venting at me?
Gosh. I want to vent at someone.
Our viewers have given us nothing
but compliments.
They've never criticized us before.
You're right.
It's all thanks to that scumbag
who blabbered such nonsense.
You're right.
What was that jerk's name again?
It's Park Soo Chang.
Yes, him.
If I ever see him, I'll...
Hello.
It's been a long time,
Reporter Choi.
Sir.
Are you okay?
Me? Why?
Your team is having it rough
right now...
because of Jeong Hoon.
And to make things worse,
Director Choi's future
doesn't look too great either.
Her future doesn't look too great?
What are you talking about?
Is something wrong?
I don't want to talk about it
with you.
That must mean...
it's related to me.
What is it?
Thanks to you two
being awfully close,
I can never have peace.
Is something going on with her?
The president wanted to replace you.
And of course, she said no.
So they're discussing
whether to appoint...
Mr. Han of business
as the new director.
What? That's absurd.
How could they replace her
that easily?
She received her first warning
last time...
from the disciplinary committee.
Don't you know that two strikes
are all that you need to get fired?
(Lee Jeong Hoon's News Live)
We have five minutes.
Come in.
If you're done with the news,
you should have gone home.
Why are you here?
I have something to tell you.
Why does my heart pound...
every time you say that?
What is it?
(Letter of Resignation)
Thank you for allowing me
to be the news anchor.
I was especially honored...
to have worked
with someone like you.
You put up with whatever I did.
And thanks to that, I was able
to do everything that I wanted.
Why are you doing this?
I don't want to trouble you anymore
with my personal issues.
I hope you will keep your job
for a very long time.
Jeong Hoon.
Take this away.
Please accept it.
I've never thought of "News Live"
without you.
And I will continue
to think that way.
So cut this nonsense
and take this with you.
You know I won't stop submitting it.
I'm sorry.
(Call)
(Ha Jin)
Hey.
Why aren't you asleep? It's late.
I wanted to hear your voice
before going to bed.
Actually, there's something
I need to confess.
What is it?
It's nothing good.
I submitted
my letter of resignation today.
Why all of a sudden?
My workplace has been in a pickle
because of the current situation.
The higher-ups wanted to replace me.
If I were to remain there,
Director Choi would also have
to take responsibility.
I'm sorry I couldn't
discuss it with you beforehand.
I hope you still like me even though
I'm no longer a news anchor.
You liked to address me that way.
I'm a bit sad about that.
But I'll call you by your first name
from now on.
That sounds too awkward.
I know.
Then...
I'll just call you Anchor Lee
for the time being.
Sounds good.
Are you okay?
Yes, I am.
How about you?
I'm all right.
Okay.
So, you don't have to go to work
starting tomorrow?
They need to look
for my replacement,
and I need to teach them
a few things.
I'll still be going there
for some time.
You must be exhausted.
You should go to bed.
Okay. You should too.
Let's talk again tomorrow.
Goodnight.
You startled me.
What are you doing in the dark?
Ha Kyung.
Yes, what is it?
I need to go to the States.
I'll do the movie.
Talk to Ms. Park for me.
It's pretty far.
And surviving there won't be easy.
Do you still want to do it?
I think it's the right path for now.
I should go.
Guess who I am.
I can see your shadow.
You're right. How smart.
Aren't you hungry? Let's go and eat.
Sundaetguk?
Was that a lame offer?
- Or back-bone stew?
- I'm going to the States.
Are you going on a trip?
Good for you.
When are you going?
How long is the trip?
Sit down.
It's not a trip.
If I go, it might take years
before I come back.
What do you mean?
My sister is going to film
a movie in the States.
A while ago, she had an offer.
To be honest, things are really bad
for my sister's profession,
so I can't stop her.
Then, how long will you stay there?
I can't give you a definite answer,
but it will take longer than a year.
It could take longer than that.
I know we just started dating.
I'm sorry that I have to leave.
To be honest,
I can't ask you to wait for me.
I'll accept it
if you want to break up.
Do you want to break up with me?
Is that what you want?
No.
- Then, it's all good.
- What's good?
I don't want to break up with you.
And I don't want us to be apart.
- So I'll find a way.
- A way?
I'll go to the States with you.
As a correspondent.
Can you get that position
if you just want it?
Not really.
But a while ago,
they were recruiting...
correspondents to be dispatched
in the States.
Look at that. Perhaps,
we're meant to be together.
It's the perfect timing.
Then, will you get the job
if you apply?
I've never failed at getting a job
after applying for it.
What if you don't get it?
I'll get it. Don't worry.
My gosh. I don't think
it's that simple.
Right. Does Jeong Hoon
know about this?
That Ha Jin is going to the States?
Hi. Ha Kyung. What brings you here?
I'm not sure if you've heard.
My sister is leaving soon.
To the States.
What?
(Anchor Lee)
You're here.
How's the packing going?
Ha Kyung told me.
Why didn't you tell me?
You thought I wouldn't let you go
if you told me?
- I'm very good at waiting.
- Thank you for everything.
Thanks to you, I was very happy.
Those moments with you
were the brightest of my life.
And that will never change.
You won't be able to erase me...
in your memory.
But let our memory
belong in our past.
I promised that...
I would always be there for you
to cheer you on.
But having me by your side...
will make things harder now, right?
Yes.
By being together,
we will only be hurting each other.
This is the right thing to do.
If that's what you want,
let's do that.
I'm going to give it my all.
I want you...
to give it your all too,
so you don't think about me.
I will remember
every moment of you.
Take care.
I won't cry today.
I don't want you...
to remember me with a crying face.
(2 years later)
Gosh, what a day.
Goodness.
- There she is.
- Look. She's here.
- Hey.
Ma'am, it's your first day back
after getting your charge acquitted.
How does it feel?
You were suspected
to have abused your husband.
Things must've been rough
for you. Say something about it.
My innocence was finally proved
in court,
so I'm relieved.
Congratulations on getting
your assault charge acquitted.
I heard you hired
over eight lawyers...
from the biggest law firm in Korea.
You must have formed a dream team.
Mr. Lee Jeong Hoon.
Thank you for your compliment.
By the way,
will you form the same team...
when you get indicted
for a murder charge?
Murder?
On the 23rd of last month,
the day of your 2nd trial,
you hired an illegal detective
agency to introduce...
someone who would do
anything for money.
I don't know where and what kind
of rumors you've heard...
On the night of the 24th, you met
a man the agency introduced to you.
You secretly rendezvoused
with him at work.
And you talked to him
over eight times afterward.
Meanwhile, your husband,
Sim Jae Chul, went missing...
along with the video evidence he was
going to hand over to the judge.
I do not remember doing that.
It hasn't even been two weeks.
There's no way you already forgot.
You can't accuse me...
as a murderer
after I was just found innocent.
Do you really think
you can deal with this?
It's a recording of a whistle-blower
and the call history.
Do you really think
you can deal with this?
There they are.
You can ask them
for the original file.
Ms. Kang.
You're arrested for suspicion of
your husband, Sim Jae Chul's murder.
- Arrest her.
- Yes, sir.
I think...
I think there is a misunderstanding.
- No, I didn't.
- Let's go.
Hey, let me go. Take these off.
- Who do you think you are?
- Wait!
- Let me go!
- What are you doing?
- What's going on?
- Arrested for murder?
- Tell us the details!
- Say something!
- Why did you kill him?
- Do you admit to your crime?
- Tell us more!
- Say something before you go!
- Do you admit?
Jeong Hoon.
You've done something huge again.
It's not the first time
I got my hands on a big scoop.
What a show-off.
- What did you say?
- You heard that?
I keep saying how I feel out loud.
Take this.
That's a voice recording
of the informant...
who called the prosecution
regarding what Ms. Kang did.
Edit in whatever we need
for the news.
Thank you.
How long will the article take?
- About an hour.
- Okay, then.
I'll let Mr. Kim know.
Hurry up and go.
You'll get scolded by Mr. Kim
if you lurk around here.
Gosh. I'm leaving.
(City Desk Reporter Lee Jeong Hoon)
Hey, Anchor Cha.
Hello. Goodbye.
Keep it up. Yes, sir.
Hello.
- Hello.
("Cha Seon Woo's News Live")
- Cheers.
Hello, viewers.
I'm Cha Seon Woo of "News Live".
Director Kang Do Young of
Seongjae Group was...
arrested by the prosecution
for murder this afternoon.
Reported by Jo Il Kwon.
Director Kang Do Young of
Seongjae Group was...
recently found innocent for
habitual assault of her husband.
Lee Jeong Hoon! Can you hear me?
Hey! It's you, Lee Jeong Hoon.
Don't you have any friends?
Why do you always call me
when you get drunk?
I do have one. A girlfriend.
But she went far away
because of you.
I want to pat
my dear Ha Kyung's head.
I only get to
see her on video calls.
This time, I really thought
I'd be a correspondent.
Are you all right?
Don't you miss Ha Jin?
She's filming another movie there.
What if I never get to see Ha Kyung?
Gosh.
Jeong Hoon, let's go eat.
I don't have an appetite.
What do you want?
What?
This is good for you. Eat up.
Why are you suddenly doing this?
You're making me anxious.
Hey, am I not allowed to
buy you a meal?
I think
I've gone through this before.
Do you have a favor to ask?
What favor? It's not like that.
Eat up.
It won't be as good when it's cold.
This is good.
This place definitely cooks well.
- Let me ask you for a favor.
- I didn't eat anything yet.
It's too big to call it a favor.
I think I'll call it begging.
What is it?
Can you take charge
of "News Live" again?
- What?
- You spent enough time away.
Aren't you dying to return too?
No, not at all.
I love my life now.
I like going out on the field,
and I like having free time
at nights.
Like, my foot. You don't even have
anything to do after work.
How did you know?
Hey, the new president has
a very favorable attitude about you.
He's on our side now,
so there's no need to turn it down.
Return to "News Live".
That's where you belong.
People haven't
forgotten about me yet.
Once I'm shown on TV again,
things will get chaotic very soon.
Yes, that could be the case.
But people are more concerned
about the news you bring...
than your love life.
And there are a lot of people
who want you to deliver the news.
And above all, I need you.
If "News Live" continues like this,
it might get taken down.
I plead you. Won't you do it?
Jeong Hoon. Hey, Jeong Hoon.
Come on, Jeong Hoon. Please.
Please, do it. Just once.
Yes, Jeong Hoon.
Are you coming tonight?
Yes, I'm on my way.
Instead of eating out,
let's cook at home tonight.
I became a pretty decent cook now.
You said that last time.
You can't fool me again.
I'm serious.
I'll make spicy noodles for you.
I made a reservation
at a great place, so let's eat out.
Make me the noodles next time.
Okay, then.
I'll make it for you next time.
See you soon.
All right.
(Yeo Ha Jin)
("Yeo Ha Jin's 'Kill the Venus'
Draws Many People's Attention")
("Yeo Ha Jin Captures Hollywood
with 'Kill the Venus'")
("Yeo Ha Jin Shoots Part 2,
But When Will She Return?")
("Kill the Venus")
(Yeo Ha Jin played Jenny in season 1
of "Kill the Venus".)
(She's currently deciding
on her next Hollywood movie.)