(Episode 19)
Hello?
Goodness, Director Song!
One second.
What's the occasion?
Wow, it has been so long.
You can hop in first. Go ahead.
It's always the same with us.
Ms. Park will be here
after that phone call.
Okay, sure.
What is this?
Stop that car!
You have to get that car!
- No!
- Wait!
Who do you think you are?
Ha Jin!
Anchor Lee.
Hey. Are you with Ha Jin?
I can't get a hold of her.
She...
She just got abducted.
What?
(Find Me in Your Memory)
Ha Kyung.
Anchor Lee.
What's the situation?
Her phone was turned off
right after the situation broke out,
so we can't track her.
What about her location?
We're tracking down that car.
Are we yet to find out who did this?
We found a security camera nearby
and are looking into it,
but we'll have to see.
And the current suspects,
Ji Hyun Geun and Moon Chul.
We're looking for there whereabouts,
but they're both unreachable.
Goodness, Ha Jin.
- Yes?
- What will happen to her?
You found the car?
Where is it?
- Did you find anything?
- Over here.
I think he changed cars here
and ran away.
Hey. Sir!
What is it?
Darn it.
Hey.
He found a place
with no security camera,
prepared another car to run away in,
and even used anesthetics?
This jerk had this planned.
Take this.
- Yes.
- Where are you?
Do you know what time it is?
Why aren't you at work?
Come in.
What's going on?
Are you coming in just now?
Mr. Kim has been
looking for you everywhere.
I have something to tell you.
What's going on? What is it?
Something happened to Ha Jin.
I think she was
abducted by her stalker.
What?
Are you saying
Ha Jin is abducted right now?
The police are investigating this
behind closed doors.
How long has it been?
Do you have any information?
They're still investigating.
And they don't know
her location yet?
No.
Okay, I understand.
Don't worry about the news and go.
- I'm sorry.
- Hey.
I told you to hurry over.
Why are you here?
- Do you think I'm a joke?
- That's enough!
Why do you always tell me to stop?
What's with you two?
I told you to stop.
- What's wrong?
- Hurry up and go.
Yes, ma'am.
What's going on?
What is it?
Shouldn't he be preparing
for the news?
Jeong Hoon won't be able
to read the news today,
so tell Reporter Cha to do it.
I'm his team leader!
So why can't you tell me
why he can't do it?
Actually,
Ha Jin was abducted by her stalker.
- What?
- The police is investigating it...
behind the closed doors,
so we'll have to wait and see.
Darn it! What kind of a lunatic
would do something like that?
Really? Okay, I'll call you back.
- Sir.
- Yes?
Moon Chul lied about
having a drink with a friend...
on the day
of the motorcycle accident.
What?
He wasn't picking up his phone
since yesterday.
I just talked to that friend,
and he said the last time
the two met was over a week ago.
Darn it. I knew
something was fishy about him.
I think it was his doing.
Hold on.
It's Ji Hyun Geun.
Hello?
I just got in touch
with Ji Hyun Geun.
According to him, he was
at his studio since last night.
I'm going there right now to check.
We're sorry for disturbing you
when you must be busy.
Thank you for your cooperation.
Not at all.
I'm sorry I didn't pick up sooner.
I'll answer my phone on time
from now on,
so call me
whenever you need my help.
- Okay.
- Goodbye.
How did it go?
We looked around,
but we couldn't find
anything suspicious.
I see.
It's become highly likely
that Moon Chul is the culprit.
Once we dig deeper,
we'll be able to find a lead.
- So please be patient.
- Okay.
Did you not receive
any suspicious calls?
No, I didn't.
If you do receive any in the future,
please let us know.
All right. I'll do that.
- All right. Goodbye.
- Goodbye.
Stop.
I got you, you rat.
Isn't this enough evidence?
Request for an emergency warrant...
and put out an APB for Moon Chul.
Find out which way he drove...
and get his credit card activity.
- Yes, sir.
Ha Kyung.
Ms. Park.
Are you okay?
Do you want some water?
Did the police call?
No.
Hello, detective.
Chul was at the scene?
Are you saying he's the culprit?
Okay, I'll be waiting for your call.
Goodbye.
Is it Chul?
Did he really abduct her?
They're not certain yet.
They're going
to search his house first.
Oh, dear. Poor Ha Jin.
She must be terrified.
- Open it.
- Yes, sir.
There's no one here.
I think it's been vacant
for some time.
What? These are all luxury items.
Really?
I'm sure managers don't earn
hefty wages.
- Did you find anything?
- No, sir.
What is this?
What? It's an earring.
Don't you know me?
We met several times with Seo Yeon.
Who is this? Why are you
answering Seo Yeon's phone?
Jeong Hoon, save me.
- Save me, Jeong Hoon!
- Are you okay, Seo Yeon?
- Jeong Hoon!
- Seo Yeon?
Please get yourself together,
Seo Yeon!
You scumbag.
Jeong Hoon.
This is all your fault.
Seo Yeon changed all because of you.
It's all your fault, Lee Jeong Hoon!
Hey, Tae Eun.
Are you saying her stalker
mimicked Moon Seong Ho?
I think he became more aggressive
as he met with Moon Seong Ho.
Had it not been for me,
he would've never known about him.
Then none of this would've happened.
Don't blame yourself.
Even if you weren't involved,
scumbags like him
would've found a way.
You're also a victim,
so don't be ridiculous.
Didn't you say the police
were after her manager?
Now that they know their target,
he'll get caught soon.
There's something unsettling
about Director Ji.
What do you mean?
It's hard to explain.
But I've always felt this way.
He reminds me of Moon Seong Ho.
After seeing Moon Seong Ho recently,
this feeling became even stronger.
Did you tell this to the police?
It's just a feeling that I have.
If all the evidence they found
point to Moon Chul,
then he must be the culprit.
Is this Ms. Yeo's earring?
Are you looking for something?
I can't find the other one.
Didn't you keep them together?
I thought I did,
but I can't find one of them.
This would've been perfect.
Yes, it is. She lost it a while ago.
We found it at Moon Chul's place.
He must've been sneaking
into your house for some time now.
We were like family,
so it must've been easy.
He knew the passcode as well.
How dare he?
Ma'am.
Is there anything you know
about his family...
or his close friends?
Do you know whom he'd visit
during this situation?
He said his parents lived
in Gangwon Province.
He said it was a very rural area
and that I wouldn't know.
He could be hiding there.
Call his parents and ask
if he has contacted them recently.
Yes, sir.
Don't get the wrong idea.
Seo Yeon loves me.
(Don't get the wrong idea.
Ha Jin loves me.)
- Bye.
- Goodbye.
(Directed and written
by Ji Hyun Geun)
(Juun Pictures)
(Directed and written
by Ji Hyun Geun)
(Ji Hyun Geun)
(Traffic Ticket,
2:05 a.m. March 16)
Gangjeong Lake?
Gangjeong Lake...
- Yes.
- This is Lee Jeong Hoon.
When you recently
questioned Director Ji,
are you sure he said he only stayed
in his studio as he was working?
Yes, he did.
I stumbled across something
that doesn't make sense.
You don't need to worry
about Director Ji anymore.
- What?
- We located the culprit.
Her agent, Moon Chul,
is the culprit.
I can't explain to you
in detail right now.
Anyway, we just located him
and we are on our way there now.
Did you locate Ha Jin?
Moon Chul who was on the run
called his cousin...
who lives in Gangwon Province...
and asked his cousin
to reserve a vacation rental.
I think he'll probably go there
with the abducted victim.
Where is that? I'll meet you there.
No.
Your presence
might provoke the culprit.
Trust us on this and wait, please.
Okay.
You, go into the house.
And we'll go to the other side.
Open it.
Moon Chul.
Freeze. Don't move.
Look for Yeo Ha Jin first.
- Search the house.
- Hey, check upstairs too!
- What's that?
- My gosh.
- She's not here.
- No?
- What about upstairs?
- She's not there either.
I'm sorry.
Please let me off the hook
just this time. I'm sorry.
Hey!
I'm locked in here!
Is anyone out there?
Help!
What about Ha Jin?
Darn you.
Put him in the van now.
Hey!
Is anyone out there?
I'm locked in!
Please.
Hey!
Open up.
Hey.
Ha Jin, you're awake.
It was you, Director Ji?
Were you the one who sent
the threatening letters,
broke into my house,
and tried to run over Ha Kyung
on a motorcycle?
It was all your doing?
You must have a headache
because of the drug.
Don't strain yourself, Ha Jin.
How could you do this to me?
You must be very angry, Ha Jin.
First, why don't you eat some food?
Sit down.
Let's talk after you eat.
Don't come near me.
That's dangerous.
- Don't do that.
- Don't come near me.
This isn't right.
This is not like you, Ha Jin.
You were always kind to me.
Weren't you?
I prepared them because
I wanted you to have a proper meal.
Sadly, I should put them away.
They might be dangerous for you.
I'll bring other utensils.
I'll be back soon.
Sit down and wait for me.
Right.
Ha Jin.
Happy birthday.
Let's have
a proper party later. Okay?
(Gangjeong Lake)
(Pollution-free Shelter)
Oh, you mean Yeo Ha Jin's stalker?
I don't know.
We just exchanged a few letters.
That's all.
I gave him all the hints.
I wonder if he understood them.
So...
you don't know
where Ms. Yeo Ha Jin is, correct?
What happened?
Did you locate Director Ji?
No one is at the studio.
But he canceled his appointment
at the editing studio...
in the evening unilaterally.
How about this? Why don't
we disclose this to the public...
and launch a nationwide manhunt
on Ji Hyun Geun?
No.
He's a famous celebrity
everyone knows.
If we publicly expose him that
he's a stalker and a kidnapper,
I don't know what that crazy jerk
will do to Ha Jin.
She has a point.
- That's too dangerous.
- I understand that, but...
Man, this is driving me insane.
Yes, Anchor Lee.
I found out where Ji Hyun Geun is.
I think he's with Ha Jin.
You found out where Ji Hyun Geun is?
I'll see what's going on
and try to stall for time.
Come as soon as you can.
("Actress Yeo Ha Jin Abducted,
the Police Are Under Investigation")
So? What did you two talk about?
Wait, are you serious?
You really have
feelings for Yeo Ha Jin?
Jeong Hoon, have you been well?
When you have some time,
can you stop by to get examined?
Why haven't you eaten?
Don't you have an appetite?
It probably got cold.
I'll make it again.
You can have this for now.
Ha Jin will soon find out...
that you're human garbage,
Jeong Hoon.
No one can keep us apart anymore,
Ha Jin.
What is this?
A blackout?
You little...
Darn it.
Why are you here?
How did you know we were here?
You lunatic.
No matter what you do
and how much you try,
you will never lay a finger on her.
You're the one who's insane.
You couldn't get over
your dead girlfriend...
and began to
hit on her friend, Ha Jin.
Stop pretending
like you're so great!
Over here, I'm locked up in here.
Over here!
Darn it, you.
How dare you mess with my plan?
How dare you?
This is a place
only for me and Ha Jin.
This isn't a place
where jerks like you can show up!
Come here. Come.
Over here!
Lee Jeong Hoon. Lee Jeong Hoon!
Come here, Lee Jeong Hoon!
Open this!
Open this immediately!
How much longer will it take?
We'll be there soon.
Could you go a little faster?
Sure.
Is anybody here?
Over here!
Ha Jin!
Anchor Lee.
Ha Jin.
Anchor Lee, I'm in here.
Give me a moment.
Ha Jin.
Are you hurt?
Anchor Lee.
Thank you.
Thank you for staying safe.
We have to get out of here.
We don't know when he'll be here.
He can't come.
Don't worry.
Look at your face, Anchor Lee.
I'm fine.
Can you walk?
Yes.
Let's go.
(Episode 20)
Be careful.
Hang in there.
Are you all right?
- Yes.
- Where's Ji Hyun Geun?
He's in the garage.
You two can get in the car.
We'll control
the rest of the situation.
Let's go.
Ha Jin.
Ha Kyung.
I'm sorry. I'm so sorry.
You don't need to be sorry.
I'm so relieved.
What a relief.
It's okay.
It's all over.
Let's go.
Goodness, Ha Jin.
Ha Jin, are you okay?
Ha Jin, are you all right?
Wake up, Ha Jin.
- Goodness.
- You jerk.
- Don't come near me!
- Hey!
- Don't come near!
- Stop it.
Let me go! Let go of me!
Let me go!
- He's here.
- They're back.
Is it true that
Ms. Yeo Ha Jin was abducted?
How is she doing? Is she all right?
We thought the police
had been protecting her.
How was she abducted?
Who's the culprit?
Is her stalker
also the one who abducted her?
Yes, he was.
We will debrief you soon
on the result of our investigation.
- When do you plan on doing that?
- Who was the stalker?
- There he is!
- What is this?
- Who is it?
- How do you feel?
- Why did you abduct her?
- Show us your face!
- Say something.
- Why did you do that?
- Share a word.
Say something.
- Why did you do that?
- Why did you abduct her?
- Since when did you...
- How did you get...
Hey, aren't you Ji Hyun Geun,
the film director?
- Ji Hyun Geun?
- It's Ji Hyun Geun!
- Hey!
I really wasn't trying to hurt her.
I know I wasn't
supposed to do that,
but I was in need of money.
You wanted to gamble
and buy luxurious goods,
so you stole her sponsored goods,
pocketed clothes that were borrowed,
and broke into her house?
I'm sorry about that.
But I really was going to
tell her everything and apologize.
I waited for her many times
in front of the studio,
but she had bodyguards...
("Suspect Ji Hyun Geun Arrested
for the Abduction of Yeo Ha Jin")
Man, Ji Hyun Geun, that jerk!
Ms. Park, please stop crying.
These are tears of happiness.
Don't worry about me.
Why would you cry when you're happy?
You should smile.
She didn't collapse
because she's hurt.
It just means she can finally relax.
She's sound asleep, so don't worry.
I know. I heard that with you.
It's her birthday today.
We can't let her feel gloomy.
We should show her a smile
when she wakes up.
You're right.
I can't look miserable.
Stop crying.
Ha Kyung.
- Ha Jin.
Ha Jin.
Ms. Park.
Ha Jin, you've done well.
You've done so well
in returning safely...
and waking up bravely.
Thank you, Ha Jin.
I'm sorry I made you worried.
You shouldn't have to be sorry.
I'm the one who's sorry.
Ha Jin, look over there.
Your fans sent you presents
to help you feel better.
Gosh, I got so many presents.
I'm so thankful for all of them.
Look, don't you love
those flowers too?
Yes, they're very pretty.
Anyway, it feels like...
what happened yesterday night
was nothing but a dream.
A really bad nightmare.
Yes, let's just think of that
as nothing but a nightmare...
and forget all about it.
I should do that.
If I don't,
it'll make my birthday way too sad.
Yes, it was a bad dream.
Forget all about it.
Right, where's Anchor Lee?
He left right after
you were hospitalized.
Oh, I see.
You should call him.
No, he must be busy at work.
I'll wait until he calls me.
You're the one who's insane.
You couldn't get over
your dead girlfriend...
and began to
hit on her friend, Ha Jin.
Stop pretending
like you're so great!
Hey, Tae Eun.
You were right...
about Director Ji.
Is everything all right, then?
Yes. Hey, I forgot to call you.
I was out of it.
Of course, you were out of it.
But I'm relieved
the culprit was caught.
Is Ha Jin all right?
She's at the hospital.
She's not badly hurt,
but we're checking just in case.
When you have some time,
please give her a hand.
You said you were a good doctor.
All right, man.
And let me know
if you need any help too.
Yes, I will call you,
so I expect huge help from you.
All right, then. I'm glad
everything is okay. Bye, then.
Okay. I'll call you again.
Yeo Ha Jin's stalker
who also abducted her was...
found to be
Film Director Ji Hyun Geun.
- Ji had been obsessing over her...
- Wow.
Look at smiling
even with all those cameras on him.
I told you that
he looked really awful...
when he came for the interview,
didn't I?
I did think he was extraordinary,
but I didn't know
he was such a scary guy.
You really don't have
a good discernment on people.
Where's the picture that he took?
Let me burn them all.
I already got rid of that.
Ha Jin must've been shocked.
She probably worked very hard for
months filming that movie with him.
And he turns out to be her stalker.
Goodness, it's really difficult...
to live as a celebrity.
It's very hard.
Should I call her?
Call who? Jeong Hoon?
No, Ha Jin. I'm worried about her.
She probably has no time for that.
Let her get some rest.
We can ask Jeong Hoon later
and visit her or something.
You're going to visit her alone
with Jeong Hoon, right?
You can't do that.
You have to take me.
Since when were you so close
to Yeo Ha Jin? Stop overreacting.
Of course, we're close.
I even sent Jeong Hoon to her...
to comfort her.
Goodness.
Why? Are you jealous
that I'm close to her?
Hey, you're really jealous.
Don't look at me like that.
This isn't home.
And stop talking casually.
It doesn't matter.
We're here by ourselves.
If you're done watching the news,
get back to work.
Go now. Get up. Go.
And when Jeong Hoon gets here,
bring him to me.
This isn't our house, you jerk.
Yes, ma'am.
(Call Log)
(Anchor Lee)
Has he called yet?
No.
Goodness.
Just call him first.
I'm going to wait.
You were always the one
who didn't listen and called him.
He helped out a lot.
He was searching everywhere for you.
If it wasn't for him,
we wouldn't have found that villa.
Really?
He probably thinks
that you're still asleep.
Maybe he's not calling you
on purpose so you can rest.
What if that's not true?
"Not true"? What do you mean?
- Never mind.
- What is it?
Forget it. I'm going to take a nap.
Cover yourself properly.
There you go.
(Reporter Jo)
How could you do this to me?
I'm truly hurt.
Reporter Jo.
How could you not tell me...
about all the things that happened?
I'm sorry. I'll treat you
to something delicious instead.
I'm really hurt, you know?
I even offered my place
for you guys.
I know. I promise to treat you
to something scrumptious.
I don't usually
introduce this place to others.
But you're an exception, okay?
Where is it?
Get in first. It'll take some time.
Hurry up.
So this was it?
I'm not a big fan of rice soup.
How is that possible?
It's a Korean, hearty meal.
Try it first. It'll be the best
rice soup you've ever had.
Fine.
Here it comes. All right.
It looks so good.
Thank you.
- Enjoy your food.
- Thank you.
All right.
I don't like to add
a lot of things to mine.
What? I didn't say
you could do this.
Just try it.
If you don't like it,
I'll order something else.
Isn't it good?
It hurts my pride to say this,
but it is good.
It's the best rice soup ever.
It's really delicious.
I told you.
You'll crave this again
tomorrow morning.
- Eat up.
- Okay.
Director Ji Hyun Geun, who stalked
and abducted actress Yeo Ha Jin,
was arrested.
He broke into her house...
- How dare you smile?
- and stalked her continuously.
He's currently under arrest...
for locking her up
in his villa in Gyeonggi Province.
Are you okay?
He looks fine.
Even after doing what he did,
that psychopath looks fine!
After locking her up...
I should've punched him
when I had the chance.
He cooperated with the police...
- Do you want to throw some punches?
- so that they wouldn't suspect him.
Look at your score.
I want to do it again.
Give me a dollar.
A dollar?
This won't do. Follow me.
Where are you going?
I'm not done here.
Hey, don't do that.
Why isn't it running?
Stop it, stop it.
Stop it.
You're no match for me.
I was so close to winning.
Hey, it's a shooting game.
Are you any good?
I just enjoy it.
I can see that.
You're pretty good.
Here you go.
(Ha Jin, Jeong Hoon.
You two look great together!)
Come in.
- Happy birthday to you
- Happy birthday dear Ha Jin
Happy birthday.
- Happy birthday.
- Congratulations.
Thanks.
Even though things are hectic,
you should still blow out
your birthday candles.
Take your time
and pick what you want.
I'll buy anything for you.
Really? Then I'll come up
with something nice.
Ha Jin, it's me.
- Hello.
- Could you?
- Sure.
Why are you here?
I'm visiting her. And you?
Me too, you punk.
I was worried about her.
Are you feeling okay?
Yes, I am.
Thank you for your concern.
I'm glad you look well.
By the way, whose birthday is it?
It's yours?
Gosh, had I known earlier,
I would've prepared a gift.
Why isn't Jeong Hoon here?
I came here alone
because he wasn't at work.
Hey.
Hello.
What happened to your face?
Did he beat you up?
What? Of course, not.
I was being careless
and ran into something.
Go to my office.
I'll be there soon.
Okay.
You went to the pharmacy?
Hey, you should take better care
of your face.
Why would you walk around
and show it off?
It's not bad.
I even got free ointment.
Seeing how you're joking around,
you're finally back
to being yourself.
I heard Ha Jin is hospitalized.
Did she get hurt?
Fortunately, she's well.
But she must've been shocked.
You're right.
She'll need time to recover.
I'm truly glad
that she's safe and sound.
Me too.
I'm trying my best to cover for you.
But I don't think the higher-ups
will let you off the hook.
No matter what the reason may be,
you did bail on the news.
I know.
Will you be okay today?
You'll have to read news
about Ha Jin.
I'll do it.
Thank you...
for letting me off the hook
last time...
and for yesterday as well.
I'll come to my senses and do well.
Forget it.
Tell the makeup artist
to cover that up well.
Okay.
You may leave.
- I'll be going, then.
- Okay.
- Hey.
- Thank you.
- Hey, you were here.
- Yes.
Did you watch the news
about Director Ji?
It was a good one.
Who taught you to reveal
a culprit's identity like that?
Whom do you think?
I'm your one and only junior.
The entire world ought to know
who abducted our dear Ha Jin.
- "Our dear Ha Jin"?
- Yes.
You two must be close.
Of course. I just got back
from her surprise birthday party.
She had a surprise birthday party?
Yes, I went with Ha Kyung...
I visited the hospital
with Ha Kyung...
and had a small party.
She looks much better now.
Really?
I should go work.
Sure.
I'm Reporter Lee Ji Jeong.
Director Ji Hyun Geun, who stalked
and abducted actress Yeo Ha Jin,
was arrested.
He broke into her house...
and stalked her continuously.
He's currently under arrest...
for locking her up
in his villa in Gyeonggi Province.
He claimed to have committed
the crime because his love...
- Lee Jeong Hoon...
- was unreciprocated.
caught him, indeed.
After being rescued,
Yeo Ha Jin fainted...
Who are you?
Why did you want to see me?
I'll tell you that later.
But first, you're the one
who killed Ms. Jung Seo Yeon, right?
Who are you?
Don't be so cold.
We're on the same team.
Who are you?
I see.
You must be in the dark about
what Lee Jeong Hoon has been up...
being locked up in here.
Hold on.
("Yeo Ha Jin's New Boyfriend,
Lee Jeong Hoon")
What is this?
This woman...
That's right. It's Yeo Ha Jin.
She was a close friend
of Jung Seo Yeon.
Lee Jeong Hoon...
is dating this woman right now?
It's nothing serious.
They're going to break up anyway,
but I got annoyed
when I had to watch him date her.
This can't be.
They can't be together, you know.
So what?
What is it that you want from me?
I want you to tell me...
everything you did
to Lee Jeong Hoon.
That way, he'll get scared and
stay away from my Ha Jin quickly.
And you can get your revenge
against Lee Jeong Hoon too.
Isn't that a win-win?
I like it.
That sounds fun.
(Inmate Moon Seong Ho)
So are you going
to start afresh with Yeo Ha Jin?
I can't let you do that.
Here.
Now, tell me. What is this about?
What do you mean?
You keep saying you're fine today,
but I can tell you're sad.
What's wrong?
Are you still scared?
Are you still anxious?
Is that it?
It's all over now.
You don't have to worry now.
I think it's really over now.
What?
I think I have become...
his past to Anchor Lee now.
He had been nice to me
all this time...
because of the stalker.
Now, he doesn't need
to worry about me.
I'm afraid he might leave me again
and wish me happiness.
Is that why you didn't call him
and have been moping around all day?
Yes.
I'm afraid.
Why don't we get some fresh air?
Doesn't it feel suffocating
to stay indoors?
Let's go for a walk.
Okay.
This feels nice.
The view here is
better than I thought.
How do you feel? Do you feel
better with some fresh air?
Yes.
I think I'll feel much better
with some tteokbokki.
What are you talking about?
No tteokbokki.
- How about fried chicken?
- No fried chicken.
My gosh, I feel so sad.
You feel sad?
Fresh air will lift your spirit.
It's chilly here.
Let me get some blankets.
Just order some food for me.
How about a run around here?
It'll put us in a good mood.
Get the blanket.
Okay. I'll be quick. Wait here.
You're back already?
Are you feeling okay?
I didn't call you because I wanted
you to rest up without distractions.
What is it? Did something happen?
How could you not call me once today
after leaving me this morning?
Do you know how long
I waited for your call?
I see. I didn't think
that you'd be waiting for my call.
I had to take care of something.
I was distracted.
It's your birthday present.
I didn't know what to get you.
So it took me some time
to pick out a present for you.
I hope you like it.
You left to buy my present?
Yes.
Won't you open it?
What are all these?
You don't get to sleep well
because of your nightmares.
They help you sleep better.
I wanted you to sleep well
without any nightmares.
Picking out one was harder,
so I decided to go for the quantity.
What is it? Do you not like them?
No, I like them.
I was touched. I'm very thankful.
But you don't look like
you're touched.
I'm really touched, but...
But?
I'm afraid...
that this might be the end.
We started this because
of my one-sided crush on you.
And then, we realized
there was a stalker.
You were worried about me,
so you were taking care of me
in case something happened to me.
But now that he's arrested,
it's really over.
I'm scared that
you'll be nice to the end...
and say goodbye
like the other time.
Is that what this is?
I won't say goodbye to you.
I won't be saying goodbye
to you from now on.
Why not?
I want to stay by your side now.
So you don't have to worry.
You can't take that back.
That's a promise, okay?
I promise you.
Happy birthday.
(Find Me in Your Memory)
What were you doing?
Were you thinking about me?
Square your shoulders.
Straighten your back.
We should have a proper first date.
Let's officially go on a date
this weekend.
People will recognize us.
They can watch us if they want.
We don't have to hide.
How could you meet someone new
as if it's not a big deal?
That's why it's fate.
We are destined
to meet and fall in love.
Because of you, Ha Jin's memory
might come back.
I don't want to regret
any of the time I have left.
What are you thinking?
Grant me a wish too.
Whatever situation we may be in,
let's never say
goodbye to each other.