Hello.
I'm the guy who's dating Yeong.
Seo Yeon and I...
Right.
I'm the guy who's dating Yeong.
I...
love her a lot.
You remembered, didn't you?
Then...
you can't do this to Seo Yeon.
(Yeo Ha Kyung)
One second.
- Yes, Anchor Lee.
- Tell Ha Jin to leave right away.
She's doing a fan signing event.
She'll be done soon.
I have no time to explain.
You have to stop the event
and get her out of there now.
(Yeo Ha Jin's Fan Signing Event)
- What?
- Ha Jin!
- Ha Jin, what's wrong?
- Wake up, Ha Jin. Hey.
- Ha Jin!
Can someone call 911?
(Find Me in Your Memory)
(Episode 25)
Ha Kyung.
You're here.
What happened?
Nothing's particularly wrong
with her.
She must have been overwhelmed
with a lot of work lately.
Did you see anyone suspicious
during the fan signing event?
There was a huge crowd,
and no one stood out.
Today, a lifer ran away
from the National Forensic Hospital.
He ran away in that direction,
so I got worried and called you.
This isn't a dangerous situation
for her, is it?
Don't worry.
He'll be caught very soon.
I see.
You won't have any trouble
with your everyday life...
if you continue to do
your rehabilitation exercise.
Ha Na.
I can do this by myself.
Right. I'm sorry.
I can do this by myself, so go.
I'm sorry.
But sadly,
you won't be able
to do ballet again.
Hey, Jeong Hoon.
I'm at Ha Na's hospital.
Yes. I think so.
Ha Jin, where are you going
at this hour?
Yeong was here,
but I avoided seeing her again.
She must be heartbroken
because of me.
It's late,
so let's call her again tomorrow.
I mean, it wasn't her fault.
Do you think she'll be back?
Of course.
Don't worry about that
and go to sleep.
Hello.
You're Yeo Ha Jin, aren't you?
Who are you?
Seo Yeon and I...
Right.
I'm the guy who's dating Yeong.
I've heard a lot about you
from Seo Yeon.
She said you're her best friend,
and that you're
the most precious person to her.
Yeong said that?
Yes, so much so that I get jealous.
Seo Yeon is the most precious to me.
That's why
I always wanted to meet you.
Right, and I have
a favor to ask of you.
A favor?
Seo Yeon and I got into a fight,
and I wanted to make up with her,
so I prepared a surprise for her.
But I still don't know the passcode
to her practice room.
I thought you might know,
so I wanted to ask you.
Ha Jin, you're up.
Are you feeling ill?
Are you all right?
I have to go somewhere.
Can you drive me?
Right now?
You can't go anywhere
in this condition.
Ha Jin.
Ha Jin!
Why are you doing this?
Why haven't you told me?
Why did you lie to me?
Why did you let me forget? Why?
Ha Jin...
How could I forget Yeong?
Don't you remember how Yeong died?
Don't you know who caused her death
and why she died? How can I...
I should visit her.
Where was he last spotted?
He was spotted three hours ago
at J Shopping Mall.
That was the last of him.
No one has spotted him ever since.
The police put out an APB.
Where have you been amidst all this?
- Come join the meeting right now.
- Okay.
The main news team didn't have
enough time,
so they're only going to brief
the viewers in the beginning.
I think our program will have
to give an in-depth briefing.
That means this will be
breaking news.
Right.
Gosh, which news
am I supposed to omit?
How about receiving
real-time reports from our viewers?
Are you serious?
Yes. Moon Seong Ho was arrested
for murder.
We need to catch him
before he commits another murder.
That is true.
Since the police
have put out an APB,
let's ask them
to share their information.
And let's ask for real-time reports.
Do you think we have enough time?
We can make time.
But what if they catch him
before our news begins?
I mean, that's good news.
It won't be that easy.
He risked his life
to escape from prison.
He's going to hold out
until he gets what he wants.
I'll report this to the higher-ups.
First, contact the police...
and look up information about him.
Okay. I'll call the police.
I'll look for a forensic artist.
Wouldn't it be helpful to show
photos of him...
with long hair or glasses?
Smart move.
If you have any other ideas,
share it with us.
Let's get busy.
Yes, ma'am.
(Ha Jin)
I'll wait here.
(Jung Seo Yeon)
I'm sorry.
It took me so long, right?
I'm truly sorry for being so late.
I really am.
Father.
What happened?
The police called.
Did you get into an accident?
It's only a mild concussion.
You don't need to worry.
Did Jeong Hoon call you
by any chance?
Why would he?
Seo Yeon's stalker
escaped from prison.
What?
There's only one reason why
he'd escape.
He probably wants
to avenge Seo Yeon.
He's probably after Jeong Hoon
or Yeo Ha Jin.
I didn't tell the police
about Jeong Hoon,
so keep an eye on him.
The stalker had harmed himself
in order to escape.
I should've caught onto it.
Let me get this right.
Seo Yeon's murderer escaped,
and you're involved in all this?
That's not what's important
right now.
How far are you going to take this?
Are you sane?
Do you even know how much danger
you had put yourself in?
What were you planning to do
after meeting with the murderer?
What's going on in your head?
Don't you dare talk
to your father that way.
If...
something happens
to Jeong Hoon or Ha Jin,
I will never forgive you.
Ha Jin, I'm coming in.
Ha Jin.
I'm going to open the door.
Ha Jin, don't be like this.
Are you going to repeat
what you did in the past?
No sleep, no food. Are you going
to not take care of yourself?
It's about time you stopped.
It's been eight years already.
You should focus on yourself now.
Ha Kyung, please.
Let me be alone for some time.
(Information on Moon Seong Ho)
(Wanted: Escaped Prisoner)
This is the first batch
of information from the police.
They'll keep sending more,
so make sure you get them.
There's the number of the detective
who was in charge.
Call him if you need to.
Okay.
Did you find a forensic artist?
Of course.
And a very competent one, at that.
I'll write up a list of questions
and give them to you.
Come on. I can do that much.
Just trust me
and focus on your script.
Okay. Let me know if you need help.
All right.
(Warden Kim Byung Yoon)
Hello, sir. This is Lee Jeong Hoon.
Hello. You're calling
because of Moon Seong Ho, right?
Yes. How did he escape?
I believe he was already planning
an escape...
when he had harmed himself.
I should've known.
We decided to talk about him
on our program.
"Where is the wound
that he caused himself?"
"How big is it?"
"How is his mental state as of now?"
"What should we watch out for
if we run into him?"
I need as much information on him
as possible.
All right.
I'll send you his doctor's note
and other documents on him.
Thank you.
Ha Kyung.
Yes?
Did you throw away my belongings?
What belongings?
My old diary and the photos
Seo Yeon and I took.
Did you get rid of them?
Why do you ask?
I guess you still have them.
I'd like to see them.
I'm not going to harm myself.
Don't worry.
I just want to see them.
(Ha Na and Yeong's Exchange Diary)
(Let's wear the lipstick
we bought today tomorrow.)
(My dear Ha Na)
(Anchor Lee)
Hello.
Hi, Ha Jin.
I got worried
when I couldn't reach you.
Where are you?
Did you get discharged?
Do you know
someone named Jung Seo Yeon?
Jung Seo Yeon.
You said you got injured
and stopped doing ballet, right?
When exactly was that?
After Seo Yeon passed away,
he was in so much pain.
She was his first love.
Ha Jin?
(Anchor Lee)
Hello? Ha Jin.
Ha Jin.
I thought something happened to you.
I was worried.
I need to talk to you
about something.
What's wrong? What is it about?
Didn't you ask me once...
if I knew Jung Seo Yeon?
By Jung Seo Yeon, are we...
talking about the same person
we both know?
I remembered everything.
Everything about Seo Yeon.
You already knew...
that I was Seo Yeon's friend, right?
I wasn't trying to deceive you.
I wasn't sure
if telling you the truth...
was the right thing to do.
I shouldn't have asked you out.
I should have stopped pursuing you
when you pushed me away.
I am so sorry.
I think I caused you a lot of pain
all this time.
No, it's not your fault.
No, you don't know anything...
and what I have done.
I just realized
why it was hard to figure you out.
It sounded like you were
always telling me the truth,
but it didn't feel completely true.
It felt like
you were telling me a lot,
but you weren't telling me anything
at the same time.
It was all because of Seo Yeon.
I finally learned
everything about you now.
But I don't know what to do.
I did expect that you would regain
your memory one day.
My heart was always heavy...
when I thought about the pain you'd
feel after getting your memory back.
I'm sure you must be
very confused right now.
But nothing will change, Ha Jin.
It's all in the past.
I really can't think right now.
I don't know what to do.
Okay.
Our country is in a ruckus
because of Moon Seong Ho.
Make sure to get all the subtitles
for the callers and the photos.
And if you get any useful calls,
let me know right away. Okay?
- Yes, sir.
Okay.
Assistant director,
what about the photo?
I'll bring it up now.
(The most recent photo
of Moon Seong Ho)
How did you get all of these?
Jeong Hoon gave me these photos.
All of these photos?
Yes.
My gosh,
this is what I hate that guy.
He's too perfect.
How did he get all of those photos?
When he's done with his lines,
put these photos on the screen.
Yes, sir.
Hey, Jeong Hoon. How did
you get all of those photos?
I got the tip through
my personal connection.
I see. You're still a journalist
with connections.
The screenshot of the footage
is the most recent photo.
When I checked, it was clearer
than the one from the CCTV.
Use that as the main photo.
Okay. Run the title.
Be on standby.
Three.
Two.
One.
Anchor Lee.
Hello, everyone.
Let us begin
"Lee Jeong Hoon's News Live".
This afternoon, a prisoner
serving a life sentence...
at the National Forensic Hospital
escaped from a hospital...
- while he was being treated.
- Get his photo ready.
As soon as the police received
the report, they put out an APB.
They're using all of their resources
to locate Moon Seong Ho.
However, they still haven't
located the prisoner.
In an attempt to help
the nationwide search...
and the police
to locate the prisoner,
we will be taking calls
from the viewers.
Wait. Are they short-staffed?
Please call the number below...
to report anything
about the prisoner.
- This is the 40-year-old prisoner,
- Get the video ready.
- Play the video.
- Moon Seong Ho.
We captured this photo when
he was just leaving the hospital.
Please take a good look
at the man on the screen.
This man, Moon Seong Ho, brutally
murdered a woman eight years ago...
and was locked up
at the National Forensic Hospital.
- Yes. I see.
- His height is 180cm.
- And he has a slim build.
- This is "News Live".
- And he has gray hair.
- Yes. Go on.
- Close up on his wrist injury.
- As for a distinctive feature,
he has an old scar
on the left side of his neck.
And he also has a recent injury
on this left wrist.
It's been confirmed that
his mental state is very unstable.
In order to catch
the prisoner swiftly,
getting cooperation from the public
is the most important.
Please take the initiative
to call us with any reports.
- Hello? Yes.
- Hello.
- This is "News Live".
- Did you get it?
What's happening?
A lot of people are calling
the police and our TV station.
Answer them and give the police
any information we get.
Okay.
Hello? Yes. This is HBN News.
Ma'am, you have to answer that.
You need to answer it.
Hello, this is "News Live".
A murderer who brutally
murdered a woman...
escaped today.
He managed to escape
from our legal system.
And the man who inserted himself
among the people was smiling.
Will you watch him point his knife
at another innocent victim?
- Here.
- It's time for us...
- It's 2 dollars and 20 cents.
- to make it aware...
that Moon Seong Ho...
is nothing
but a shameless prisoner...
who won't be able to do anything.
I'd like to ask for your cooperation
and attention to the manhunt.
Excuse me.
I'll put them in a plastic bag.
This is all for today.
- Have a goodnight.
- Wait.
Excuse me!
We got a lot of reports,
but we didn't get anything
to confirm his whereabouts.
Nonetheless, a lot of people are
aware of his escape now.
We'll be able to catch him soon.
Thank you.
You can thank me
after you catch him.
Call me if there's progress.
Okay, sure.
You did very well with today's news.
The more I think about it,
the more frustrating it seems.
We could have gotten him
if they were a few minutes faster.
We need to lock him up
before he harms innocent people.
Why is our world filled
with crazy and bad people?
Goodness. It's horrible.
Thanks.
Thank you.
Please pour me one too.
I guess something is up.
A lot has happened.
Too many things have happened.
That's the problem.
Did you have a fight with Ha Jin?
No. It's not that.
Yes, that's it.
Actually,
there's a favor...
I need to ask you
and confess something to you.
A confession? What confession?
The girl I used to date before...
died because of Moon Seong Ho.
What?
That's why...
I can't tell you that today's news
was completely professional.
I'm sorry.
But until Moon Seong Ho
gets arrested,
I want to continue receiving calls.
Please let me do that.
My gosh.
How...
Yes, Tae Eun.
Did you watch the news?
Are you worried
because Moon Seong Ho escaped?
I'm sorry, Jeong Hoon.
Why are you sorry?
Moon Seong Ho escaped...
because of my dad.
My dad went to see him
as an outpatient.
And he held my dad hostage.
Is he hurt badly?
No, he's okay.
That's a relief.
I didn't know
your dad was involved in this.
Will you be okay?
According to my dad, he'll probably
go to you or Ha Jin.
Actually, he already did.
Who? Ha Jin?
Yes.
That jerk showed up
in front of Ha Jin.
Please don't tell me she did.
She did.
Her memories came back.
She's in a lot of pain
and confusion.
Does she know
about you and Seo Yeon too?
Yes.
I want to run over to see her
and stay by her side,
but I'd be asking for too much
if I do that right now.
I'd be way too selfish.
It must be tormenting for her
to see me right now,
so I'm just waiting.
I thought time is
what she needs the most right now.
I knew this would happen in the end.
Who have I been blaming for this?
We can't do this.
Why not?
We'll regret it.
I won't regret anything.
You will.
You might regret this
more than I would.
I finally learned
everything about you now.
But I don't know what to do.
I can't even bear to stand here
and look at you right now.
(Ha Jin)
Yes, Ha Jin.
It's really great weather.
Have you been well?
Are you feeling all right?
(Episode 26)
I'm feeling okay.
As you can see, I'm doing well.
I wanted to see you
because I had to tell you something.
I thought about this a lot
and came to this decision,
so I hope
you could respect my decision.
Let's go back to the time...
when we weren't in any relationship,
no, when we didn't know each other.
It's not your fault.
It's just that
I can't stay by your side.
So let's stop here.
No.
I can't do that.
I told you.
I love you very much.
I know it'll be really tough.
I know that you'll need time.
So let's bear through this together.
I don't want to.
I don't want to be a bad person.
What makes you a bad person?
Because of me, Seo Yeon...
Why is that because of you?
Her stalker is the one at fault,
not you.
You were only deceived too.
You are...
just another victim
who lost a precious friend to him.
You knew?
Yet you stayed by my side?
No one has any right to blame you.
So please don't be hard on yourself.
Don't forgive me that easily.
That makes me feel
even sorrier for you...
and for Seo Yeon.
Don't worry about me anymore.
I can't make any rash decisions now.
I feel way too sorry for you
to do anything like that.
I'll be very busy from now on.
I probably can't stop myself
from thinking about you,
but I'll try my best.
So let's stop here.
Ha Jin.
You promised...
never to say goodbye.
I'm sorry.
I don't think I can keep my promise.
Ms. Park, you're here.
Where's Ha Jin?
She's in her room,
but she must be asleep.
She has been pretty quiet.
Is she all right?
I'm not sure.
She looks fine on the outside,
but that makes me feel
even more nervous.
I feel so bad for our dear Ha Jin.
I'm sorry we ended up
making you worried too.
Don't be sorry.
It's not like
I didn't know about this.
You already told me everything
about Ha Jin from the beginning.
That's when I realized
how much you love her...
and how considerate you are.
You said you wanted her to be happy,
and you asked me
to make her into an actress...
because she's a person
who shines very brightly.
Thank you so much
for accepting her back then.
Don't say that.
I'm thankful for her.
I never thought of you two...
just as my business partners.
You seem like my daughters,
so I'm always worried about you.
You two are both way too kind.
I thought you were asleep.
You're here, Ms. Park.
Hey, Ha Jin.
I brought some side dishes.
Ms. Park,
I have a favor to ask of you.
Do you want to get some rest?
Yes, you probably should
get some rest for a while.
I'll keep your drama schedule,
but I'll drop everything else.
Can you get me more work?
I want to be extremely busy...
to not think of anything else.
We look so good.
This is unfair.
Why am I always home alone?
There you go again.
You're not picking up.
What time is it?
(Jo Il Kwon)
I'm in front of your house.
I'll be waiting until you come out.
Why did you come all the way here?
What took you so long?
I thought you weren't coming.
Did I do something wrong?
If I did, tell me.
I promise I can change.
They say people don't change easily,
but I'm different.
I can change very easily.
What are you talking about?
You did nothing wrong.
Then...
If you've developed feelings
for someone else...
Don't go. I'll do better.
I'll work out much more.
It's not that.
Then what's wrong?
You neither pick up my calls
nor reply to my texts.
You say you're too busy to meet.
About that...
I'm sorry.
Do you not like me anymore?
That's definitely not true.
Something just...
came up.
I had no idea.
Is everything okay?
She's fine. She's smiling again.
She's working hard as well.
But I feel anxious.
I'm afraid she's crying
on the inside.
No. I'm asking about you.
Are you okay?
What?
It must've been tough.
I'm fine. Ha Jin's the one
who had it rough.
My suffering is nothing
compared to hers.
I'm sure she and Jeong Hoon
are both having a rough time.
But I'm worried about you the most.
You matter the most to me.
You must've kept this
all to yourself up until now.
I'm sure you were suffering.
Tell me whenever you're going
through a rough patch.
I want to be there for you.
Okay.
Shall we cheer ourselves up
with something tasty?
I'm not hungry.
I'm not craving anything.
Then shall we have a drink,
your favorite?
You can't even drink well.
No, thanks.
This won't do. Follow me.
- Why?
- Hurry up.
- Where are we going?
- Just follow me.
This is the best thing you can do
when you feel frustrated.
Shout until your throat gives out.
- What?
- Come on.
Look straight ahead
and shout for 10 seconds!
I can't do it.
Do it. It's really effective.
Ready, set, go.
What was that?
Were you calling out for someone?
Where's all that power you had
when you subdued me? Summon that.
- Okay?
- All right.
Okay. Let's do it once more.
Ready, set, go.
Jo Il Kwon! You're an idiot!
Why am I an idiot?
You're an even bigger idiot
than I am!
- This is nice.
- Yes, it is.
(You will understand me as well.)
(You should lose someone you love.)
(Don't kid yourself.)
(You will be punished.)
("Moon Seong Ho Has Run Away,
Possibility of Another Victim")
(Wanted: Escaped Prisoner)
Hello, Father.
Are you busy?
I can talk.
I'm sorry about last time.
Don't drink too much.
You should take care of your body.
Okay. Are you all right?
Yes.
I'd like to meet...
your girlfriend.
Can you make some time?
Okay.
I'll call you again. Goodbye.
What is this for?
You seem exhausted these days.
It's on me.
Thanks.
How is everything with Ha Kyung?
It's great.
But we rarely meet these days,
thanks to Ha Jin.
Right.
Anyway, thanks.
No problem.
1, 2. Good. 1, 2.
That's good. 1, 2.
Good.
Great.
All right, then.
Let's change her clothes.
Don't I seem too stiff?
Should I smile?
No, I like it.
You look relaxed and charismatic.
Can I see the previous photos?
Okay.
Can I have some water?
You haven't eaten anything.
Do you want some snacks?
Later.
Yu Jin, can I see the photos
you took back there?
Here you go.
That was quick.
I'd like to change the concept
and incorporate some items.
What do you think?
Since I'm a news anchor,
should I sit down?
That's brilliant.
You seem to really love your role.
I do.
- Okay. Please prepare a chair.
- Yes, ma'am.
1, 2.
(It's chilly today.
Make sure to dress warmly.)
(My feelings will never change.
I'll be waiting for you.)
(Is everything all right?
I miss you.)
Let me see all the calls
we got so far.
This is it.
Okay. Thank you.
Ha Jin, we're going home.
I want to work out.
Drop me off, and you can go.
You've been working
since the morning.
Don't overwork yourself.
Get some rest.
I'll sleep better
once I run for a bit.
Okay.
(Doctor Yoo)
Come on.
- Hello.
- My gosh, Anchor Lee.
Any update on Moon Seong Ho?
He's still on the run.
I'm not sure if that jerk knows
where we're searching...
or if he's just getting lucky
when he's moving around.
But we're still pursuing him.
I'm sure it will
mentally pressure him.
Okay. Right.
He might be quiet now,
but we don't know what he might do.
Right. So we must try harder
to catch him, right?
We'll call you if we get a lead.
- Okay.
- Bye.
You're early.
Hi.
You wanted to see me
because you were worried, right?
I'm sorry.
Why are you sorry?
You didn't give me these memories.
These were my memories,
to begin with.
I just found my place now.
I'm fine. Don't worry.
But you're not okay.
If it's hard, you can say it is.
Cry if you want to.
That way, people around you
can comfort you. That way,
I won't be a fool like before...
and finally do something for you.
I'm really okay, Doctor Yoo.
I'm handling it.
Are you trying your best
to endure this pain...
out of guilt...
or for the sake of Jeong Hoon?
When you came to me a while ago...
and told me that you had dreams
about your past,
to be honest, I was very worried...
in case you got your memories back.
So I told Jeong Hoon
to break up with you.
I said you might be remembering
your past because he was with you.
So I told him to stop.
But Jeong Hoon told me...
that he didn't want to hide
because he was scared.
Even if you get your memories back
and have a hard time,
he said he wanted
to stay by your side.
Is that what Anchor Lee said?
Yes.
I've been his friend
for a very long time.
I've never seen him
so determined like that day.
I know that...
it took a lot of courage
for him to decide that.
Ha Jin,
don't get scared and hide.
Be courageous.
She's an anchor in the drama,
so going with
a sophisticated career woman...
might be a win-win for both of us.
Secret tips on how to take care of
yourself from a career woman.
I like it.
I think we settled on the concept.
Once you give us the draft,
we'll check it and call you.
Okay. Let's do that.
Can you also think
about sponsorships for the drama?
Ha Jin, you're so invested
in this drama.
This drama is all I have right now.
Are you sure you want to cut it?
Won't you regret it?
The writer said
you could just tie it up neatly.
Since I'm going with a new image,
I want to do it right.
Isn't it better
with a visible change?
Yes, it is.
But it took so long
to grow your hair.
Can you reconsider?
I'll be okay. Please cut it.
Will this do?
No, that's too short.
No. We need to get an offer
for a shampoo commercial.
It's fine. Just cut it up to here.
Yes, Ms. Park.
What?
What do you mean
the drama might be canceled?
How...
We already did a read-through
and had a test photoshoot.
Why are they canceling it now?
I don't know the details.
The production company
and the TV station...
were negotiating
on the final terms.
And there was a dispute.
This is making me anxious.
- Hello.
Hi.
I'm sorry for asking you
to come all this way.
I thought it was better
to tell you the news in person.
We already did the read-through
and the test photoshoot.
What is this about?
We asked you to come in...
because I have unfortunate news.
It seems like...
this drama will be canceled.
- Pardon?
- I mean,
this is different
from postponing the shoot.
How could you just cancel
a project like this?
We invested all of our time
and energy into this drama.
Right. I'm sorry.
We were negotiating
on the final terms.
When a new management team
took over the company,
the negotiation fell through.
The scale of the drama is quite big
as it is Writer Hwang's drama.
And it was one of the blockbusters
for the year.
But it is the company's decision...
that we cannot proceed
with high-risk factors.
Then, does it mean this drama can
air on a different TV channel?
Well,
the terms of Writer Hwang's contract
are quite complicated.
This drama can only air on HBN.
On top of that,
the current production company...
is facing a lot of trouble...
regarding the crew's wages
of the previous project.
What is this?
What's going on?
Excuse me, Ha Jin.
I heard the production of the drama
will be halted. Is this true?
I heard it's halted because of...
the high appearance fees
of some actors and actresses.
Are you one of them, Ha Jin?
She's a victim too.
- Ha Jin, please give us a comment.
- Give us a comment.
Try to comfort her.
She's been pouring
all of her energy into this drama.
Right. I don't know why things are
getting so hard for her.
("Production of 'Hello, Everyone'
Is Halted Due to a Budget Problem")
("Hello, Everyone")
Try again. This time,
pronounce them more clearly.
Now, say your line.
- Korean conglomerates...
- No.
I want you to enunciate
one at a time.
Square your shoulders.
Keep your back straight.
Hello, everyone.
This is the 9 p.m. news.
Ha Jin.
Where did she go?
("The Production of Yeo Ha Jin's
'Hello, Everyone' Gets Canceled")
Yes, Ha Kyung.
Anchor Lee, are you with Ha Jin?
No, why? Is something going on?
She's suddenly gone,
and she left her phone at home.
What?
Since when?
Do you know anywhere
she could have gone to?
But I'll stop saying yes so easily
like I did back then.
I want you to be happy.
So I'll stop saying goodbye to you.
Where on earth are you?
Ha Jin.
Where have you been?
I've been worried sick.
At the least,
you should have told Ha Kyung.
Anchor Lee,
don't you hate me?
Why would I hate you?
There is no reason
for me to hate you.
No.
I'm a really bad person.
Ha Jin.
Do you know what I thought about
as I sat here waiting for you?
I'm the one who broke up with you,
but I missed you to death.
I couldn't even breathe...
to think I'll never see you again.
May I just stay by your side?