(Episode 27)
Ha Jin.
Where have you been?
I've been worried sick.
At the least,
you should have told Ha Kyung.
Anchor Lee,
don't you hate me?
Ha Jin.
I'm the one who broke up with you,
but I missed you to death.
I couldn't even breathe...
to think I'll never see you again.
May I just stay by your side?
(Find Me in Your Memory)
You should get changed into these.
How long were you
sitting out in the rain?
What if you really catch a cold?
Here.
I'm sorry.
I must've been out of my mind.
I didn't mean what I just said.
Please pretend like
you didn't hear it.
Please excuse me.
You said you wanted to
stay by my side.
Are you sure you didn't mean that?
No. I didn't mean it.
All right.
I understand.
But do get changed...
and grab a cup of hot tea
before you go.
Then I'll pretend like
I didn't hear you.
You broke all of our promises...
and had me worried all day long.
So you can do this much for me.
Ha Jin.
Come out
if you're done getting changed.
I changed my mind too.
I can't let you go
after a cup of tea,
so eat this before you go.
Take a seat. Come on.
I'm not sure if it's any good
because I had to make it in a hurry.
Here.
Drink that
and take your time to eat.
You should get changed.
You might end up
catching a cold too.
I'm fine.
You're making me feel uncomfortable.
You should go get changed.
No, I don't want to get changed.
Why not?
I'm afraid you might leave
while I get changed.
You told me to finish this
before I go.
Go get changed.
You must be upset about your drama.
You prepared so much for it.
Yes.
I'm sure you'll find
another great work soon. Cheer up.
Thank you.
Take your time and eat.
I'll take you home when you're done.
I'm fine. I can call Ha Kyung...
or take a taxi.
I already called her
and told her I'm with you.
I thought she'd be worried.
It's late and raining.
If I let you go alone
after telling her that I'm with you,
Ha Kyung will think
I'm completely irresponsible.
That's why I have to take you home.
Go home safely.
I'll return your clothes
through Ha Kyung.
I'm the one who's bad, not you.
I knew everything,
but I didn't want to lose you
and got selfish.
I couldn't go on without you.
So you don't have to try hard.
I'll be the bad person.
Ha Jin!
Do you know how much I was worried?
I'm sorry.
Goodbye, Anchor Lee.
Let's go inside.
I found this out front,
so I brought it in.
I think you threw these out
by mistake.
I threw away the scripts.
But you can throw these away again
if you want to.
(Anchor Lee)
What is it?
I came for my long sleeves.
Your long sleeves?
Yes. The one you wore last night.
I have to wear it today.
If today's not the best time,
I can come by tomorrow.
No, that's okay. Hold on.
Is it delivery?
No, it's Anchor Lee.
He's here? Why?
He wants the clothes
I wore yesterday.
What?
Here you go.
Thanks. I forgot
I had to wear it today.
Did you sleep well?
Yes.
Did you have breakfast?
Not yet.
Don't skip your meals.
Goodbye.
Have some macarons.
What's gotten into you?
You've never offered me sweets.
It's still early in the morning.
You can have two.
You feel sorry for me
since the drama fell through, right?
Don't be ridiculous.
You're going to work
on something even better.
I heard there's a pile of scripts
this high at the office.
Are you going...
to break up with him?
I already did.
I know that's not what you want.
I know you like him a lot.
Didn't you dive into work
because you were in pain?
I'm going to endure it.
I have to.
I can't be with him.
I don't deserve him.
Did you receive any tip-offs
on Moon Seong Ho?
Yes, a few.
But they turned out to be false.
They mistook others for him.
I thought this would be easy,
but he's more tenacious
than I thought.
Let me know every time
you receive new calls.
Okay. I'll do that.
What is this shopping bag?
It's just an excuse to see her face.
What?
Ha Kyung.
Hello.
I'm sorry for calling
out of the blue.
It's fine. What is it?
There's no one
more important to me...
than my sister.
But she's in a lot of pain
right now.
She didn't break up with you
because she wanted to.
It's all because of Seo Yeon.
She feels guilty.
I know.
You're not going
to let her go, right?
I can't.
She's the most important person
to me as well.
Seeing how you came
all the way here to tell me this,
I guess it's safe to say
that you're on my side.
I'm glad to have an ally.
Chul.
Hello.
Did you have lunch?
Yes, I did.
Let's go.
Here you go.
Why are there so many?
These are only a few
that I picked out last night.
Everyone has been sending in
their scripts...
ever since they found out
that our drama flopped.
All these people want you.
So don't you worry about a thing,
and let's pick a new one.
- Okay.
- First, read these.
This is from Director Song Min Seok.
It's a movie script.
The female lead is a reporter.
And this one is
from Writer Kim Soo Ji.
This will be aired
during the first half of next year.
It was quite amusing.
The rest of them are
also quite nice.
Thank you.
We're in no rush.
Take your time to read them all.
Okay.
She's right.
Your opinion matters the most.
We should hit the jackpot once more.
I'd love that.
(Advertising Campaign - Timetable)
(Advertising Campaign - Concept)
Ha Jin, I don't think
the shooting will take too long.
You just need to say something.
I didn't know there would be others.
Who else has done this?
I'm not sure. But since it's a PSA,
I'm sure many have.
Excuse me.
We have a bit of free time.
If you'd like, you can meet
the puppies right now.
It'd make the shooting easier
if you guys become close.
Sure. Let's go.
Okay.
What? Is Jeong Hoon not here yet?
How dare he slack off?
Let him be.
He'll be running late today.
Why? Did something happen again?
Not really.
I'm serious. He has something else
to take care of.
What else does he have to do
other than the news?
He couldn't be receiving
another award without my knowing.
Why are you keeping me in the dark?
Don't shout at me. We're not home.
Hey. Don't call him.
Gosh, I'm so irritated.
I'm going to call him. Darn it.
Hey.
Why are you here?
To film. I'm filming
the same advertisement as you are.
You're shooting an advertisement?
Yes. I liked what
they're trying to achieve.
And I really love puppies.
Aren't they so pretty?
I'll be filming with them,
so we should become close.
This one's Bori. This one's Choco.
And this white one is Coco.
I don't know why people abandon
such beautiful animals.
Did you have lunch?
If not, do you want to join me?
I bought some sandwiches.
No, that's fine.
I don't want to eat alone.
I feel awkward here,
and there's no one I know.
Please?
Have some.
It's bacon and egg sandwich
and honey black tea.
What is it? Do you not like them?
Ha Kyung told me
that you like this sandwich.
Why are you doing this?
Why do you keep doing things
that are unlike you?
Because I like you, miss you,
and want to spend time with you.
I told you that I was going to be
the bad one.
So just stay where you are.
I'll come to you.
Ha Jin, they'll begin now.
Okay.
I should go.
Every year, 100,000 dogs...
roam the streets on empty stomachs
while trembling in fear...
or become euthanized.
Please give these precious animals
your love.
The most heartwarming way
of creating a family is...
by adopting an abandoned dog.
Cut. Okay. That was great.
Thank you.
- Let's move onto the next scene.
- Yes, sir.
Okay.
You looked so pretty.
I'm sorry for this sudden request.
But how about we film...
you two together?
Sure, that's fine with me.
That's fine.
That's great. I was feeling awkward
about doing it alone.
Okay, let's do that.
It's quite simple,
so let me explain.
Then,
we'll start filming right away.
Okay? Good.
All right. Next.
I'm so nervous. What were the lines?
"Give them a hug. Love them."
"Welcome these precious dogs
into your family."
Right.
"Give them a hug. Love them."
If I knew that I would have lines,
I should have thought a bit more
before accepting it.
Someone once scolded me...
for doing an awful job
with reading lines.
I'm scared to deliver my lines.
Okay.
- Hello.
- Hey.
Goodness, you two
make such a nice couple.
You guys look like a real family.
Looking good!
We'll start now.
Ready.
Action.
Give them a hug.
Love them.
Welcome these precious dogs
into your family.
Okay. Cut!
Ha Kyung. I'm sick.
I'm coming down with a cold.
And I have a fever.
I'm here.
Is it serious?
Yes.
Let me see.
You don't have a fever.
No. I have a fever.
You won't know if you just
put your hand on my forehead.
You have to put
your forehead on mine.
My forehead?
See? I'm burning up.
You're not sick, right?
No.
I've been sick today.
But when you said you were coming,
strangely, I started to recover.
I knew it. You're not sick.
No, I'm sick.
I'm serious. I've been sick.
Are you sure you're okay now?
Any other symptoms?
- Right here.
- Gosh.
I bought some medicine and porridge.
Take them if you still feel sick.
Are you leaving already?
Can you stay for two more hours?
No, just an hour.
Please? Just an hour. Please.
My goodness. It's so scary.
You have to go forward.
- Go, go.
- No!
Don't touch me.
Don't touch me. I'm serious.
Don't do that.
Darn it.
Do you think it's funny?
- I'm hungry.
- All of a sudden?
I bought some new stuff
from the convenience store.
Do you want to try it?
All right. Let's eat.
- Let's play a game.
- What game?
We'll ask each other a question.
The one who can't answer them
in five seconds...
will have to eat as much as
the other person gives.
Are you sure you can handle it?
I heard it's really spicy.
I can just answer
your questions then.
Sounds good. I can answer
anything you ask me.
I'll go first.
Since when...
did you start
having feelings for me?
When I learned jujitsu from you
for the first time.
You were so cool.
Is that so?
What about you?
When you tied my hair
at the hospital...
Wait. Then, you liked me first.
That's not it. It was after that.
I don't think so.
It was after that.
After we worked out together.
You liked me before that,
didn't you?
I said no.
It was after that.
Okay, fine.
I'll play along.
It's your turn to ask a question.
How many guys did you date so far?
So far?
I'm counting now.
5, 4, 3,
2, 1. Time's up.
What about you?
Me? I had...
5, 4, 3, 2, 1. Time's up.
Come on. What was that?
You counted too fast.
Then, answer me.
No. I'll just eat it.
Fine. Let's just eat it.
We should eat this together.
We'll help ourselves.
Hey, this got soggy.
It's better than I thought.
It's not spicy.
Water!
(New message, Anchor Lee)
I was taking photos of Coco,
but you look good in the photos too.
So I'm sending some to you.
Because I like you, miss you,
and want to spend time with you.
(Inbox)
He just checked in.
He sort of matches the descriptions.
Please don't disclose
my personal information.
(A tip on Moon Seong Ho, Forward)
Yes, Detective. Please check
the email I just sent you.
Okay.
- Jo Il Kwon.
- Yes?
Get ready for coverage
and come with me.
Now?
Hello. What about Moon Seong Ho?
When another guest tried to call it
in after recognizing him,
he attacked the guest and ran away.
We're searching the area now.
What about the victim?
Is the victim okay?
Yes. It's not a severe injury.
That's a relief.
We were a step late.
Can we report from the scene?
Yes. I'll set it up for you.
Thank you.
A while ago, an inmate named
Moon Seong Ho...
who was incarcerated
at the National Forensic Hospital...
ran away from the hospital
when he was being treated.
And we have received a report
that he was sighted at a motel.
Did you find any leads?
When he was running away,
he dropped this journal.
This is what it said on it.
He just wrote down
some nonsense on it.
I don't think this will
give us any leads.
I see.
How will the investigation
move forward now?
He attacked a civilian on the run.
We must dial it up a notch.
We'll inspect at the checkpoints
more aggressively.
And we'll launch
an extensive search.
We should keep asking
for any tip-offs.
These tip-offs are
definitely getting to him.
Yes. I ask for your cooperation.
Sure.
My father will be back soon.
I'll wait inside.
Do you want any beverages?
It's okay.
Right.
You must be busy
with my father's work these days.
When he focuses on something,
he goes all the way.
I see. Are you talking about
the book he's about to publish?
It's fine.
I only research
to gather information.
I see. Is that so?
Right. Don't mind me.
You can go back to your work.
All right, then.
("The Man Who Cannot Forget")
When did I give you permission...
to go through my stuff in my office?
I don't need to talk to you. Leave.
No.
You must explain to me what that is.
I said I don't need to talk to you.
Is this it?
Is this why you've been spying
on Jeong Hoon?
And you even went to a murderer
to ask about him.
Did you do all that
because of a book?
Have I been too lenient with you?
How dare you scold me about my book?
This is my life, my achievement,
and my entire research.
This is Jeong Hoon's life.
Even if you were his doctor,
you don't have any right...
to disclose everything about him
to the world!
If it weren't for my help,
he wouldn't have been able
to live a normal life.
No, he probably couldn't bear
the weight of his memories...
and could have died already.
You already know
he can enjoy his life now...
thanks to the result of my research!
I know him the best.
If he continues to do this,
he'll make everyone's life painful.
Yeo Ha Jin knows everything now,
so she'll stay away from him too.
What do you mean?
What do you mean, she knows?
I told her more
about Jeong Hoon's condition.
I asked if it's okay for him
to never forget about Seo Yeon.
There's no use in holding out
for the sake of love or whatever.
Nothing will change.
That's what
Jeong Hoon's disease does.
He'll never get over Seo Yeon,
who's dead now.
He'll live forever...
in that pain. That's his fate.
What are you doing? How dare you?
What's with those eyes?
I'm devastated that my father is
someone who's this low.
What?
Once this book gets published,
everyone will look at you
like how I'm looking at you now,
as an immoral scholar...
who treated his patients like
a lab animal for your research.
So you need to stop here!
How dare you do this?
Have you really gone insane?
If you won't stop,
I'll make you stop.
Wait and see.
That little...
What do you mean...
we can't publish
Professor Yoo's book?
I'm the current doctor
of that patient.
I found my medical records
cited in that book.
You do know that you'll be liable...
for illegal leakage or citation
of medical records, don't you?
Pardon?
I never provided my medical records,
and I do not plan on doing so.
If you decide to push ahead
with the publication,
I will take the legal measure
right away.
Wait,
of all people,
this is your father's book.
No.
He may be my father,
but nothing will change.
I'll assume that you have understood
what I said.
Please excuse me.
Is that what Tae Eun said?
All right.
Goodnight. Sweet dreams.
You too.
Hey, it's me.
You don't go to work today, right?
What's this chair?
Did you make it?
Yes.
It's a present.
Why did you
suddenly bring a present?
Thank you.
Sure.
Have you had lunch?
If you haven't,
you should stay for a meal.
I'll have a glass of water.
Sure.
Here.
Is everything all right?
Jeong Hoon.
I remember how I locked you up
in that closet as a child.
I am sorry...
for what I did back then.
I know I hurt you deeply,
and that you'll never forget.
I'm truly sorry.
You should get back to work.
Father.
I love this chair.
Thank you.
From now on,
this chair will be my memory of you.
I'm going to try
to let go of my past from now on.
Moon Seong Ho?
You must've been
dying to hear from me.
Where are you?
That's not it.
You shouldn't ask for my location.
You need to ask me
what I'm about to do.
That's the essence.
What do you want?
Yes, I like that question.
What do I want?
My eternal love with Seo Yeon.
I'll prove it to you.
The number you reached
cannot take any calls.
Yes, Detective.
This is Lee Jeong Hoon.
I just received a call
from Moon Seong Ho.
It seemed like a payphone.
Can you find the location?
(The late Jung Seo Yeon)
I'm too late, aren't I?
I'm sorry for leaving you alone.
(The late Jung Seo Yeon)
Yes, Detective.
I found the location
of Moon's cell phone.
Where is it?
It's near Inho-dong in Paju.
Does that ring a bell?
Did you do this?
You came faster than I had expected.
You're really good
at catching onto my hints.
If I was a second too late,
I may have not been able
to bring Seo Yeon with me.
Don't you think so?
Why are you doing this?
Am I not the one
you want to get rid of?
Yes. You're right.
I'll come to you. Tell me where.
I can go right away.
Are you worried?
Do you think I might harm
Yeo Ha Jin?
Shut it and tell me where you are.
Mr. Lee.
Be quiet and wait.
I'll call you again.
Ha Kyung, are you with Ha Jin?
Yes, we're
at the broadcasting station.
She has a meeting regarding a drama.
You're at the broadcasting station?
You had to go through security
to get to the office, right?
You're right.
Can you wait there
after the meeting ends?
I have something to say to her.
I thought you're not working today
since it's the weekend.
No, I'm just about to leave.
Don't go outside the building.
Make sure to stay inside.
I'll call you when I'm almost there.
Okay.
Thank you.
Wait a little bit more.
We're almost there.
This was the last location
of his phone.
I'll look for him as well.
It's dangerous.
You should wait here.
He even stole her ashes
in order to lure me.
If I don't show up,
he'll hide once again.
No, it's too dangerous.
All right, let's look for him.
Let's go.
- Which channel are you on?
- Channel one, sir.
One? Okay.
- Hurry up.
- Yes, sir.
- All right.
- Where could he be?
Check that side.
- I'll check this area and go up.
- Okay.
I told you to wait for my call,
but you came here first.
You even brought some guests.
Sir, he's on the rooftop.
Watch carefully.
It's almost over.
It's been a long time.
What do you think about this place?
It seems familiar, right?
I couldn't think of a better place
than here to carry out my last task.
This is where Seo Yeon and I
will begin our love.
It was this place all along?
Is it locked?
Mr. Lee!
- Open up!
- Oh, no.
We should end this quickly.
- Mr. Lee!
- I want to see Seo Yeon...
as soon as possible.
You're insane.
- Hey, hey!
- Don't forget.
The one who'll be by her side...
is me, not you!
Mr. Lee!
Moon Seong Ho! Stop right there!
- Stop!
- Stop it!
- Drop your knife!
- Put it down!
- Don't come near.
- Drop that knife.
Don't come near me.
Calm down. Seong Ho.
Don't come near.
- Come down.
- Hey.
- Seong Ho.
- Come down.
Lee Jeong Hoon.
Don't forget.
I won. I did.
Seo Yeon.
I'm on my way.
He wanted me to wait
because he had something to say?
Yes.
Maybe he's driving.
He's not replying back.
You guys aren't up to anything,
are you?
Don't be ridiculous. Gosh.
You know what?
Let's be honest with each other.
I want you guys
to get back together.
When you're with him,
you seem at peace
like you did in the past.
I know you don't want to break up.
Aren't you happy with him?
How many times
do I need to tell you?
I can't be selfish about this.
Do you really think this is
the best solution for you guys?
Focus on what's most important
to you right now.
I think that's
the right thing to do.
But then again, I know I am
the most important person to you.
Oh, it's Anchor Lee.
I'll pick it up.
Hello?
(Restricted Area, Operation Room)
I was the one who called.
What happened?
You know Moon Seong Ho, the inmate
who escaped the hospital, right?
Mr. Lee was trying to catch him.
Is he in a critical situation?
They'll only know
once the surgery is over.
You should wait for now.
How did it go? How is he?
It went well.
Thank you.
He was bleeding a lot.
But thankfully,
the wound wasn't deep,
and his organs weren't damaged.
He'll be okay.
Then is everything all right?
Yes. He'll wake up
once the anesthesia wears off.
Don't worry. Goodbye.
Thank you.
- Thank you.
- No problem.
That's a relief.
Are you awake? Can you see me?
Am I dreaming right now?
You're with me and holding my hand.
How can you make a joke now?
You gave me a scare.
I guess I'm not dreaming
since you look really angry.
I wasn't angry.
I raised my voice
because I was happy.
I'm sorry for scaring you...
and making you wait.
You said you'd be the bad guy.
Bad guys don't apologize this often.
Wait. I'll get your doctor.
I don't want you to go anywhere.
I won't leave you here.
I should let them know
that you're awake.
I need you the most right now.
Can you bring
some comfortable clothes for me?
Will you stay with him all night?
Yes. I think
I need to stay with him.
I can't just leave him alone
when he's sick.
Come on. Just get me my clothes.
Okay.
(Intensive Care Unit)
When he fell,
his fifth cervical vertebra
was fractured...
and pressed on his central nerves.
Due to the nerve damage,
he's paralyzed from the neck down.
Due to the brain hemorrhage,
it's likely that he'll face
a speech impediment.
We were able to save his life,
but there's nothing
he can do by himself.
You can't even run away on your own.
Before you pay
for all of your crimes,
don't even think about dying.
You scared me when
you disappeared without telling me.
It's cold.
What are you doing up here?
I was just getting some air.
It was stuffy inside.
Even so, you must stay indoors.
Let's go.
Why are you staring at me like that?
Can you just accept it now?
You won't be able to bend my will.
Let's talk inside.
It's cold out here.
You can't catch a cold.
I'll go once you answer me.
I don't think I can do it yet.
But when I thought I might not
be able to see you again,
I was more scared of making...
the same mistake
and suffering from it...
for the rest of my life.
This must have been harder on you.
But you still mustered up
the courage for me.
You win.
Stop walking around.
You should go to sleep now.
Get home safely, Ha Jin.
I'm not leaving.
If I leave,
you'll walk around again.
I'll be watching you
the whole night.
I'll stay in the room. Don't worry.
Go home now. It's late.
No. I can't because
it makes me anxious.
There's no place to stay.
It's uncomfortable for you.
The doctor said you needed to rest
to recover. Lie down.
Now.
I don't think I can sleep when
you're staring at me like that.
I'll go to sleep
if you answer my question.
Okay. I'll answer it.
What is it?
Did you miss me?
I missed you like crazy.
I'll pass. Next question.
The text messages I sent...
Did you read them
before ignoring them...
or did you not read them at all?
Well, that's...
Just go to sleep. If you keep
talking, you won't get sleepy.
Close your eyes.
Go to sleep now.
I'm serious. Sleep now.
Okay.
I think I'm getting sleepy...
because you're covering my eyes.
Right?
Goodnight.
The defendant was instigated
by Ji Hyun Geun,
Yeo Ha Jin's stalker,
to stalk the actress...
and to secretly take photos.
He used his position
as a reporter...
and ended up blackmailing
the actress.
But I will accept his argument...
that he wasn't aware his photos
could be used...
in criminal activities,
I sentence the defendant...
2 years in prison
or 3 years on probation.
Hey, it's me. Mr. Hwang.
I just wanted to thank you
for introducing me to a good lawyer.
I need to buy you a drink.
When are you free?
Here you go.
That looks good.
I was so shocked when
I heard Jeong Hoon got stabbed.
My heart is still beating
like crazy.
I'm relieved that
it's not a severe injury.
And he's recovering quickly too.
Right. And Ha Jin is with him too.
Things will work out
for them, right?
Right?
I want my sister to just think
about her own happiness.
You did well.
I didn't do much.
- Let's eat.
- Okay.
Here.
By the way, we played
a game a few days ago.
- Eating the spicy ramyeon.
- Yes. What about it?
I want you to answer
the question you didn't answer.
Did you date a lot of men?
Or did you just date a few?
Are you that curious about that?
Yes.
I'll tell you
if you tell me your answer.
Fine. Let's say it at the same time.
Sure.
In 1, 2, 3.
- A lot.
- Not a lot...
- You didn't date a lot?
- A lot of women?
How many women did you date?
About 4 or 5?
What do you mean by that?
I bet it's over 5. Is it over 10?
No. I'm serious.
How many men did you date then?
I didn't date a lot of men.
What is it? How many is it?
I can't be your first.
It's okay. Just tell me.
Wait. Am I really
your first boyfriend?
No!
As if!
Let's stop talking about this.
My gosh, you're so cute!
Fine, yes. It's in the past.
Let's move on.
What's important is
our present, isn't it?
Why? Are you sulking?
It's more than 10, isn't it?
No way. Come here.
Open your mouth. Here.
Gosh, you're eating so well.
Are you sure you can do this?
Don't you trust me?
I'll do just as you told me earlier.
Yes, that's true,
but it's pretty tough...
Quiet.
- I'll do it.
- One second.
Why? Mouth.
I think I have a knack for this.
Are you busy, Director Choi?
How does some Americano sound?
Sounds great.
Why do they make you work so hard
that you can't even go for lunch?
I'm almost finished.
I was just getting thirsty.
- Thanks.
- I knew you'd be thirsty.
My gosh.
Gosh, this is great.
What's this?
This? It's a book.
It seemed
very uncanny and interesting.
You read books?
What are you talking about?
I was once called a bookworm.
I've known you for about 30 years,
but this is unheard of.
Goodness.
What's it about?
- Honey.
- What?
Do you know
what hyperthymesia is?
- What?
- It's someone who remembers...
everything about their life,
all 365 days in a year.
There's someone
who has that condition in Korea.
Really?
Yes. This book is about that person.
Don't you think it'll be uncanny
to meet them in real life?
What's so uncanny about that?
I'm sure it's someone
who just remembers well.
This person is apparently an anchor,
and he seems
very similar to Jeong Hoon.
He has a great memory too.
Does Jeong Hoon look like
someone with this disease?
Yes, well,
I know he's good at his job,
but he's way too normal and rude
to have a condition like this.
So who could it be?
Is it someone at our station?
I'm so curious. I'm dying to know.
It's driving me crazy.
Why are you curious about that?
Stop asking a useless question
and get ready for the news.
Our coffee date is finished.
The end.
Get up. Come on, get up.
Get up and go. Go now.
Yes, of course.
I'll do as you say, Director Choi.
Hey, wait.
Can you leave that book here?
Let me read it.
See? Don't you get curious too?
I haven't finished it yet,
so read it quickly and give it back.
Thanks.
Gosh.
Keep it up.
Okay.
"The Man Who Cannot Forget"?
Are you sure you're okay?
I'm fine.
The doctor said
I can carry out my everyday life.
But don't work too hard.
If you have to carry something heavy
or do something tough,
make someone else do it.
I won't have to do
anything like that.
But still. You never know.
All right.
This is great.
What is?
To have you worry about me.
I'll do it so much from now on that
you'll get sick of it. Be ready.
I'll look forward to it.
I'm almost at work.
I'll call you later.
Okay. Be careful.
You really have to be careful.
Okay.
- Is that him?
- I don't think that's him.
It's Anchor Lee Jeong Hoon!
Anchor Lee, have you read the book
titled "The Man Who Cannot Forget"?
Are you the man of this book?
Is it true that
you suffer from hyperthymesia?
Tell us something.
- Say something.
- How are you feeling?
- Excuse me.
- Say something!
- Please say something.
- Anchor Lee!
Did you know that
your story will get published?
- Anchor Lee!
- Is this you?
- What's your take on this?
- Say something!
- Anchor Lee!
- Tell us something!
- Say something!
- Anchor Lee!
Hey, Lee Jeong Hoon!
I picked up a huge scoop.
Don't you want to know what it is?
(Find Me in Your Memory)
Now that everyone knows,
I'm a bit scared of their reactions.
Did you miss me?
Of course, I did.
Okay, you pass.
Did you read the book?
Is that why you prepared this
to cheer me up?
People forget
much faster than you think.
So I don't want you to be
in too much pain.
I found a new story.
A woman he loved died,
then he fell in love with
her best friend all over again.
Why do they have to make
such a big deal out of this?
I didn't think
it would blow up like this.
It could be tougher than
what we expected,
but let's live through this
like we did today.