(Episode 21)
Welcome home, girls.
Gosh, Ms. Park.
This is why you told us
to come an hour later.
Did you prepare all these yourself?
I just blew up a few balloons,
that's all.
Goodness, how many balloons
did you blow up?
Ha Jin, do you like it?
I love it.
Ms. Park, you must have taken
an interest in surprising people.
Wait till you go upstairs.
I redecorated everything
just in case...
something brings back bad memories.
Don't worry about that.
I already forgot everything.
What do you think?
It's so pretty.
I like this much better than before.
I'm glad.
I put in a bit of an effort.
Get some rest. I need to take this.
Are you sure you're okay?
Of course. There's no reason
for me not to be okay.
You should unpack and get some rest.
I need to rest too.
Okay.
Get some rest.
Ha Jin.
What's going on?
What's with that face?
- What is?
- You were making an odd face.
You were touching your lips and all.
When? I didn't do that.
You seem suspicious.
Very suspicious.
No, it's nothing. What is it?
Right. We're getting
some sandwiches.
- Do you want one?
- Yes, I do.
Okay. Bacon and egg?
Yes.
(Find Me in Your Memory)
What's the point of coming
to see me? It does nothing good.
You're only ruining my day.
What?
Did you want to see how frustrated
I was to be locked up here?
Too bad. I'm perfectly fine.
Ha Jin will come to me in the end...
once she finds out that you're
her best friend's boyfriend.
I'm here to tell you
there's nothing you can do in there.
Listen up.
First of all, you'll be in prison
a lot longer than you think.
I'll make that happen.
Who do you think you are?
No matter what you do,
I'll be released.
The law works that way.
There's no way
you can keep me here forever.
Breaking and entering,
special violence,
confinement, kidnapping...
Those crimes may get you
three years in prison at most,
maybe even less.
But do you really think that's all?
What are you trying to say?
What if you approached
Moon Seong Ho,
who was sentenced to life
for murder,
figured out his methods,
and tried to commit a copycat crime?
How will the law, the press,
and public opinion...
react to that?
I'm different from that murderer.
All I wanted to do was
tell Ha Jin the truth...
and vow our love.
Do you think
people will believe that?
That's just one of
those delusions...
lunatics like Moon Seong Ho
and you have.
No, that's not true.
Never!
Fine. You don't have to
either admit it...
or apologize for it.
Just watch your life
get destroyed in there.
Hello, Anchor Lee.
You were sleeping?
This stuffed animal you gave me
is really effective.
I hugged it for a second
and fell asleep right away.
I'm glad to hear that.
Did you get home safely?
Yes, I'm home now.
It's so nice to be back home.
Everything is finally over.
Are you on your way to work?
Yes, I am.
Go back to sleep then.
Hold on.
We can talk some more.
I've rested enough.
Can we meet today?
I really need your help
with my script.
The read-through is coming up.
All right.
But on weekdays,
I can only meet after the news.
Is that okay with you?
It'll be pretty late.
Don't worry, I'm a night owl.
Then shall we meet
after the news tonight?
I'll come to you.
Okay, let's do that.
Drive safe. See you later.
I don't have time for this.
Sandwiches are here...
What are you doing?
You're going somewhere?
I'm meeting Anchor Lee
for some practice later.
- When?
- After his news.
It's only 10 a.m.
You have 14 hours, and you're
already picking out an outfit?
I want to get a head start.
You're going to make a mess
for the next 14 hours, aren't you?
The thing is...
Come here.
What? What is it now?
It's happening for real.
What do you mean?
Anchor Lee and I are dating
for real now.
You are?
It's true.
Sure. Just don't go overboard
and get dumped later.
I'm sure of it. Believe me.
It's happening for real, I swear.
What are you doing with your lips?
What? What happened between you two?
You guys kissed?
That hurts!
That's what happened.
Are you in the lobby yet?
The cafe in the lobby has
amazing honey black tea.
I highly recommend it.
Get a cup on your way.
Have a nice day. See you later.
I almost forgot.
If you run into Mr. Kim,
please thank him for visiting me
in the hospital the other day.
(Please thank him for visiting me
in the hospital the other day.)
Gosh, this is unbelievable.
After all this wait,
you finally won his heart.
It'd be more accurate to say...
that Anchor Lee finally realized
his feelings.
So? Are you happy?
Yes, I really am.
Right, weren't you and Mr. Jo
going to work out together?
When are you starting?
Your shoulder is fine now.
We're starting today.
Be honest.
Is something going on
between you two?
What are you talking about?
He got dumped because
he's too weak, so I'm helping him.
Really?
I think you two would make
a cute couple. Too bad.
Don't be ridiculous.
Do you really think...
we'd make a cute couple?
He and I?
Yes, I do.
I see.
Well...
Why? What makes you think so?
You two have the ideal
height difference and all.
What? Why are you asking?
- I was just curious.
- Are you interested in him?
Don't be ridiculous.
- Why are you stuttering?
- It's not like that.
Your voice is shaking.
I said, no!
- Good morning.
Good morning, Anchor Lee.
Good morning.
You look like you're in a good mood.
I'm devastated.
What's wrong? Did something happen?
Because he switched you out
the other day,
he, you, and the director
will be disciplined.
Not only me but you two as well?
Unfortunately, yes.
The news still has to air,
so you and I will be fine.
But Director Choi will be suspended
until the disciplinary committee...
makes a decision.
She's been told to stay
out of his office from today.
What if she ends up getting fired?
But why the director?
I'm the one who is responsible for
what happened.
It doesn't make sense.
What do you mean,
it doesn't make sense?
We switched the anchor out without
reporting it to the higher-ups.
Also, this isn't only about
what happened that day.
Think of all the things
you've revealed...
on the news so far,
ignoring the higher-ups.
You've gotten on their wrong side.
This is just an excuse
to bring you down.
I'm sorry, Mr. Kim.
Where is Director Choi now?
Come in.
Director Choi.
Judging by your face,
I guess you heard the news.
It's no big deal.
Don't worry and go back to work.
I apologize.
For what?
For trying to save someone close
to you who got kidnapped?
Or is it because you left...
after only asking for my permission
instead of following protocol...
and asking everyone in management?
It was only a natural thing to do.
So why would you apologize?
I caused you and
the team manager trouble.
We switched the main anchor out
without any prior notice.
We should take responsibility
for that.
But that's it.
Don't read anything more into it.
I'll try to explain it
to the president in person.
Gosh, you talk too much.
Don't you trust me?
What are you talking about?
You know how much I look up to you.
Then just let it go
when I tell you everything's cool.
Also, consider yourself lucky
to have an amazing boss like me,
okay?
Besides, the disciplinary
committee's decision...
will come in 3 or 4 days
at the latest.
I think I'm going to take
this chance and take some time off.
So leave me alone and get out.
I'm sorry, Director Choi.
All right.
I love you, Director Choi.
Thanks.
Gosh, I've never had a break before.
I mean,
I rarely get to take a break.
Why am I reading the newspaper? Why?
Come on. Seriously.
Goodness.
Ha Jin, are you ready to go?
Don't tell me
that's what you're wearing.
Is it too much?
Yes, it is way too much.
It's like you're going...
to an awards ceremony.
I wanted to dress up
since it's our first date.
Date? It's not a date.
Isn't he helping you
with your lines?
That's the same thing.
I'll be professional while spending
time with him like a mature lady.
I'll get the best of both worlds.
I doubt that Anchor Lee
will agree with you.
- I should change, right?
- Of course.
You look like a mix of apples
and strawberries.
- I'll go change.
- Okay. Hurry.
Be careful.
Don't hurt yourself
on your first date with him.
Okay!
I want to go work out.
Make it quick.
No, be careful first.
Where is she?
Hey, Chul Woong.
Hey, have you seen Hee Sang?
I saw her just now on the rooftop
when I went up to smoke.
Where on earth is she?
She was right here.
There she is.
What? Is she crying?
Go and try to comfort her.
Sweetheart.
Why are you crying out here?
My gosh.
Why do your shoulders look so small
from the back?
You've been so strong for me,
so I have been taking the back seat.
Now, I'll take the burdens...
you've been shouldering.
Goodness,
it must have been tough on you.
Oh, poor you.
Darn it.
If the higher-ups give you a hard
time because of this incident,
you should just resign.
I'll be able to support you.
You've been working so hard for us,
so I'll take up your burdens now.
Don't let this ruin your mood.
Stop crying.
Sweetheart.
My gosh.
When did you get here? You should've
told me if you were here.
I did. I've been talking to you
all this time.
Really?
I probably didn't hear you
because of the earbuds.
My goodness. This is so funny.
I've been laughing so hard. Look.
I'm literally crying.
Were you watching this?
While shaking your shoulders?
I haven't seen this for a while,
so this is hilarious.
- It's so funny.
- My gosh, Chul Woong.
Look at you.
By the way,
did you come up here to find me?
Whatever!
How could you be watching
a variety show now?
You startled me.
What else could I do?
I have nothing to do.
And time is moving so slowly.
I need to entertain myself.
Fine, go ahead.
You should catch up
with all the shows...
you missed so far
now that you're suspended.
Good for you. This all worked out.
Shut it.
My goodness, my husband
sure makes me feel safe.
Darn it.
Try again. This time,
pronounce them more clearly.
Now, say your line.
Korean conglomerates...
No, I told you before.
I want you to enunciate
one at a time.
Okay. Enunciate.
Korean conglomerates.
- Now, say them together.
- Korean conglomerates.
That's good.
Let's move onto the next line.
The first half
of their recruiting program.
Pronounce the vowels 10 times again.
10 times?
Start.
Enunciate.
Slowly.
I did it. 10 times.
You're done?
Can we just use it
without permission?
I already got
the coach's permission.
We just have to clean up afterward.
Here. Go put this on.
Okay.
By the way, what are we doing here?
Jujitsu.
I've heard of it a lot.
But this isn't right, you know.
- What do you mean?
- I get that I'm a first-timer.
You know, there are
weight classes in fights.
Jujitsu isn't a form of fighting.
It's martial arts.
And this allows us to overcome
physical traits.
But still, this won't work.
I can't do this when I know
you won't be my match at all.
Where are you? You know?
I can't see you.
I told you this sport allows us
to overcome our physical traits.
You ought to listen to people
to the end.
Okay.
Okay?
Okay. Since it's your first day,
we'll stick to the basic moves.
The basic moves?
My back. My gosh.
Hold on a second.
I didn't start yet.
But it already hurts.
Hold on! Wait!
Tap out. I'm tapping.
Tap out.
By cutting down...
on their recruiting programs,
which were held twice a year,
they increased the number of hires
by accepting resumes all year round.
And this has led to confusion
for the job-seekers.
You did well,
but your voice keeps going up.
Try to lower your voice. It's lower
than the voice you have in mind.
That way, your voice
will sound stable.
Try again.
- Again?
- One more time.
You've been saying that
more than 50 times.
This is boring.
What are you doing?
I knew it.
There's a saying that
we shouldn't learn...
to drive or to be an anchor
from the significant others.
All the sayings were true.
I've never heard of such a saying.
Had I known how this would turn out,
I would've asked someone else.
You sound like a scary, strict
teacher, not my boyfriend.
Today, I'm not your boyfriend.
I'm your teacher.
If I knew I would be reading lines,
I shouldn't have dressed up.
I got excited for nothing.
You give me no choice.
We need to dial it up a notch.
Where are you going?
Get your script and follow me.
My gosh.
We were already
practicing so hard here.
Why are we in the studio?
Sit down in the anchor's seat.
Me?
Practice as if it's real.
Hurry.
You look much better in that seat
than I expected.
Really?
All right.
Square your shoulders.
Keep your back straight.
My outfit feels uncomfortable.
I can't get the right posture.
What's the correct posture?
Help me one more time.
Listen carefully.
Square your shoulders.
Keep your back straight.
Okay?
Okay.
Think about what we practiced.
And give it a try.
Try to remember
your breathing points.
Now that I'm in a new environment,
I can focus better. It's nice.
Since I'm focused,
let me practice other scenes.
Help me.
Other scenes? Which one?
Scene 35.
You're not leading the news
in that scene.
This is a very important scene.
You need to help me.
You just have to read lines for me.
Let's start from there. Hurry.
Okay.
"It was as if
I've been bewitched today."
"I have been following traces
of you all day today."
"It felt like some force was
stopping us from seeing each other."
What was that? Are you a robot?
You didn't put
any emotions into that.
I thought you just needed me
to read the lines.
You need to read with your emotions
for me to get into my character.
Try to sound more sorrowful.
Try it again.
"It was as if..."
"It was as if
I've been bewitched today."
"I have been following traces
of you all day today."
Relax and try again.
"It was as if
I've been bewitched today."
"I have been following traces
of you all day today."
All right. I'm sorry about that.
Let's call it a day.
I'm so glad
I didn't become an anchor,
and I'm also very glad
you didn't get into acting.
You're an awful actor.
Agreed.
What do you think will happen to
this drama? Will it be a big hit?
I'm not sure. I don't know
a lot about dramas,
but it's a little...
It's a little what?
It's a little far-fetched.
What's far-fetched?
There are a lot of things,
but especially the scene
where the man and the woman reunite.
They run into each other three times
on the same day in the same place,
then they miss each other by a hair.
Then they get into
a ridiculous accident on a street.
Don't you think there are
way too many coincidences?
That's why they're meant to be.
They're destined to meet each other
and fall in love.
And I'm sure more dramatic things
happen in our reality.
Think of us. We didn't know
we'd end up like this.
You're right.
It's pretty late. Let's go.
You said you have work tomorrow.
That's true.
But this is pretty disappointing.
I didn't think we'd spend
our first date working.
I didn't think
this was our first date.
Then?
I can't count
meeting you this briefly as a date.
We need to have
a really good first date.
Let's go on an official date
this weekend.
Sounds great.
Oh, right.
You have to grant me a wish.
You said you're sorry
while we read the script.
What? I don't remember that.
You can't pull that on me.
Fine. What's your wish?
You'll find out soon enough.
You're suddenly making me anxious.
Doesn't it hurt?
What are you doing?
I'm doing as I'm told.
Goodness.
This is how you pull off the move.
Got it?
Are you all right?
Are you hurt?
I think I hurt my head.
Your head? When?
Hey, Ha Jin.
You're already leaving
on Anchor Lee's car?
Okay.
This is great.
I was craving a drink.
Excuse me! One gizzard
and a bottle of soju, please.
Sure.
Do you want some soda?
What are you talking about?
I'm a good drinker.
Excuse me! Can we have
a soju glass and a regular glass?
Sure.
Have a drink.
- Cheers.
That's sweet. A drink you have
after your workout is the sweetest.
It's far from sweet.
You haven't worked out enough, then.
I went easy on you today
since it was your first day.
You can expect more from now on.
We'll work out for real.
You went easy on me today?
Don't say that.
You have to do your best
to get your revenge on your ex.
Why are you rushing? Take your time.
I can totally handle my drinks.
Don't worry about me.
Sure.
I don't think so.
Ha Kyung, don't you
want to become an athlete?
I was an athlete in high school.
I played judo.
I knew it!
Why did you quit?
At first, it was
because of an injury,
but now, it's because of my sister.
I thought I should be by her side.
Then did you give up on your dream
because of Ha Jin?
You two are very loving sisters.
But you two do look that loving.
It's also my dream
to live happily with my family.
We don't live with our parents,
but it's still fun to live
hand in hand with my sister.
Sometimes she doesn't listen to me
and gets in trouble,
then I'd get angry and upset,
but we still have a laugh
and make great memories.
Every day is...
What is this? Mr. Jo. Mr. Jo?
I was just telling a serious story.
Hey, Jo Il Kwon! Hey!
Are you doing this to avoid paying?
Hey! Get up. Hey. Hey!
This guy is really out.
"I can handle my drinks"?
My foot. You're such a weak drinker.
This is weird.
It doesn't feel like I'm walking.
Be quiet. It's already tough enough.
Something smells.
What's this smell?
Shut up, you idiot!
I don't feel good.
I'm never drinking with you again.
Man, that was tough.
That was tough.
You're so tiny and cute.
Thanks for making time for me.
Don't mention it.
How's the result?
No one would find any difference...
even if we switched this
with the previous result.
There are no new anomalies.
Everything looks clean.
Just think of this
as your regular checkup.
I mean, some people
put aside time to do this.
- All right.
- Do you have some time today?
Yes, I can spare some time.
Then let's have a chat for once.
When did we first meet?
October 17, 1995.
It was a rainy Tuesday.
When you were young,
you were the most scared of...
getting locked up in your closet.
Are you still scared of that?
Dad, I'm sorry.
Please open this. Dad.
Lee Jeong Hoon!
Why won't you listen to me?
Dad, I'm sorry.
Please let me out.
Be quiet!
Dad!
Dad! Dad!
Yes.
I know it's embarrassing, but I am.
What about regarding Seo Yeon?
Are your memories and feelings
about her the same?
The images
are still very vivid to me.
I see.
To be honest,
I was meaning to ask you this
for some time now.
But I felt hesitant to ask
about your private life.
That's okay.
Is it true
that you and Yeo Ha Jin...
are in a serious relationship?
Yes, it's true.
But you'll never be able
to forget Seo Yeon.
How could you start
a new relationship in that state?
Is it actually possible?
I'm just surprised, that's all.
I'm going to try to work it out.
She's someone dear to me.
I don't want to live
the rest of my life in regret.
Is that so?
All right.
You look happy, so I'm relieved.
I'm glad.
Thank you.
What do you think?
("The Man Who Cannot Forget")
I like this one the best.
Okay, we'll use this.
All right.
How long will it take
to finalize your manuscript?
Well, I think I'll need
a few more weeks.
Oh, right.
You wrote about a patient.
The renowned news anchor
who suffers from hyperthymesia.
I can understand
that you can't reveal his name,
but it would be nice
to offer more details about him.
I think
it's already detailed enough.
There are two factors that'll grab
your readers' attention.
One, the fact
that he's a real-life individual.
Two, the fact
that due to his illness,
he's still living in pain
from the memories of his first love.
And for eight years, at that.
When I had first read
your manuscript,
an individual came to my mind.
Anchor Lee Jeong Hoon.
But we all know
that he's dating Yeo Ha Jin.
In that case, I can't think
of anyone else.
I'm afraid your readers
will find it odd as well.
You must be busy.
You should head back in.
Good work today.
- I'll call you.
- Sure.
You can't do that.
How could you date someone new?
That's not right.
You aren't capable of doing that.
But you'll never be able
to forget Seo Yeon.
How could you start
a new relationship in that state?
Is it actually possible?
Hey, Tae Eun.
What do you think?
It suits you. Not only will you be
the nation's first love...
but also the nation's news anchor.
- Really?
- Yes.
Why don't we take a photo?
Sure, that'd be lovely.
Let's take a photo to commemorate
your first lead role.
Try this on. Let's create a theme.
Why would I wear your clothes?
Forget it.
Come on, I think
it'll look good on you. Go on.
Ms. Park, try this on.
Oh, please. It won't even fit.
Come on.
Should I give it a try?
I do like the color.
It looks good on you.
You look wonderful. Put yours on.
It's okay.
I'll take a photo of you two.
Let's take it together.
Hurry up and pose.
It's going to be one-take.
Okay.
That's good.
You look great.
Done.
- It came out nicely.
- Let me see.
Look.
Look at how pretty we look.
You're right.
Ms. Park, you got a call.
Oh, dear. I completely forgot.
I have a meeting to attend.
Ma'am, the jacket.
Right.
- Bye, then.
- Goodbye.
Try that one on.
- This yellow one?
- Yes.
Did you leave...
Get out this instant!
Chul.
I'm truly sorry.
I really am.
How dare you come here?
Do you have no shame?
I know that I can't be forgiven.
But I couldn't deal with the guilt,
so I decided to come here.
I'm sorry.
This won't work.
I know you just want us
to lessen your punishment.
That's not true.
I'm just here to sincerely apologize
for what I've done.
I'm truly sorry.
I couldn't handle the debt.
- The debt?
- My father suddenly passed away,
and his debt kept increasing
no matter how much I tried.
About Chul...
Don't you dare mention lessening
his punishment. That's absurd.
But I feel bad for him.
You know he's a goodhearted kid.
What kind of a goodhearted person
deceives and steals from others?
He seems to be repenting a lot.
How will his family manage
if he's put behind bars?
I'm not buying it.
Don't you ever mention him again.
I guess my father called you over.
Yes.
Next time he calls, say no.
You don't have to listen to him.
But I have to listen to you?
No, you don't have
to listen to me either.
When you were young, hypnotherapy,
medication, and counseling may have
helped you, but not anymore.
Your determination
is what put you here.
You need neither my father
nor my help anymore.
So don't listen to us.
There's nothing difficult
about receiving a checkup.
And I'll be forever grateful to him.
That'll never change.
So was the checkup
all that you received?
Did he have any other questions?
He asked about Ha Jin.
He asked if we were serious.
He had asked me
several times before.
I think he's been watching the news.
You don't have to explain it to him.
We are in a serious relationship.
What do you mean?
It's exactly what I said.
Don't you know her condition?
Her memories might come back...
if you remain by her side.
I know. I know that.
But I don't want to shun her
because of that.
Even if her memories come back
and she struggles,
I'm going to be there for her.
I've given this a lot of thought.
Among all the decisions
you've made to this day,
I had never gone against any.
Because you were
a cautious and wise individual.
But not this time.
You don't seem like
the Jeong Hoon I know.
That's because I did change.
I'm not going
to hide in fear anymore.
Doctor, Ms. Oh Mi Young
is waiting for you.
I'll let you go back to work.
I'll call you.
Oh, hi. How's the hangover?
It's fine,
but I don't remember much.
How did I go home?
I carried you home, of course.
Seriously?
How could you have carried me
with that tiny body of yours?
Don't you ever boast
about drinking well, got it?
I'm sorry.
I didn't make any mistakes, did I?
No... No, you didn't.
Really? I'm glad.
Will you be working out today?
Yes, I will.
Then I'll see you
around the same time as yesterday.
All right.
You're so tiny...
and cute.
Why do I keep thinking about her?
I must have had too many drinks.
Goodness.
My entire body aches.
I should ask her
to go easy on me today.
I'm sorry for calling you
all of a sudden like this.
No, it's all right. Actually,
I wanted to get some fresh air.
But I hope everything is okay.
I was just a bit worried.
You recently went through
something traumatic.
I was worried if it took
a psychological toll on you.
And I was wondering
if you needed my help.
I'm okay now.
It's all in the past.
I'm glad to hear that.
Right. If you need help later,
feel free to call me.
Thank you, doctor.
The other day,
we talked about your dream.
You said you had a weird dream.
Did you have a similar dream
like that ever since then?
I did have similar dreams
after the first one.
But I'm really fine these days.
Thanks to Anchor Lee,
I'm really happy.
- I see.
- If you aren't too busy,
we should meet up together.
We can get
something delicious and talk.
Sure.
(First Date, 7:40 a.m.)
Who is it this early in the morning?
It's for me!
It's for me. Don't touch it!
My goodness. What on earth is it?
What did you buy this time?
Some stuff.
I thought you were going
on a date with Anchor Lee today.
You said it was
your official first date.
Yes, that's right.
Can you help me move them?
I decided on my wish.
Today, you have to do
everything I ask you to do.
She's making me anxious.
I'm in front of your house.
Open the door for me.
What's going on?
We were supposed to meet
two hours later.
I need water.
Could you give me a cup of water?
Water? Okay.
Here.
What's all this?
Open them now.
Presents.
They are all yours.
What are...
Don't you think
you'd look great in these?
It's perfect on you. Right?
I'm not sure.
I don't know.
That was made for you.
Put that one. And what else
will look good with that?
And try them with this.
Put them on now?
Yes, it's my wish.
Wait. Have you been hating
my outfits all this time?
You did talk about my tie
when you were on my show.
Are you giving me
a wardrobe makeover?
It's not that.
It's our first date.
There's this place
I really want to go,
but I don't want people
to recognize us.
If you go out dressed like that,
people will spot us in five minutes.
It'll be so easy to recognize you.
Think of this as a type of disguise.
I don't think that will work on me.
Trust me on this.
People won't recognize you at all.
I assure you.
Besides, you're supposed to do
whatever I ask of you today.
Hurry and get changed.
I did have a bad feeling about it.
I really don't think
this is working.
Let's try the next outfit.
Is it supposed to look like this?
What do you say? Do you like it?
The last one.
- Another one?
- It's the last one.
See?
I bet you also think
this color stands out too much.
No, I'm looking at you
because it looks great on you.
From now on,
wear an outfit like this.
It lightens up your looks
and makes you look more dashing.
I really think you're teasing me.
No, I'm not.
By the way,
what is this place
you wanted to go on a date?
Oh, that.
You'll know once we get there.
I daresay
you never thought of this place.
All of a sudden, you're scaring me.
Was going on dates supposed
to be full of thrill like this?
I'm really excited.
Is this the place
you wanted to come on a date?
Yes.
I don't see anything special here.
Isn't the cherry blossom path
just so gorgeous?
Whenever I passed by here in a car,
I saw couples holding hands here.
I was really jealous of them.
What is it?
Were you disappointed
because it's too plain?
No.
I would not have thought
of this place.
I like it.
Let's get off now.
Right. Hold on.
Just in case.
There.
Let's go.
The weather is great today.
Right?
Hey, it's them.
- My goodness.
- Gosh.
Isn't that Yeo Ha Jin?
Isn't that Anchor Lee Jeong Hoon?
I don't believe this. No way!
My goodness!
- You guys look great together!
- You look great together!
Let's go.
That was quicker than I expected.
Right.
We should give up on this path.
Let's go back to the car.
You said you really wanted
to walk this path.
But people can recognize us.
Let them, then.
There's no reason why we must hide.
Let's go.
This is beautiful.
This is how it feels
to see it up close.
What do you say?
Isn't this worth it?
It's nice.
I only saw cherry blossoms
on the news every year.
Let's come back and see
the cherry blossoms every spring.
Yes.
What are you thinking?
That it's unfair.
What's unfair?
Come to think of it,
I granted you
more than just one wish today.
I had to try on
so many different outfits.
Do you really think
it's that unfair?
But sorry, it's too late.
You can't take it back.
Instead,
grant me a wish too.
That's so cheap.
Fine, what is it?
No matter what happens,
don't ever say goodbye.
That's my wish.
I'll probably do it anyway
even if you didn't wish for that.
Okay, then. I'll do that.
You promised.
Okay. I promise.
Go inside.
Okay. Call me when you get home.
Okay. You should go in.
Anchor Lee, give me your phone.
My phone?
- Why do you want my phone?
- It'll take only a second.
You can't change that
without my permission, okay?
Okay. Go in and get some rest.
Okay, I'm really going in.
This is bad.
I miss him already.
(Incoming video call: Ha Jin)
What is this?
Yes, Ha Jin.
What were you up to?
Thinking about me?
I was just...
looking up some news articles.
Oh, I see. I was thinking about you.
You didn't text me
after you got home,
so I called because I missed you.
I was about to text you.
Why are you laughing?
I was wondering
how you could be so honest.
Now that I told you that honestly,
can you raise up your camera?
I can't really see you.
Like this?
No, not like that.
About 45 degrees up.
About 45 degrees.
Like this?
Can we just talk on the phone?
It's a bit awkward
to be on a video call.
No. Then stay still.
I'll just find a way to look at you.
Right, did you see how
I changed my name on your phone?
You can't change that
without my permission.
I'm the only one
who sees this phone anyway.
Is it that important?
Of course, it is.
Of all people,
you'll be seeing my name like that.
"Yeo Ha Jin"? That's so cold.
You might end up
losing the love you had.
How did you store my name?
"Anchor Lee".
It doesn't sound
that different from mine.
It's completely different.
I put hearts surrounding your name,
and two each.
I like calling you Anchor Lee.
In dramas, I've seen people called
as a general manager or a director,
but never an anchor.
Okay, do whatever you want.
Get some rest, then.
Are you hanging up already?
Oh, it's not like that.
Do you not want to talk to me?
Yeo Ha Jin! Look at your room.
It's like a pigsty.
Is this a pigsty?
Ha Kyung, later. Do that later.
- It's nothing.
- Look at your outfit.
- I'll call you again.
- Anchor Lee, look at this.
Look at this.
Hey. I'll call you again. Sorry.
Hello, viewers.
This is "Yeo Ha Jin's Dirty Room".
Make sure you keep your promise.
Goodnight.
- Hey.
- What?
You need to knock.
Show some manners.
"Manners"? I was going out
to eat something delicious,
so I thought I'd ask you to come,
but forget it.
Where are you going?
I'll go with you.
If you come out in 10 minutes
after cleaning up your room.
I'll clean it up after we eat.
No.
You have 10 minutes!
(Tae Eun)
Can we meet for a second?
I have to talk to you.
It's about Ha Jin.
Wait.
This is yours.
These are mine. Don't touch mine.
Only if it wasn't past 10 p.m.,
I'd have a bite of each one.
That looks good.
This is good.
I'm so jealous.
I'm hungry.
I'm hungry. I'm so hungry.
- You can have a bite.
- Okay.
Hey, wait!
That's not a bite. Hands off.
- You can't take it back.
- This is too big of a bite.
- My bite is that big.
- Hey. Hey.
Hey, wait.
I'm not doing this for myself.
Wait, think about this
one more time.
Wait. That's coffee. Wait.
Wait here. I'll bring the coffee.
Don't eat this.
I have my eyes on you.
- I'll keep watching you as I go.
- Trust me.
- Don't eat that.
- I won't.
- Ha Na. Over here.
- Yes?
Ha Na, you look so pretty.
- Don't say that.
- My gosh.
No way, you look much prettier now.
Ha Jin. Ha Jin, what's wrong?
Are you feeling sick?
Do you have a headache?
How does it hurt?
This isn't good.
Let's go to the hospital.
What is it? Why did you
want to see me this late?
You're here.
What is it?
There's something
I couldn't tell you.
Ha Kyung.
Do you know who Yeong is?
What?
You know that name, don't you?
Who's Yeong?
I'm sure you know.
Tell me now. Please?
The reason why
Ha Jin was so tormented...
that she wanted to
take her own life.
Yeong...
Yeong died because of me.
She died because of me.
(Find Me in Your Memory)
I want Ha Na to be happy again.
I want to tell Ha Jin that...
it was an accident.
She was murdered by her stalker.
Her name is Seo Yeon?
He's a guy who has
another person in his heart.
Can you really take him?
The time I spend with you is
very special.
I hope that's the case with you too.
Is something going on
with Anchor Lee?
Do you want to
talk about Anchor Lee Jeong Hoon?
So you want to hear the truth?
I made Ha Na unhappy.