(Episode 17)
- Hello?
- It's me.
You know me, don't you?
How did you find...
Where are you right now?
Where else would I be?
I'm locked up.
Do you know how much I had to spend
to make one phone call?
Why are you suddenly calling me?
Are you with her right now?
Yeo Ha Jin.
What?
Make sure you protect her...
if you don't want to lose her.
That idiot...
He's quite the character.
What are you talking about?
What do you mean,
"he's quite the character"?
How much do you know?
You have too many questions.
You can come and see me
if you're that curious.
You didn't stay long
the last time you came.
Stop talking nonsense
and tell me right now.
Who is he?
Hey, hang up already.
I have to go now.
See you soon.
Thank you.
Hello?
(Find Me in Your Memory)
Anchor Lee.
Hey.
Why are you out here?
I was going to be there soon.
It's way past a minute.
Who were you on the phone with?
It was for work.
I'm making some honey tea.
Is that all right?
Yes.
Grab a seat. This time,
it'll really take a minute.
Here.
Thank you.
I'm sorry.
I talked big
and said you don't have to worry,
but this is all I can do.
You don't have to be sorry.
This is what I needed the most
at this moment.
It's perfect.
Warm and sweet.
Drink up and lie down again.
You won't be able to fall asleep
if you wake up completely.
Are you leaving?
I'll stay here,
then I'll drop you off at
Ha Kyung's hospital room tomorrow.
I told you that I won't go anywhere.
Who was that jerk?
So he knew exactly where we'd be?
What's wrong with you?
Reporter Jo?
I'm sorry.
Why are you still awake?
Are you having trouble sleeping?
Yes.
If it's because of me,
I'll close the door.
No, don't.
I think I'll be even more scared.
Could you just...
chat with me for a bit?
I think that'll help me go to bed.
Sure.
What should we talk about?
It would be nice to chat
about simple things...
such as your interests and hobbies.
But you have neither.
Did you always want to become
a news anchor?
When I was little,
I wanted to become a writer
like my mother.
But I had no talent
and had to give up.
After I matured,
I wanted to become a reporter.
Your dream came true.
Did you become a reporter...
to make a righteous society?
No, I didn't have
such a grand dream.
I was upset.
People would go back
on their words...
and lie.
I was upset that they didn't
even feel guilty.
Don't get me wrong. I didn't become
a reporter to vent on them.
I just wanted the public
to know the truth.
I bet you can easily see...
how selfish and full of lies
people can be.
That must be painful.
What do you like?
Me?
I already told you that
I enjoyed taking pictures.
I like working out and shopping.
I also like listening to music
and watching movies.
I enjoy reading as well,
but I like eating the most.
Why are you laughing?
I think I asked you
the wrong question.
There might be no end to this.
You could be right.
I do like many things.
I like seeing you smile.
I know I shouldn't feel this way
in this given situation.
But I like this moment.
I like that it's just you and me.
I thought you were injured,
but you look just fine.
By the way, why did you
open the door so suddenly?
I was going to kill you
if you were the stalker.
What brings you here?
I just wanted to visit you.
I thought you'd be bored.
I was hospitalized once
when I was young.
I was bored to death.
That's why I came.
Your presence alone
won't be entertaining.
That's exactly why
I've prepared some stuff.
What is all this?
Ta-da.
Are we going to play games
while having snacks?
Come on. Just wait there.
Watching movies is the best way
to kill time.
You pretty much have the VVIP seat.
Sit down.
This one looks interesting.
It'll help relieve stress.
What movie is it?
I'm not sure. I don't think
this is suitable for a patient.
Let's watch a comedy
so that we can laugh...
No, this looks really fun.
Let me raise the volume.
Don't tell me you can't watch
scary movies.
I love horror movies.
I enjoy getting scared.
Gosh, my hair's a mess.
Hey.
Where are you going?
You should play with me.
What is it?
What are you doing down there?
I was picking up the remote control.
Why did you throw it?
You startled me.
You startled me even more.
Your hair's a mess.
My hair tie got loose.
I think this is the first time
I saw you with your hair down.
You're right. I always had it up.
Don't stare at me.
It's uncomfortable.
I mean, you look like a ghost.
But you also look like
you live in the wild.
Anyway, you look better
with your hair up.
You should always tie it.
I want to tie it as well,
but my shoulder hurts too much.
Then give that to me.
Why?
I'll tie it for you.
Forget it.
Why would you tie my hair?
You look too frightening.
I'm good at this.
I used to tie
my younger sister's hair.
Done.
You look so much better.
Don't go.
How did you...
end up here?
Did you sleep well last night?
I didn't even know I fell asleep.
You didn't snore, so don't worry.
Did you not have nightmares?
No.
I think the honey water
did the trick. I slept like a baby.
I'm glad.
Are you sure you slept well?
I hope you didn't stay up all night
because of me.
I didn't. I slept well.
I'm glad.
- Hello?
- Are you up?
Yes.
I'm on my way there.
Did you sleep well?
It's freezing.
What? Come on.
Hey.
Why is he sleeping here?
He's so weird.
Gosh, it's freezing.
It's so cold.
Yes. I slept well. I did.
Yes. Yes.
- Do you need anything?
- What's wrong with you?
No, I don't.
- So where are you?
- I'm almost there.
You're almost here?
I missed my sister.
Yes. Me too.
Hurry. I missed you too. Gosh.
Where are my shoes?
Oh, my gosh.
Ha Kyung, I'm here.
You're here.
Hi.
Mr. Jo?
What brings you here at this hour?
I came to see how she is.
I just got here.
He just got here.
I see.
Ms. Yeo Ha Kyung.
The doctor is ready
to tell you the test result.
Okay.
Let me come with you. I'll join her.
You're not busy today, right?
What? No.
Then, can you drive them
to your place later? Do this for me.
Me? What about you?
I have an important meeting.
Okay.
Are you with her right now?
Yeo Ha Jin.
Make sure you protect her...
if you don't want to lose her.
(Warden Kim Byung Yoon)
Hello, this is Lee Jeong Hoon.
I know I'm asking a lot,
but I have a favor to ask you.
My gosh, we're home.
Thank you for driving us here.
Do you want some tea?
What's wrong with them?
They are all shriveled up.
Right. This was your place.
Yes.
We're treating
the owner like a guest.
I thought they were fake.
They are real plants.
You have to make sure
they get enough sunlight.
Thank you for helping us out.
- No problem.
- Oh, right.
Let's postpone our training
for about a week.
Will that be enough time for you?
I think you should rest up
for a whole month.
A week will be enough.
You should still be careful.
You might not have fully recovered.
Okay.
But what training?
I promised to be
a physical trainer for Mr. Jo.
Why all of a sudden?
That sort of happened.
What is this?
There's something going on
between you two. What is it?
- What is?
- What do you mean?
There's nothing weird about this.
By the way, where did
Anchor Lee go so urgently?
My gosh, I don't know.
He doesn't tell me these things.
Is that so?
You're here.
You should've hurried.
I've been waiting for you
since morning.
Talk now.
- About what?
- Everything you know.
How much do you know?
Who is that jerk?
Oh, you mean Yeo Ha Jin's stalker?
I don't know.
We just exchanged a few letters.
That's all.
- Letters?
- Yes.
He sent me the letters first,
so I just answered
some questions he asked me.
And I asked him some questions too.
Right.
And I got some photos as well.
So...
what did you talk about?
Answer me right now.
What kind of reaction is this?
By the way,
are you serious about her?
Do you really like
that woman, Yeo Ha Jin?
Do you?
My gosh, you're one crazy guy.
You're completely out of your mind.
Mr. Lee.
Wake up.
You're the one who should
be locked up here, not me.
Come inside. Let's switch places.
Just answer my question.
You answer mine.
Don't you feel bad for Seo Yeon?
Why can't you answer me?
We could have been happy together
if you didn't get involved.
But you killed Seo Yeon.
And now, what do you think...
you're doing with her friend?
If she sees you like this,
I wonder how Seo Yeon must feel.
Poor Seo Yeon.
Darn it.
Ha Jin. Ha Kyung.
My gosh, what is this about?
It must have hurt so much.
Are you sure it's okay
to get discharged already?
You should get all the treatment
you can at the hospital.
There's nothing to treat here.
I'm all better now.
After hearing the news,
my hands were shaking.
I don't even know how I drove here.
Ms. Park, let's sit down.
At this rate,
you might faint before we do.
Sit down and calm down.
Ha Jin. Ha Kyung.
Let's officially request the police
to investigate the stalker.
It's not the time to worry
about your image right now.
Who knows
what that jerk would try next?
I agree with you.
On my way here,
I talked to our lawyer.
The lawyer says it's better...
to report the break-in incident
at home and this attack together.
Then, what about the letters
Anchor Lee received?
Those letters will be hard to be
considered as criminal conduct.
It might just end up
piquing people's curiosity,
so the lawyer advises
not to share that.
And I agree.
And I feel bad
in case this affects Anchor Lee.
Not disclosing the letters
might be better.
Yes. Let's report this
as soon as possible...
and catch that stalker first.
Once I catch that stalker,
I'll break his wrists, so he never
does something like this again.
Ms. Park, leave that to me.
Yes.
So Ha Jin, don't worry about this.
Just take care of yourself
and trust us.
Okay?
I will.
Do you really like
that woman, Yeo Ha Jin?
Don't you feel bad for Seo Yeon?
But you killed Seo Yeon.
And now, what do you think...
you're doing with her friend?
Yes. Hello?
It's me. Is it a bad time to talk?
I just wanted to let you know...
that Ms. Park
suggested officially...
requesting the police
to investigate.
To report my stalker.
I see. Yes.
Given the turn of events now,
I think it's better too.
The media will probably
publish a lot of articles on this.
Probably, right?
Be extra careful for the time being.
Ask the police to protect you.
And have bodyguards accompany you.
Okay.
I'm sorry that
I'm not much of a help to you.
You are such a big help. I mean it.
Stop saying stuff like that.
I'm not the only one in danger.
You're also in danger.
Be careful, okay?
By the way, you don't sound good.
Are you sick?
No. I'm fine.
Rest up. I'll call you again.
(I'm always watching you.)
(You're mine, Ha Jin.)
(I want to make you happy.)
We will try our best to investigate
as quickly as we can.
Please catch the stalker.
We'll try.
Given the evidence,
it seems he's been
inside the house several times.
Are there any suspects
you can think of?
Someone who knows the house well
and Yeo Ha Jin's schedule.
Usually, for cases like this,
there's a high possibility that
an acquaintance is the culprit.
There is someone
I've been suspecting.
("Yeo Ha Jin to Take a Severe Action
Against Her Stalker")
My goodness. I can't believe this.
Yes? Hey, come in.
You're here.
Come here and take a seat.
Sit.
How's Ha Jin doing?
She must've been shocked.
Yes.
He better be caught soon.
She'll be way too anxious.
Hey, so I gave this a thought.
What do you think about
doing a report on this incident?
Around Ha Jin's case?
As you know,
everyone agrees that
stalking is a crime.
But it's tough
to get a stalker arrested,
and even if they do get caught,
their sentencing isn't much.
So let's take this chance...
to change the idea people have
about stalking and stalkers.
I think that could
help out Ha Jin a little too.
I know what you mean
by making that suggestion,
and that you're making that offer
because you're concerned about her.
But...
if I mention her stalker
on the news,
it'll provoke him even more.
What's more important now is
to keep Ha Jin safe...
instead of worrying about
the stalker's punishment.
You have a point too.
I understand what you mean.
Anyway, if you need anything,
let me know whenever.
Yes, thank you.
Okay. You can go now.
It looks like something is
definitely going on between them.
("Yeo Ha Jin's Stalker
Breaks into Her Home")
("Yeo Ha Jin Shows Up
After Revealing Her Stalker")
("Nation's First Love, Yeo Ha Jin,
Harassed by a Stalker")
Hurry, hurry, hurry.
(Moving files)
Darn it, this is so slow.
Man, I can't believe
that got noticed.
(Left alone at 9 p.m.,
headed to a movie theater.)
(Are you sure
you wish to delete everything?)
Please...
(Moving files)
I'm here to inspect your gas pipe.
Sir, over here.
Taxi!
(Inbox: From Lee Jeong Hoon)
This is the script
for today's "News Live".
Turn yourself in and keep
a little bit of dignity you have,
or be publicly acknowledged as
human garbage. It's your choice.
You have exactly four hours left.
I just got some money
from that stalker...
and sold him Yeo Ha Jin's pictures.
I'm serious. I'm telling the truth.
I just did whatever
that jerk asked me to do.
Darn it.
(To Park Soo Chang, No subject)
(Read)
(Episode 18)
Ha Kyung, look up some articles.
Yes.
People won't blame her for this
since she didn't do anything, right?
Gosh, I doubt that.
She's the victim.
What are people saying?
We're asking our listeners
for the movie of their life.
We're getting a lot of other texts
that aren't movie recommendations.
"Other texts"?
From number 2332,
"Ha Jin, cheer up!"
Number 1012, "Arrest everyone
who harasses Ha Jin!"
Number 3809, "Hey, you, stalker,
you jerk! We'll get you!"
Gosh, we're getting bombarded
with messages of support for you.
You have a lot of fans
who show their support for you.
Will you share a word with them?
Okay.
Everyone, I'm fine.
Don't worry too much.
Thank you for
giving me your support...
and cursing him instead of me.
I'll cheer up with your support.
Thank you.
You have such a great personality.
Then let's listen to
one more song...
to help Ha Jin cheer up.
- Ha Jin!
- You're the best!
- I love you!
- She's coming.
- Ha Jin!
- You're so pretty!
- Ha Jin, cheer up!
- Ha Jin, keep it up!
- You're so pretty!
- Keep up your spirit!
Don't get stressed out!
How about a picture?
- Yes!
- Sounds great!
Can you take a picture for us?
There are too many people here.
Are you sure?
It's okay. My bodyguards are
here too. Come on.
- She's so pretty.
- My gosh.
- Thank you.
- Can you look over here?
- Over here too.
- Look over here too.
- I want to take one too.
- I don't think I'm in the picture.
- I think I'm cut out.
- Exactly.
- I want to be in it too.
- She's so pretty.
She has such a tiny face.
- This is amazing.
- It's awesome.
Good.
Did she get all of us?
Looks great.
- I love you.
- Ha Jin.
- Take another one!
- You're the best.
- It looks so great!
- What about me?
Look, doesn't it look great?
- It looks great.
- We look great.
- My gosh, that's so good.
- You look so pretty.
- That's Ha Jin.
- Hey.
- What is this?
- Who is this guy?
- Go away, man.
- You're so pretty.
- Excuse me, everyone. Move aside.
- You have our support.
I'm a huge fan.
May I take a picture with you?
Haven't we met before?
Goodness, you remember me.
I'm the audio director
for "Lee Jeong Hoon's News Live".
- Oh, we've met before. Hello.
- Hello.
Yes, hello. May we take a picture?
- Of course.
- Hey, man. Go away.
Chul Woong, come on over.
Let's take one together.
No, I'm all right.
I don't like taking pictures,
but if you insist...
Excuse me.
- Come, Chul Woong.
- We're acquainted.
It's an honor
to take a picture with you, Mr. Kim.
- Okay.
- Yes, sure.
Okay, let's take it.
- In 1, 2, 3.
Hey, hey. We need to talk.
About what?
There's something.
Come up to the rooftop with me.
Wait, no. You can tell me here.
Why do we need to go up there?
Mr. Kim, why are you here?
You never know.
I set them up like this.
I can't let anything happen.
You won't have to worry about that.
We can handle this.
Come on.
I used to be a good athlete.
Oh, sure.
It seemed like
Ha Jin has a lot of fans.
I'm one of them.
Sure, thanks.
I just received a call
from the police.
They said Reporter Park Soo Chang
turned himself in.
He gave the stalker my photos
in return for money.
Right.
You helped out, didn't you?
You were investigating it.
Reporter Park isn't the type
to turn himself in like that.
I'm sorry I couldn't tell you
in advance.
I had to sort some stuff out.
You've become strange these days.
You're helping me out a lot
these days,
but you keep apologizing.
There's nothing to be sorry about,
so don't say that ever again.
I should charge you 50 dollars
every time you apologize.
Better yet, you should grant me
a wish.
Whoever apologizes first will grant
the other person's wish.
Fine, I won't apologize ever again.
Darn it. What a disappointment.
I already thought of a wish.
- Here.
- Thank you.
Oh, right.
- Here you go.
- Thanks.
Jeong Hoon's not up to anything,
is he?
No. The last time they met,
he had asked Tae Eun for help.
He's still incarcerated, right?
How's Moon Seong Ho doing?
It's a bit strange.
What do you mean?
Last time, when he met
with Anchor Lee,
he became very agitated.
But we had expected that.
But this time,
he looks even calmer than usual.
"Calmer"?
Yes. So we're keeping an eye on him.
But we haven't spotted
anything unusual.
I see.
Can you please tell me
what this is regarding?
Later.
I'll tell you
once it's all finished.
(Records)
(Voice Record
of Inmate Moon Seong Ho)
Tell me.
About what?
About everything you know.
(Inmate Moon Seong Ho, Visitation,
Tell me.)
(What?)
- Hello.
- Hi.
The flowers are pretty.
Father.
Hey.
How was the conference?
It went well. Prof. Park said hi.
I heard you haven't been
showing up to the gatherings.
I have many lectures
and some stuff I need to do.
I see.
Don't overwork yourself, though.
I wanted to ask you something.
It's about Jeong Hoon.
Okay.
Is he visiting
the National Forensic Hospital...
because of that woman, Yeo Ha Jin?
I read the articles.
I heard the stalker
has been threatening her.
Moon Seong Ho is incarcerated.
There's no way he's involved
in what's been happening.
If that's the case,
it's even stranger
for him to go there.
I heard he begged you for help.
I don't know anything about this.
And even if I did,
I wouldn't be able to tell you.
Why not?
This is his privacy.
You don't need to know everything
that's going on with him.
I'm his doctor in charge.
No matter how trivial,
I must know about it
if it's related to his illness.
Jeong Hoon has been doing well.
Why are you being...
Is this regarding something else...
other than his treatment?
Cut that nonsense and let's go eat.
Are you saying it's impossible
to catch the stalker...
with the evidence Reporter Park has?
There is a way.
First, we'll ask the head office...
of the messenger app he used
for the stalker's IP address.
We'll have to track
his cryptocurrency as well. But...
It'll take some time...
since both of the servers
are overseas.
You're correct.
Please hurry.
We're suffocating here.
We will.
Oh, right.
There's something else we found out.
Did anything about him
stand out in particular...
when you talked with him?
Not really. He was always brief.
Right.
He did say one thing.
He was looking at the photos
I took of her at a cafe...
and said she looked similar
to when they first met.
"When they first met"?
And when was that?
He didn't go into detail.
Right. He was boasting.
He said he knew her
even before her debut.
That's why she was
even more special to him.
He said he knew me for a long time?
Yes. Can you think of anyone...
in particular?
If he knew her before her debut...
Chul first joined the agency...
when Ha Jin was about to debut.
How may I help you?
Police.
I have a few questions
regarding Ms. Yeo Ha Jin.
Why me?
I heard you were in charge of her
up until not too long ago.
Were there ever times
when you suspected something?
I don't think so.
Nothing really stood out
during my time with her.
I see.
Right, I heard you left work early
last Saturday.
What did you do after work?
Why do you ask?
I'm just following the procedure.
I was stressed out about something,
so I had a drink at my friend's.
I was totally wasted
and blacked out.
I see.
The stalker's motorcycle falls into
one of the higher power classes,
so he needed a type two license
for small vehicles.
Do you have a type two license
for small vehicles?
Yes, I do.
But I rarely ride my bike.
Ever since Ha Jin's debut,
Director Ji Hyun Geun would talk...
about wanting to cast her
for his works.
Didn't the photo turn out great?
Yes, you're right.
Are you and Ms. Yeo close?
Of course. We were practically
stuck to each other...
throughout the movie's filming.
I heard you visited her house...
last Saturday.
May I ask why?
I had a gift for her.
It was that photo.
But I couldn't meet her.
And after that?
I came back here and worked.
I wrote my scenario
and edited some photos.
Was there anyone who saw you?
I like to work alone.
Does this mean
I don't have an alibi?
Not at all. I'm just following
the procedure.
Please call me if you remember
anything in particular.
- Sure.
- Thank you for the coffee.
What was this coffee called?
Chanchamayo.
By the way,
you must enjoy traveling.
You even bought that coffee
while overseas.
It's a lovely place.
You should also visit if you can.
Then you must enjoy
riding motorcycles.
People who enjoy traveling
tend to bike a lot.
I used to bike a long time ago.
But I sold it after finding
another hobby.
Oh, I see.
Thank you for your time.
Not at all.
Sir, please catch the stalker.
I beg you.
Don't you worry about that.
I'll see myself out.
- Okay. Goodbye.
- Goodbye.
I'm really fine.
Don't worry about me.
All right.
They said the stalker
is 1 of those 2.
We'll catch him soon.
Right, Ha Kyung?
Of course.
The detectives said
they'd catch him. Let's trust them.
Let's not worry about it. Let's go.
By the way, what was all that stuff
in the supply room?
Right. You should take them.
- We should?
- Yes.
They're all Ha Jin's birthday gifts.
It's your birthday in two days.
I forgot.
You're right. I forgot as well.
We've been receiving so many gifts.
Gosh, I guess she really made it.
You're right.
What will you do on your birthday?
I should start thinking about that.
Hey, Tae Eun.
Now?
What in the world happened
to Ha Jin?
Well...
I had no clue about any of this.
I was too busy to tell you.
Things kept happening.
Is she okay?
You know that she's cheerful
and strong.
She's dealing with it well.
That's a relief.
What about you?
Are you okay?
I'm okay.
Don't worry.
You got so many presents.
My gosh.
We still have more in the car.
How could I forget
about your birthday?
Things are so hectic these days.
Right.
Anchor Lee knows
it's my birthday soon, right?
How would he know your birthday?
He can find my information online.
He must have looked me up
at least once.
Who would look you up online
and memorize your birthday?
Besides, even if he did,
he probably forgot it.
No way. He wouldn't.
Yes, he would.
Don't be disappointed
after your birthday.
You should just
bring that up casually.
You're making me nervous again.
I'm worried you'll say goodbye again
like last time.
That time, you were nice to me
at first and then said...
you didn't want to see me again.
But I'm not going
to listen to you anymore.
You see, I want you to be happy.
That's why I'm not going
to say goodbye.
I enjoyed the news today as always.
Did you get home safely?
Actually, this Wednesday
is my birthday.
Do you have some time to spare
before the news?
I don't need a present.
Just have a meal with me.
You look so pretty
when you're not talking.
Really?
Be quiet. You look so beautiful.
I'll take one for you. Give me that.
Sit down.
Smile.
Nice.
I'll take a photo of them too.
Anchor Lee didn't text back yet?
Why isn't he texting me back?
Is he already sleeping?
Look at this.
Instead of counting
millions of things,
you should only count 5 or 6 things.
What does that mean?
It's saying
we should lead simple lives.
So we can finish calculating things
only by using our two thumbs.
That's cool.
Yeong!
(Courier Service)
Ha Na. Are you all right, Ha Na?
Ha Na. Are you all right?
Are you okay?
Oh, no.
- Ha Na.
- Is she okay?
- Oh, no.
- Please help!
- Call 911. Please.
- Ha Na.
What's wrong? You can't sleep?
What is it? Are you sick?
You don't have a fever.
Did you have a nightmare?
It's all right.
You can fall back to sleep again.
Let's go back to sleep.
(The breath of spring lands
on my lips after meeting you.)
(Dad)
Take this with you.
What is it?
Your mother saved them just for you.
All right.
Mom!
Be careful.
Look at this.
Doesn't this look like a turtle?
My gosh. You're right.
This is the head.
And this part is the shell.
And these are the legs.
Yes, that's right.
My goodness. This is fascinating.
You can keep this, Mom.
It was hard to find this rock.
But I'll give it to you.
My gosh, thank you.
I'll keep this forever.
Okay.
My good boy, Jeong Hoon.
Thank you.
Mom, not that color.
Why not?
It's my favorite color.
Don't just waste it like that.
I see. Really?
I just wanted
to color the roof in gold.
I'm sorry.
My gosh. Then...
Use it then.
What? You told me
not to waste it. Forget it.
It's your favorite color.
I should lend it to you.
Color with it as much as you want.
What is it?
Really?
- I'll waste this away, then.
- No. Hold on.
No. Then, leave me about this much.
If you say that,
I'll use it and leave
only this much.
You're really giving me this, right?
I'll color the wall with this too.
Will that be okay?
Okay. Sure.
- My good boy, Jeong Hoon.
- Stop it.
Jeong Hoon.
Even if all the people
in this world don't know,
I'm sure you know...
that this box was my treasure chest.
The precious moments
you have given me are enough...
to fill up and spill over the chest.
I cherished them like jewels.
So Jeong Hoon,
I hope you won't doubt me
even for a moment...
when I write...
that I was very happy...
to have you as my son.
Jeong Hoon.
Promise me this, please.
Promise me that if you find
something precious,
you won't hesitate to go after it.
I truly hope you'll be happy.
Not for someone else's sake,
but for yourself.
Have some morning juice.
So? what kind of a dream
did you have last night?
You know,
just a weird dream.
If you aren't doing well,
we can cancel the photo shoot.
We can't do that.
We postponed this once already.
That's not what's important.
You're more important.
But we still have to go.
Right? We should, shouldn't we?
You're important, but you can get
more energy by working. Right?
Get ready and come out.
No, I'll get ready
after I finish this.
1, 2.
Looks great. 1, 2.
Okay. 1, 2.
That's great. 1, 2.
Her makeup looks really great.
Okay. 1, 2.
Ha Jin, are you doing all right?
- Yes.
- You look pretty.
Let me check if they need to take
a few more shots.
Sit down and get some rest.
Okay. Thank you.
I really don't think
that was just a dream.
(Search for articles)
(2011, Yongcheon alley
motorcycle accident)
(Search, No results found.)
(Yongcheon car accident)
Yes, Anchor Lee?
Ha Jin, where are you?
Can you talk right now?
I'm at a photo shoot. I can talk.
What about you? Where are you?
I came out for a bit.
- I didn't return your text. I'm...
- Wait.
I'm what?
Wait, you weren't going to say
"I'm sorry", were you?
I'm free on Wednesday.
Let's have dinner together.
I hope your shooting goes well.
Go home safely.
And let me know when you get home.
Okay. I'll do that.
Ha Jin, we looked through the shots,
and they like everything.
They said you look very pretty.
Let's go now.
Okay. I'll get changed.
Okay.
- Did you get changed?
- Yes, let's go.
- Wrap up and come. We'll go first.
- Okay.
Ms. Park!
What brings you here without a call?
I came to buy something delicious
for you and Ha Kyung.
I'm sure you recently had only
delivery food stuck inside home.
You're right. She couldn't eat well
because she had no appetite.
That's not good. Ha Jin, let's say
this is your early birthday party.
Tell me whatever you want.
I'll buy anything for you.
Anything is fine with me.
Really? In that case,
there's a great eel place nearby.
Let's go there.
Sounds great.
Ms. Park,
then let's all take my car.
Please wait at the entrance.
I'll bring the car.
All right.
- See you soon.
- Okay.
Man, who drives like that?
My car.
Pick up. Please pick up. Darn it.
Hello?
Goodness, Director Song! One second.
What's the occasion?
Wow, it has been so long.
You can hop in first. Go ahead.
Ms. Park will be here
after that phone call.
(Anchor Lee)
(Power Off)
What is this?
Stop that car!
You have to get that car!
- No!
- Wait!
Who do you think you are?
- Ha Jin!
Anchor Lee.
Hey. Are you with Ha Jin?
I can't get a hold of her.
She...
She just got abducted.
What?
(We thank Yangpa
for her guest appearance.)
(Find Me in Your Memory)
Did you track her location?
We can't track her.
Do we still have no idea
who did this?
Moon Chul lied about
having a drink with a friend...
on the day
of the motorcycle accident.
Then is he the culprit?
I still have a bad feeling
about Director Ji.
What happened?
Did you track his location?
So you're trying to
work things out with Ha Jin?
I can't let that happen.
Is anybody there?
Ha Jin, wait a little.
Don't come near me!
Who are you, you jerk?
No matter what you do
and how much you try,
you will never lay a finger on her.