(Episode 1)
He came to the ER at dawn.
Hey, does it hurt a lot?
I asked for an orthopedist.
Why is it you again?
Why do you suddenly want
a different doctor?
It hurts even when I just touch you?
I'll give you some analgesics.
Have you been using crutches?
I can't even walk due to the pain,
so I have to use them.
Just get me an orthopedist.
Why do you keep
asking for an orthopedist?
I want my leg amputated.
What?
I can't play soccer with this leg.
I'm always walking with a limp
because it hurts.
So I'd rather
just have it amputated.
How are you going to play soccer...
with an amputated leg?
Are you going to give up?
I'm not giving up. I just can't play
because of the pain.
How am I supposed to play soccer
with this leg?
You're right.
There's no point in playing soccer
when you're not well.
Call orthopedics.
I already did, but he needs to wait
at least a month.
What should we do?
I guess there's no other choice.
I'll amputate it for you.
You... You're going to do it?
How can a psychiatrist
perform surgery?
Why can't I?
I even fix people's minds.
Amputating a leg is easy.
I think you made the right choice.
Let's just get rid of this leg.
You're always sick,
and you can't even play soccer.
So what's the point
of having this leg?
I'll make sure
to cut it nice and clean.
These days, artificial legs
are very nicely made.
So you won't even need crutches.
Let's get ready for surgery.
- Okay.
- Let's go.
My gosh.
- Sorry about this.
- Hey, wait.
What... What are you doing?
We need you to stay still.
- Please wait just a little bit.
- No, wait.
Just a second.
Why... Why do you need
to tie me down?
No! No!
No! No! Don't!
Did you really think I'd do it here?
Take him to the OR.
- Doctor.
- We're almost there.
- Let's go.
- You're really going to cut it off?
Doctor, I don't think this is right.
No, wait.
- Please wait.
- Gosh, wait!
- We're here now.
- Let me go!
- Let me leave.
- Sir.
- Where are you going?
- Don't come near me!
Wait!
Sir! Wait!
I'm sorry.
My gosh.
(Eun Kang Medical Center)
They're completely nuts.
They're crazy.
Yu Min.
You forgot your crutches.
You ran so fast.
You really are an MVP.
(Eun Kang Medical Center)
There's something called
a somatic symptom disorder.
You feel pain when nothing is wrong
with your body.
It's a type of nervous disease.
That's what you've been
suffering from.
You kept losing,
so you lost your confidence.
Your game performance
only kept getting worse.
And due to severe stress,
your leg suddenly started to hurt
when it was actually fine.
Suddenly, I found myself
getting scared of playing soccer.
So what if you don't win
all the time?
That can't be more important
than your leg.
Who doesn't make mistakes?
And think about it.
That game you played in Tokyo
against Japan.
You ran through three defenders...
and dribbled the ball
all by yourself for over 60m.
Then you scored by kicking the ball
right through two other defenders.
Gosh, I almost got...
a heart attack
while watching that game on TV.
You were amazing.
The number of times
you made mistakes is nothing...
compared to your achievements.
Why do you think people call you
"Golden Left Foot"?
"Golden Left Foot, Oh Yu Min!"
My hometown
Is Namwon
Where Chun Hyang
Once lived
I was
Only 16 years old
A young and cheerful girl
With so many dreams
But one morning
The fog was dense
And we were dragged away
By men with swords
We didn't know why
Or where we were going
No one told us anything
Just like our country
That was taken from us
Our fate
Was walking the same path
It was my first performance
as the main character.
It was after 10 years of having been
a minor or supporting actress.
Who were those people?
Fans of Baek Jenny,
the famous idol star.
She was also cast for the same role.
Why did her fans do that?
Because they think I'm bullying her.
Is that true?
She always made a mess
of the dressing room.
She's so irresponsible.
- The last part was the best.
- Seriously.
I was always the one
who had to clean up.
- That part was the best.
- The guy was so handsome.
- I should do my best.
- You're already amazing.
What got me really angry...
was when she ripped my outfit
but didn't even get them mended.
("Dawn")
(We cheer for Jenny.)
(Beautiful Jenny! Good luck!)
(The smiling fairy, Baek Jenny)
What a joke.
(We wish "Dawn" a huge success.)
(We will continue to be your stan.)
I got on their bad side that day.
You have no idea how much
they drove me nuts...
during the past two months
of the show.
The day that was abandoned
At the break of dawn
After a long journey
We were
Abandoned
They made reservations
and didn't show up on purpose.
They wanted to make
a fool out of me.
Doctor, don't I have every right
to be angry?
Yes, of course.
But the problem is
the way you portrayed your anger.
I know.
You told me...
to count to six
every time I get angry.
I didn't know six seconds
was that long.
- You did great.
- The show was amazing.
- I loved it.
- You rocked the show.
- I'm serious.
- You were great.
- I'm so proud of you.
- Really?
- Yes, of course.
One.
Two.
Three.
I should've kept counting.
Did anything else
make you get angry recently?
I saw a kid crying outside.
His mom just left him behind.
- Let's go find your mom. Come here.
- Mom.
There we go.
Hey, wait!
How could you
leave him behind like that?
What do you care?
Are you kidding me?
Do you want him to think
that you abandoned him?
I'll raise my kid the way I want to.
I'm telling you this
because you're doing a bad job!
She apparently did that
to teach him a lesson.
Woo Joo, why do you think
you cared about that kid so much?
You told me...
that your life changed
after you turned six years old.
If you don't mind, can you tell me
what happened back then?
What does this have anything to do
with my past?
It won't help to keep avoiding it.
I'm not avoiding it.
I think I should go now.
But we still have some time left.
(Ji Young Won Psychiatric Clinic)
(11th counseling, Shows no progress)
(Intermittent explosive disorder)
(Might have a suspicious borderline
personality disorder)
(Police)
Sir, you're not allowed
to urinate there.
- What?
- Sir.
I'm sorry.
Sir, are you okay?
I'm a cop. Do you need help?
I'm not drunk. I'm fine.
You say you're not drunk,
but that means you are.
No, I'm not drunk.
I'm completely fine.
Where do you live?
We'll get you a cab.
I'm fine.
I'm not drunk at all.
I'm really not drunk.
We should go home now.
Your shift is over.
Constable Cha Dong Il,
returning to the station, over.
You did great today, Constable Cha.
You too. Thanks for helping.
Stop. Who are you?
- Are you all right?
- He took my bag.
- Darn it.
- Hey, you! Stop!
Stop!
Get out of the way!
Darn it!
Stop!
My gosh.
- Shoot.
- He's over here!
Stop!
I got you.
Don't move.
Don't move! Don't move.
He caught the guy.
It was a mistake.
I meant to kick the knife.
I underestimated my leg's reach...
and kicked his head.
Anyway,
he turned out to be fine,
so the police took him right away.
Why were you there?
I happened to be passing by.
You were passing by...
and happened to meet a patient
who had gone AWOL?
Yes.
He left the hospital before,
and you knew and let it happen.
So that... You're mistaken, sir.
You play police with...
a patient who has
a delusional disorder?
What do you think you're doing?
You even speak casually
with other patients?
That's to befriend them quickly.
That way, they open up easily.
Summon the disciplinary committee.
I won't let this slide.
Why summon the disciplinary
committee over this?
A month ago, your
fake police officer patient...
used excessive force on
a sexual predator in the subway,
causing an injury that'll take
six weeks to heal!
Two weeks ago, he entered a bar...
and checked if they hired minors!
You're the one who let him do that!
Mr. Deputy Director.
It wasn't 6 weeks. It was just 2.
Transfer that patient immediately.
Are you telling me to
give up on my patient?
The average number of outpatients...
a psychiatrist must see
each day is 60.
You have other patients.
Why are you so fixated on him?
I'll take fewer patients then.
Mr. Deputy Director.
Won't it work as long as the patient
doesn't leave the hospital again?
Dr. Lee.
Do you agree that
you won't let the patient...
leave the hospital again?
Do you agree?
- Yes.
- If it happens again,
will you have him transferred?
I will.
He agreed. If the patient
leaves again,
have him transferred
and leave it at that.
I'm not on patrol...
with Cha Dong Il just for fun.
He has a rare kind of
delusional disorder...
that causes him to think
he is what he isn't.
You know patients with delusional
disorders don't trust their carers.
I'm doing this to build rapport.
You can't just ban me from helping.
He's in panic mode.
He's in shock because
he was told he can't patrol again.
Then...
you must take him out immediately
and patrol the neighborhood.
- Can I do that?
- Go ahead.
I'll have a car ready
to take him to another hospital.
Are you threatening me or what?
That's more than enough rapport.
Stop talking about patrol.
Follow the books...
and put him on medication
right away.
(Cha Dong Il)
- He's been like that forever?
- He won't even eat.
He's protesting because
we won't let him patrol.
He'll eat when he's hungry.
Dermatology asked for a consult?
- Yes, just now.
- What's the case?
Next patient, come in, please.
You can't scratch yourself.
Let me...
Don't spray that.
- Let go of me!
- Stop it.
The patient believes that
insects live in her skin.
She has serious wounds.
Kim Yu Ra, 29 years old.
She was diagnosed with
contact dermatitis at a clinic...
and prescribed diphenhydramine
and a steroid ointment.
Her symptoms didn't subside,
so she came to
our dermatology department.
The dermatology specialist...
decided it's not simple dermatitis,
and suggested
she see a psychiatrist.
The patient vehemently refused,
only to return three months later.
Dermatology asked us for a consult.
It's most likely...
a physical delusional disorder
that involves parasites.
From the photos,
I'd say she sprayed something.
Yes. Disinfectants, insecticides,
herbicides, anything that'll
kill bugs, she sprayed.
Shouldn't we suspect
poisoning due to insecticides too?
Good point. She coughs
and has difficulty breathing.
How do you think we should
proceed with treating her?
First, we must calm her
with medicine.
Most physical
delusional disorders...
are accompanied by anxiety issues.
A benzodiazepine
anti-anxiety drug should suffice.
With delusional disorders,
I believe an anti-psychotic
is the treatment of choice.
But...
if you start by medicating
a patient without any rapport,
do you think the medicine will help?
Which is why I think we should
start with psychological counseling.
The patient's vehemently
refusing psychiatric help,
so how will you do that?
Why not speak with her family?
Will the patient wait?
I have a feeling...
she'll scratch off her skin
before we manage that.
I think going out as a team
is the only option.
To find out what happened to her.
Why are you sitting there?
I'll get going now.
- Good luck.
- Thanks.
We might get her to talk first.
That's your method.
I'll deal with my patients
my own way.
See you.
Why must I see a psychiatrist
for a skin problem?
Are you saying there's
something wrong with my mind?
I'm just checking if there are
any psychological issues.
You don't have to take it
too seriously.
I'll ask a few simple questions,
then have you admitted
to treat your skin.
You said that insects
keep burrowing out of your arm?
Yes.
But the dermatologist
won't believe me.
When did this start?
A little under three months ago.
Did something happen to shock
or upset you around that time?
Listen.
Do you want to say that
stress caused this?
Not really.
You're so annoying.
What are you doing?
I'm done. Just a moment.
Ms. Kim. Look at this photo.
The photo doesn't show any insects.
It seems like you're the only one
who can see the insects.
So why don't we try to figure out...
why this is happening?
You're calling me crazy, aren't you?
- No, that's not it.
- Don't lie to me.
Remember Kim Yu Ra that got
sent here from Dermatology?
Have her hospitalized right now.
Okay.
Do you want her hospitalized
at the psychiatric ward?
No, she's showing
a lot of resistance.
So send her to the general ward.
Okay, bye.
We didn't know why
Or where we were going
No one told us anything
Just like
("Dawn")
(Musical Practice Room)
Sir.
Idol stars get paid
70,000 dollars per show.
But we only get paid 70 dollars.
We're only asking for
a 20-dollar raise.
Are we really asking for too much?
We don't even have
official practice sessions.
So we practice on our own
and buy our own food.
My gosh,
I guess there's no other choice.
You guys should just quit.
I don't want this fight
to get any bigger.
You should just quit.
Sir, you can't do this.
We only have 15 days
until the show begins.
You're unbelievable.
Don't worry about the show.
Tons of people are
willing to replace these guys.
That's why you guys are
only worth 70 dollars.
An idol star is irreplaceable.
That's why they get paid 70,000.
You're upset, aren't you?
But if you're that upset,
you should work hard and succeed...
instead of crying like a baby.
Sir.
What you're doing is wrong.
They may only play minor roles,
but it's wrong to humiliate them.
Woo Joo, you've changed a lot.
You finally got yourself a lead role
after 10 long years.
And now,
you think you're all that?
How dare you try to lecture me
about right and wrong?
That's not what I meant.
Don't you know
who gave you that role...
and who helped you become
a candidate for an award?
You'd better watch what you say.
You might lose everything overnight.
My gosh.
(Gongbap Restaurant)
Eat up.
Chew your food properly.
My phone doesn't work
because I couldn't pay the bills.
And he's about to get kicked out
from his room.
I'm sorry, you guys.
You're the reason why
we were able to hang in there.
You always bought us food and
gave us money for transportation.
Thank you.
I'll never forget
how kind you were to me.
Why are you crying...
while eating?
I suddenly remembered...
the gloves you gave me last winter.
You told me I should stay warm.
I used to wear those gloves.
They were used. Don't cry.
Those gloves...
were so warm.
You can't give up.
Okay?
Ji Sun, give us
some strong alcohol...
so it'll knock them out.
And can you give us some warm soup?
That's enough.
Mr. Cha, you didn't eat again?
Are you going to keep doing this?
Should I order pizza for you?
Just let him starve.
It must be tormenting
to starve for so long.
If I don't go on patrol,
I might get disciplined.
Do you know how hard I studied
to become a cop?
Why did you become a cop?
It's cool.
I also have a friend...
like you.
You have a friend like me?
He lost his parents
when he was young,
and he was raised
by his grandmother.
But they weren't financially stable.
When he was about 15 years old,
he stole bread
at a convenience store...
because he was hungry,
but he got caught.
But thanks to a certain cop,
he was able to avoid getting sent...
to a youth detention center.
Ever since then,
he dreamed of becoming a cop.
But he kept failing the test...
because he had to work part-time
as he studied for the test.
And in the end,
his grandmother passed away...
without being able to see
her grandson become a cop.
She died due to a DUI car accident.
On the day of her funeral,
he stole a cop's uniform
and wore it...
so he could make
his grandmother's dream come true.
But he kept wearing the uniform
even after the funeral,
and it made him feel like
a real cop.
And ever since then, he actually
started to think of himself as one.
You know
who I'm talking about, right?
(Congratulations
on your graduation!)
I know...
how hard it is
for you to hear this.
But you know you're not a cop.
Why do you keep telling me
that I'm not a cop?
I need to patrol the neighborhood.
Let me out of here right now.
You can't do that anymore.
I won't allow it.
You want to patrol the neighborhood?
Then become a real cop.
- You fools.
- Don't.
Oh, right.
Woo Joo.
- Taxi fees.
- Wake up.
- No, no.
- Take a taxi.
I don't need money.
- No, thanks.
- Yes, you do. Take it.
She's just too caring.
Thank you.
You two, you know how much
I care for you, don't you?
Go on home now.
Hey. Wake up, will you?
Wake up.
My gosh.
You'll spend all you have.
Food, drink, and allowances too?
Are you a charity worker?
I'd like to be a charity worker.
You're too generous.
Stop eating.
Woo Joo, long time no see.
- You too.
- Who are you?
You look familiar,
but I don't know who you are.
I know. I won't even recognize you
on the streets now.
Why does she look like such a mess?
No matter how much she dresses up,
it doesn't make a difference.
I'm hungry.
Give me something to eat.
There's nothing.
We're out of ingredients.
What? You've got to be kidding me.
I starved all day long.
Make me some noodles then.
Just eat me instead.
Hey!
How could you really bite me?
- Give me food, I'm hungry.
- Let go.
- What's with you? Let go of me.
- Make me food.
What's the matter with you?
(Eun Kang Medical Center)
Dr. Lee.
What a rare sight
to see you going home.
You came back?
I have no one waiting at home
anyway.
Right.
Here.
It's a picture of Kim Yu Ra
from three months ago.
She's totally different
compared to now.
This is really a picture of her?
Yes. Her guardian verified it.
Considering that it's been
three months...
since she received treatment
for dermatitis,
I think something happened
back then.
But...
you went to a patient's home to
find out the cause of her illness?
You do that too.
Hey.
Do you think
there's a way I can help them?
Stop being so nosy.
Stop meddling in other's business.
How could you call them others?
They're my juniors who work with me.
How could you still be drinking...
when you have an
awards ceremony tomorrow?
Your face will be super swollen.
It was my dream to step on
the red carpet at least once.
I'm about to achieve that dream
tomorrow...
but strangely, I'm not that happy.
Stop worrying meaninglessly...
and go home and sleep.
What are you doing tomorrow?
Are you going to
the baseball stadium again?
I'm going to the awards ceremony too
to cover a story.
Really?
Hey, then we'll finally be able to
see each other tomorrow.
Do you like it?
You need to wait 15 minutes.
Sorry.
Yes, sir?
I'm getting ready now.
What? Me?
I might really receive an award?
Of course, don't worry.
I won't be late.
Yes. Okay.
Get out! Get out!
I'm not going!
Ma'am, calm down.
Please calm down and listen...
No! I won't go to see
a psychiatrist!
I told you I'm not crazy!
How is she?
She's refusing every drug,
and she won't take a shot either.
She's resisting pretty severely.
- What is this?
- It's a picture of Kim Yu Ra.
Woo Jung found this yesterday.
It's a picture from
three months ago.
This is?
She lost so much weight,
and it's hard to recognize her.
Don't you think this is the cause
of her delusion?
Woo Jung hit the jackpot.
Yes.
Okay.
- Why? Is something wrong?
- I have to go.
(Ward 1, Entrance)
Dr. Lee.
Are you sure?
Did you search everywhere?
I checked the security cameras.
He went outside.
What should we do?
If he's caught,
he'll be forced to transfer.
What do we do?
- Who else knows about this?
- No one but us.
We didn't tell anyone.
No one can find out about this
until I find him. Got it?
- Yes.
- Yes, sir.
Okay.
Do you understand what
you guys did wrong now?
- Yes, we're sorry, sir.
- We're sorry.
- What's your plan henceforth?
- We'll move faster, sir!
We'll try harder, sir!
All three of you better find out
how to treat Kim Yu Ra...
and bring me the results
as soon as possible.
- Yes, sir.
I warned him so seriously
that he must not leave.
You just wait.
I won't let this slide this time.
There's heavy traffic
near Seongsan interchange...
but Seongsan-ro is showing
smooth traffic both ways.
Shinyoung three-way intersection...
is showing signs of
slow traffic near downtown,
but there isn't any
heavy congestion yet.
Dongbu Expressway near
Changdong Bridge...
is showing heavy congestion
both ways,
and there is also heavy traffic
up to Nokcheon Bridge,
between Jungnang Bridge
and Gunja Bridge,
and also near Seongdong Bridge.
Also, there is partial congestion
between Topyeong IC...
and Gangil IC near Seoul Expressway.
We're expecting more traffic...
(2020 Korean Musical Awards)
It's been such a long time.
Wait. You can pass.
- Thank you.
Guys!
You don't look familiar.
Which division do you work for?
I'm Constable Cha Dong Il
of Eunpyeong Division.
I see.
I guess you came from so far
because of the celebrities.
- Let's move!
- Thank you.
Get in.
Yes, I think so.
Does Eunpyeong...
Team Five, go to the parking lot
and sort things out.
Team Five is on its way.
(2020 Korean Musical Awards)
(Lee Ji Su is the best!)
What's going on?
Wait.
Me?
You can't park here.
Move your car.
Oh, I'm sorry. I know, but...
I really have to go inside
right now.
I'll come right back out
and park again.
I'm in a real hurry. Please.
Did you drink?
No, I didn't.
Can you please blow into this?
I really didn't drink.
Why? Do I smell or something?
Oh, last night.
It's because I drank last night.
Blow.
Which division do you work in?
I'm Constable Cha Dong Il
of Eunpyeong Division.
Then after the awards ceremony,
I'll go to your precinct
and blow it.
Will that do?
Are you refusing to take
a sobriety test?
Are you satisfied?
Your blood alcohol level is 0.08.
Your license will be revoked.
- What?
- You need to come to the station.
This doesn't make sense...
I said I didn't drink.
I drank last night.
You need to come with me.
Okay, I understand.
But... I really have to go in there
right now.
I'll go find you after the ceremony.
I promise.
I'm sorry.
Stop right there.
You'll be arrested for a crime
if you run away.
Constable Cha.
Didn't you hear the radio?
The VIP is about to enter,
so come up to the front.
- Woo Joo.
- My gosh.
- Why did you jump?
- It's nothing.
Do you feel nervous?
Very.
Let's go inside.
The ceremony starts soon.
Let's go.
Hey. Did you find him?
He's not nearby.
Ji Hee called
all the local stations...
and couldn't find him.
What now?
Should we report him missing?
Yes. Report him missing.
And call the hospital.
- But let's keep looking.
- Okay.
Woo Jung, wait.
Cha Dong Il.
I found him.
What's he doing there?
Congratulations.
Please give them a lot of applause.
(2020 Korean Musical Awards)
Now for the nominees for
Best Female Newcomer.
Presenting the award
is last year's winner,
Ms. Baek Jenny.
(I love you, Baek Jenny.)
Hello, I'm Baek Jenny.
I feel so nervous
and I'm the presenter.
Let's find out who was nominated.
(Nominees for Best Female Newcomer)
Lee Yoon Ha from "Hoop's Court".
Here, there are
no politics or destiny
All I need is to make
a choice in a moment
Lee Ji Su from
"The Legend of King Arthur".
If a new road
is paved in my direction
I will give my soul in return
Choi Seo Yeon from
"Welcome, Transylvania".
I love you
I love you too
I need you
I would cross the sea
And finally,
Han Woo Joo from "Dawn".
Just like our country
That was taken from us
Our fate
Was walking the same path
I'll announce the winner.
The 25th Korean Musical Awards,
Best Female Newcomer.
(Best Female Newcomer)
Han Woo Joo from "Dawn".
Congratulations.
Congratulations, Ms. Han Woo Joo.
The passion and energy
you show on stage,
alongside your great voice
are just amazing.
(2020 Korean Musical Awards)
- Who's he?
- What's going on?
What's this?
Who on earth is that?
Can you please blow into this?
What's happening?
I guess a surprise event
was arranged.
Is this a scene from a musical?
What are you doing?
For refusing
to take a sobriety test,
according to Article 148
of the Road Traffic Act,
and for obstruction,
according to Chapter 8 Article 136
of the Criminal Code,
you're under arrest.
Well done!
You have the right to remain silent,
and everything you say can be
used against you in court.
You can also appoint a lawyer.
What's happening?
Is this for real?
Hey. Listen.
Mister.
- Woo Joo.
- Hey.
What happened? Is he a real cop?
What's this about?
She drove under the influence.
Even so...
How could you do that
during an award ceremony?
Drunk driving is a felony.
I arrested her because
I think she's a flight risk.
Did you really drive drunk?
I did drink,
but I drank yesterday, not today!
Cha Dong Il!
What happened?
She refused to take
a sobriety test,
so I'm bringing her in.
Hey...
I apologize.
He's a rookie and
doesn't know what he's doing.
I'd like to apologize instead.
Who are you?
I am...
his senior partner.
- What?
- It's not right...
to barge in...
and arrest someone
during a live broadcast.
I apologize. I'm truly sorry.
I'm very sorry.
If you take this to the police,
things will get very complicated.
Shall we wrap it up right here?
Uncuff her right now.
Uncuff her or we both die.
Uncuff her before people swarm over.
Reporters will barge in soon.
Uncuff her this instant!
Don't just stand there!
Let her go.
You're under arrest for
impersonating a civil servant.
You have the right to
refuse to give a statement...
and can hire a lawyer.
What are you doing?
He's not an officer.
What is he then?
Who are you?
He's a doctor.
I'm sorry.
I am...
a psychiatrist.
His psychiatrist.
His...
What do you mean
you're his psychiatrist?
The truth is,
he isn't a policeman.
Then what is he?
Why did he put me in handcuffs?
He is...
my patient.
He's a patient? A patient?
Are you saying that he's crazy?
There they are.
Ms. Han, do you admit the charges?
How will you explain this?
- Isn't this a scandal?
- Did you drink before coming here?
How do you feel right now?
Why did you refuse a sobriety test?
At the Korean Musical
Awards ceremony today,
Han Woo Joo who won
Best Female Newcomer...
was arrested for drunk driving...
when she was on stage
to receive her award.
It turned out that...
- a delusional disorder patient...
- What now?
This is shocking.
When did Cha Dong Il sneak out?
As of now, the details...
None of us knew, right?
The fake officer...
We're not responsible, right?
Didn't you say...
he'd be transferred
if he escaped again?
He has to be.
Next news.
Did he have to arrest Woo Joo?
Do you know her?
We're close too.
What now?
Mr. Cha who suffers from...
a delusional disorder
arrested an actress...
on stage during an award ceremony.
He went on stage...
and brazenly managed to...
put handcuffs on Ms. Han Woo Joo.
Everyone attending the ceremony...
believed it was a surprise event.
My gosh.
I knew something bad would happen.
He's known to have carried out
random sobriety tests.
Ji Sun. Are you okay?
So where is Woo Joo right now?
At the police station, I think.
Close up for me.
There's no point in
going over there now.
You don't even know
which station she's at.
Calm down and wait until
you hear from her.
How did she end up getting arrested?
How can you get handcuffed
and dragged out on a live TV show?
He isn't a real officer.
He's one of our patients.
That's why I'm so furious!
What did you lot do?
Who's his doctor?
It's me, Ji Sun.
I was in charge of his floor.
How could you do that to Woo Joo?
I'm so annoyed!
He got into huge trouble this time.
Don't you people
control your patients?
He has a severe delusional disorder.
Blame everything on the hospital...
and please let him off lightly.
You can say that to the judge.
Forget about everything else.
Take my blood.
- What?
- Do a blood alcohol test.
I feel really wronged!
Don't worry.
A fake cop
can't revoke your license.
That's not the issue right now!
Take some of my blood already!
Take my blood!
Right now.
It says nothing.
What?
This is the real thing.
It's broken.
It's broken?
- Blow into this.
- Okay.
It's broken.
It says 0.08 percent all the time.
Then...
this happened to me
because a fake cop...
shoved a broken machine in my face?
Just a moment.
Hey.
I just took another test...
and I wasn't drunk driving.
Can you write about it?
I didn't drive drunk...
and the machine was broken.
No, wait.
How about you interview me?
Okay.
I'm going into a meeting.
I'll talk to you later.
This was just an accident.
Like a car accident.
I couldn't have done anything,
so I can make things right.
The sobriety test was wrong...
and the fake cop
was just a happening.
The receiver cannot be reached.
You will be...
Are you okay, Woo Joo?
Where are you?
Did you see this video?
Did you really drive drunk?
I did drink,
but I drank yesterday, not today!
Hang on.
Why is this...
- Mister.
- Yes?
- Turn the car around.
- Okay.
It's okay, he's always
like that. Don't mind him.
What shall we eat?
Whatever you want to eat.
Isn't she Han Woo Joo?
Stay in the car. Don't come out.
Are you two-timing me?
How could someone like me do that?
She's a friend.
- Did you like it?
- As if.
- She's just a friend.
- Not that.
Getting an exclusive scoop.
Did you like it, you scumbag?
You jerk.
I had no choice.
My superior saw it first and...
Hey. Hey!
What are you...
Han Woo Joo!
Everyone creates a basement
in their heart.
And in that basement,
they hide their secrets.
Things that other people don't know.
What are you hiding
in your basement?
(Special thanks to Wi Ha Joon.)
(Fix You)
Must I abandon my patient?
Are you the only doctor?
Actors are all about the image.
What does the truth matter?
Could you please settle?
Why should I settle?
Why is my life so messed up?
I just want to live like
other people.
Oh? What are you doing here?
Oh Yu Min said he's your fan.
- Did he really?
- Yes!
He did it!
Why do you keep
treating me like a patient?
It feels really messed up!
Woo Joo, get down from there.
It's very dangerous.
I have a patient for you.
You met already.
Darn...
Where did you learn to
swear like that?