(Episode 3)
(Police)
Earlier, you came as a victim.
And now, you're here as an assailant.
Hello.
My gosh.
You've been investigated multiple times for assault.
The victim doesn't want you to get punished.
So we're going to let you go.
But you'll have to pay a fine...
for having committed criminal damage.
And you really shouldn't wield baseball bats like that.
It could lead to a big accident.
- I'd rather get punished. - What?
Just lock me up in a holding cell.
If you don't, I might go and kill that jerk!
So just have me locked up.
Excuse me.
What? Do you have something to say?
I know this may sound shameless,
but can you please settle?
I'm responsible for what happened as his doctor.
It's all my fault.
I'm so sorry.
Why should I be so merciful?
I went through so much for the past 10 years.
And now, I finally got to see the spotlight.
But I suddenly became a law-breaking offender.
On top of that, my boyfriend even backstabbed me.
Then I got investigated for assault, and people will think I'm crazy.
So why in the world should I show mercy?
Why should I settle?
Right.
It really was...
shameful of me to ask.
Don't even bother to apologize.
I'm not going to settle.
Okay, I understand.
I'm very sorry.
What's going on?
(A Megalomaniac Patient Causes an Absurd Scene)
What's happening?
He's arresting her.
What's going on right now?
I heard this patient escaped from the hospital numerous times.
How do you think we should hold Si Joon responsible?
What do you think about settling the issue...
by having the patient transferred?
You think we should just let it slide?
Si Joon is the face of our hospital who received both...
the Asan Award in Medicine and the Yuhan Medical Award.
The face of the hospital can always change.
He's already fully booked for the entire year.
Why don't you forgive him for the sake of his patients?
You know very well that I let him off the hook...
numbers of times because of that.
Then think of this as his last time.
Please do me a favor, ma'am.
Dr. Park.
Why are you trying so hard to protect Si Joon?
Can't the psychiatric department function without him?
I'm also responsible for what happened as his superior.
I want you to stop giving him research expenses.
But that's a bit too...
Okay, I'll do that.
Hello, sir.
Where is Cha Dong Il?
He's in a holding cell.
They're going to send him to prosecution tomorrow.
Once he's freed, I want him transferred right away.
- What? - You promised...
to have him transferred if he escapes the hospital again.
Let's not argue about this.
Why are you doing this?
Are you telling me to abandon my patient?
There are other doctors.
You're not the only doctor who can treat him.
The fact that you've failed to treat him until now...
means your method is wrong.
Haven't you ever thought of that?
My method isn't wrong.
This is your problem.
Hasn't it ever crossed your mind that you might've worsened it?
Who are you? Stop right there!
- Stop! - Darn it.
Stop right there!
Move! Out of the way!
Oh, gosh.
- This way. - Careful.
Go on.
Thank you.
It's so salty.
You put too much soy sauce on it.
Was I really wrong?
(Eun Kang Medical Center)
(Hospital Director Office)
I thought we settled this yesterday.
What more do you have to say?
Please let me treat...
Cha Dong Il.
Dr. Lee.
This isn't something to beg about.
If his doctor suddenly changes,
he might never be able to get better.
Don't tell me you think you're the best.
As a psychiatrist treats his or her patient,
they build something called a therapeutic relationship.
If that breaks,
the patient will feel abandoned, and it'll worsen their symptoms.
And that could cause them to do something extreme.
Are you scaring me right now?
Can you let me treat him until he gets his trial result?
I'll try my best to convince the victim to settle.
Doesn't Cha Dong Il have a family?
Why would you do that for him? You're just his doctor.
The doctors at our hospital care for our patients like family.
Please do me a favor, ma'am.
Hello.
- Hi. - Hello.
Hey, you guys.
- Hello. - Hello.
Hello.
Ms. Han, what are you doing here?
What do you mean? I'm here to practice.
Didn't the assistant director tell you anything?
I wanted you off the show.
Where's the assistant director? Why can't he do his job properly?
Sir.
I already proved that I was sober that day.
It's true that I got humiliated in front of the entire nation.
But it was just an accident, and he was a megalomaniac.
I know that.
But actors and actresses need to keep a clean image.
The truth doesn't matter.
Haven't you seen the internet?
Everyone's talking about you.
You got dragged away in handcuffs in the middle of an award show.
I can't put you on stage again. Do you want me to ruin the show?
I'll ask the reporter to write a corrected version of the article.
Sir, I'm a victim.
Let's be honest. This isn't the first time you caused a problem.
You also caused lots of problems during the past show.
- That's... - I heard you're receiving therapy.
Is that why I'm getting fired?
The director feels burdened to have you on the show.
And they're all scared of you.
What are you guys doing?
Hurry up and practice.
- Yes, sir. - Yes, sir.
Stay focused.
The show starts in a few days.
- Okay, sir. - Okay, sir.
One.
Two.
Three.
Four.
Five.
Six.
(Gongbap Restaurant)
Yes.
Ma'am, can we have two more glasses?
Glasses? Okay.
Can we have more kimchi?
You can help yourself. It's over there by the counter.
She's busy.
Here you go.
Hey, stop it.
This is great.
- I really like this one. - Me too.
My gosh, you're hilarious.
Drink up.
Stop it, I'm going to beat you.
What is it
That's making you so sad?
When the earth gets covered in green grass
And the ripples gently
(Pedestrian Entrance)
What brings you here?
Did you get hurt?
I'm here to meet that guy. The fake cop.
Where is he? Can I meet him?
He's not here.
Why isn't he here?
Are you protecting him?
He's with the prosecution.
Why don't you get yourself treated?
- It looks like you got injured. - It's okay.
If you don't get it treated, it might get infected.
You shouldn't underestimate small wounds like this.
Foreign substances could enter your body and form pus.
And if things get worse,
you might have to get it amputated.
Are you trying to scare me?
Why did you want to meet my patient?
You can't sleep here.
Let me sleep a little.
Wait.
This isn't a hotel. It's a hospital.
I like how it's so crowded.
This is what you call life.
Dr. Lee.
Are you on duty again?
Woo Jung didn't get to go home for the past few days.
Dr. Lee, I respect you so much.
It sounds like you're trying to flatter me.
Gosh, that's not true.
But why do I keep smelling alcohol?
Woo Joo?
- Do you know her? - She's my older sister's friend.
Really?
Did she get hurt?
No, she fell asleep because she's drunk.
- I'll wake her up right now. - Just leave her.
You don't need to shed blood to be an emergency patient.
("An Actress Gets Arrested for DUI by a Fake Police Officer")
Are you busy?
Didn't you eat dinner?
I'm eating it now thanks to you.
You sound excited.
Are you happy that you're busy?
But what's up? It sounded urgent.
I want you to entrust you with a patient.
- What kind of patient? - She has trouble controlling anger.
How bad is it? Does she have IED?
She sometimes can't even do her job properly because of that.
So I guess you could call it that.
Why do you want me to treat her?
I had 11 therapy sessions with her,
but I don't see any progress.
And I'm starting to lose confidence because there's no progress at all.
You know I get depressed if I don't receive acknowledgment.
Gosh, stop being such a baby.
Okay, I'll meet her.
You already have.
Who is she?
Han Woo Joo.
Where am I?
What?
Where is this place?
What brings you here?
Let me sleep a little.
This isn't a hotel. It's a hospital.
I can't believe this.
This is crazy. I must've been nuts.
What's the matter with me?
Hey! You know we're always short of hospital beds.
How could you let a drunk woman sleep there?
Do you think this is a hotel?
An ER is where we treat emergency patients.
Not all emergency patients...
come with a burst intestine or a severe wound.
What are you talking about?
My patients also have the right to get admitted as an ER patient.
Will you please wake up?
Tons of patients get sent away because there's no room for them.
Thank goodness she didn't cause a scene in the ER.
You're a psychiatrist. You should know better.
Do you remember...
Hey. Hey!
I'm no longer the guy I used to be!
(Outpatient Elevators)
Are you running away?
You caught me.
Follow me.
Why are you looking at me like that?
You were pretty cool earlier.
"Not all emergency patients come..."
"with a burst intestine or a severe wound".
You're a true actor.
That's how you looked last night, Ms. Han.
Was I mistaken?
I was let go from this production.
I sang my lungs out for two months.
I'm the victim, but they turned me into the assailant.
Just because I have a temper.
She has trouble controlling anger.
How bad is it? Does she have IED?
She sometimes can't even do her job properly because of that.
So I guess you could call it that.
The worst part is,
my boyfriend two-timed me and says it's my fault.
Because I have a temper.
Does that make sense?
- He's total trash. - A scumbag jerk.
Is that enough?
Oh, do you not know how to curse?
I'll poke out your darn tongue and use it to swat flies.
Do you mean something like this?
Yes, like that. You're pretty good.
I may look gentle and handsome,
but I speak quite coarsely. Just a moment.
(Prescription)
You're the worst punk I've ever seen!
I'd love to spill 18 boiling cups of tea on you!
Shall I switch around the order of your ribs?
Before I do that,
disappear to some Siberian plain!
My goodness.
I feel much better.
I was dying to cuss someone out.
Where did you learn to swear like that?
I get cussed out a lot, you see.
Here and there.
Use it whenever you need to.
(Prescription. Put your true feelings inside.)
(Prescription)
I'll settle with your patient.
How nice.
Doctor, Cha Dong Il's here.
How is he?
He looked dejected.
He didn't put up a fight.
He's with Ji Hee now.
He must've learned something after that disaster.
I'll make him pay this time.
Are you all right?
Here's a present.
A present? For me?
Open it quick.
(Congratulations on your promotion.)
You're a corporal now.
You did well until now, so we're promoting you.
You're really promoting me?
Is this true?
It's true.
It's real.
Good job.
Do you know how many great deeds...
you did while on patrol?
You caught a bag-snatcher and stopped a fight.
You organized traffic too.
And you got into trouble looking after the drunk.
You did so well.
We all know that.
You did a better job than some real officers.
Although you're not a real officer,
after everything that you did,
you deserve some respect.
So don't think that you failed.
Just because you're not someone...
doesn't mean you failed in life.
To us, you are a police officer.
Mr. Cha, you did well until now.
Good job.
You were amazing, Corporal Cha.
Corporal Cha.
Delusions...
come to you when you can't accept your reality.
(Cha Dong Il)
When you start denying your reality because you can't accept it,
you create a world of illusion.
Eventually, you believe that to be true.
After seeing that photo,
I assumed that something shocking may have happened to you...
three months ago.
That's when you started to believe that parasites lived in your skin.
Can you tell me what happened?
It began...
when he left me.
He called me an insect.
Sometimes, a huge shock...
makes you want to deny your life.
Psychiatric experts say...
delusional disorders are caused by...
excessive amounts of dopamine in the brain's limbic system.
But that's what the bookworms think.
The biggest cause is...
having a broken soul.
That's why people need a repairman like me.
Don't measure yourself with standards set by others.
Praise and reproach...
are all...
just a passing breeze.
They don't last.
Whatever your illness may be, don't struggle alone.
I don't know what to do.
If you can overcome it on your own,
it's not an illness.
Who are you to call me that?
It hurts.
I'm scared and in pain.
The moment you admit your pain,
the healing begins.
A psychiatrist's secret ramblings.
This is the Soul Repairman.
You referred the actress you were treating,
to Si Joon?
He hasn't agreed yet.
You don't let anyone else take any of your cases.
That patient is borderline.
(Borderline personality disorder)
I didn't say so, though.
He wouldn't accept her if I did.
The patient herself doesn't know either.
You're in trouble.
Si Joon will cause a huge fuss if he finds out.
That's why I need your help.
I want to help him overcome what happened.
You worry about him a lot.
We're friends.
How about you? Are you okay?
- What do you mean? - Do you still feel guilty?
It's not something I can easily brush off.
I want to help Si Joon.
That way, it'll put me at ease.
But one day
On a foggy morning
We were dragged away
By men with swords
We didn't know why
Or where we were going
No one
Told us
(Open Audition for "Tears", Han Woo Joo)
I'm sorry. Let me try again.
No, that's enough. You may leave.
You're not supposed to chat during an audition.
You guys talked about me just now, didn't you?
I told him you needed to work on your singing...
even though I like your voice.
We're here as judges. Aren't we allowed to say that?
(Open Audition for "Tears", Audition Hall)
(Open Audition for "Tears")
I must be crazy.
What is the matter with me?
Kim Yu Ra suddenly got dumped...
by her boyfriend three months ago.
Due to the shock, she lost her self-esteem,
and that's what caused the symptoms.
I heard Young Won asked you to treat her patient.
Yes, her name is Han Woo Joo.
But I'm still thinking about it.
Why? Don't you want to do it?
I'm grateful for the offer.
But she settled with no strings attached.
Then you should help her.
But for some reason, I feel so hesitant about it.
First, I'm going to check a few stuff.
I need to see if I'll be able to handle her.
(The next episode will air soon.)
(Episode 4)
(Doctor Lee Si Joon)
Hello?
I'm not a policeman.
I am not a policeman.
He's been doing that all day?
He's battling on his own.
He has fewer random outbursts.
That's a good thing.
He needs to go out for a bit.
Where will you take him?
We won't go far.
Where are we going?
You seemed a bit down, so we'll get some fresh air.
Come on. I know you're pleased.
Isn't she the...
It's her, right?
Ms. Han Woo Joo.
What are you doing? It's dangerous.
Get down from there. It's really dangerous.
It's your fault.
Because of you, my career's over.
Because of you,
I can no longer perform in musicals.
It was my whole life.
I have no reason to live now.
But...
Please... Please...
Calm down and get off the ledge. This is wrong.
There will be a way.
Dying won't change anything.
You can only find out once you die.
Woo Joo, get down from there. It's very dangerous.
Come on, please, don't do this.
What police officer arrests someone during an award ceremony?
No officer would be that stupid.
That was...
What I did was...
Come on, please.
But I won't resent you.
Because you are sick.
One day, I hope you become a real officer.
No, you can't die because of someone like me!
Please. Please don't.
I'm really, really sorry.
When the doctor gave me the corporal insignia,
that's when I knew.
That...
I'm not an officer.
So you can't die because of someone like me.
Don't die.
I'm sorry. I'm so sorry for what I did.
I'm sorry.
Do you want to work part-time at our hospital?
What?
We need an actor for stage therapy to do what you did today.
I mastered all that when I was a nobody.
You have no idea,
but I'm pretty well-known now.
Oh, right.
- I didn't know. - It's okay.
(Tongil-ro)
(Eun Kang Medical Center)
Thanks so much for today.
Thank you too.
I'd been feeling down all-day after messing up an audition.
Strangely enough, I feel so good now.
Do you?
What will happen to that patient now?
Psychiatrists usually call illnesses a disorder.
That implies that a person is out of order.
In other words,
they may have lost a function due to certain reasons,
but they can become normal if they're fixed.
You fixed Mr. Cha Dong Il today.
He'll be fine.
Are you free tomorrow?
- Why? - I owe you one.
I'll buy you a meal.
You can refuse if you want, no pressure.
I'm in.
(Eun Kang Medical Center)
Hey. Who's on night duty at the ER?
I want to take his place.
What? Why not?
What did the professor of the Emergency Team say?
Well, too bad then.
Okay.
Where do you want to go?
- Let's eat something good. - Okay.
What shall we eat?
Dr. Lee.
- Hello, sir. - Hello.
- Are you leaving? - Yes.
We're all going for a drink.
Sure, you should blow off steam from time to time.
- See you. - Good night.
Oh, Dr. Lee.
There's no need to go to the ward.
I already checked.
If you keep going at night,
the nurses find it uncomfortable.
Okay, I understand.
You should go home and sleep tonight.
What are you doing?
I'm having a drink.
Can I go too?
I'm afraid not.
Okay, then.
I'm sorry.
- Have a seat. - Okay.
I heard Lee Si Joon begged to the director.
The director is a very tolerant person.
She should try to maintain her image as a director.
Why did she let it slide?
Her term is almost over.
Lee Si Joon is a quite well-known man.
He received several big awards...
and didn't Mayho Clinic try to scout him last year?
Am I right?
He is a weirdo, but there's no doubt he's talented.
Mr. In, you're so humble.
I'm flattered.
Why didn't Lee Si Joon go there?
He would've become a full professor right away.
Since he's a lunatic.
Oh, by the way.
Mr. Deputy Director, I want to congratulate you in advance.
For what?
The new psychiatric center that's about to open.
I heard rumors that you've already been selected...
as the new head of that center.
Come on, that's nonsense.
Stop saying that. I'm not interested.
Congratulations.
- Congratulations! - Congratulations!
Even you too, Mr. In? There's no need for this.
I'll live.
Have some coffee.
Where is Doctor Lee Si Joon?
Something urgent suddenly came up...
so he left his patients to me.
Did he say that? That I'm a patient?
I'm not a patient.
I'm sorry.
How do you feel lately?
You went through something stressful last time.
Are you coping well?
Why do you keep treating me like a patient?
I didn't mean to...
But if you felt that way, I apologize.
I must've made you very upset.
Yes. I feel so darned upset.
She just left.
One,
two,
three,
four...
That jerk.
She doesn't think of herself as a patient at all.
She continued to show signals of rage.
She experienced a breakup lately.
The sense of betrayal probably made it worse.
It won't be as simple as we thought.
It doesn't seem like a simple explosive disorder.
I think her symptoms come from another illness.
Really? Is there anything you have in mind?
I'll look into it from now on. Since it's Young Won's favor.
I'm glad you're helping her.
It's about time.
Thanks for today.
(Gongbap Restaurant)
What are you doing? I'm hungry.
Hey. You just ate all of this.
Do you have a beggar inside your stomach or what?
Ji Sun.
No matter how much I eat, I'm still hungry.
It's because you feel empty inside.
Eating won't solve it.
Didn't you say you'd just consider it as an accident?
Should I call your boyfriend?
Isn't this what boyfriends are for?
I broke up with that jerk.
What? When?
It turned out he was two-timing me.
He was the one who wrote that article too.
Why is my life so messed up?
I'm not asking for much.
I just...
want to live like others.
Is that so hard?
Is it because I wasn't born like others?
Hey. There's no one as kind and pretty as you.
You tend to be too nosy though.
There's something that makes me even angrier.
You know Dr. Lee Si Joon too, right?
The doctor at Ji Hee's hospital? What about him?
That jerk used me.
He's not someone who would do that.
- Do you have a plastic bag? - What for?
To cuss.
Five cents.
How about we go to a club tonight?
I'll close early today just for you.
Let's go.
- Really? - Yes, let's go.
- Can we go somewhere else then? - Where?
Where? Where? Let's go.
I'm thinking of your face right now
I drop my head and shed tears
Although I can't say anything
I love you
- I love you - Hey.
You're the only one in this world
Goodness.
Although I cry out your name
- The sun sets - The sun sets
- silently without answering - silently without answering
Let's go!
This feels great!
Hey, wait.
Stop. That's enough.
Stop.
Go ahead then.
Enjoy the sea all you want.
What are you hiding in your basement?
The sea.
I will now read the sentence...
for case 2020-KD-578.
Impersonating an official...
becomes a crime when the culprit abuses the official's authority.
It's hard to state that defendant Cha Dong Il...
abused an official's authority.
Also, according to his psychiatric evaluation,
he has a very poor sense of reality,
and he was diagnosed with a delusional disorder.
Therefore, the charges of impersonating an official...
are dismissed.
I know I'm not a policeman,
but I keep getting confused. I feel so stupid.
Next time, be a real policeman, not a fake.
Here.
The next exam is in three months.
(Introduction to Police Administration)
It was for a short while,
but let's say you were pretending to be the lead of a superhero movie.
You saved earth and protected people from danger.
Once you completed that mission,
you came back to being an ordinary man.
Do you think I'll be able to make it?
The first law of a superhero movie.
The hero comes back even stronger.
The second law.
The most dangerous enemy is...
you, yourself.
Don't you even think of giving up.
I have to go.
Well done.
I thought Si Joon would fight against it.
He really agreed to the transfer.
He keeps his word.
I won't be admitted.
I won't come to your hospital.
My reason?
I can overcome this on my own.
Lee Si Joon.
You knew about it, right?
Know what?
That Cha Dong Il wouldn't be admitted.
What do you mean? He left.
He called the other hospital and said he's not coming,
then got out of the van.
You didn't know? It wasn't your idea?
No, it wasn't.
He made the call.
You need to be honest with me.
If you're involved in this...
I didn't know. I really didn't.
You're smiling right now?
I'm proud of him.
Nice one, Cha Dong Il.
It was a dark and early morning
At the end of the long journey
We were
(Doctor Lee Si Joon)
What do you want?
I want to apologize.
I'm very sorry for not seeing you last time.
Everything I say will sound like an excuse,
so I won't try to explain.
Cha Dong Il's case was dismissed.
He got better, thanks to you, and left the hospital.
Is there anything else you want to say?
- Do you like soccer? - I don't.
Do you know Oh Yu Min? He's on the national team.
He's training hard to make a comeback.
- Shall we go and support him? - Why me?
Oh Yu Min said he's your fan.
How does he know me?
He liked you for a while.
He knows everything you were in.
- He does? - Yes.
Meet him and ask for yourself.
Kick it! Nice pass.
Well done.
Keep it up.
Good.
There he is.
Over there.
What's his number?
Number eight. There he is.
He's good. Full of energy.
Keep it up, Oh Yu Min! Keep running!
You're doing great!
Yes! Run, run!
Run! Keep running!
Yes, that's it! Looking good!
Yes. Very good!
Nice!
Oh Yu Min, don't push it!
Don't show all your skills!
You'll make everyone cower!
Who's he?
Yes, yes, yes!
Very good!
That's it! Nice!
Yes, yes. He's great.
Go.
- That's it! - Let's go!
Kick, kick! Kick it high!
Well done!
That's it! Yes!
Did you see that?
- Okay! - You still have it, Oh Yu Min!
Oh Yu Min!
Keep going!
Go, go!
He's amazing.
- What's going on? - Hey.
- Are you all right? - Play nicely.
It's a practice match.
Are you okay, Yu Min?
Why did he shove him?
You're doing great!
Golden Left Foot Oh Yu Min!
- Golden Left Foot Oh Yu Min! - Oh Yu Min!
- Golden Left Foot Oh Yu Min! - Golden Left Foot Oh Yu Min!
He scored!
Oh Yu Min!
My throat hurts because of all that screaming.
It was a lie that...
he's my fan, wasn't it?
Did I say he was?
This is it.
Thanks for walking me.
Bye.
Oh, right.
I think you're a good doctor.
Good eye.
Do you want to get treated...
by that good doctor?
- What do you mean? - Woo Joo.
I want to help you.
Do you think I'm crazy?
No. I don't.
I am crazy.
I am, but...
are you confident?
Can you really treat me?
You are not crazy.
You're in pain.
If you just admit that you're in pain,
you can be treated.
(Special thanks to Lee Sung Min and Wi Ha Joon.)
(Special thanks to Hwasung FC's coach, staff, and players.)
(Fix You)
Fury, go away.
You swallowed the house whole.
Why did you? Do you eat paper often?
- What's this? - A present.
Open it at home.
Why are you doing this to me?
You canceled today's appointment.
I thought you were busy, so I came over.
The positive symptoms are getting worse.
I feel...
When it comes to treating anorexia,
isn't Lee Si Joon's method right?
- What are you doing? - My gosh.
I'll work part-time at the hospital.
What can you do there?
Right? You're that musical actor.
After that kind of disgrace...
Stop!
Do something about your temper.
It messed things up so many times.
Hey!
There's no illness without a cause.
There's a reason you became so furious.