(This drama is fictitious...)
(and all characters, events, organizations, and settings...)
(are unrelated to real life.)
(Episode 2)
(3 years ago)
While chasing the culprit,
agent Kwon Min Seok dropped his gun,
and the culprit happened to shoot him right then.
An agent lost his life trying to apprehend a criminal.
You chased him on foot, shot your weapon, and yet lost him?
Maybe you didn't lose him.
Did you let him go?
Listen.
Your fingerprints were on Agent Kwon's gun.
Did you take it, shoot him,
then let the criminal go?
Will you keep your mouth shut?
Shall I go through your relatives' finances?
Hey.
Ms. Baek Jang Mi.
Ms. Baek Jang Mi?
Yes?
(Il Kwang Hitech Interview)
(Present day, Il Kwang Hitech interview hall)
What did you do for three years, Ms. Baek?
I lived like a corpse for the three months I was suspended.
I spent time reflecting on myself.
Once I returned, I realized what I must do.
I set a plan for my future.
I was sent from team to team for two years.
I pulled myself together and reassessed my goal.
And finally, to catch Michael myself...
And now...
I am here.
(Il Kwang Hitech)
Did you not plump up her resume?
She said she'd get in the right way.
Hey. She acts like a bulldozer.
Did you not fear...
a break in your career?
I believe the problem is...
with those who look down on such women.
The government does a sloppy job of supporting moms,
and when women try to get back into the workforce,
why don't they do anything to help?
Such inconsistency...
is the current state of our nation.
Why are you all so silent?
Shouldn't a large company like Il Kwang Hitech...
lead the way...
and provide a solution for such women?
If you hire me,
I will become your example.
(Resume)
(Disqualified)
Ms. Im Jung Eun.
Yes?
Ms. Im, can you please introduce yourself to us?
I'm... Well...
We made sure you'll get in, so relax. Don't get intimidated.
I will help Il Kwang Group create an eco-friendly semiconductor.
I'm determined and ready. And My name is Im Ye...
I mean, my name is Im Jung Eun.
My name is Ki Mi Seon.
Kim Hee Seon?
No, it's Ki Mi Seon, not Kim Hee Seon.
Oh, I see.
(Ki Mi Seon)
Ms. Ki, how old are you?
I'm 27 years old. I was born in the year of the sheep.
I've been studying really hard to get a job.
And that gave me a lot of stress.
That's why I look old for my age.
But contrary to how I look, I have really great stamina.
I have frozen shoulders.
I'm okay.
(Resume)
(Disqualified)
We'll have to go with Plan B.
Let's start...
Plan B.
(Il Kwang Hitech)
If you fail the interview again, we won't be able to help.
So make sure you do a good job.
Do your thing.
And mind your own business.
That's my motto.
I always tell people...
that you should know your place.
Leave your personal feelings out of this.
Every secretary wishes to work...
for a decent boss.
A person who can't keep things professional at work...
can be very disappointing.
Will you stop it already?
As I spent the last 10 years working for many CEOs and executives,
I learned that you need manners to be a good boss.
Is she crazy?
Do you know her?
Did I ever tell you this?
I once experienced a really bad heartbreak...
because of my first love.
Gosh, no wonder.
Is that why you always broke women's hearts?
You must've been madly in love with your first love.
She looked just like her.
She was beautiful.
(15 years ago)
How you express yourself is very important.
First, think of the place you used to live.
I personally looked back...
and thought of my hometown...
Excuse me.
Do you have a pen I can borrow? I didn't bring one.
Thank you.
You must like dolls.
Do you have another pen?
It doesn't work.
Thanks.
Do you have another color?
I don't feel comfortable writing in red.
Something you haven't done in a while.
"I hung out with someone yesterday."
Let's say you haven't shopped for a while.
Then instead of saying you haven't shopped in a while,
you need to express it differently like this.
(Just use what you have.)
That's the end of today's class.
Great work, everyone.
Your pen! Wait! Your pen!
Hey! Your pen!
- Your pen!
- Hey.
I didn't like the lecture at the academy.
My gosh.
I'll just study with a private tutor.
Anyway, thank you for looking into it for me.
I'll call you again. Okay, bye.
Hey, your pen...
Hey, wait. Your pen...
Then I'll just keep it.
Sir, wait!
Thank you.
Excuse me.
I believe that a secretary's duty...
is to help a less than ideal boss...
become a decent person.
My gosh.
What should we do? I don't think Plan B will work.
She's doing that on purpose, right? She wants me to hear this.
Why would she do that?
Did you do something to upset her?
Darn it.
She got the job.
Hello, I'm Hwang Mi Soon...
Excuse me?
I haven't even started the interview yet.
You may leave.
You want me to leave? Now?
Why?
As for Hwang Mi Soon...
Let's skip Plan C.
Let's move onto Plan D.
Why skip Plan C?
You saw what just happened. It won't work.
I'll begin Plan D.
Hello? Is this Wash and Clean?
(Good Casting)
The ultimate goal of this mission...
is to stop the technology from leaking overseas.
And we also need to catch Michael, the industrial spy...
that the Industry Security Team always failed to catch.
What's the update?
According to Team Three,
there will be three transactions in total.
They're going to back up their data.
It looks like the first transaction was made during the explosion.
So we need to stop the second transaction.
Do you have any information about that?
It's planned to be fully developed in a month.
It's highly likely that they'll try to sell the information before that.
So we need to infiltrate Il Kwang Hitech before that...
and gather information about who, where, and when...
and stop the transaction from happening.
Who's our mark?
Why don't you just do this yourself?
If I was the team manager, the briefing would already be over,
and we would already be out in the field.
So, who is our mark?
There are three.
3-on-3 sounds great.
The first mark.
(Il Kwang Hitech)
CEO Yoon Seok Ho.
The official successor.
(CEO Yoon Seok Ho)
Yoon Seok Ho?
He worked abroad...
and became CEO just a year ago.
He's still green.
Thanks for coming.
Il Kwang's true big shot is Director Myeong Gye Cheol.
He controls the board.
Hello.
Congratulations.
Director Myeong's right-hand man is Chief Tak Sang Gi.
He takes care of everything.
Remember him. He's someone we must watch.
This Director Myeong...
looks like an old tiger that lost all its teeth.
How powerful is he that he has more influence than a relative?
He's as cunning as a snake.
He never leaves any files to trace.
He uses burner phones and an external flash drive.
Other than the official company email his secretary handles,
he doesn't have a personal one.
In other words, he has no shadow.
(Director Myeong Gye Cheol)
The more secrets they have, the more fun it is to go digging.
I see the gold vein.
According to an inside source,
CEO Yoon is in constant touch with Taiwan...
and travels there often in an unofficial capacity.
So? Don't you smell it?
It stinks all the way over here.
The better-looking one is for their position,
the more they stink.
Between Director Myeong and CEO Yoon...
is this man.
Isn't that Kang Woo Won, the celebrity?
You all know him.
Kang Woo Won is the hottest star of the Korean wave.
He's really popular in East Asia,
especially in China and Taiwan.
He flies to Taiwan at least every two months,
making him the ideal person to sneak...
something suspicious out of the country.
CEO Yoon, Director Myeong, Kang Woo Won.
One of them is definitely connected to Michael.
Or they could be Michael.
(Il Kwang Hitech)
Chan Mi, you take Yoon Seok Ho.
Im Ye Eun will watch Kang Woo Won.
What about me?
You can't even eat from a table we set up.
Back them up.
You mean she watches the security cameras?
Where will you put it?
The research lab, obviously.
You need an entrance code to get into the research lab.
It's reset every morning.
You have to get into CEO Yoon's office to change it.
His office has a two-fold system. Facial recognition...
and a security card.
No, no.
It won't be me.
Chan Mi infiltrates the CEO's office.
Mi Soon infiltrates the research lab. That's all.
- Why me?
If this goes south, it's all on me.
Set it up by tomorrow.
- On day one?
On our first day?
What... Are you crazy?
What are you talking about? Do you think this makes sense?
You're a psycho. Die.
Chinese food is too greasy.
Are the cattle given feed soaked in oil?
The tenderloin has way too much fat.
Hey! Bring the suitcase right now! Hurry up!
I get sick whenever I eat it.
You added too much spice.
You get the money after the alpha test.
Do you understand? Do you?
Get the antacid.
What are you doing?
Are you out of your mind?
What are you?
Who are you people?
In Korea, it's polite not to bother even a dog during its meal.
The deal is done.
(10 million USD was deposited. Call if you have inquiries.)
Round 1 is done. We should move onto Round 2.
That leaves too little time for development.
We haven't yet tested the first round of development.
Backing up the second round already...
- That's...
- Dangerous, I know.
If we're found out, you and I both...
will lose our positions for sure.
I'm glad you understand, sir.
Who made you head of research?
Why do you think...
no one betrayed me all these years?
It's simple.
I weed out the ungrateful fools,
so in the end, I have no issues.
I'll get started right away...
on Round Two of backing up classified material.
We'll be done before winter ends.
I'm in position. Do you hear me?
I'm in as well.
Shall we...
get to it then?
Hey, lady.
What are you doing?
Where are you going?
Didn't you hear me?
I haven't seen you before. Who sent you? Wash and Clean?
Weren't you told to stay behind that line?
Okay.
I'll go back there.
We can't have you meeting the CEO...
while you're mopping the floor. Go.
- But I'm...
- I don't care. Move it.
How dare you treat me like that?
I have a kid your age!
Lady. Do you want to lose your job?
- No.
- I think you do.
- I'm moving.
- You're sure?
- Yes.
- Let's go.
- This gets you fired.
- Which way then?
- That way.
- Okay.
- I'll help move your things.
- Okay. Thanks.
- You're sure?
- You're so kind.
I know.
(Listening device)
Hey, you.
Are you here to play?
It's your first day and you're out of it already?
Follow me.
I think Ye Eun's device is broken.
Let's forget about that side for now and focus on the big guy.
Chan Mi is a legend, isn't she?
I bet she'll be fine.
Darn you.
You obviously look pretty old.
We heard you got the job via special recruitment.
How old are you?
These cute brats. Are they trying to haze me already?
I'm twenty...
nine.
You're younger than me, so I won't use honorifics.
Look at her trying to act all tough from the start.
Yes, of course.
Who do you have watching your back?
How could you get appointed to the president's office...
as soon as you got hired?
Be honest with us.
Who's helping you from behind?
You must all have someone...
who helps you from behind.
My gosh.
Everyone knows that you used your connections to get a job here.
Don't act like you don't know anything.
Chan Mi, don't mess this up.
Suppress your anger.
Don't get angry. Just stay calm.
"Connections"?
I don't know about that,
but I do have a few friends who taught me how to fight.
What do you say? Should I show you what I learned?
Hey! Hey!
Let me go. Let go of me.
- Stay still.
- Let me go.
Let me go.
My gosh.
What's wrong with you?
Jung Eun, where's the report...
regarding the advertisement agencies in Gangwon Province?
Yes, I'll have it ready in a minute.
Nice pose.
You look amazing. Make the wind a bit stronger.
Great. Give me some more wind.
Give me a strong wind. Show me some action. Great.
You look fabulous.
Nice. I love that pose.
Woo Won, why don't you show us your abs this time?
Come on. Show us.
Let's see your abs.
Look at those abs. Nice.
You look great. Flex your abs.
Great.
I'm going to do a close-up now. That's great.
Let's see your back muscles. Show us how manly you are.
Gosh, it's freezing.
My gosh, look at those muscles.
One more time. Great.
Nice.
Gosh, it's freezing. Can we please stop?
Gosh, it's so cold.
Can I at least do a photoshoot that suits the current weather?
It's a magazine in Southeast Asia.
You can't wear winter clothes for that.
Gosh, look at these goosebumps.
It's so cold.
Il Kwang called again...
to talk about renewing your advertisement contract.
I told you.
Forget the past. I'm no longer who I used to be.
Gosh, it's hot.
I'm Kang Woo Won, the most popular star in Korea.
What are you so scared of?
I'm worried they might cancel the advertisement...
if we keep playing hard to get.
Then let them cancel it.
Keep your chin up, and stay confident.
Just do as I say.
Are you sure?
Do you really want me to ask them for three times the original pay?
They should be grateful I didn't ask for four times the original amount.
Has Woo Won lost his mind?
His career was coming to an end, but because he was cheap,
we used him for the rice cooker advertisement...
and made him into a huge star.
But what? He wants to get paid three times the original price?
My gosh.
He's not willing to negotiate.
We need to renew his contract no matter what.
Tons of companies wish to advertise their products in his new drama...
because it was written by Kim Yu Ri.
If it exceeds our budget,
the upper management won't let us use him anyway.
Can't we just pay him two times the original pay?
Ma'am.
I'm sorry, but I need to go home.
- What?
- Seriously? Today's your first day.
Cut the nonsense and bring us some coffee.
Okay.
- Bye.
Yes.
I'm sorry.
I tried to leave as soon as possible.
I'm so sorry.
I'll be there as soon as...
Mr. Dong, can you do me a favor?
(Shooting Star Daycare Center)
(Wash and Clean)
Sir, we're here.
Go and get the kid.
- Me?
- Then should I do it?
Hey, you.
What do you think?
- What?
- You should know what's going on.
I'm not done learning the ropes yet.
Forget it. Just leave.
I know it's important to have long meetings.
But can't you just meet Kang Woo Won and try to convince him...
face to face?
If you need to renew the contract,
wouldn't it be faster to convince him...
in person?
Really? Then go ahead.
What?
You mean me?
You just said...
we should meet him in person instead of wasting our time.
What's wrong? Are you not confident?
How do you expect a new recruit to convince Kang Woo Won?
She can't even make good coffee.
What are you doing? Hurry up and volunteer.
I can't do it.
You thought...
I'd say that, didn't you?
I'll try my best to convince him.
Mom!
Sir, I think she pooped.
- Mom!
- Hurry up and change her diaper.
You want me to change her diaper?
I've never done that before.
Do you think I have?
I really don't know how.
My gosh.
- Mom!
- My gosh.
- Sir.
- Mom!
My gosh. Get it out of my face.
- Where should I put it?
- Roll it up.
- Mom!
Roll it?
- My gosh.
Are you making a sushi roll?
- This is my first time.
- Mom!
My goodness.
Mom! Mom!
Sir, what should we do?
What is it this time?
- There aren't any new diapers.
- Mom!
What kind of nonsense is that?
Mom!
Hey, did you try calling Mi Soon and Chan Mi?
I'm driving right now.
My gosh, I'm taking care of the kid.
- Mom!
- Why won't she stop crying?
- Hurry up and do something.
- The person you have reached...
- I'm trying to reach them.
- Mom!
There, there.
- My gosh.
- Mom!
(Team Leader Dung)
Yes, how may I help you?
You wish to know about your medical insurance?
Yes, of course.
What on earth are you saying?
Give it to me.
How can I be on standby after my shift ends?
Are you kidding me?
Janitors get off work at 3pm.
I can't wait around all day, you know.
Be that as it may,
you still can't get off work without telling me.
It's not like you'll pay me overtime, right?
I'm busy, so bye.
Hey!
Mom!
- My gosh.
- Mom!
Look at you rubbing your feet like that.
You'll eat your popcorn with that hand, won't you?
I knew it.
You disgusting jerk.
- Are you kidding me?
- Stop it.
Don't smack me like I'm a fly.
Darn.
Gosh, no.
Seriously?
I'd give anything to chop off that hand.
Get over here.
- Must you be so disgusting?
- Bring it on!
I'm home.
Joo Yeon, you should eat, right?
I made cheonggukjang...
Joo Yeon?
Joo Yeon, you should eat.
Get out here and eat, you brat!
Hey, you. Aren't you heading home?
CEO Yoon went home, so we should too.
I still have some work left. You should head out first.
That's odd.
How can you have work to do when Mr. Yoon didn't come in today?
Why is he talking to me like I'm his junior?
I should familiarize myself with the work...
before he comes in tomorrow.
Isn't that what you expect from experienced new recruits?
Sure. Carry on then.
Have a good night.
You'll need a key card to gain access to CEO Yoon's office.
Find that first.
Darn, I forgot my employee ID card.
CEO Yoon carries his around...
but his chief secretary would have one too.
What do you think you're doing?
Here's your employee ID card.
You seemed to have left it, so I was going to bring it to you.
You have excellent timing, sir.
Nice catch.
That was a good one.
What the...
Chan Mi...
probably found the key card, right?
Don't worry too much, sir.
I'm sure Im Ye Eun would've done her part too.
Right.
Look into the camera now.
Follow the camera lens. Perfect.
Looking good.
How macho.
Hands in pockets. This way, first.
Look into the camera and think you're a superstar.
There's a reason...
why I'm known as...
the master of negotiations.
First, you must build trust.
Find out what your target likes...
and use it to earn a good first impression.
That's one of the most basic rules.
Snacks that Kang Woo Won likes.
(Snacks that Kang Woo Won likes)
"Organic snacks with natural flavors that don't harm the body."
Kang Woo Won allergies.
(Kang Woo Won allergies)
He's allergic to peanuts?
Second,
set the mood.
You know how they say that love amidst a war is most passionate.
Why do you think that is?
Sweep him off his feet...
and he won't hesitate to accept your requests.
Now for the most important one.
This is more important than being a good talker.
What's that you ask?
Oh, no.
What am I using?
Look away!
I was going to say "a touch of luck" but...
Hold on. I have some dishes to wash.
I should turn this off.
What on earth am I seeing?
It seems like the guy is naked.
Where on earth are you?
Tell me who you are.
Are you a stalker, a spy,
or just plain crazy?
I'm terribly sorry.
- I'm here from Il...
- You were just doing your job?
You dare say that...
when you forced me to do a strip show just now?
Go on and explain yourself then.
I'm terribly sorry. It's all my fault.
All I wanted was to...
- You have no respect for me.
- I wanted to meet you.
So you walk all over me?
Want me to show you the powers I possess?
That isn't it.
I just want to...
Make fun of me?
Renew the contract...
You think this is funny?
I'll get going then.
Where do you think you're going?
You're leaving after showing everyone my naked body?
While we're talking then...
That's right. Finally, you show your teeth.
So tell me. Who on earth are you?
I'm here from Il Kwang Hitech...
to discuss the renewal of your contract.
Then tell this to your superior.
I'm now requesting for four times the money.
Four times.
The key card?
Of course, I have it.
I must return it before he comes back to work.
CEO Yoon gets to work at 7am,
so the operation will take place before that.
Get a good night's sleep.
Good job today.
I want a full scan of CEO Yoon's computer by tomorrow.
The team just infiltrated the office, sir.
It's dangerous to make a move before they've had time to adjust.
The team is there to take risks...
and that's in our job description.
What's with the sudden amateurism?
The team leader decides what goes on in the field,
so leave it to me, sir.
This isn't like you, you know.
Don't let your personal emotions get in the way.
Let your past drag you down...
and your career will suffer once more.
When firing a gun,
the hand that pulls the trigger can only do so much...
if the other hand doesn't provide a steady grip.
You'll never get a good shot.
Didn't I tell you to...
have the flash drive on my desk by this evening?
And I told you...
that we need more than a day to pull the operation off.
What good will all my hard work do...
when my subordinates can't get their jobs done?
I'll try and make it work...
by today, sir.
Enough with the useless promises...
and get to work!
Clean up and turn that in.
Yes, I'll make sure it's done soon.
Don't worry.
(Il Kwang Hitech)
(Adversaries)
(Target: Michael Lee)
(Failure to apprehend)
(3 years ago)
(Case number)
(Access Denied, No Clearance)
I'm the team leader,
so why don't I have access to the case files?
Didn't I tell you to lay low until...
your suspension is lifted?
Why are you digging into a closed case?
Because of me, an agent died!
I won't stop digging...
until I find the scumbag.
(Target: Michael Lee)
(Nationality: Korean-American)
(Murders broker after deal is complete)
(Blue scarf?)
(2016 Busan Harbor Operation)
(Personal Information: Myeong Gye Cheol)
(Personal Information: Ok Cheol)
(Personal Information: Tak Sang Gi)
What I showed you the last time...
was all the evidence we have.
This cell phone.
It isn't in evidence.
A cell phone?
Wasn't this dropped by one of the agents?
Who on earth uses a phone that has no Wi-Fi connection?
Right, unless it's a burner.
Anyway, I don't know anything about this.
(Il Kwang Hitech)
(Wash and Clean)
Let's go over the plan to be sure.
Baek Chan Mi will infiltrate Yoon Seok Ho's office...
and deactivate the security measures of the research lab.
(Chan Mi hacks into the research lab's security system.)
Mi Soon will then enter the research lab.
(Mi Soon installs a security camera in the research lab.)
She'll install a security camera and leave within 10 minutes.
You have a 20-minute window.
Now, let's play.
(Mission complete)
(Il Kwang Hitech Research Center)
I'm in the research lab.
Do you have a clear visual?
This'll go without a hitch, right?
Focus on your own job.
Out on the field, every second is vital.
Don't get distracted and focus on the screens.
You will not miss a second.
Are you getting this?
Explain what I need to do as easy and fast as you can.
Take out what Agent Im gave you...
and grab the red wire.
Note that...
it shouldn't be connected to the FPCB...
but the TD.
In layman's terms, you moron!
I understood that just fine.
Sure.
Are you not done yet?
(CEO Yoon Seok Ho)
Mr. Dong,
he's here.
CEO Yoon is headed toward the elevator.
Are you still not done? Get a move on it!
Yes, ma'am.
I'm in the restroom.
Well, hurry back.
I'll need some time.
Why didn't you tell us about what happened with Kang Woo Won?
We're in the middle of a crisis,
so get back over here.
Yes, ma'am. I'll be right there.
His computer is password protected.
Darn it. I guess we must pull out.
Hold the elevator for three minutes.
What on earth? What was that?
Gosh.
What's going on?
- I'm in.
- You're in?
Thanks.
Here we go.
What was that?
Didn't you see that just now?
See what?
I'm the fool for asking.
What do we do? Chan Mi could get caught.
Go back to your office for now.
Yes. We're good to go.
Unbelievable.
It's been a while since I've stretched my legs.
Mi Soon, this is all you now.
What about Chan Mi? Didn't she make it out?
I see that she didn't.
She acts like she's the smartest person in the world,
but she always makes a mistake at the last minute.
Hold on.
May I ask who you are?
You worked overtime again?
Gosh, look at the bags under your eyes.
Take it easy, will you? Overtime pay isn't worth it.
Please tell me you have health insurance.
Health insurance? Right, thanks for the advice.
Well, keep up the good work then.
Thank you.
It makes sense though. She wouldn't be that smart...
since she got dumped by someone as wishy-washy...
as our team leader.
Mi Soon, let's focus on the job, shall we?
I'm right though, aren't I? Wishy-washy is exactly...
how you are.
Darn it.
Place it where it can't be found.
All it needs is a Wi-Fi connection.
Would you look at that?
The technological advancements are outstanding.
The cameras don't even need wires now.
Sweet.
Why is it stuck?
Mr. Dong, what is Ok Cheol doing here at this hour?
What?
(The signal is weak. Please try again.)
You've got to be kidding me.
Come on, Wi-Fi signal. Come on.
(Il Kwang Hitech)
- Hello, sir.
- Get back to work, guys.
One moment, sir.
Here is the thing you asked for yesterday.
Let's see.
(Head of Research Ok Cheol)
What was that?
Budge, you stubborn thing.
Stop trying to make it move.
(Stay tuned for the epilogue.)
(Epilogue)
(10 years ago)
Why did you want to see me?
Let's order some coffee first.
I'm in the middle of an operation...
and I need to hurry back.
Can you put your gun away first?
Remove the fork and knife too.
What's this about?
We... Well...
Right.
Thank you.
We what?
I'll tell you after we finish this.
What is it?
Is something up?
You see...
- Go ahead.
- It's nothing.
And here I thought you got all serious...
to say that you're breaking up with me.
What's with that expression?
Well,
you see,
I've thought long and hard.
Then think some more.
No,
I've thought it through.
So what are you saying?
Let's break up.
You just had to say it, didn't you?
You paid a fine for damaged property last month, remember?
Didn't you say you were working an operation?
You would say weird excuses and hang up,
not smile at me,
not spend time with me,
and go off the grid.
Even when you avoided me at work, I tried to brush it off.
I don't care if you're seeing another woman...
or if you've changed your mind about me.
You're a disloyal jerk.
Right.
I'm a scumbag.
For the record,
you're dumping me.
It's not the other way around.
All right.
This is 100 percent my fault.
You know...
how I treat those who've wronged me.
Of course. Don't I know it.
You have three seconds to run. After that, you're dead.
3, 2, 1.
Get out of my sight!
Darn it.
(Good Casting)
- Isn't Mi Soon back yet?
- My arms are numb.
Find Mi Soon right now.
Is anyone there?
Found her.
- Have them enter.
- Okay, got it.
Find and press the reboot button.
- It's the red one.
- Seriously?
Something doesn't feel right.
I think she took a photo of me that day.
What do you say to a meal?
Tak Sang Gi.
His scarf is the same brand as Michael Lee's.
Infiltrate Tak Sang Gi's office.
Are you sure you're 29?
And your name is really Baek Jang Mi?
Yes, that's right.
Baek Jang Mi used to work for the NIS.
But I don't keep anyone I don't trust close by.