(Episode 1)
Hello.
Hey. Bring the cooler over here.
Here it is, boss.
Come and check the goods inside.
Okay.
Here you go.
Let's get going.
Sir, it's a bomb.
The whole team was wiped out?
Four including the team leader.
Fortunately, they had no backup...
as it was a top-secret mission,
so casualties were few.
(Geum Dong Seok, Deputy Head of NIS)
The whole team perished...
and it's fortunate?
We told the press that
a wheelhouse fire...
was the cause.
I'm Dong Gwan Su,
leader of Team 3 here to take over.
(Dong Gwan Su,
Industry Security Team 3)
I'll start the briefing.
Industry Security Team 3
was carrying out a mission...
when they got wiped out.
We believe that Michael,
who is Level 1 on our watch list,
was behind the mishap.
Are you sure of that?
Based on the recording
the Coast Guard found,
I'm positive.
His full name is Michael Lee.
After being identified trying to
sell US weapon technology to China,
he took classified
US Air Force intelligence...
and defected to China.
All parties of the deals...
he was involved in disappeared
or were found dead.
Because his identity
is still unknown,
no one was able to apprehend him.
He's called an unidentifiable ghost.
What company was
Team 3 investigating?
(Il Kwang Hitech)
Il Kwang Hitech with funding
and support from the government...
is preparing to apply for
a patent regarding 176-layer...
4D NAND Flash technology.
We got a tip that...
Qingni Yuhua Group
invested heavily in...
Il Kwang Hitech in return for
the stolen information.
If the technology is leaked...
before the patent is granted,
the loss to our economy will reach
at least three billion dollars.
What's your point?
We can try to
smoke a tiger out of its den,
but it will never show
its true self.
We will go into the den.
Anyone who gets involved with
this Michael...
ends up dead,
even if they're our best agents.
Who'd risk their lives to do that?
I do think I know of a few people.
If you know, you know.
What do you mean you think you know?
There are a few agents who will...
stay with the NIS,
whatever mission they're given.
Who are they?
The door is opening.
(Together Insurance Company)
Sorry. Excuse me.
Was it a month or so ago?
There was a fire in Baekmok-dong.
- There was a fire?
- I don't know.
Was there?
See? I knew it.
Listen.
Sharing information is key,
especially when it's bad news.
You can't hide the truth
by keeping quiet.
- My gosh.
- A fire?
The woman had no fire insurance,
so money for repairs,
hospital bills,
counseling, she had a tough time.
I felt so sorry for the woman.
- How much is it for fire insurance?
- Yes.
Drinking one less cup of coffee
a month...
won't kill you, will it, ladies?
(Insurance Queen Hwang Mi Soon)
It costs just one cup of coffee
a month.
My gosh. Oh, dear.
We should get fire insurance.
Mom, a gun.
Okay, I'll get you one later.
No, a real gun.
What are you talking about?
Give me just a minute.
Hwang Mi Soon.
She spent 24 years
in Domestic Security.
She identifies spy sects...
and persuades North Korean spies
to change sides.
When UN Secretary-general Ban
was abducted,
she flew to Russia and negotiated
a release within 20 minutes.
She's a master of
negotiating and placating.
Where is she now?
(Together Insurance Company,
Hwang Mi Soon)
(1.20 dollars)
(Agent Hwang Mi Soon)
The next agent
joined four years ago.
- She has a bright...
- She's a white agent.
A white agent?
She has no field experience at all?
That is true,
but she supported
field agents for years...
and is an IT specialist,
so when undercover,
she's the ideal person
to hack Il Kwang Hitech.
The first exit is blocked.
Take the back door out.
Seven meters to your left
is an underground escape.
You have 90 seconds left. Hurry.
2XL flying in from the east.
I'll find an emergency exit.
Emergency exit by Gate 37.
Good job.
We'll barely succeed
with our best men.
Can they manage?
This is currently our best option.
She could still be useful.
Who are you referring to?
(Baek Chan Mi,
Industry Security Team 3)
Call Baek Chan Mi.
- That's...
- Sir, that's...
If we want to pull this off,
we must put...
our best and craziest agent...
up against him.
Where is Agent Baek now?
I will forgive all who wronged me.
I will love even my enemies.
Even an annoying ant...
I will not kill a single ant.
Every single life
you created on earth,
I will value and care for.
I thank you daily...
for your love and grace...
and will live a life full of joy.
Inmate 2208. Get up.
(Kindness and education lead to
a reliable and advanced correction.)
She even killed someone.
She looks completely normal.
There's a reason why
they call her RP.
- What?
- It's short for Royal Psycho.
(Royal Psycho)
What was her job?
She was some kind of
a civil servant.
I heard she even took bribes.
What a piece of trash.
- Hey, hey.
- Darn you.
- Here you go.
- It's nice and cool, isn't it?
- Hey, stay still.
- Look at her trying to avoid it.
Darn it.
I worked so hard
to clean this place.
What's wrong?
Do you want us
to wash your face as well?
Shut your mouth and get lost.
I'm just saying
you should keep it clean.
I get indigestion
every time I see your face.
So I told you not to walk around
showing your face to others.
Was that so hard for you
to understand?
- You darn wench.
- I'm sorry.
You're the one
who can't seem to understand things.
What did she just say?
Has she lost her mind?
You crazy wench.
Get her!
Let me go, you wench!
Hey!
Kind people
always keep their promises.
And you promised to keep it clean.
Of course.
She beat them all up...
in just one round.
You're really a psycho.
You're the only one who volunteered
to receive solitary confinement...
before getting released on parole.
Are you crying?
Can you give me one more spoon
of red pepper paste?
This tastes amazing today.
Whoever cooked the vegetables
did an excellent job.
My gosh.
Bring Baek Chan Mi back
and make her catch Michael.
Sir, I don't think
it's a good idea...
to have her on the case.
The president is keeping an eye
on this case.
Our department might disappear
if we fail to catch him.
Why don't we leave this to Mr. Dong?
I'm sure he'll do well.
Mr. Dong, I want you...
to be in charge of this mission.
But...
I can't handle Baek Chan Mi.
I don't like her either.
But you heard what he said.
We were given orders.
If you don't want to follow orders,
you can either quit...
or become more competent.
Then I'll just quit.
I heard your monthly pay
got distrained...
because you couldn't even afford
to pay your alimony.
You need a job to make a living.
(Good Casting)
Get back to work.
(Sweet Americano: 70 cents,
Ice: 60 cents)
How many times
do I need to tell you...
that you can't make a claim
for what you spent...
outside of work?
I drank this while I was
waiting for the summit to end...
last month.
- Oh, the summit?
- Yes.
At Hongdae?
At two in the morning?
Don't mess up.
Hello?
Yes, this is Hwang Mi Soon.
I think you called the wrong number.
Here you go, sir.
I got you iced tea.
And I got you an iced Americano
since you're always...
doing fieldwork.
I should be buying you a drink.
I owe Ye Eun so much.
A field agent is like a motor,
and the support team is like fuel.
Not just any type of fuel.
I'm talking about the best kind.
All I do is help her do her work.
It doesn't matter
how good the motor is.
Once it breaks, it becomes useless.
Ye Eun, don't you want to do
fieldwork sometimes?
Gosh, that kind of work
isn't for everyone.
I prefer working in the office.
My goal is to keep this job
until I retire due to old age.
We're better off staying quiet
until we're too old to work here.
I've seen tons of colleagues
get fired...
because they failed to meet
their performance standards.
Yes, of course.
A white agent in the field?
There are no precedents,
and it's totally absurd.
That's right.
Just a second.
Hello, this is Im Ye Eun
from the support team.
What?
I don't want to do it.
If I do fieldwork at my age,
I might actually die.
I don't even take the stairs
these days because I have arthritis.
Forget it.
I'm really not interested.
Gosh, what's the matter with you?
You'd never let arthritis
get in the way of your career.
It's been a while since
we worked together, dear colleague.
Who cares about colleagues and such?
It's been way too long.
I don't care
if you're my colleague or not.
Don't anger me.
And seriously? Her?
You want me to do
fieldwork with her?
I've never worked as a field agent
in my entire life.
See? She's a complete rookie.
What am I supposed to do with her?
I have a kid.
I may look young,
but I have a three-year-old kid.
Early childhood insurance is a must.
Do you have one?
Kids get hurt very easily.
And hospital bills cost a fortune.
Right.
I'm sorry, sir.
But can't you just tell them
that I'm not capable of doing...
You're right. It's practically
a battlefield out there.
Why would anyone volunteer
to work out in the field?
- Exactly.
But the upper management still
wanted me to give you something.
So make sure you take it.
Hwang Mi Soon,
you need to repay your loan...
by the end of this month.
Im Ye Eun, you have to move out...
of the housing provided to you
by the organization.
That will be all.
Hey, wait.
You're blackmailing me.
Do you think I'm here
to convince you?
Where am I supposed to live
if I move out of employee housing?
Don't ask me.
Who's our target?
That's the question
I wanted to hear.
Michael.
"Michael"?
What do you say?
Are you in or out?
Darn you.
Kwon Min Seok.
Kwon Min Seok. Min Seok!
Min Seok! You can't give up!
Don't give up! No! Don't you dare!
Min Seok! Wake up, you fool!
I'll kill you all.
Mom.
Yes, I'm coming!
(Access Denied, No Clearance)
Im Ye Eun, you have to move out...
of the housing provided to you
by the organization.
Mom's the only one
who can protect So Hui.
Dad would be so angry
if he found out.
Darn it.
Shoot.
I'd scratch with glee
if this were a lottery ticket.
How old is this wallpaper?
I'm exhausted.
This is the last cell.
If it's not here...
Darn it.
Shoot.
I found it.
That weirdo.
She's still so lively.
My gosh.
Hi, Barbara Massalitinova.
That was so hard to say.
The thing I'm looking for.
You have it.
There's no such thing.
If you keep pestering me,
I'll call for a guard.
Madam Wu who died in...
the solitary cell three months ago.
I bet she left it with you.
I don't know such a person.
No. Do you think I'll let it go...
because you pretend not to?
I can't do that.
I really don't know, okay?
How about we talk this out now?
If I give it to you,
how much will you give me?
You want me to pay you
for holding onto it?
I'll be deported
once I get out of here.
I can't just let you have it.
100,000 dollars...
should be enough to get you home.
Keep your word.
For breaking
Immigration Control Law,
you'll be sentenced to
10 more months in prison.
And for industrial espionage,
Barbara Massalitinova,
you'll get
at least three more years.
Congratulations.
Hey! Hey, you mad wench!
I knew she could speak Korean.
(Personnel Transfer)
(Geum Dong Seok, Deputy Head of NIS)
You've aged a lot in three years.
Your seat doesn't agree with you?
We lost Michael because of you,
and I barely clawed my way back
from certain death.
How could I look okay?
That was my only mistake.
Give me a chance to make up for it.
Sure.
That's why you
came to prison, right?
Turn around.
When did you join forces
with the deputy head?
Are you upset I made a deal with him
behind your back?
If you ruin my plans again
like you did three years ago,
I will not let you off.
Don't worry.
I'll wrap it up with "TOP".
"TOP"?
In time, without going overboard,
perfectly.
Shall we?
Will this team be trustworthy?
What do you mean?
Three years ago,
a jerk of a teammate
I trusted with my life...
gave me a really hard time.
He told the boss
that I took a bribe...
to let Michael go.
Who was it?
It can't have been you.
This team will be fine
as long as you behave.
I'm excited!
What amazing aces
did you put in line for me?
Long time no see.
Not really.
You came to visit me in prison
last week.
I heard you were in jail.
My body must've gotten used to
solitary confinement.
It's quite awkward to sit
on something so comfortable.
Okay, let's catch up while we eat.
Wait.
Where did you bring
that rookie from?
The industry team?
The international team?
Or the terror team?
I worked for the support team in
the industrial security department.
What?
One is an old lady who hasn't
been in the field for years.
And the other one is a rookie
who's only seen stuff...
through a monitor?
Do you want me to succeed,
or do you want me to mess up?
That's why the deputy head
personally asked for you.
He knew that you'd do better
than 10 ordinary agents.
But she's no longer a team leader.
She's just an agent.
If you act up like how you used to
when you were a team leader,
I'll just kick you off the team.
You know me, right?
I do what I want...
once I make up my mind.
Yes, I know.
You were like that when we broke up.
Are you kidding me?
What? People talk about it
behind our backs anyway.
So it's better to be
honest about it.
You haven't changed at all.
You don't care about others.
You think you're the best,
don't you?
Obviously.
I even went to prison all by myself
because that's how good I am.
Well, it looks like
we all get the point.
Shall we start eating then?
I'll order five Course A meals.
- Sure.
- Okay.
You're the type of guy...
who's very careful and skeptical.
What if I join forces with Michael?
Are you warning me
before you betray us?
I didn't get dismissed...
because our bosses
wanted to save face.
But I bet no one trusts me anymore.
No one barely knows
because it's confidential.
And I never thought of you
as someone...
who'd do something like that.
- How can you be so sure?
- You may be...
out of control sometimes.
But you never cross the line.
About Baek Chan Mi...
Yes?
Why did she go to prison?
She didn't go there
because she did anything wrong.
She went there
as an undercover agent.
I see. I get it now.
But you'd better brace yourself...
now that she's in our team.
What?
The tiger is here.
This is your first time
doing fieldwork?
Yes.
I'm lacking in many ways,
but I'll try my best to learn a lot.
I don't care how much you lack.
And don't even try to learn stuff.
When we're out in the field,
there's no time to teach you stuff.
Okay, then I'll do my best.
That kind of mindset
only works in the office.
But that can't bring
a dead person back to life.
I want you to bring 100 sheets
of shooting paper by next week.
"100 sheets"?
It's not so you can shoot people.
I just want you to protect yourself.
And I'll see you at the gym
every day at 6 a.m...
so we can train together.
But I have a kid.
I think 6 a.m. would be
too early for me.
You look young.
I'm surprised you have a kid.
Then let's make it 6 p.m.
Do you get what I mean?
Whatever. I'm just going to eat it.
Do you want one too?
No?
Ye Eun, will you come with us
to the indoor playground?
The indoor playground?
Goodness. I see you didn't
check the chatroom.
We agreed to all go today.
You're probably too busy to come...
since you have to work.
It'll be a lot more fun
if we all went together though.
I'm actually free today.
The dads all agreed
to come with us too.
I guess that's
not exactly ideal, right?
Why? Ask So Hui's dad
to join us too.
What was that for?
Let's wash up now, guys.
We'll see you later
at the indoor playground.
- Come on.
- Kids, let's go.
- See you later.
- The indoor playground!
- Let's go.
- Off we go.
- Let's head home.
- Come on.
What?
Don't you know
that So Hui doesn't have a father?
My gosh!
I made a terrible mistake then.
Goodness.
So Hui,
we should head inside now too.
Let's go.
Come on.
So Hui,
I promise to take you to
the indoor playground next time.
Promise.
Yes, promise, and seal.
I hope it's a daughter.
What's this thing I see?
It's the hand.
The baby looks like a gummy bear.
Fascinating, right?
Even though it's tiny,
it still has arms and legs.
How much more must we wait?
A while.
We'll have to wait all winter.
I can't wait to meet our baby.
I'm going to be
the coolest dad on earth.
Growing up, I was most jealous
of kids who had dads.
Even though I'm ecstatic,
I'm also nervous.
I'm worried about losing
my first ever family.
We won't go anywhere
and stay by you forever,
so don't worry.
Let's get married
as soon as I finish this job.
I'll man up and meet your parents...
and tell the boss about us.
But you said we should
keep it a secret...
until the mission is over.
I don't want to cause you
any trouble.
Promise.
My little gummy bear.
Bring it on.
Come at me.
Hey...
I give up!
You're physically inept...
with a weak mentality,
but you hope to work in the field?
I don't operate
on a sense of duty...
or patriotism like you do.
I work this job to make a living.
I do this for fun, actually.
Always...
stay on your toes.
(NIS Martyrdom Hall)
It's been three years.
(In memory of the agents who devoted
their lives to our nation)
(3 years ago)
We're a go in one minute.
Get ready for our customers.
Stay focused and alert.
We must...
You called a deluxe cab, right?
You're dead meat.
How many times did I tell you
to call a deluxe cab?
Welcome!
Sorry. Coming through.
Welcome.
Groups must gather
in front of the Skyway...
before they enter.
Yes, thank you.
Welcome.
So it's 10LT?
Wait. Where's the Skyway?
Darn it.
Goodness, young man.
I'm terribly sorry.
(I'll head home
straight after work.)
I'll head home straight after work.
Is there anything you want to eat?
There's something...
I'd like to hear more than eat.
(I love you)
You just can't say
you love me, can you?
Group tourists, over here.
This way, please.
Over here, everyone. Gather around.
If you wish to go to the restroom,
please make your way there now.
Let me tell you where it is.
It's over there.
Over there?
I've lost my touch
out here in the field...
to the point
where my sense of direction is off.
Darn it.
Can you send a text for me?
The father of my child
is still at work.
Tell him that our baby is coming.
(Restricted number:
2 o'clock, blue scarf)
Hang in there, ma'am.
I need to go first.
But this is the ladies' room.
Look over there.
(Out of order)
You get my drift now, so run along.
But I really need to go as well.
Just how stupid are you?
Get lost before I punch you.
Darn it.
(Out of order)
Seriously? I told you to beat it.
You have a death wish, don't you?
Surprise!
Seriously, it took hours
to do this makeup.
Can't you just stay down?
Do you get how much
I needed to use the restroom now?
Good.
Darn it.
I'm in.
I'm tailing him from 7m behind.
Stay at your posts...
including the taxi.
Call out if you spot Michael.
Got it.
Ma'am, breathe.
Deep breaths.
Yes, you're doing great.
(Ha Si An)
Are you all right?
Let me help.
My apologies, sir.
Guide, Kangaroo, come to the tower.
You're requested for backup.
Coming, ma'am.
(Rabbit, Kangaroo, Guide)
I think Rabbit is in trouble.
Code Red. Head to the tower!
Kwon Min Seok, what happened?
- He took it.
- What?
Blue scarf...
Found him.
He's wearing a blue scarf.
Secure the elevators.
Excuse me. Make way.
- Ms. Baek?
- Where's Michael?
Darn it!
Ma'am, the deputy director
is telling us to standby.
No, I can't do this. I won't.
I just can't.
- Don't make me.
- Ma'am!
Ma'am!
What now?
What's going on?
Did Baek do
something crazy again?
I'm headed to the east gate.
Get the taxi there.
Move!
What on earth?
What are you doing?
Don't you see that motorcycle?
But you told me to standby
until backup arrives.
Move. Get out!
I couldn't stop Ms. Baek.
Gosh, I'm sorry.
You should've told her
that you had to wait for backup.
Are you kidding me?
I told you to standby
until backup arrived.
Why would she go after him alone?
Track where she went!
This is why we needed a deluxe cab!
Min Seok?
I almost shot you, Chan Mi.
When did you get here?
I followed you out right away.
Are you all right?
I'm fine, so search the area.
Michael is here.
It's all right.
It'll be all right.
Hang in there.
Chan Mi.
Chan Mi!
- You did great.
- Your baby made it.
Gosh, you did amazingly.
(Min Seok,
I'm about to have our baby.)
I love you.
What? Kwon Min Seok.
Kwon Min Seok. Min Seok!
Min Seok! You can't give up!
Don't give up! No! Don't you dare!
Min Seok! Wake up, you fool!
Oh, no...
Chan Mi!
No...
Michael!
You're under arrest...
for violating
the Prevention of Divulgence Act.
As if an arrest will stop
a scumbag like you.
Forget the law. You're not...
getting out of here alive!
Chan Mi, snap out of it.
Don't you see all those civilians?
- The person you called...
- Clear.
- is unavailable. Please leave...
- Shock!
Again. Charge.
Clear, shock.
The person you called
is unavailable.
Please leave a message...
Kwon Min Seok. Time of death, 20:30.
- Come on.
- Don't do this.
Stop it.
Stop it. That's enough.
- Just let him go.
- Chan Mi.
Don't be like this.
Get a grip on yourself!
- Why...
- Stop it.
Let him go. Come on!
Pull yourself together!
You won't have to wait long.
I'll find the scumbag
who killed you...
and have him kneel before you.
There's only one path
laid out for us all.
Either we walk forward on it
or we dive to our demise.
If one person messes up,
that'll be the end for all of us.
Now, get going.
(Stay tuned for the epilogue.)
(Epilogue)
(Baek Chan Mi)
(NIS Personnel Record)
Three agents in total...
begin their undercover work
at Il Kwang Hitech.
(Good Casting)
- Ms. Baek Jang Mi.
- You didn't fill out her resume?
You took a break from your career.
Isn't it scary
to get back out there?
People like you
who look down on women...
with career breaks...
Is she insane?
Got it.
Every second counts in the field.
Don't ever lose your focus.
Look here, lady.
Where are you going?
- He's here.
- How far out are you?
Hurry!
What do we do if Chan Mi is caught?
- Nice!
- It's me,
top celebrity Kang Woo Won.
Where are you off to? Tell me.
Who on earth are you?
Don't let personal emotions
get in the way.
You don't want history
to repeat itself.
I won't stop...
until I catch that scumbag.