(Episode 3)
Budge, you stubborn thing.
Stop trying to make it move.
(The signal is weak.
Please try again.)
One moment, sir.
Here is the thing
you asked for yesterday.
Let's see.
Darn it.
(Head of Research Ok Cheol)
What was that?
Will you just open?
(Head of Research Ok Cheol)
What are you doing?
Gosh, I'm getting a headache.
I think this is broken.
It won't even budge.
- My gosh.
- I'll check, sir.
Please sign this.
This song is for the woman
who stole my heart.
The name of the song is
"Red Backpack".
Her red backpack
It looks so heavy
I want to carry it for her
Her red backpack
It looks so nice and warm
I also want to be in her arms
just like her bag
Not everyone gets to see
how attractive she is
She gives foolish boys
the red light
But for me,
it was love at first sight
She gives me the green light
She's my blue ocean
No one could love her
Because my love, she is so selfish
Red backpack
I think Director Myeong is
planning to do something big today.
He gathered
all the executives at 7 a.m...
and had a breakfast meeting.
Maybe he wanted to woo them a little
before the actual meeting.
We'll be late for the meeting.
Let's go, sir.
Let's go ruin their plan.
Yes, sir.
I personally don't like it.
I prefer eating dried persimmons
that were slowly dried in autumn.
We need to use this opportunity
to ruin Chairman Yoon's business.
We need to
completely take control...
so that he won't even think
of supporting Yoon Seok Ho again.
We're keeping an eye on CEO Yoon.
He doesn't let anyone
near this office.
But it looks like he recently hired
a female secretary.
I'll look into it, sir.
Mr. Ok will soon deliver
the second round of material.
You just need to continue
what you've been doing.
You know what you need to do, right?
Keep the transaction quick,
and make sure no one complains.
I'll bring you the money
for your dried persimmons...
as soon as I deliver
the second batch.
It's best to eat them
before spring comes.
Isn't Mi Soon done yet?
No. What's taking her so long?
Darn it. They say the world
has become more convenient.
What a load of nonsense.
Gosh, we could've just
connected it with a wire.
Then this would've been over by now.
Gosh, my arms and legs
are killing me.
Darn it. Where is it? Where?
Let's go. Come on.
Darn it. Please connect.
(Il Kwang Research Center)
(Data backup)
(Top Secret:
Round 2 research results)
(Proceeding with backup)
Raise the volume.
Are we here?
- Yes, it's over there.
- That's a pretty house.
Here.
Thank you.
See you then.
Is that sea squirt
your new boyfriend?
He's a med student,
not a sea squirt.
He's going to be a dermatologist,
so he can get a chemical peel.
It hasn't been that long since you
broke up with that sea cucumber.
I broke up with that guy ages ago.
Stop interfering
with my private life...
by comparing the guys I meet
with seafood.
How could I not care?
I'm going to become
your boyfriend soon.
Get into college first.
If you still feel the same way
when you turn 20,
you can come visit me again.
But I bet you'll be the one
rejecting me when that day comes.
I'll still like you
even when you turn 40.
Do you think I'm crazy?
It's already depressing to think
I'd be single at 40.
But you even expect me
to date a guy I used to tutor?
She didn't have to get so angry.
Hey, wait for me.
Wait for me. Give me your bag.
Here.
Where are we going?
You probably skipped class
and waited here.
So I bet you didn't eat dinner.
What do you want to eat?
Ramyeon with rice cakes!
There are a variety
of ramyeon dishes to choose from,
but that's what you want again?
Once I like something,
I rarely change my mind about it.
It'll taste a lot more delicious
if you cook one for me yourself.
Gosh, come on. Be honest with me.
Was that guy really your boyfriend?
That's none of your business.
To be honest, the guy that looked
like an octopus...
seemed pretty decent.
He failed the bar exam.
That's why you broke up with him?
Hey, I didn't dump him.
He just had no self-respect.
Gosh, that's complete nonsense.
Baek Chan Mi. Baek Chan Mi.
Is there something wrong?
Just leave me alone, will you?
First, bring me the flash drive.
The flash drive.
(Good Casting)
Are you constipated?
I called you ages ago
and you showed up 15 minutes late.
I apologize.
The truth is,
I do have severe constipation.
If it won't come out here,
you can deal with it at home.
Okay. From now on,
I promise to deal with it at...
Your constipation
isn't the issue right now!
What on earth did you do
to Kang Woo Won yesterday?
You dare say that...
when you forced me
to do a strip show just now?
Then tell this to your superior.
I'm now requesting for
four times the money.
Four times.
Why didn't you report right back
about your mess-up?
Jung Eun. Are you a spy?
Pardon?
If you're incapable,
don't get involved at all.
You're so confident about nothing.
Anyway,
you'd better prepare yourself
for when...
the team leader comes back.
Before that,
make copies of these.
Am I exaggerating?
The government gave us
60 million dollars.
How much of our money did we spend?
150 million dollars.
Goodness. For a project that costs
over 200 million dollars,
you get all the reports
and the results are secret?
Is this a secret nuclear experiment?
The late chairman gave me...
full authority to run
the research laboratory.
Everyone present is aware of that.
You just got back from
setting up a branch overseas,
and don't know
how things are done here.
You're right.
If I'd known how irregular
the processes are here,
I'd have returned sooner
to set it right.
That's what
the late chairman wanted.
Why are you mentioning my father?
It's easy to try to pick apart...
something that's set before you.
The late Chairman Yoon knew that...
which is why he valued
and supported the research lab.
That is how our company
could grow so large.
That is how...
you went from
Head of Research to director,
which is unprecedented.
After I spearheaded the development
of lithography technology,
do you know how much
our shares jumped?
Five times.
The estimated profit is
4.7 billion dollars.
You alone helped to increase
the price of our shares,
so you can spend what you want?
I'm asking for
some respect at least.
Since you're being so direct,
I'll speak freely
and directly myself.
From now on, all reports regarding
the NAND Flash research...
require the CEO's approval.
Director Myeong.
What power does
a mere director have?
If that's what you say,
that's what I'll do.
(Top Secret:
Round 2 research results)
(Backup complete)
(Il Kwang Research Lab)
(Head of Research Ok Cheol)
I got it. I have a signal.
I got it! At last!
Yes. I got it.
Now stay there.
Stay still.
Oh? It's working.
Team Leader.
Ok Cheol's camera is online.
He's not up to much, is he?
No. He's quiet.
I guess Mi Soon got out safely then.
I heard from Mr. Ok.
The package is ready.
He does as he's told.
I just don't like the weaselly fool.
CEO Yoon's new secretary.
What's she called?
Do you mean Baek Jang Mi?
A newbie at this moment?
I have a bad feeling about it.
Something smells.
I'll look into her.
Look deeply.
Who knows? We might find
a diamond in the rough.
I love you. I love you.
What are you doing there?
Hello, sir.
I'm the new experienced secretary.
My name is Baek Jang Mi.
Ms. Baek Jang Mi?
Are you all right?
I'm fine.
I think I dropped a pill somewhere.
I don't think you're fine.
Hang on.
This.
I'll get another set of vitamins.
No, don't.
Skipping just one pill
won't kill me.
Take a seat.
Pardon?
Sit down.
Do you know why I hired you?
I don't believe...
I saw you in the interview hall.
I had a meeting,
so I observed in my car
from a monitor.
I believe that a secretary's duty...
is to help a less than ideal boss...
become a decent person.
Everyone knows that you used
your connections to get a job here.
What an odd specialty.
(Specialty: Throwing)
Do you throw things?
I tend to throw things pretty well.
What do you tend to throw?
This and that. Everything.
Are you really 29 years old?
And your name is
definitely Baek Jang Mi?
Yes. That's right.
No way.
Did he recognize me?
What a relief.
I wondered.
What does he mean it's a relief?
Is he relieved I'm not Baek Chan Mi?
Did you work for
many subhuman bosses?
Oh, I wasn't talking about you, sir.
You got lucky with
a very humane boss.
I don't mind...
mistakes or poor work skills.
We're all human.
But I don't keep
untrustworthy people close.
I'll remember that.
You should.
I'm quite humane...
and give second chances.
It's Friday.
What are you doing tomorrow?
Shall we eat out?
I'd make plans if I didn't have any,
but I really do have plans.
Then shall we have tea
after you're done?
I'll come over.
I might stay with the guy
if the date works out.
I guess you could tag along.
We'll be working
on this mission together.
Don't you think it's time...
to get comfortable with one another?
The worst choice I ever made was...
when I said okay
to having dinner with a jerk...
the first time I worked overtime
after I got this job.
I had really bad indigestion
because he was a senior.
And I ended up
falling for that darn jerk...
when he pricked my finger for me
to help cure my indigestion.
I had just graduated from college,
so I was way too naive.
That's how I was.
I want a full scan
of CEO Yoon's computer by tomorrow.
What good will
all my hard work do...
when my subordinates
can't get their jobs done?
Why am I always the one...
who has to take care of
all the dirty jobs?
My gosh, this is so exhausting.
My goodness.
There's no end to this thing.
I can do it.
If I can fit my head inside,
the rest will just follow along.
I can do it.
Come on.
What's going on?
Why can't I move?
No way.
Am I stuck?
Can you hear me?
I'm stuck.
I'm stuck in the air vent.
Hello?
Can you hear me? Hello?
Hello? Oh, no!
No! No!
Hello?
Hello? Is anyone there?
Can anyone help me?
Ok Cheol hasn't done
anything suspicious.
Do you think we made
the wrong guess?
Maybe he already extracted the file.
Then what should we do?
What do you think?
We should stop the transaction.
Here.
I got it from CEO Yoon's computer.
Have it copied as soon as possible.
Without reporting it
to the director?
That's why I'm telling you to hurry.
We need to give it to him.
Okay, sir.
But why haven't we heard
from the others yet?
They should report to me
before they get off work.
I haven't heard from Mi Soon...
after she went inside the air vent.
And you still haven't checked?
Ms. Hwang?
It's weird.
I think something happened.
Find Mi Soon right now.
They haven't forgotten about me,
have they?
You guys.
I'm still here.
Hey, Rookie. Where did you get this?
I couldn't find anything
in the security team.
So I just hacked the system.
The last time
we heard from Mi Soon...
was at 9:56 a.m., right?
It's about 340m
from Mr. Ok's office...
to the air vent exit.
And the fastest one can go
inside an air vent...
is 0.5km per hour.
If she moved at the fastest speed...
starting from the moment
the security camera was installed,
she should've arrived
at the connecting vent...
at about 10:34 a.m.
But the passage is
only about 40 inches high.
That's where she got stuck.
Once everyone leaves
the research lab,
they sterilize the place...
by releasing sterilizing gas
every single hour.
And that's about to start now,
so we need to get her out of there
as soon as possible.
She's somewhere near here.
We found where Mi Soon is.
Okay. Now, it's my turn.
- Won't it work?
- What's the matter with this?
Wait.
I'm calling from
the research department.
We need you here because there's
a problem with the security system.
Okay, we'll be right there.
Okay, bye.
Send the girls.
Okay, sir.
Did you call the head office
to inspect an error...
with the security system?
I didn't know we had
female employees...
in the digital security department.
By any chance,
when did you last update
the security system?
Well...
I think we did it last weekend.
The biometric
authentication system...
shoots structured light
into an infrared sensor.
So every time light
goes into the sensor,
it saves even the smallest
additional changes.
Therefore, you're obligated
to check the server...
when the access rate
increases by 20 percent.
Didn't you check?
Well...
Everything was fine
even if we didn't check.
I'm sure you were told...
that it'll cost at least
tens of thousands of dollars...
if the projector is damaged...
due to repeated errors
in the illuminator.
Then you should go ahead and check.
Go ahead.
I'm only asking you to go because
you'll find her faster than me.
But be careful.
If I don't get out of there
by 6 p.m.,
find the reboot button and press it.
That will ventilate the gas.
6 p.m. The reboot button.
It's a red button.
Red.
6 p.m. The reboot button. Red.
Mi Soon.
It's a red button.
Darn it.
What is this?
Mi Soon.
What should I do?
Eeny, meeny, miny, moe
Catch a tiger by the toe
If he hollers, let him go
Eeny, meeny, miny, moe
- Mi Soon.
- Is anyone there?
Hello?
- Hello?
- Mi Soon?
Is someone there?
Mi Soon, is that you?
Yes, it's me. Please...
Mi Soon.
Can you please
get me out of here?
Why are you stuck here?
- Mi Soon.
- Get me out.
Hang in there.
I will...
- Mi Soon.
- What?
I'm sorry, but...
can you curl up a bit more?
It's not easy to change my posture.
Wait. Let me try.
Is that the Maintenance Team?
I think our ventilation system
is infested.
Isn't it time you gassed it?
Pull, pull. Pull hard.
I'm out.
Insecticide gas is released.
We released insecticide gas
to clean the research lab.
There will be a loud noise
for about five minutes.
Please understand.
I'm out at last.
Are all my bones okay?
Am I okay?
You seem to be fine.
Can you crawl out of here?
Yes.
What? What's wrong?
My leg. It's cramped.
What is cramped? Where?
No, not there.
My leg. My leg.
Your leg?
What is that smoke?
Doesn't it smell poisonous?
The gas!
Let's run. Go that way.
Hurry. Move it.
Move quickly.
I hate gas more than anything.
Hurry! Move fast!
Darn it.
Is there a problem?
Oh, no.
It's all fine.
Okay.
Let's go.
Wait. Just a moment!
I pressed the reboot button
by mistake.
- I'll check it later.
- Okay.
Wait!
My gosh.
What's wrong with him?
My goodness.
Are you all right?
My shoes are half a size too large.
They fly off whenever I run.
What are you doing?
Call someone.
- Wait.
- Finally.
It was out of order.
Go on inside. It's fine.
The system is back online.
Since your system is back online,
I should get going.
(Wash and Clean)
Here.
Tracking devices?
Keep that on you
even when going to the restroom.
Right. Duly noted.
In an emergency,
press the button for three seconds
to activate Code Blue.
Code Blue for me...
is not being able
to go home at this hour...
when dinner is long overdue...
at my house.
Would you be able
to stomach anything...
after breathing all that gas?
That's already been...
What?
Gosh.
What is it?
Let go of me, darn it!
Let go.
(Chief of
National Intelligence Service,)
(Seo Gook Hwan)
(Chief of
National Intelligence Service,)
(Seo Gook Hwan)
Who still uses old junk like that?
Yes, of course.
Why won't it come out?
Gosh.
Right.
I'm in possession of the item.
Good. Make sure the delivery
goes as smoothly too.
The delivery will be made soon.
Get ready.
They still have a chance.
Let's see.
I feel like I'm dying.
It hurts.
Gosh, I'm aching all over.
You've got this.
You were supposed
to take out the recyclables.
Fly bugs will be crawling
all over the house.
I can take them out next week.
That's it. What a hit!
Make a run for it.
Run to the base!
To the third base.
- We're winning!
- My gosh.
You.
Didn't I tell you that I was...
going to be busy for a few months?
I work my butt off at the office...
only to come to
a heap of household chores.
Have you no conscience?
All you do is meet ladies...
and chat with them over drinks.
Then if you're lucky,
you get them to sign a contract.
You earn money
while laughing around, right?
I'd even pay for a job like that.
Are you serious?
Honey, what's wrong?
Honey...
These are the files
from CEO Yoon's computer.
I hear that no one in the NIS
can hold a candle...
to your computer skills.
How long until a full analysis?
Nothing seems to be
out of the ordinary.
Let's get married
as soon as I finish this job.
I'll man up and meet your parents...
and tell the boss about us.
But you said we should
keep it a secret...
until the mission is over.
I don't want to cause you
any trouble.
Promise.
Something doesn't feel right.
- What do you mean?
- The other day.
The female employee
from Il Kwang Hitech...
who was at the studio.
You sent her away
by telling her that...
you'll only agree
to four times the amount.
Come to think of it,
I think she took photos of me.
So what if she took photos?
But I was naked.
Are you sure she took them?
I don't know which is why
I'm asking you to check.
What do you take me for?
A secret agent?
It's not like I can just ask her.
Would she honestly tell you
if she took the photos?
If she had taken them,
she would've already tried
to blackmail you.
This is why you'll never
join the big league.
Just because I provide
a cushy life for you...
doesn't mean that the world
is all rainbows and butterflies.
Do you have any idea...
how many conniving scumbags
are out there?
I get it. It's not something...
a blue-collar worker like you
would understand.
Of course I know.
Celebrity Kang,
I have errands to run tomorrow.
You don't have any gigs,
so could I have the day off?
Are you kidding me?
What about my salad?
Who'll feed Poppy?
Who'll give my pets a shower?
Who will do all those chores?
Useless idiot.
(Caller ID restricted)
Yes, it's me.
You have until 9:30 p.m. tonight...
to retrieve the package from 7-49.
Wang Kai will call you
once you arrive in Taiwan.
All you have to do
is deliver the package.
Will delivering the package
to Wang Kai...
be my last task?
If there are no hitches.
Then when will I receive
the money you promised?
7-49.
Suraksan Station.
(Suraksan Station)
(Exit 4: Noil Elementary School,
Noil Middle School)
The delivery man
picked up the package.
Keep tabs on him
until he gets on the move.
(Il Kwang Hitech)
(Wash and Clean)
It seems like Ok Cheol
already stashed it elsewhere.
Darn it.
(It seems like Ok Cheol
already stashed it elsewhere.)
Unbelievable.
So I went to all that trouble...
for nothing?
I doubt he had the time
to sell an item...
that's worth
hundreds of millions of dollars.
Looking into Chief Tak
will lead us to any transactions.
(Looking into Chief Tak
will lead us to any transactions.)
We must stop him
before the transaction happens.
- Mr. Yoon.
- Is that your lunch?
I was waiting for you
to return from your meeting.
My apologies.
Right, my meeting.
- Here you go.
- Sorry?
It's a welcome gift.
I'm bribing you so that
you'll stay with us for years.
So,
how about a meal together?
I tried to negotiate
with Kang Woo Won.
What on earth did you say...
to make him ask for four times
the original signing bonus?
There was a small
but insignificant issue.
There was an issue?
Is it solvable?
Of course, it's solvable.
I mean, probably.
Then reverse the damage.
By myself?
I'm coming from a meeting
with Kang Woo Won.
He said...
that he'd only talk to you...
about the details of this contract.
Why?
It must be because of this...
small but insignificant issue
only you can solve.
Right.
I'll talk to Mr. Kang
and try to resolve this matter...
If you don't, it's over for you.
- Over?
- The end.
You know?
Good job on finishing
the second round of the research.
Thank you, sir.
Chief Tak will take of the rest,
so focus on the third round now.
Yes, sir.
When will the package
be delivered again?
An event will be held in Taiwan
the day after tomorrow.
A launching event...
joined by the one and only
Kang Woo Won?
The buyer...
will be contacted while
he attends the launching event.
I hope there won't be any hitches.
Once the package is delivered,
the money will be picked up
from Kaohsiung.
When you do,
keep the amount I promised you
as a bonus.
Thank you, sir.
If the third round of research
ends successfully too,
a few million dollars
would've been worth it.
Do you have anything more to say?
No, sir.
I'll get back to work then.
Since you're here,
you should join us for lunch.
I should get working
if I wish to finish...
the third round of research on time.
Unbelievable.
What was that for?
Why would you say hello to me?
I'm the one taking the risk...
by moving the package
out of the lab.
What for though, right?
It's someone else making the money.
Darn you!
- Goodness, Mr. Ok.
- My gosh.
I appreciate your hard work.
Please don't mention it.
It's not like I did much.
We all know that
you do the heavy lifting.
I'm glad you know that.
You must've known that
I'd be eating here today.
You prepared a feast.
Of course we always prepare
something special for you,
but we honestly didn't know
that you were eating here today.
Right?
- Of course not.
Mr. Yoon, you like
stir-fried fish cakes, right?
Have as much as you want.
Thank you.
Please enjoy.
- Thank you.
- Hello, Mr. Tak.
Chief Tak Sang Gi.
Tak Sang Gi is
Director Myeong's right-hand man.
It's safe to call him
the chief operator.
He's a notable target,
so keep tabs on him.
- I should've gotten that for you.
- Please sit.
We're all supposed
to serve ourselves here.
I only picked up yours
while getting mine.
Don't mind me and dig in.
Then I'll enjoy the meal.
Sure.
I eat at the cafeteria
on the 1st and 3rd Wednesday...
every month.
I had no idea that
you ate at the corporate cafeteria.
I come by often
for late-night snacks too.
The head chef here...
makes a delicious
ramyeon with rice cakes.
What?
Did I seem like a fake?
CEOs probably look cooler
when they look...
audacious and serious.
Not at all.
It's nice to see you care...
about your employees' well-being.
If we ever get to work late,
we should come here
for that ramyeon.
Ramyeon with rice cakes!
There are a variety
of ramyeon dishes to choose from,
but that's what you want again?
Once I like something,
I rarely change my mind about it.
Mind if I join you?
I haven't eaten
at the cafeteria in a while,
but it serves delicious food.
Michael!
Forget the law. You're not...
getting out of here alive!
(Armenya scarf 2019 edition)
Why is Chief Tak wearing...
the same brand of scarf
that Michael had on?
Take a look inside
Chief Tak's office right now.
(Chief Tak Sang Gi)
I was wondering about
the new assistant you hired.
We finally meet.
We should get up if you're done.
- Sorry?
- I don't want indigestion, you see.
I've lost my appetite too. Let's go.
What took you so long?
I almost died waiting for you.
Where are the files?
I want my money first.
Hand it over.
(Baek Chan Mi)
What a cute little rat.
(Baek Chan Mi,
Industry Security Team 3)
It's me.
You have it?
Yes.
Baek Jang Mi's real name
is Baek Chan Mi.
That's intriguing.
Tell me more.
Did something happen to your hand?
I injured myself accidentally.
You should've been more careful.
Scars never look pretty on a lady.
Here are the bandages
and ointment you requested.
Apply these before it scars.
Get going then.
Let's go.
(Baek Jang Mi)
You must have urgent business...
to be cutting your lunch short.
An unexpected guest
is waiting for me in my office.
Chief Tak, ETA, three minutes.
Don't tell me that this is
one of her famous hunches.
Baek Jang Mi...
used to work at the NIS.
Her real name is Baek Chan Mi.
She's 38...
and was part of
Industry Security Team Three.
She was dismissed from the agency...
after failing to capture Michael
three years ago.
One of her junior agents
Kwon Min Seok...
died during the operation.
(Epilogue)
How did it go with CEO Yoon?
What?
How is he in person?
Handsome, right?
Right, well...
So it's protocol...
to report anyone we have
a personal connection to.
That's right. Did you cross paths
with someone you know?
Well...
If CEO Yoon was my mark,
I would've charmed...
the pants off him.
Did the gas get to your head?
You think I can't do it?
I was the famous
Catherine Hwang, you know.
Didn't you know that?
What about your husband?
I'm just saying, you know.
All I do is...
clean restrooms and sweep floors.
I wouldn't mind...
a little eye candy.
You know,
I should've been the one
to play his assistant.
See? She's interested in him too.
Right?
That's not what I mean.
Anyone can tell...
that Kang Woo Won isn't the culprit.
He's just not capable...
of planning an intricate crime.
Are you saying...
that Yoon Seok Ho is capable
since he's smart?
Not exactly,
but he does have
the highest level of education.
Don't you know that
anyone can look suspicious...
if you watch them...
while considering them as suspects?
Why are you suddenly
getting all serious?
I'm just saying...
that Kang Woo Won...
can be the culprit.
Your mark is
a globally famous celebrity...
while yours is a rich CEO.
I don't get what
you're complaining about.
So what were you
about to say just now?
What?
It's nothing.
It sounded important.
She asked about protocol...
Can you get me
Kang Woo Won's autograph?
My daughter loves the kid.
I'll at least ask.
Really?
Let me get you a piece of paper.
Where can I find one?
Gosh.
(Good Casting)
She's your new English tutor.
I hope we get along, Seok Ho.
Once you enter Kang Woo Won's house,
observe where
the security cameras are.
She's the worst kind ever.
Chief Tak may be Michael.
Get me any viable evidence.
Five minutes is more than enough.
Let's go.
- I'm sorry, but you can't enter.
- Me?
Get him before he runs off.
Get her!
Chan Mi, Mi Soon, hurry!
If Michael is here, leave him to me.
Consider this...
your last day.