(Episode 4)
(Baek Jang Mi)
Baek Jang Mi's real name
is Baek Chan Mi.
Her real name is Baek Chan Mi.
She's 38...
and was part of
Industry Security Team Three.
She was dismissed from the agency...
after failing to capture Michael
three years ago.
One of her junior agents
Kwon Min Seok...
died during the operation.
I wasn't introduced to
the new secretary.
What's your name?
I am Baek Jang Mi.
(Chief Tak Sang Gi)
Nice.
Fine, live a long life.
This is insane.
Chief Tak, ETA, three minutes.
You have work experience?
What did you do before?
You must be bored these days.
You're showing interest
in random things.
You two seemed so close,
so I got curious.
Is there a story I'm not aware of?
I don't care about
your story with Director Myeong.
Should I start to show interest?
Now I'm getting curious.
Let's go.
A crow landed on the puppet CEO.
How amusing.
Why did this break...
and make me toss food on the floor?
Is this all he eats?
(Chief Tak, ETA, three minutes.)
1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7, 8, 9...
Gosh, I can't seem to find anything.
What does she want me to find?
There's absolutely nothing to...
"8:30 p.m. on the 15th".
"Red Purple"?
I looked into it.
And Red Purple is
a private wine bar.
All members need to make
a reservation beforehand.
And they protect
their guests' privacy at all costs.
That means he met someone in secret.
But why are you suddenly
so interested in Chief Tak?
Because he might be Michael.
Chief Tak?
If Chief Tak
turns out to be Michael,
he would've met someone
prior to the transaction.
Then do you think the transaction
took place at Red Purple?
Let's check the security footage.
The place opens at 7 p.m.
So let's go right after work.
(Good Casting)
(Il Kwang Hitech)
(Red Purple)
(Clubbing in Gangnam: Red Purple)
(Gangnam Club: Red Purple)
It's a welcome gift.
I'm bribing you so that
you'll stay with us for years.
Let's see.
(Screech)
(Oh, no! My bag!)
(My gosh,
my hands are on your breasts.)
(She throws a punch.)
(Say hello. She's your new tutor.)
(Scars never look good
on a handsome face.)
(Stay still. My hands may be small,
but they can really hurt.)
(I hope we get along, Yoon Seok Ho!)
(I love you. I love you.)
6 p.m.!
Can I ask you something?
I'll be going now.
About that doll. Did you...
What are you doing, sir?
Well...
The blinds don't work properly
these days.
The machines in my office
are also a mess.
And the rail for the bookshelf too.
Sometimes, it doesn't work.
Did the new secretary go home?
Yes, she bravely went home
the moment the clock hit 6 p.m.
Should I ask her to come back
if you need anything?
No.
If I make her work too hard,
she might quit. Think about it.
What?
What is it?
I'll just keep acting like
I don't know anything.
"Kang Woo Won's
autograph event in Taipei..."
"to congratulate
the new product launch."
Gosh, I only sign stuff
when I spend money.
But this guy earns money
by signing stuff.
What a great life.
Kang Woo Won is the most
popular star in China and Taiwan.
No wonder he asked
for three times the original pay.
I think this is enough.
I don't think they'll all
fit in the bag.
You never use your brain properly.
That's why you're so dumb.
Pack another bag.
That will solve the problem.
You're right.
I'll just pack another bag.
No, wait.
I should have an extra bag
for my shoes.
You're going to bring...
three luggage bags?
Can't you do simple math?
2 bags for my clothes,
1 for my shoes,
and another bag for food.
You forgot the bag for food,
haven't you?
I was going to pack it last.
I'll do it once I finish packing
the first three bags.
You can't even pack properly,
and you can't do math.
And you even pout.
What is it that you're good at?
My gosh, that little...
(Caller ID restricted)
You have until 9:30 p.m. tonight...
to retrieve the package from 7-49.
Wang Kai will call you
once you arrive in Taiwan.
All you have to do
is deliver the package.
(Caller ID restricted)
Taiwan, my foot.
I'm done with this stupid job.
Whatever this is must cost
way more than the delivery fee.
(Wash and Clean)
As soon as you enter Red Purple,
Mi Soon inserts the hacking chip
into the security system,
and Mu Hyeok hacks into
the security camera.
Meanwhile, Chan Mi gets
all the useful evidence.
It's easier than eating cake,
so be done in 10 minutes.
Enter.
(Mission complete)
It's been a while
since we were on double duty.
Shall we get a move on Chief Tak?
Wait.
Use these.
Let's keep quiet about
Baek Chan Mi for now.
Let's not inform
Director Myeong yet.
We got handed a joker card.
She'll come in handy one day.
The call cannot be connected...
I can't reach Pi Cheol Woong.
What do you mean?
He turned off his phone.
I think he went into hiding.
Track him.
What's this?
Was I mistaken?
I thought I saw something shine.
He's still at Kang Woo Won's.
Get him before he disappears.
Kang Woo Won said...
that he'd only talk to you...
about the details of this contract.
What a pain in the neck.
Just the type that I hate.
Let's add another condition.
Do you mean
you'll sign with us again?
I didn't say that yet.
Whatever the condition is,
we're ready to accept it.
It's me. I got the contract.
Let's amend one thing.
Article 4 Section 5.
For all future events
regarding the commercial.
Article 4 Section 5.
The employee in charge will be...
What's your name?
- Pardon?
- Your name. What is it?
It's Lim Jung Eun.
The employee in charge
will be Lim Jung Eun.
That's all.
What?
Whenever Il Kwang Hitech's
products are shown,
you must be there to
manage the site.
Why? You can't do it?
No. I must do it.
I will do it.
And the most important detail.
Hand over the photos.
What photos?
Do you think I'll let it go
if you feign ignorance?
The photos you took of me!
Why are there only photos of a kid?
I never took photos of you,
and I never will.
I don't even want to.
Peeking into...
someone else's private life
without permission!
That's rude!
Since I know there are no photos,
I won't sign the contract.
If you don't, it's over for you.
- Over?
- The end.
You know?
(Commercial model)
What's taking them so long?
(Wash and Clean)
- It's here at last.
- Really?
Where are they?
What took so long?
My gosh.
Here you go.
I want a receipt.
Give it back. I won't sell to you.
- Come on.
- It's fine, then.
Where are the pickles?
What? Forget it.
- What?
- Pickles?
We need pickled radish.
- Pickled radish!
Pickled radish! Pickled radish!
My gosh.
Shouldn't they give us
pickled radish at least?
Turn on the mic.
Baek Chan Mi, Hwang Mi Soon.
Get out before
we finish our noodles.
We just need five minutes.
Let's go.
Please leave.
Me? Where to?
Don't be so harsh.
We've been here many times.
I've never seen you before.
Don't you know...
a woman looks different
from day to day?
Take care.
She got a new nose and I got...
Oh, come on.
This is getting annoying.
I'll see you again.
They have no idea that
if I played the Korean zither...
back in the day,
even the Russian
Minister of Defense swooned.
What do you want?
It gets busy on Fridays.
The kitchen needed extra help,
so here I am.
Can you confirm
if you're expecting kitchen staff?
They are.
How many times
must I tell you they are?
How can people have
so little trust for each other?
It's terrible.
Hey, it looks like Chan Mi got in.
Where's Mi Soon?
Mi Soon.
Mi Soon!
I'm on standby in the kitchen
on the seventh floor.
Hey.
We have to prepare
seven fruit platters.
Let's hurry up.
Okay, I got it. I'll be quick.
What took you so long?
They've been waiting for ages.
Bring some more side dishes
before they get sober.
Okay.
(Portable Emergency Light)
- Hey, guys.
- Who is she?
This is on me.
You must be tired.
You should take it easy.
Have some while you take a break.
What is all this?
Hey, why aren't the guys
by the backdoor answering us?
I don't know.
Then go check.
Hurry up.
Why do I always have to go?
Have a good one, guys.
Thanks.
Go 5m straight as soon as you exit
the emergency stairway.
You'll see an emergency exit
next to the boiler room.
(Boiler Room)
(Emergency Exit)
Mr. Park, did you have fun today?
Yes, of course.
- You're leaving already?
- Madam Jung, thanks for the food.
- Did you have fun?
- Yes.
Chief Tak Sang Gi.
We're in.
Okay, great. I'll get what we need
in just two minutes.
Yes, you do that.
If Ye Eun was here, it would've
taken less than a minute.
Once you enter Kang Woo Won's house,
check where the security cameras are
and hack them.
You want me to hack them?
It's not an open circuit,
so you have to go inside to check.
But isn't that illegal surveillance?
So just hack the ones
that are outside.
Why? Can't you do it?
I have no choice.
I'll do it, sir.
There we go.
Hey.
Hey, you can't take that, Come here!
Which one should I eat?
Eeny, meeny, miny, moe.
And you are it.
My manager doesn't even care
what I eat.
He's been busy all day
taking care of his own business.
Why is he busier
than a top celebrity?
What's that?
Where did you get that?
Poppy.
Don't touch anything dirty.
Poppy. Poppy.
Gosh, let's go home.
What's that?
(I wish you fail.
Crazy jerk.)
(You have no conscience.)
You crazy psycho. I'm going to quit.
Have a great life!
I can't believe this. This is crazy.
Is... Is that a thief?
Bring me Pi Cheol Woong right now!
You're the one who hired him!
How would I know where he went?
Gosh, my precious cars.
I'm not going to attend
the event in Taiwan...
until my cars
are back to normal. Bye.
Gosh, why won't this work either?
What's the problem?
Gosh, everything is in English.
I barely got this to work.
But why did I get so little?
Oh, my gosh.
Has she lost her mind?
She even broke into my house?
I can't believe her.
You're dead.
68G 3877.
68G...
What was it again? Darn it.
What do you mean there's a woman?
Did she see everything?
Then bring her in too.
(68G 3877)
It's all right.
Always stay on your toes.
It's me.
I have both Pi Cheol Woong
and the woman.
I'll meet you at
the abandoned factory.
Okay, I'm in the system.
Ladies, your job is done.
Why isn't Ye Eun
answering her phone?
The person you called...
Mr. Dong,
stop grilling Ye Eun, will you?
Data analysis
can't be completed overnight.
You're right.
I should've made you do it
even though it would've...
taken you almost a year.
Watching over the ladies
is exhausting enough for me.
Gosh, my stomach is rumbling.
I'm off to the restroom.
Sorry.
(Wash and Clean)
Darn it.
Where on earth did he go?
We have trouble!
What?
Block all the exits.
Get her!
Grab her already.
(68G 3877)
In an emergency,
press the button for three seconds
to activate Code Blue.
Don't you dare!
I need to do this.
Darn.
Did he get stuck
in the toilet or something?
Must I do this at this age?
What? Code Blue?
No wonder Ye Eun wasn't
answering her phone.
Chan Mi, Mi Soon,
Ye Eun is Code Blue.
Get back here right now.
Chan Mi, Mi Soon, come on!
Get her!
Get back here.
Darn it.
Open this!
- Darn!
- Get the keys.
Open it up.
Get her.
- You!
- Get her.
The shutter is coming down.
Please let this work.
Wait. Darn it.
Get her!
Get back here.
My gosh.
Darn it.
Why does this...
always happen to me?
Goodness, that's twice in a row.
Sorry about that.
Hey!
She's getting away.
- Get her.
- Follow her!
(Wash and Clean)
What took you so long?
Just drive, darn it!
- What?
- Get driving.
Gosh.
Darn it.
Gosh, that was close.
Hey, Team Leader Dung,
any boss with a conscience...
would pay double in hazard pay.
Let's watch
the camera footage we retrieved.
Why are you behind the wheel though?
Ask Mu Hyeok when you see him.
It was 8:30 p.m. on the 15th.
so we'll start at 8:00 p.m.
8:00 p.m.
Wait.
Let's head back.
Mr. Dong? What on earth?
Was I left behind?
What's going on?
Where did it go?
Hey, where are the empty bowls?
This is who I am, you know.
This is an urgent matter, so drive.
- You work for the NIS?
- Yes.
No way.
Put on that helmet.
Even those in the NIS
should wear one.
- Now, hold on.
- Just drive.
Here we go!
Wait.
It wasn't Kang Woo Won
but his manager?
He's from China.
Darn it.
We were barking up the wrong tree.
So Chief Tak met with
Pi Cheol Woong because...
Because he's in possession
of the item.
So where are we headed right now?
NIS guy, where to?
Isn't it obvious?
Keep following that truck!
Say no more.
(Wash and Clean)
Ye Eun is in Code Blue? How?
I don't know.
She went to see Kang Woo Won.
Something must've happened
because of Pi Cheol Woong.
Hang in there, Ye Eun.
We need to take a left. Go left.
Don't be ridiculous.
Do what the GPS system says.
Make a left.
The GPS system knows best.
Make a left!
Would you please keep it down?
- Then make a right here!
- Red light.
- Make a right.
- Stop!
- I see it too.
- Don't just blink...
- and step on it.
- What?
- Let me take over.
- No way.
Your license has been suspended.
I'm on duty, so it's fine.
Let me take over.
Stop it.
- Let go of me.
- Insurance won't cover it.
- He's driving too slowly.
- Leave him be!
- I'll do it.
- Stop it.
Guys, stop this.
- Stay put.
- Make a right!
- Please.
- Let go of me.
- Don't make this any harder.
- Let me drive!
Unbelievable.
Is this the best NIS can offer?
Can't we afford a high-pass device?
We need to fill out
a form for it first,
so it's a bit of a nuisance.
What if we lose them?
They're heading to Pocheon,
so the destination
must be an abandoned factory.
Let's go.
What on earth?
Mr. Dong, it's me!
Please open the door.
- Hey!
- Mr. Dong.
Why that... Unbelievable.
Where on earth were you?
What was that?
Keep following us, okay?
We can't hear a word you're saying.
Keep following the truck.
Got it?
I didn't understand any of that.
- Come on.
- What are you doing?
- Hey, NIS guy.
Keep your eyes on the road!
It hurts.
- Mu Hyeok!
- Pull me up.
Let go of me!
- Help me get in there.
- Let go of her.
Guys, watch the bus ahead!
The bus, darn it!
My gosh.
Should I break their legs?
Did you see him flinch like a baby?
Pi Cheol Woong.
Pi Cheol Woong?
No, that's not me.
I doubt you stole from us
without being prepared to die.
Right?
No, I'm not Pi Cheol Woong.
Say something, darn it.
No, that's worth
over 100,000 dollars,
you scumbag!
I requested for backup,
so be our eyes out here.
Gosh.
Let me make this clear.
If Michael is here, he's all mine.
I understand
your desire for Michael,
but let me remind you
that this is a mission.
I won't tolerate anyone going rogue.
You're making my ears bleed.
Guys!
- Look.
- I see we have company.
It's just the two of them.
Guys!
Ye Eun!
Consider this...
your last day.
Let go of me.
Darn, that stings!
Guys, we have a runner.
Are you all right?
How long have you been on the floor?
Guys...
I rarely pull my gun,
but guys who hurt my team...
definitely deserve the bullets.
Sorry about that.
Calling you a guy was sexist of me.
(Stay tuned for the epilogue.)
(Epilogue)
He said...
that he'd only talk to you...
about the details of this contract.
Hello, Mr. Kang,
I'm Lim Ye Eun
from Il Kwang Hitech.
I mean, Lim Jung Eun.
Surprise!
What a pain in the neck.
Just the type that I hate.
Wait, did that seem fake?
I'm Lim Jung Eun
from the Advertising Department.
I heard that you asked for me.
That I did.
What are you going to do about it?
I knew that
a top celebrity like you...
wouldn't be petty enough...
to back out of
an existing contract...
over something so trivial.
What? Something so trivial?
If I'm being honest,
what happened wasn't on purpose.
It only happened because...
I was trying my best
to close this deal with you.
Only someone
so small-minded and spiteful...
would use it to leverage
a higher signing bonus.
How could you be so mean?
What? Unbelievable.
You're insane, aren't you?
If only you had the guts
to actually say that to his face.
Whatever I say
is nothing but an excuse anyway.
I'd be that mean too
if I were in his shoes.
If only I took the advice
and did a better job.
I totally deserve
his hostility toward me.
How can someone like me...
negotiate a deal with
a top celebrity anyway?
I took on a task
that was above my paygrade.
What now?
She'll fire me
if I don't get him to sign the deal.
(Good Casting)
Let the police handle it
and step aside.
You'll be happy with
what you find in the trunk.
Your wish is my command, sir.
Do what you have to do.
I trust your judgment, Chief.
Chief! Why did you pick me
for this mission?
- Where am I?
- He has amnesia?
- Found him.
- Pi Cheol Woong has been located.
In Taipei?
It sure is a good day to fly.
Don't you dare drag them.
I'll look for it.
- Ma'am!
- Is it jammed?
It's about Baek Chan Mi.
There's no record of her return.
A fish that can't be seen
can still stick up the place.
- He's on the plane.
- Why did you play dumb...
when you knew who I was?
It's you, isn't it? You're Michael.