HI BYE, MAMA!
December 19th.
My dear Yeol-mu.
Did you do a kick, Yeol-mu?
You're doing dozens of kicks today again.
I guess you might become a soccer player.
It'll be tough being an athlete.
No. You can do anything you want.
You've grown so well for ten months.
When you come out to the world,
I'll let you have anything in the world.
I'll let you dream of having anything
and becoming anything you want.
I'll see you soon, my baby.
Since the day I can see you
is arriving soon,
I'm looking forward to tomorrow
more than today.
EPISODE 15:
MY LIFE'S TOMORROW
What did you say?
Can I
live?
I want to live.
I want to live, Ms. Mi-dong.
What did I do so wrong?
Is everything
my fault?
I wanted to live,
and I still do.
Seo-woo, Mom, Dad...
I want to be with them for a long time.
What did you just say?
Yu-ri
is going to die?
Why is Yu-ri dying?
Why is Yu-ri dying again?
Hyeon-jeong.
Gang-hwa, hang on.
Hyeon-jeong, what are you talking about?
Yu-ri...
Yu-ri didn't just come back to life?
Tell me.
Tell me everything you know.
All right.
Yu-ri...
dies again in 49 days.
And there aren't
that many days left now.
Why?
Why would she die again?
Why would she die?
They sent her here
to find her place within 49 days.
Then she'd be able to live.
"Her place"?
Her place as Gang-hwa's wife.
Her place
as Seo-woo's mom.
If she does, she can live.
But she says she won't.
She says she won't because
she can't do that to you and Min-jeong.
She says she's already dead,
so
she'll just leave again.
Why didn't you tell me sooner?
Why are you telling me this now?
Maybe...
A vacation as a reward.
Maybe I got something like that.
For about 49 days.
No, just 49 days.
Just leave me be for 49 days.
I'm not here to ruin your life.
I'm sorry.
I shouldn't have come. I'm so sorry.
Yu-ri.
She wants to live?
I told you she would.
Even for a ghost
who's given up everything,
it would be impossible not to want life
when they can have it again.
So I can go to her daughter now, right?
Why
are you doing this to me?
-Cho Gang-hwa.
-Were you
thinking of staying here for 49 days
and dying again?
How did you find out?
So it's true.
When I was
missing you so much that my heart hurt
that I wanted to carve it out,
you weren't here.
And
when I thought I could do anything
to just touch you one more time,
you never answered me.
Then you appeared out of the blue, and now
you're going to die again?
What will I do if you leave like that?
How can I live?
If you decide everything on your own
and leave like that, then what about me?
If I have to lose you twice,
how can I live?
You should've told me!
"I don't have time. Why did you remarry?
I want my place back."
You should've talked to me!
Was I supposed to lose you again
without knowing anything?
You wanted me to do that?
You should've told me, Yu-ri!
How could I have said that?
My place is gone already.
You should've lived a great life then!
This wouldn't have happened
if you were happy!
I hated seeing you live a miserable life,
so I was planning on going up
after seeing you remarry.
I was about to leave everything behind
and go up and live my next life!
But you're the one
who didn't let go of me.
You kept holding onto me,
and made me torture you!
You're the one who held onto me
and made me feel sorry
so I couldn't leave!
You're the one who stopped me
from leaving.
You're right.
I held onto you.
I held onto you more on purpose.
I endured one day.
I could live through it.
Then I endured another day
and lived through it.
But I hated that I could.
I felt guilty,
but I kept on living.
So I felt sorry again.
If you get your place back,
can you live?
Can you really live?
What will you do if I can?
What about your wife?
Will you let her go?
Just tell me if you can or not.
Can you
really live?
Then live.
Why would you die?
Hello, Ms. Jeon.
CHA MU-PUNG, JEON EUN-SUK,
CHA YU-RI, CHA YEON-JI
It's okay. I'm not crying.
It's fine.
SEO BONG-YEON
It really is a wonder how I got
these looks from a dad like you.
JANG DAE-CHUN
Is she a doppelgänger?
She looks like that woman.
I haven't seen her these days, though.
His parents were sent up helplessly.
But he probably has no clue. My goodness.
Hey, run!
Oh, my gosh!
You guys.
Do you think
I won't take you if you hide?
JANG DAE-CHUN
SEO BONG-YEON
Go up voluntarily if you don't want
to be sent up like these useless spirits.
I got you.
You were first in line,
but I was busy sending up
some useless spirits,
so you gained some time.
Hey!
-Who are you?
-What...
Let go of me.
-Let me go.
-Did you just say "useless spirits"?
How dare you call my parents that!
What's this? Why are you
carrying around a cane?
Do you want to get beaten up with this?
Wait. Let me go.
Hey. Wait, sir.
What?
How dare you do this
in such a sacred place?
I...
Wait...
Please.
Excuse me.
What?
Me?
I'm sorry about last time.
A shaman was saying something
unbelievable, so I--
No, it's fine. I was talking
without thinking.
But
how long have you known Yu-ri?
She said you were friends.
Yu-ri?
Well, I guess maybe about
five or six years?
-Five or six years?
-Yes.
Then you knew her before the accident.
You must know about what happened, then.
Well, yes.
I don't really know
how this happened, though.
Is that so?
Anyway, I'm sorry about yelling
at you last time.
-It's okay.
-Well, then. Bye.
Bye.
I already told Min-jeong
-that you're Cha Yu-ri.
-What?
Why did you tell her?
Why would you do that?
You couldn't tell her you're
Seo-woo's mom and you kept feeling sorry.
And Min-jeong didn't have a clue.
That was painful to watch.
Oh, no.
What do I do?
I'm sorry.
I'm the one who told Gang-hwa.
I guessed.
You're the only one who knew.
What did Gang-hwa say?
He told me to live.
You're thinking the same thing, right?
Oh Min-jeong.
What should I do about her?
No.
This is the right thing.
Saving you comes first.
If you leave again,
Gang-hwa won't be able to live properly.
Right?
He won't just feel guilty.
He won't be able to endure it.
Right.
I'm sure he won't.
Yu-ri.
When you told me everything
and said you wouldn't get your place back,
do you know how I felt?
"Because you were
around us for five years,
unable to make a sound,
that made you learn to give up."
That thought broke my heart.
Don't give up because
you feel sorry about hurting
Gang-hwa and Min-jeong.
Grab that chance.
It's your life.
Hyeon-jeong.
I wasn't giving up.
I was accepting
that my life was over.
I was just
accepting that for five years.
Yu-ri.
You're going to find your place,
right?
Min-jeong.
I haven't
gotten my thoughts organized yet.
Just wait until I do.
KANG BIN
KANG BIN (KANG SANG-BONG)
KANG BIN FOUND DEAD
If it's not suicide, why did he die?
What?
He says his best friend killed him
and made it look like a suicide
to frame him for the match-fixing.
What an asshole!
Then we should catch that person!
And my friend
committed suicide later from the guilt.
He says his friend committed suicide
after that from the guilt.
But I heard they found his will.
Well...
I was told to write
a letter of apology
for the match-fixing scandal.
When I was talking about leaving,
I meant retiring, not dying.
I was exhausted, so I wanted to retire.
But that's when I was killed.
It was a letter of apology
for the scandal.
And he got killed
while he was writing that.
I don't need anything else.
Just tell my mom.
Can you just tell my mom
that I didn't die because of her?
-Your mom?
-His mom?
What about her?
My mom
thinks I died because of her.
HE SINKS HIS HEAD AND TRAILS OFF
WHEN I ASK HIM ABOUT HIS FAMILY
THE PATIENT SEEMS TO WANT
TO RESOLVE HIS ISSUES WITH HIS PARENTS
Your eyes, nose, and lips.
You look exactly like her in the photo.
How could I not figure that out?
I'm so stupid.
Sorry.
I'm sorry.
Why are you so sorry?
That you came back to life?
That you deceived me?
Everything.
I'm sorry about everything.
If you keep apologizing to me,
what am I supposed to do?
I want to ask you
why you deceived me and lied to me,
but you keep apologizing to me.
What should I do then?
Instead of apologizing to me, demand me
to give back Gang-hwa and Seo-woo
because they are your family.
Why do you keep saying you're sorry?
I can't do anything if you do that.
It's because I was grateful.
I was grateful
for everything.
That's why I just wanted
to see Seo-woo quietly
and be done with it.
You just wanted to see Seo-woo?
Is that even possible?
That's all you want?
To me,
being able to do that was
something to be grateful for.
This would've been better
if you were mean.
I could have used that as an excuse
and done whatever I wanted.
I had the same thought.
-Min-jeong.
-I will
leave you.
The hand tremor isn't
why you can't operate.
I knew why,
but I pretended that I didn't know
because I didn't
want to be jealous of a dead woman.
But now, she's not dead anymore.
You were her family, to begin with.
You
and Seo-woo.
You weren't my family.
I am
going to leave you.
I'm sorry.
-Yu-ri.
-Yes.
Mom.
Do you want to go for a walk
around the area?
Yes, I'll join you.
Now,
the weather has gotten warm.
Yes, flowers are blooming, too.
Right.
I should go and see the flowers
with my daughter.
Yu-ri.
Yes?
Aren't you disappointed?
About what?
It has been only five years,
but nothing is yours now.
I have you.
You are mine and will be mine forever.
I had you when I was born,
alive, and dead.
You had always been mine.
Right.
And you will be mine forever, too, right?
Should we count your dad and Yeon-ji, too?
Shall we?
Gang-hwa was very sick.
I prayed a lot,
so he could remarry quickly.
Really?
I didn't pray that
for the sake of Gang-hwa or Seo-woo.
But I did it for you.
I thought about how you would feel
if you were watching
and how painful it would be for you.
Well done.
Are you sure that was the right thing?
Yes. You were great.
You're the only one who understands me.
Why don't we sit for a while?
Sure, Mom.
I always sit on this bench.
And Gang-hwa's wife usually sits
on the bench over there.
Was it last year or two years ago?
Seo-woo was playing out here.
I pretended to be passing by
and sat on this bench.
You'll fall. Be careful.
Seo-woo, do you want to play
in the playground before we go home?
Yes.
Strangely, ever since that day,
Seo-woo was always playing
in the playground around that time.
The day after that,
and the day after that.
At first, I just thought
it was a mere coincidence.
Strangely, they only came
whenever I was sitting on this bench.
And
they wouldn't leave the playground
until I left.
And then, I figured out
that
she knew who I was.
She instinctively knew who I was.
You should have asked.
Some relationships are better off
when they are not pursued.
Keeping that boundary was the best.
Someone whom I was grateful for.
That was it.
That way, I wouldn't want more from her.
Can you give me a glass of beer?
Right.
I
shouldn't come here now, right?
I'm sorry.
Sorry.
Why is everyone
apologizing to me?
Why do you all say you're sorry?
If you keep apologizing,
what am I supposed to do?
What should I do?
Gang-hwa has made up his mind.
Yes, saving Yu-ri comes first.
I would do the same.
I don't think
he told everything to Min-jeong.
Telling her everything
won't do her any good.
That won't change anything, anyway.
It might be better for her to curse
him out and make him the villain.
Right.
My gosh, I don't know anymore.
You startled me. Why did you fling that
to the table without a warning?
What's wrong with you these days?
You get so easily startled.
Hyeon-jeong.
Never mind.
I just have a problem. That's all.
What problem?
Did your followers unfollow you?
Are you serious?
What do you take me for?
I'm going through something crazy
that has never happened
in my life.
Did you know that?
You know nothing.
What's the matter with you?
A ghost is following me.
What?
A ghost is following me. I'm scared.
Do you know how scared I am?
Even now,
somewhere in our restaurant,
he might be watching us. I'm scared.
I'm so scared.
Right.
I'll do him that favor.
I'll do it.
Really?
Will you leave me alone
if I do this for you?
If you do this for me,
I'll stop following you. Okay?
Can't you hear me? I'll stop
following you. I'll leave you alone.
You have to keep your promise.
If you don't, I'll call my aunt.
My aunt...
What are you doing, Doctor Gye?
-You're alone here.
-Should I call her or my uncle?
It's my mother's birthday next week.
My aunt is not married,
so I should just call her, then.
-What is it?
-Please come in.
Hello.
Mom?
I'm Kang Sang-bong's mother.
You wanted to see me.
What is this about?
Yes, I did.
Well...
Take a look at this.
What
is this?
This is your son's medical record.
I thought you should take a look.
What?
Unlike what you said in your interview,
was he sick?
No.
Ma'am, could you take a look first?
KANG SANG-BONG
HE SINKS HIS HEAD AND TRAILS OFF
WHEN I ASK HIM ABOUT HIS FAMILY
THE PATIENT SEEMS TO WANT
TO RESOLVE HIS ISSUES WITH HIS PARENTS
What
is this?
That's Kang Bin's mental state
before he died.
Is this true?
He didn't
resent me until his last breath?
That's what I thought.
My mom
blames herself that I killed myself
because of her.
I came out to my family
for the first time when I was in college.
It took a lot of courage
for me to tell them,
but my parents didn't say anything.
They didn't believe me.
That can't be true. No.
No. No, my son.
That can't be true.
Can you think about this again? Please?
I was really disappointed back then.
It felt as if she denied my existence.
So as soon as I joined the team,
I moved out of the house.
And I dodged all of their calls.
I didn't visit them, either.
-That's what I did.
-My gosh.
Because I stopped seeing my family,
I couldn't call them afterward at all.
When I decided to resolve our issue,
it seemed too late.
During the session with this doctor,
actually,
I asked him how I could resolve
this issue with my family.
That's why I went to him.
And after his session, I gathered up
my courage and decided to visit my family.
I bought a present for my mom
-and one for my dad.
-Here you go.
-I bought presents for them.
-Thank you.
Bye.
But that night, I died.
ENDLESS LINE OF VISITORS
It was too late.
YOU'RE THE BEST IN THE WORLD
But after I died,
my mom thought I killed myself
because of what she said back then.
I'M SORRY, MY SON
She kept blaming herself.
I can understand that.
That's understandable.
I found out after I died.
When I came out to my family,
my mom
wasn't denying my existence.
She just felt sorry for me.
That's why she said that.
She was just so shocked.
I realized that too late.
I wanted to tell
my mom that I don't
resent her.
THE PATIENT SEEMS TO WANT
TO RESOLVE HIS ISSUES WITH HIS PARENTS
Ma'am.
The patient didn't resent
any of his family.
It was quite the opposite.
Really?
I see.
I'm sorry, Mom.
I regretted it too late.
What are you doing?
Taking a tour of my room.
Everything is here.
What do you mean?
My life as a teenager,
in my 20s, 30s, and up to this day.
Right. We've been living
in this house for over 20 years.
After you passed away,
Mom brought all of your stuff
from Gang-hwa's house to this room.
Right.
Yu-ri, why don't you start
making glass art again?
You won a lot of awards
and had several exhibitions.
And it was your dream, too.
It's not my dream anymore.
It changed.
Is there a new career you want?
What is it?
Seo-woo.
Yu-ri, come on out!
What brings you here again?
Are you here to drop off Seo-woo?
No, I came here for Yu-ri.
We need to go somewhere.
With Yu-ri? Where?
Seo-woo.
Go change your clothes.
We should get going.
Go where?
Let's just go and get some fresh air
with Seo-woo.
Well...
What's gotten into Gang-hwa?
Did something happen?
This isn't like him.
Where are we going?
What?
I'm not sure.
Seo-woo, where should we go?
Where do you want to go?
An amusement park.
Welcome. Please show me
your ticket. Have a great day.
Please show me your ticket. Have fun.
Let's say hello to the bear.
Hi.
-My gosh, you look like a princess.
-A princess?
Do you want to see yourself in a mirror?
All right.
Ta-da.
You look beautiful, right?
Wow, it's a clown.
Do you know what a clown is?
Right.
Thank you.
-Seo-woo, say goodbye.
-Goodbye.
She must've been tired to be outside.
Right.
She's so cute.
You know what?
She wriggles her mouth from time to time
while she sleeps.
That's you.
You wriggle your mouth when you sleep.
You're right.
That was my habit.
It was times like these
when I'd be
reminded of you
through Seo-woo.
I began to see bits of you
as Seo-woo grew up little by little.
It's not that I held onto you.
I couldn't help but hold onto you
because you left me with something so big.
But even if
I went back in time,
I still would have saved her.
You know who I am, don't you?
I guess you knew instinctively.
It's not easy to hide one's heart.
I knew it.
I thought it was odd. It happened.
I guess he told you.
Seo-woo's mom.
Why are you surprised?
You're Seo-woo's mom.
Just as you know Seo-woo the best,
I know my daughter the best too.
So I can tell you this for sure.
What you're worried about
won't happen.
Thank you for minding me too.
That's something
I really wanted to tell you.
Seo-woo, did you have fun today?
Yes.
I had a lot of fun too.
Thank you for playing with me.
Thank you.
Mom!
-Seo-woo.
I'm sorry.
Seo-woo.
My goodness.
Ms. Mi-dong might end up
hurting her knees.
She hasn't had a drop of water
since this morning doing that.
What's going on?
It's Yu-ri.
She's determined to find out
why Yu-ri was the only one
who was sent back here.
Yu-ri.
You should quit
working at the kindergarten too.
First, you can get your place back
as Seo-woo's mom,
then we'll bring back everything.
I told the hospital
that I'm taking a few days off.
Let's all stay with Seo-woo
starting tomorrow.
You need to stop, Gang-hwa.
You've done enough.
That's enough.
What?
I won't
take my place back.
No, I can't.
What do you mean
you can't take your place back?
I've never
loved anyone else
more than I loved myself.
It was the first time
I had someone
who was more precious than myself.
My daughter.
Our Seo-woo.
What about her? What about Seo-woo?
If I live,
Seo-woo will end up
seeing ghosts for life.
You...
You said she won't see them.
That she'll stop seeing them soon.
I want to live.
I want to live, Ms. Mi-dong.
I was wondering
why you didn't spill out your heart yet.
You held out for a long time.
Live. You can live.
But if you don't go back up,
I can't keep my promise that
your daughter will stop seeing ghosts.
What are you talking about?
If you live,
she'll see ghosts for life.
What?
Your body isn't in this world anymore.
You're neither a human being
nor a ghost right now.
Wait.
Then does this mean
she had been seeing them all along
because of me?
I only found out recently.
I can't believe this.
Then why was I brought back to life?
That judgment or whatever.
Why was I told to take my place back?
I can't let my daughter see ghosts
so that I can live.
Goodness.
What is this nonsense?
No. I thought she'd stop seeing them,
but no.
As long as I stay here,
she'll keep seeing them
all her life.
It all started because of me,
so I have to put an end to this too.
I wanted to
let Seo-woo dream of anything.
I wanted her to want to become anything
and do everything she wants.
So I can't let her
keep seeing ghosts
just so that I could live.
Wait.
We might be able to fix that.
There could be a way, Yu-ri.
After I had Seo-woo,
my tomorrow was always filled with her.
"Will she walk tomorrow?
Will she run tomorrow?
How much more will she grow tomorrow?"
I can't ruin
her tomorrow like this.
I can't let Seo-woo be afraid
and tormented because of me.
How can I live with that?
She's only
six years old.
My daughter.
My goodness.
WISHING PAPER
I WANT TO SEE MY DAUGHTER ONCE MORE,
WRITTEN BY JEON EUN-SUK
Goodness. It's okay, Mom.
It won't kill me.
Okay. I'll finish it quickly,
and go straight home.
Okay.
Yeol-mu, should we just go home?
Should we?
-What's going on?
-Sir.
-He was hit.
-Are you all right?
Call 911!
What happened? Oh, gosh.
If your life hadn't stopped,
what kind of tomorrow would we have lived?
Gosh, Seo-woo. Give me a second.
I'm all done.
Daddy is coming. Shake well. Hurry.
Okay, Seo-woo. He's coming.
You must be hungry.
Goodness, you poor thing.
Seo-woo, it's okay. Don't cry.
Cho Gang-hwa! What are you doing?
Okay, coming!
She's crying. Hurry.
Seo-woo, Daddy is here.
-Daddy is coming.
-It's all right.
Come here. Why are you so sad?
Come here.
Look at that.
She's going. She's going to walk.
-Come here.
-Go, go!
-You did it!
-My gosh. She must be a genius.
Seo-woo!
Let's go to China.
Let's go to the States.
Is it fun? Is it?
Let's go to Japan.
-Dad, are you okay?
-Exactly.
Yesterday or today,
my tomorrow
had always been you.
Subtitle translation by Won-hyang Son