Hey, Parking Master!
Well... Can you park my bike for me?
Me? "Parking Master"?
Why did you turn around, then?
Come on. Take this.
Hey, get me some coffee!
I'll meet you in the lobby!
Hello, Professor. I'm sorry.
Don't be. I'm sorry for waking you up.
You have some time before the rounds.
-Get some more sleep.
-No, it's okay.
There you are.
Is this mine?
When did you get changed?
Hey, I can't come out to the lobby
dressed like that.
I also have to do my rounds,
so I went and took care of business
and got changed as fast as I could.
Is that so?
What you're thinking did not happen.
My anal sphincter is still strong.
Goodness.
What's this guy doing?
He's fast asleep.
Right, I'm exhausted every morning too.
Jeez, you scared me.
It's time you said goodbye to this world.
Leave everything you have behind
and come with me.
Now?
But I still have a lot to do.
Hey, wake up.
Dr. Yong, you're still alive.
-Hey, stop it.
-Seriously?
What the...
Dr. Yong, you must be really tired.
Have you taken a vacation yet?
You need some rest.
No, not yet.
-But I'm taking some time off next month.
-Good.
Professor Chae said we should all
take a vacation for a week,
so all the residents will take turns
and go on vacation.
If I could,
I'd love to take a week off as well.
If you had to take a year off
and not work, what would you do?
-Me?
-She'll probably want to study.
No.
I'd move to a place like Gangneung,
Sokcho, or Tongyeong.
I'd love to live somewhere like that
just for a year.
I want to live in a place that's not
too big or too small just for a year.
I'll work at a hospital there.
The question was,
"What would you do if you didn't work?"
It'd be more boring
if I don't work at all.
No, it wouldn't be boring.
There are so many things you can do.
-Okay, you can play all you want.
-I will!
Anyway, I'd prefer to work
at a small hospital
over a big hospital like this,
so I can give each patient
undivided attention.
There was an MBC documentary
called Success Tale.
Gosh, stop it.
If that show was still running,
they'd produce
a three-episode special feature on her.
In my free time, I'll go hiking,
go to the beach, and do fun things.
Hospitals in small towns are even busier.
"Free time"? Gosh, I doubt it.
What about you, Professor Lee?
What would you do?
Me?
I've never thought about it.
Should I assume I have a kid?
No, let’s say you’re single.
Clubbing! I'd go clubbing, of course.
I'll go to a club and dance all night.
I'll make sure my feet don't touch
the ground for over a second at a time.
-Like this.
-What about during the day?
I'll go shopping.
You see, I'm a city guy.
I love Seoul so much.
Seeing the stars and the moon
in the countryside isn't my thing.
The flashing neon signs in the city
Those things... How should I put this?
They heal my mind.
Aren't you taking flower photos recently?
There are flowers at shopping malls.
The apartment complexes
are surrounded by flowers.
I'd go to the flower shop
by the food court at the department store
and take pictures
of the neatly arranged flowers there.
Let's go. It's time for our rounds.
Come on. I have to do my rounds too.
The glamorous city
Gosh, be quiet.
I'll give you my answer
within the next 72 hours.
Is this some kind of a military
operation? You can take your time.
Then give me about a week.
All right. Don't skip meals.
Of course!
I eat two bowls of rice for every meal.
I'm sorry, Mom.
The baby's condition suddenly worsened.
I have to go to the PICU now.
You can go and get
the health checkup done by yourself.
Mom, the gastroscopy
will be done last anyway.
I should be able to make it there by then.
Of course, I can get it done by myself.
Am I a kid?
But I was told to bring a guardian
for the conscious sedation endoscope.
Gosh, what a nuisance.
So people who are single
and have no friends
can't even get it done or what?
I know that too. That's why I left the car
and took a taxi here. Anyway...
-Excuse me.
-Yes.
Where do I go for a health checkup?
Go to B1 of the next building.
You can either go outside
and find that building
or just head down to B1 from here.
It's all connected.
My gosh, you're so kind.
-Thank you.
-No problem.
Whatever. I don't need you.
I'll figure out what to do with
this damn endoscopy, so just do your work.
I have to go.
Hey, Jun-wan. Are you seeing someone?
You are. Talk to you later.
That prick, is he a psychic?
This morning, his temperature went up
to 37.8°C, so we gave him a fever reducer.
The fever has gone down.
I saw the chest X-ray you took
this morning.
Your lungs are still tight.
That's probably why you had a fever.
It's not easy, but you have
to keep doing the ball exercise.
I feel so weak
because all I eat is porridge.
You'll get rice starting tomorrow.
We'll give him normal meals
starting tomorrow.
Okay.
Can I eat meat?
I have a huge craving for bulgogi.
Gosh, even now...
I feel like I can smell bulgogi right now.
The Seoul-style bulgogi, right?
With the sweet marinade.
With a ton of green onions.
Two tablespoons of minced garlic.
A little bit of corn syrup and plenty of
enoki and shiitake mushrooms, right?
I can smell...
Ma'am! You can't give him that.
He's supposed to be fasting now.
Gosh, please. My goodness.
Your surgery is tomorrow.
You really shouldn't be eating this, sir.
Gosh, Doctor.
It's major surgery
where his abdomen will be split open.
He can't go in for the surgery
on an empty stomach.
He needs to eat at least one proper meal
for the surgery to go well. Right, Doctor?
No. That's not how it works, ma'am. Gosh.
Sir, you can eat as much as you want
after the surgery.
If you eat this now,
you'll have to fast one more day.
Just restrain yourself for today,
and you can eat all sorts of yummy foods
until you turn 100. I promise, okay?
-Great. I'll put this in the fridge.
-Gosh, all right.
Thank goodness you caught that,
Professor Lee.
He's getting his surgery tomorrow.
Doctor, wait! Doctor.
Take this.
My grandson bought it.
My gosh, it's sweet and tasty.
It's so good.
Ma'am, we can't accept things like this.
This could get us in trouble.
Gosh, it's just coffee though.
You really can't accept it?
You see, I just...
I feel bad
for causing such a nuisance today.
That's very sweet of you.
The gesture is more than enough.
I'll take it.
Thank you.
My gosh, it looks delicious.
Ma'am, I'll accept it this time,
but don't give me anything from now on.
Sure thing. You won't get anything from me
from now on.
Enjoy the coffee.
-Thank you for this.
-My pleasure.
Ms. Song! Let's go to the VIP ward.
Ms. Song and I will go check up
on Mr. Go Yeong-min in the VIP ward.
Wait.
What?
You can come too.
Let's go.
-Your kid dropped out of school?
-Yes.
The kid really can't stand school.
If the kid doesn't want to go,
you can't really do anything.
I mean, what can you do?
-Eighth grade, right?
-Yes.
Gosh.
I said, "You have
to at least finish middle school."
-But the kid wants to take the GED test.
-What?
The kid will work part-time
and buy a camera and a computer.
And the kid told me
to mind my own business.
Sometimes I feel like my kid is an alien.
Hello. My gosh.
I guess you came here
right after your shoot.
Yes, hello.
I was up all night because of the shoot.
I got here a few hours ago.
I didn't have a chance
to remove my makeup though.
Is your father asleep?
Yes, he just fell asleep.
-Hello.
-Yes, hello.
My gosh.
Even for simple surgery,
the next day is always the hardest.
After today, it'll be much easier,
so please tell him to hang in there.
He actually watched TV with me
until he fell asleep.
He doesn't feel any pain or discomfort.
He feels great.
Well, I should buy you a meal sometime.
Sure.
Then how about lunch today?
Sounds good.
How are the total bilirubin
and LFT levels?
The total bilirubin level is 25,
and LFT is 700 over 400,
but it keeps going up.
-Still no word from the KONOS?
-No.
I don't think she can hold out
for more than a week.
Gosh.
Ji-a's mother is outside, right?
Yes, she is. But she's devastated.
I explained everything to her.
Often, and in detail.
Not like the last time. I wasn't blunt.
Thanks.
I'll tell her
that Ji-a might have a hard time.
You're a big eater now.
Back then,
I only ate one meal every two days.
-It must've been tough for you.
-Yes.
Sorry.
Well, is that why you broke up with me?
Me? I didn't say I want
to break up with you.
-Did I say it first?
-Yes.
You said you were stressed and tired.
You wanted a break.
Then you were off the grid.
I did. But when I called you
after a little while,
you ignored my calls.
-I called you about 30 times.
-No, you called 29 times.
Good for you. You have a good memory.
I totally made that up.
-Hello, I'm a fan of yours.
-Oh...
-Hello, enjoy your lunch.
-Thank you.
Are you uncomfortable here?
We should've eaten out.
Yes, I said I'd take you
to a nice restaurant.
Gosh, don't you know about
the Improper Solicitation and Graft Act?
-Hello, Professor Lee.
Aren't you...
Yes. She's the person who you think
she is, but she's eating right now.
Go away, guys.
-Enjoy your lunch.
-Thank you.
Would you like anything else?
This kongguksu is good too.
My, look who's here. I'm a fan of yours.
Gosh, these pricks.
Can you please let her eat--
My gosh.
Hello, sir.
Is everything fine, my good sir?
-He's the chairman of the hospital board.
-Oh, hello.
My gosh, you don't need to get up. Please.
You look much prettier in person.
My goodness.
Are you a doll?
Gosh, no.
What brings you by?
-Are you not feeling well?
-I'm fine.
I came for a checkup.
-Is she your patient?
-Well...
I performed surgery
on her father yesterday.
Can I take a picture with you?
-Sure.
-Let's take a selfie together.
Sure, I can take it.
Hey, I want to be in the picture too.
All right.
Here we go.
Oh, I was recording a video.
Sorry about that.
-Shall I take a picture of all of you?
-No, it's okay. I got this.
All right, let's try it again.
Look at the camera.
-What are you doing?
-Here. Let's do this.
-Hey.
-This is...
Hey, you take it. Goodness.
-All right, then.
-Okay, guys.
I'll take it now. One, two, three.
You're too stubborn.
That was embarrassing,
in front of all those people.
What was I supposed to do?
I can't see very well.
Hand me your car keys.
I'll drive you home.
People become more stubborn as they age.
-No wonder youngsters don't like you.
-Come on now.
I'm still young at heart.
Age is nothing but a number.
You need to be youthful physically.
How you feel doesn't matter at all.
Jeez, give me that.
Maybe the battery is dead.
Are you sure it's on this floor?
I always park here...
I told you.
How you feel doesn't matter at all.
Let's move into a nursing home, Jong-su.
Do you know of a good one?
Frankly, I'd like that.
But first, let's find your car.
Give me that.
I took a taxi here today.
-Goodness.
-I took a taxi.
-Oh, dear.
-You think it's funny?
Yes, I have to laugh.
Goodness. You're too much.
Gosh. I get that you were
all over the place today, but how...
-Oh, boy.
-I took a taxi here.
MOM
Hi, Son. Did you have lunch?
No, not yet. I'm going to have lunch now.
What's with your voice, Mom?
Do you have a cold?
They say even dogs don't catch a cold
in the middle of summer,
yet I caught a cold. Poor me.
I'm okay though. I took some medicine.
What is it? Did something happen?
Oh... No.
I'll go to Aunt's place after work.
Yes.
I'll head over there now
and eat something.
I'll see you later.
When did you get here?
What's wrong?
Is your patient not doing well?
It's a six-month-old baby.
We performed the Kasai procedure
three months ago for her biliary atresia.
And?
Her condition seemed to be improving
after the surgery,
but her hepatocirrhosis
is quite serious now.
A liver transplant
would be the only solution.
But her mom's blood type isn't compatible,
and her dad has hepatitis B.
Have you registered her yet?
It won't be easy to find a donor
as she's a baby.
Yes, I already did.
But I haven't heard from them yet.
She's an infant, so a brain-dead donor
must be under the age of 40.
And the liver can't be too large.
It's honestly so difficult.
Her parents seem exhausted.
I think they've almost given up.
I can't give up though.
Oh, boy.
But you should try everything you can do.
Let's go.
-Let's go eat something.
-I don't have an appetite.
What? A hinoki bathtub?
Why do you need it?
Seong-beom who lives next door
got one for his mom?
What? Thirty million won?
Mom, your son is not rich.
I live paycheck to paycheck.
Gosh, seriously!
I already spoke to my friend
who's an ENT doctor.
Come to the hospital next week.
I'll go with you.
You need to get good-quality hearing aids
that fit well.
Gosh, I chose a cheap one.
Yes, seriously. It was very cheap.
Okay.
Jeong-yeon changed what?
She changed her name? To what?
Mom.
If she's still only getting minor roles
after 15 years,
it means she doesn't have talent.
Tell her to quit and learn
a practical skill or prepare for an exam.
I'll talk to her.
Okay, I'll call her.
-Jeong-yeon changed her name?
-Yes.
She's Yeon-jeong now.
-That's a pretty name.
-Pretty, my ass.
What a joke.
It sounds like a Chinese restaurant.
My gosh.
-She's so immature.
-You ordered eggs, right?
Your eggs are here. They're fresh and big.
You haven't eaten yet, right? I knew it.
Here, the lady at the cafeteria
gave me this.
-They're boiled eggs, right?
-Obviously.
Professor Chae, the flash drive. Hello.
-Yes, I'll take it.
-Here you go.
My brother, good to see you.
A younger sister's husband
is a brother-in-law.
Gosh, no.
Brother-in-law, have a seat here.
Are you busy? Sit down for a minute.
-I can't. I have to do something.
-Song-hwa.
Is he that busy?
Are you making him work like a dog?
Join us and have some food.
Yes, have a seat.
I have something to tell you.
Okay.
Well...
You know that you're the first, right?
-What do you mean?
-I'm talking about Ik-sun.
She's actually quite popular.
When you meet her,
you realize that she's funnier
than you thought.
Yes, you're right. She's really funny.
I know that very well.
Especially, the pigeon...
Right, the pigeon.
You must've seen it many times.
I taught her that.
You see, I...
This is what I do. The pigeon...
It flies like this.
Then it comes back like this.
I've been seeing that for 20 years.
-Gosh, I'm sick of it.
-I've seen his and his sister's.
That's why she's had so many guys
confess their feelings to her.
I'm telling you. Ik-sun has had
countless guys chase her.
Yes, Ik-sun is popular
in the unit as well.
Right?
She's used to having guys
confess their feelings to her.
This is my first time seeing her
being so obvious about liking a guy.
Me?
Gosh, it's not me.
We don't have that kind of relationship.
Seriously, we're just close friends.
She's my best friend.
-Really.
-That's how it begins, you know.
Soon, you guys will call each other
"babe" or "honey."
Professor Lee, we're really just friends.
You see, my sister...
She's so used to receiving love.
She's never liked a guy first.
Even if she had a crush on someone,
she never showed it.
But I think
my sister likes you.
Dr. Ahn.
I hope
you'll accept my sister's love.
Are you all right? That must've hurt.
-Why did you hit me? What the hell?
-Hey.
-Why--
-You prick.
-Hey, guys.
-What? Why?
-I didn't do anything.
-Stop.
-Who do you think you are?
-How embarrassing.
-What's your problem?
-Guys, enough!
Hey, what the hell?
I brought those eggs.
-How dare you smack my head--
-Seriously!
I thought
you guys were seven-year-old boys.
Why did you use his head to crack the egg?
Because Ik-jun kept talking nonsense.
Why is that nonsense?
I've never seen a guy
who knows so much about his sister.
He was talking about himself,
not his sister.
That's how he's always been.
Have you ever seen Ik-jun
fall for a girl first?
He married Hye-jeong
because she chased him for months.
He and his sister
are driving me nuts these days.
I'm leaving.
You won't stay for coffee?
I have to go see Mr. Instinct.
I have a gift for him.
Bye.
Have you seen Mr. Instinct?
"Mr. Instinct"?
Dr. Do stepped out to get coffee.
-Should I call him?
-No, no need.
He's never around
when I'm trying to be nice.
Why, Professor?
I was going to ask him
to take care of an ASD next week.
-Shall I call him?
-No, I can call him.
I was going to tell him nonchalantly
and surprise him.
I heard he comes here often,
so I came to find him.
Too bad. I suppose this is his fate.
Take it easy, guys.
What brings you here?
Is this Dr. Bong's salon,
where I can find out
everything about the professors
from their first love
to their health problems?
That's correct.
About Professor Kim Jun-wan?
Correct.
I love Professor Kim very much.
I want to know more about him.
What should I do?
Gosh, I'm so curious.
Dr. Ahn, I'm really jealous.
Professor Chae is like Mother Teresa.
Yes, she's great.
Dr. Ahn, you really don't look like
a military guy.
Are you sure
you're from the Military Academy?
Yes, I did pretty well in the military.
Then why did you leave?
You got into Korea Military Academy
and became a captain.
Why did you quit?
Rumor has it
that it was because of a woman.
I heard he quit because
he lacks the aptitude for it.
There was a big accident in his unit.
He quit because of his PTSD.
-I'm sure a woman was involved.
-He lacks the aptitude.
He obviously didn't follow
the MBTI test results.
It was because
of his post-traumatic stress disorder.
It can be very stressful.
Wouldn't it be more comfortable for you
to talk about this when I'm not around?
No, we never talk behind anyone's back.
We say it in front of them.
Dr. Ahn, you won't tell us anyway. Right?
Forget it. It's not like we're curious.
-All right.
-Also, the past isn't important.
The future is what matters.
Professor.
What does Professor Kim Jun-wan
like the most?
I've been observing him
for half a year and...
And?
I think he likes everyone but me.
He doesn't open up easily.
He has no interest in other people.
He's a selfish guy.
Oh, there is this one thing.
Golf. He loves golf.
He'd even go golfing
with his parents' worst enemy.
As for Jeong-won, he's from a rich family,
so he's dabbled in all sorts of things.
He has a different hobby for each season.
-In spring--
-He runs a marathon.
That's right.
He runs a marathon in spring.
In summer, he goes surfing.
In autumn, he goes hiking.
Then in winter, he goes skiing.
But he can't do any of that these days
because he's busy.
What about Professor Yang?
Seok-hyeong? Does he have a hobby?
I think he's always home.
Rumor has it that he has a 300-inch TV.
Jeez.
Song-hwa's only hobby is going camping.
As for Ik-jun...
That prick is...
He does everything.
He bikes, golfs,
and also likes video games.
He can play the guitar
as well as the bass guitar.
He even wrote a cheer song
for a baseball team. Also, he can cook.
Anyway, he does everything.
And he's good at all of them.
-He can cook?
-He sure can.
You know
he's been a single father for a few years.
He's adamant about giving U-ju
only organic, home-cooked meals at home,
so he always cooks and eats
with his son on weekends.
Does it need more vinegar?
Hands up.
Are Ma-ne and her dad the only ones
coming this evening?
-It's Mo-ne.
-Right, Mo-ne.
Does Mo-ne not have a sister?
I'm sure she does. One called Ma-ne.
She has an older sister, Jang Ma-ne.
They're twins.
See? I knew it.
Ma-ne and Mo-ne always go as a set.
Is Ma-ne not coming today?
I don't know. I like Mo-ne.
Here you go.
When it comes to love, you never know.
I made meatballs.
-I even made ketchup from scratch.
-I want jajangmyeon!
Hey, come on.
What's your name?
"Brachyscome angustifolia."
It blooms all year round?
Your life must be exhausting.
"Geranium"?
I've heard of "plutonium"
and "uranium,"
but I've never heard of "geranium."
Anyway, nice to meet you.
Shouldn't you go to the hospital?
Gosh, I'm sick of that place.
If I fall ill, I'll just quietly move
into a temple somewhere.
Oh, another flower I've never seen before.
Hold on. What is your name?
Jong-su, try taking a picture of me.
Come on.
-What does it say?
-What?
Oh, it found a name.
-Really?
-Yes.
The name is...
"Your Youth Is Gone."
What?
It says your youth is gone.
For real? Let me see.
Show me.
Come on. Show me!
Gosh, no need. What's there to see?
-Hey!
-Goodness.
-Gosh, seriously.
-Ouch. Let's go inside.
-It's cold. Come on!
-What are you talking about? It's summer.
-Gosh, it's so cold.
-Hey, show me. Does it really say that?
Hey!
YULJE MEDICAL CENTER
You look good.
You're young, so you always look pretty.
Oh, you look a little tired today.
-Menstrual cramps. I get it every month.
-Oh, no.
-I have a question.
-Fire away.
Is that the only outfit you have?
Yes, this is my summer outfit.
What? What are you doing?
I can see my reflection on your face.
This is called dewy makeup.
It's too much.
My mom said fashion that others
don't recognize can't be called fashion.
My mom said I should tell my friends
right away when they go the wrong way.
What the heck?
We'll begin the ASD closure
for patient Jeong Jin-ho.
Lead surgeon Do Jae-hak.
First assistant Kim Jun-wan.
Please begin, Dr. Do.
Okay.
Don't cut that part.
Be very precise,
or you'll damage other parts.
Got it.
Again, be precise.
Go down to the endocardium.
If you only stitch up the outer layers
that are on sight, it'll bleed later.
Understood, Doctor.
For that part, don't go too deep.
Don't fool your eyes. Look and be precise.
Okay.
Dr. Do.
I got a call from the ICU,
so I can't finish this up.
Can I go?
Yes, get going. Thanks for your help.
All right, thank you.
Professor.
Thank you for this opportunity.
I'll do better next time.
Okay, do better next time.
Hey.
You actually did better than I thought.
What's gotten into you?
-Hello.
Pass me my phone.
-Are you guys med students?
-Yes.
Where do you live?
I live pretty far.
It takes 50 minutes by subway.
My gosh, that must be tiring.
-All right, take it easy.
-Have a nice day, sir.
-Hello.
Dr. Jang Gyeo-ul.
She's in the OR.
Oh, really? Thanks.
Med students, right?
-Yes, sir.
What does your father do?
-He's a farmer.
-I see.
Have a good day, sir.
Professor.
Ji-a's hourly urine output
is less than 3cc.
-What about her vitals?
-Her BP is okay,
but her heart rate is around 150bpm.
She has tachycardia.
Professor, we're ready.
Okay, I'm coming.
It's an imperforate anus surgery,
so I'll finish in two hours.
Give her more fluid
and keep me updated, please.
Call Professor Lee Ji-yeong
if she gets worse. I'll let her know.
Okay.
-Hello.
-Hi, who are you?
I'm a med student.
Why did you choose to go to med school?
It's a hard path.
-Is there a doctor in your family?
-No.
-What does your father do?
-He's a farmer.
I see. Farming is great.
No, the surgery wasn't that hard.
It was for a condition called "ASD,"
an atrial septal defect.
I do it all the time.
Yes, I got it done in no time.
Why would I get yelled at?
Professor Kim doesn't lose his temper
for no reason.
Honey, I'll call you back.
-Where are you going?
-Not telling you. Was that your wife?
Yes, I bragged about my first surgery.
I'm envious that you have a wife.
Professor, I signed a long-term lease.
No more monthly rent!
The deposit is 200 million won.
I'll invite you to our housewarming party.
Did you check everything thoroughly?
There are a lot of rental scams.
It's me who took the college entry exam
four times, and the bar exam six times.
Long-term leases are rare these days,
so I was wondering if I should
just extend my monthly lease.
But it was one of my realtor's listings,
so I signed it right away.
In other words,
my realtor will be my landlord.
So everything was very easy.
I signed it immediately.
Hey, realtors can be scammers too.
I checked a certified copy of the register
as well as his ID.
-You should be careful.
-Of what?
Professor Cheon Myeong-tae.
I've heard bad rumors about him.
Stay away from him.
"Bad rumors"? Like what?
-It's kind of gross.
-Gosh, enough. I don't want to hear it.
Be it cheating, gambling, or stealing.
I don't care what he does.
Get back to work.
Stop following me around.
-Oh, Professor.
-What? What now?
You're seeing someone, right?
You're literally glued to your phone.
And if she takes this long
to get back to you,
it's safe to assume that she dumped you.
-Hello.
Hi, guys. Are you two
the famous Hong-do and Yun-bok?
-Yes, I'm Jang Yun-bok.
-I'm Jang Hong-do.
We've met before. I gave you a lot of
sausages at the cafeteria that day.
No way. That was him?
The chatty cafeteria guy?
Be quiet.
Hey.
Yes?
What songs do kids listen to these days?
-Pardon?
-I'm talking about music.
Tell me the kind of songs
you listen to these days.
IU's songs.
Well, I listen to...
Zoo's songs.
Hold on. Are you talking
about the band that I like?
How do you know that band?
She always listens to old songs.
She's so lame.
No, she's not.
What's lame about old songs?
-You're lamer.
-No, they are lame.
He doesn't get romance.
I can see that.
Hey, don't hang out with him.
You know nothing...
Yes, I'm on my way now. Okay.
I'm leaving for my rounds.
I'll buy you a nice meal
when I see you again. Okay?
Oh, right. Don't stay here.
Go to the cafe in the lobby.
If you stay here,
whoever walks in will try to give you
advice and meddle. Okay?
Gosh, I'm out of breath.
Bye.
-Is he a comedian?
-No.
He's Dr. Romantic.
What's wrong with you? Are you all right?
What do you mean? I want Coke.
Your face is very swollen.
You should...
Oh, this. I have menstrual cramps.
I took some medicine.
I think the medication
caused the swelling.
Hello, Professor Lee.
What happened?
-Go to the ER now.
-What?
I'm all right. I'm just
feeling under the weather today.
No, you're not okay.
It looks like an allergic reaction.
What did you have today?
Nothing really.
What?
-Hey.
-Oh, no.
We ran a blood test,
and you have
the antiphospholipid antibody syndrome.
To maintain a healthy pregnancy,
your blood has to flow well.
But with this syndrome,
it's hard for your blood to circulate.
Forming a placenta and maintaining
your pregnancy can be difficult.
Then, is this similar to
having recurrent pregnancy loss?
Yes.
So, this is your third pregnancy.
And you had two previous miscarriages.
Let's see. You're seven weeks pregnant.
Yes.
Here.
I'd like to prescribe some medication.
You should get heparin shots.
This shot will prevent
the blood from clotting.
You can easily get these shots.
This is similar to the insulin shots
diabetes patients get.
And the needle is very thin,
so it won't hurt as much.
And our nurse will thoroughly explain
how to inject the shots
and take the medication.
Come back after two weeks,
and I'll check on your condition, then.
Professor,
you must have seen a lot of mothers
with this kind of disease.
So you must think
this is nothing serious, right?
Why is miscarriage a disease?
Miscarriage isn't a disease.
Of course, you did nothing wrong here.
A lot of patients
that had miscarriages ask me
if they did something wrong
or if they must be careful in the future.
That's not true.
This can happen to anyone.
And besides, you know the cause this time.
We can prepare for it
and help you get treated.
Then you may be able to
have a healthy baby.
So make sure you get your heparin shots.
And take it easy for the time being.
Okay.
Thank you.
-Are we done?
-Yes.
We're done for today.
Lunch?
It's on me. Let's go!
Okay.
Two pieces of chocolate cake,
to-go, please.
-How many forks do you need?
-One. Both of them are for me.
Cardiothoracic Surgery, Code Blue.
To the hallway in front of Room 6210.
-Emergency for CS, right?
-Cardiothoracic Surgery, Code Blue.
To the hallway in front of Room 6210.
-Is it Professor Park Jin-u's patient?
-Yes.
The patient had endocarditis,
so they performed an AVR.
I'll check the rhythm.
-His heart is beating.
-Mr. Lee Jong-hyeon.
Mr. Lee Jong-hyeon, are you all right?
What a relief.
-Bye.
Check if it's flowing right. Well done.
Professor Kim.
Hello.
I'm Cheon Myeong-tae.
Hi. I'm Kim Jun-wan.
So you're the big shot at CS.
I am?
You're in charge of the VIP Ward,
so I say you are.
One's talent makes
all the difference to doctors.
What are you doing this weekend?
Do you like golf?
Over there. There are two empty seats.
Professor Yang, over there.
Go ahead. It's all right.
Seon-jin, take the seat over there.
Professor Yang, let's sit here.
Okay.
I have a question.
-Can I?
-Yes.
Well,
you met a woman in a navy lace dress
at the outdoor garden last week.
Who is she?
You two
looked cozy together
when you were talking to each other.
Who is she?
Oh, her.
The mistress of Taegeon Apparel's
Chairman Yang Tae-yang.
What?
She's the mistress
of Chairman Yang Tae-yang.
I see.
It was in the news, so you know, right?
I think the whole hospital knows.
I'm all right. I've been used to it
since I was in school.
I see empty seats over there.
Jeong-won, look.
Okay.
Oh, right. Hey, do we have
band practice tomorrow?
Don't make any plans tomorrow night.
Okay, Jeong-won?
Okay.
You finished.
You didn't pick at your food.
I was never picky with my food.
Don't be picky with people, you prick.
My resident is here.
You're best friends with Dr. Jang, right?
Yes, I am. How do you know that?
I see you together all the time.
Right. Gyeo-ul is in the ER now.
My gosh, why?
It's gotten better after she got the shot.
I think she had anaphylaxis from NSAIDs.
SUDDEN REACTION TO THE BODY
Her face swelled 30 minutes
after taking the pill for cramps.
Then, she couldn't breathe.
She passed out like a scene in the movie.
-Oh, no. Please excuse me.
-Okay.
She's much better now.
She's probably asleep.
YULJE MEDICAL CENTER
Gosh. Are you okay?
Are you in pain? Should I call Hui-su?
No. I'm not in pain anymore.
Did you sleep here?
Is it dawn now?
Yes, it's night.
But you've been getting
a lot of text messages.
A lot of professors came to check on you.
I should have chosen GS too.
They don't treat you like a resident.
You're treated like a princess.
I heard you were sick.
Are you feeling better now?
Get a lot of rest and feel better.
He sent me a smiley face, right?
Yes. A smiley face.
That's not a tilde. It's a smiley face.
Yes, it is. It's a smiley face.
What about it?
Could he have feelings for me?
What?
Professor Ahn likes me, right?
No.
Why not?
If he likes you,
he would have come here.
You like him, don't you?
Dr. Jang,
you like Professor Ahn, right?
Yes.
Yes, Song-hwa.
Okay. Hold on.
Jun-wan, Song-hwa needs to talk to us.
She wants to grab dinner.
-You're free, right?
-Of course.
Yes, he can.
Okay. We're on our way out, too.
Okay. See you soon.
Something sounded off about her.
Did something happen?
Why? How did she sound?
She acts as if everything is fine,
but I think something is up with her.
Why are you telling us that now?
When did you get tested?
It's been a week.
I got a biopsy.
I'll get the result tomorrow.
The core biopsy.
Yes, that.
The shape doesn't look good.
When the doctor told me that,
it did scare me a bit.
Hey, how could you joke about that?
Why did you go to Jae-an Medical Center?
If you had asked me or Ik-jun,
we would've taken care of it right away.
When does the result come out?
My cousin works there. I'll ask him now.
My gosh, stop it.
I didn't tell you
because I knew you'd make a fuss.
If it's bad,
people in the hospital will talk about it.
I hate that.
What are you talking about?
It's not going to be bad.
The result must be out already.
I'll call them.
Stop it. Don't. Seriously, stop it.
I'll find out tomorrow morning.
What's the point?
I really don't want you to do it,
so don't.
This is why I had it done
at another hospital.
Please don't do anything. Please?
What time tomorrow?
-Seven.
-That early?
Yes. My schedule is full this week.
When I said I couldn't make it,
they bumped me up by an hour.
They start seeing outpatients at eight
like we do.
I'm very grateful for it.
Did you say you couldn't get the result
because of your outpatients?
Unbelievable.
You could've talked to the hospital
and rescheduled the appointments.
Are you that inflexible?
How could I do that? Some patients
made appointments months ago.
Many are coming to Seoul
from the countryside.
I'll be fine.
I'll go and get the result myself.
My gosh, you and your nagging.
But that's an excellent doctor.
Your doctor is coming to work
early for you.
Right? It's so early. I can never do that.
Let me know as soon as you get the result.
Okay.
-Should I go with you?
-Don't you dare! I'm serious.
I'm sure it's nothing.
Hey, let's eat. Dig in.
It's not mine.
Not mine.
Yes?
Are the vitals stable?
Is there free air?
Yes, I'm nearby.
If there are a liver laceration
and a perforated bowel,
I should explore that.
Okay. I'll be there soon.
Darn it. I'm leaving.
Good luck.
I got off work,
but I'm at the hospital again.
Do you have an emergency patient?
Yes, the patient was in a car accident.
I think the patient's liver
and bowel need surgery.
Oh, no. You'll probably
have to pull an all-nighter.
Yes, I'll probably be done in the morning.
And that's if I'm fast.
Then, you should come to my shoot
when you're done in the morning.
It's nearby.
I must be on standby
early in the morning tomorrow, too.
I'll buy you coffee. There are a lot
of convenience stores nearby.
I should buy you coffee.
You treated me last time.
If I finish early in the morning,
I'll try to visit you.
I might not be able to make it, though.
Okay. Good luck with the surgery.
I hope I can see you tomorrow morning.
Okay.
ELAPSED TIME
I think the repair is holding well.
I'll take these.
COMPREHENSIVE MEDICAL EXAMINATION CENTER
Seriously? Why are you here?
Why do you think?
I came because I'm worried.
Look at that big yawn. Goodness.
You should just get some sleep at home.
-Why did you come?
-How could I sleep?
Hello.
Thank you for seeing us this early.
Gosh, don't mention it.
This happens a few times.
-Please wait.
-Hold on. Have some of this.
It's really cheap. It's nothing big.
No, it's all right.
I bought way too many. That's why.
Please take some. I'm begging you.
Thank you. Please give us ten minutes.
Okay. We can wait.
Hey, what if I have cancer?
You can get it fixed.
I'll fix it no matter what.
-It's nice.
-What?
Getting a confident answer
from the doctor.
Now, I understand why doctors
shouldn't give out such answers.
It's so nice to hear that.
It makes me think
you'll fix whatever is wrong with me.
That's why I should never say things
like that to my patients.
What if something goes wrong?
If the result comes out badly,
I think they would be in utter despair.
Yes, Seok-hyeong.
I'm about to go in.
Okay. I'll tell you right away.
Okay.
-Can Seok-hyeong make calls?
-Yes. Why?
I thought he only texted.
He calls me often.
A long time ago,
Seok-hyeong liked you a lot.
Hey.
That's ancient history.
You know the day when
Seok-hyeong told you that he liked you?
Did you know that he slept on the street?
-Really?
-Yes.
He and I had drinks that night.
He told me that he confessed his feelings
and you turned him down.
We had drinks and went home.
But late at night,
I got a call from the police station.
They told me to take my friend home.
They called me
because I was the last person he called.
I was confused and went to the station.
My gosh. He was sleeping on the street,
and the officers brought him there
so he didn't freeze to death.
Seriously.
That brings back so many memories.
So many memories.
Wait, so you knew.
Why did you pretend you didn't?
I only knew that Seok-hyeong liked you.
I didn't know it in detail.
Ms. Chae Song-hwa, please come in.
Okay.
YULJE MEDICAL CENTER
We have ten more minutes, right?
Yes.
Should I go and get you some coffee?
No. I'm good. I was just checking.
Wait. Now that you ask me,
I kind of want coffee.
What is it?
-I'm fine. It's benign.
-Okay. Great.
What's the result?
It's a fibroadenoma.
We'll test it again in six months.
I knew it.
-You did well. See you later, then.
-Okay.
It's benign. Are we good now?
Did everyone come?
There's one more.
Did you call the guys today?
I saw them visit you one at a time.
You know we have
band practice today, right?
See you later.
My brother-in-law, have a great day.
You can't finish it, right? Pour me some.
What if we get addicted to Coke?
I can't drink because I'm worried
that the hospital will call me.
Jun-wan, do you want Coke or Sprite?
He's busy.
His mom's about to build a hinoki tub.
What? You want to switch to cypress?
Mom, hinoki is cypress.
They are the same thing.
Heopa also means lung. Kongpat, kidney.
Jjijimi, pancake. Jeonguji, chives.
-Jeonguji means chives?
-Yes.
I'm with my friends.
Okay. I'll call you later.
Okay.
We're playing Zoo's song, right?
Did you bring your guitar?
You can switch back to standard Korean
right away. That's impressive.
What? I don't speak with a dialect.
Buddy, eat it with jeonguji.
All right.
Did you know
you two had a huge transformation?
-Us two?
-Yes.
What on earth are you talking about?
These guys looked worse back then.
Especially, you.
What about me?
You wanted to copy Leslie Cheung.
You parted your hair and got a perm.
Don't distort the truth, Ik-jun.
You two were worse.
How did we look back then?
Like this.
You prick.
-You prick.
-That was Jun-wan.
You prick.
No, they weren't that bad.
They looked like this.
-You prick.
-No.
-He looked like this.
-My gosh. Hey.
LINE 2, EXIT 3
Is this the way?
Where's the school? Why can't I see it?
We have to take a bus here. Bus 289-1.
It's the school entrance. Why take a bus?
If I knew the answer to that,
why would I be standing here with you,
holding this paper like a fool?
-It's freezing cold today.
-You said you'd been to Seoul. You forgot?
You've been here too, man. We went to
the National Assembly on our school trip.
-Did we?
-Yes.
Do you have any change? A 1,000-won bill?
I only have 10,000-won bills.
Same here.
How much is the bus fare?
-It's 340 won. Seriously?
-What?
Things in Seoul are so expensive.
It's no place to live!
But I'm still going to live in Seoul.
-Wait here. I'll go and break the bill.
-At where?
I'll buy something at the cart over there
and get smaller bills.
Sir.
How much is it?
Where are you from? Busan? Masan?
That's 700 won.
-What about this?
-3,000 won.
Here.
Good luck with the interview.
Thank you. Have a good day.
MEDICAL SCHOOL INTERVIEW
WAITING AREA
EXAM SCHEDULE
Ik-jun, I don't think I did well
on my essay exam.
You should cut
your side-swept bangs first.
-What do you mean?
-I had to take a dump in the bathroom.
But it was packed with people,
so I used the staff bathroom downstairs.
Guess what I heard there.
Do you know what the most important factor
they are considering this year is?
What is it?
Jeonggal.
Jeongal?
No, I said, Jeonggal. Not scorpion.
Jeonggam? You mean, "warmhearted"?
Gosh, that's my weak point.
Go and clean your ears first, you prick.
I saw a shovel over there.
-What the heck?
-Neatness.
They're going to pick neat students.
Go cut your hair now.
Really? Darn it.
-Thank you.
-Don't mention it.
I saw you again in front
Of the subway station at the city hall
When I turned around to buy newspapers
I saw your figure
At the crowded newsstand
When I called out your name
You looked surprised
When I was about to go to you
I stepped on someone's foot
I had to say I was sorry
With a big smile
We talked about our lives
And how we changed
We even talked about the weather
Which was boring
The flooding memories
Quickly exhausted us
That time which seemed so slow
Passed us by
You told me that you were a mother of two
With a gentle smile on your face
When you asked me how I am doing
I just shrugged my shoulders
In disappointment
And told you that I was still looking for
The love of my life somewhere
In this world
-If we run into each other again someday
-You said you'd show me your children
-But the song engraved in our hearts
-From that day
-Is still fresh like it was yesterday
You told me that
Things were getting tough between us
That could have been
The reason you left me
But I can't know for sure
Sing it, everyone.
I remember the night when you left me
You in my memory
All right.
Hey, I'm sorry. No, I mean... Never mind.
I'm okay.
Song-hwa, I'm sorry for bringing up
such nonsense.
Did you want to meet up?
Okay. Where should we meet?
I'm sorry. Something just came up.
Let's meet some other time.
DRINKS AND MEALS,
CUSTOMERS FOR A CENTURY
No. Bye.
Hello?
Where? Who is this?
HAPPY BIRTHDAY, CHAE SONG-HWA
YULJE MEDICAL CENTER
Thank you. Thank you for the coffee.
You're even diligent. My gosh.
If you have questions, ask Song-hwa.
She really likes that.
Okay.
Professor Chae is a good person.
She is.
I respect her very much and like her.
Okay.
Have you been talking to Ik-sun lately?
Yes.
We talk on the phone at least once a week.
She's a really close friend of mine.
Just like you and Professor Chae.
Right. There are times when I realize
she's a woman, not just a friend.
My gosh, no.
We're really not involved romantically.
Besides, Ik-sun is still hurt
by what happened in the past.
She said she's not ready to date
someone yet.
She said she can't trust anyone.
I think it will take her some time.
Really?
Probably.
I'm paying this month's utility bill.
Jeong-won said he already paid.
My gosh, I guess
he's doing better financially.
That moocher paid the utility bill.
Did something happen?
You look down today.
It's nothing really. But...
My gosh, I had no idea,
but Ik-sun...
A NEW MESSAGE FROM IK-SUN
Bye.
Yes for what?
Today is our first day as a couple.
Hello?
What are you doing?
Really? Okay.
I don't have any surgery today.
Did you eat?
Who?
I see. I didn't know
there was a position for that.
Are you guys close to each other?
I see.
Okay. When is your next day off?
No, don't do that.
I'll go pick you up.
Okay.
Are you sure?
Yes, Ji-a will be the recipient.
The donor is a 22-year-old female.
She weighs 49kg.
And her LFT is under 40. It's all good.
She stayed at Kangwoon Medical Center
for seven days.
Then, we'll get the surgery ready.
Okay.
Oh my gosh!
Thank you, doctor.
Thank you so much, doctor.
Thank you.
The committee that confirms brain death
must still go through the protocol.
And we must check the condition
of the liver from the donor.
But I think this will work.
We can proceed with the surgery tonight
at the earliest.
Then, my daughter, Ji-a,
can live now. Right, doctor?
Yes.
Thank you. Thank you so much.
How's the liver? Are you heading here now?
We have a problem, Professor Ahn.
What's wrong?
The donor's liver is too thick.
It looks like it weighs over 500g.
And her AP must be as thick as 8cm.
What should we do?
This liver seems too big for Ji-a.
It won't work.
This is the last and only way
to save the baby.
There's a lot of bleeding, doctor.
Would you like to try it
for the next surgery?
What?
I'm going to perform the surgery.
I'm so nervous.
I think you should give up.
It won't go badly, right?
It's too embarrassing if others find out.
Why is my life so hard?
What? It's fall already?
Gosh, is fall here already?
Is something good going on?
You're always in a good mood lately.
-A blind date?
-Really?
Who is it?
Who is it that you're so crazy about?
Jun-wan, do I know her?
I'm Kim Jun-wan's friend, Lee Ik-jun.
The golf course there is really great.
The ball rolls in by itself.
An anonymous letter about bribery came in.
Did you go to play golf?
I heard the membership for the golf course
costs two hundred million won.
Hey, you didn't go, right?
Why? Is something going on?
What? You did?
Subtitle translation by Liya Choi