For someone who used to be
a loan shark and rogue,
how did you make it as a city
councilor?
I need real guys.
Young guys who really know nothing
about these things.
So he took someone else's photo
and pretended it was him.
They must have drugged her.
They took pictures of her
and made money out of it.
A female high schooler was found
dead at her school this afternoon...
leading to a police investigation
over the case.
Girl A is alleged to have
killed herself by jumping off.
Someone took those pictures
and sent them to me on purpose.
Tell me now. Who was Seo Jung with?
I swear. She was with a man
with a tattoo on his ankle.
The cigarette butt. Do you remember
on the day Seo Jung died...
someone threw a cigarette butt
out the hit-and-run car and drove off?
I saw it.
What did you see on that day?
This is what Seo Jung wrote on the dating board.
It's not her.
Do you think Seo Jung really
posted that? Isn't it weird?
You know Seo Jung, right?
She used to be a good writer, too.
The post
on the dating board was not...
written by her.
Mi Ra, you wrote it. Didn't you?
I didn't know that posting will
cause this to her.
I really didn't know she'd do that.
The phone was not with her body...
I think you're the last one to see
Seo Jung's phone.
She left it in my cabinet before...
she died.
Even though
everyone says I'll win
why am I still so nervous?
That's right. That cellphone.
(Um Sae Yun)
You have a pink phone, don't you?
Why does she have
two calculator apps?
If the video gets out...
you and I will go to prison.
"Wet sand remembers one's footprints."
That sentence you wrote was
the last sentence Seo Jung sent me.
It's the same as the text Seo Jung
had sent me.
Don't you know this?
It's a signboard game.
A signboard game?
I heard Seo Jung and Sae Yun
used to do this a lot.
Wet...
sand...
remembers one's footprints.
(Episode 7)
(Cafe Sand)
In 1, 2, 3!
It'll be hard for you to earn
people's respect.
A man has to...
be dangerous like that guy.
You!
Weren't you at school on the day
Seo Jung died?
He really is a dangerous kid.
Hey, you.
You might be better than
those ridiculous investigators.
Why did you kill her?
Why did you have to kill Seo Jung?
Was that her name?
- What?
- I was at school...
to collect that annoying phone.
If I had I gotten there a bit early...
maybe I could've saved her. Right?
Anyway, thank you...
for walking in by yourselves
since I was looking for you all.
Where is the phone?
- That's...
- Don't tell her!
We'll all die if you tell her.
That punk.
- It's...
- Don't say it, Chan Hong!
Oh, I remembered.
Um Sae Yun, is it?
You should save your girlfriend.
You're pretty.
Let's start taking her pictures.
I might be able to make some
money out of you.
Hold her.
Come on now.
Hold it up so I can see her face.
That's good.
Lift her chin up. Good.
A little bit higher.
Sae Yun.
Sae Yun!
Chan Hong!
Let me go!
Sae Yun!
So what do you plan to do?
Should I sell her to some island...
and kill you two here?
Hey, kid.
Do you know why...
the things I do are kept secret
until this day?
It's because I kept a promise...
whether that's good or bad.
Am I right, Sang Pil?
Yes, ma'am.
You scumbag.
I promise you.
Just put it on my hand...
and I'll let you three off right away.
Don Hyuk!
Lady.
I'll give it to you.
I'll give you the phone.
(A Girl Commits Suicide at School.)
(Depressed About Grades,
a Student Commits Suicide.)
(Congratulating five knockdowns
with future champion Sang Pil)
Sae Yun.
Are you okay?
I'm okay.
Don Hyuk.
I don't think this is right.
- We should get the phone back.
- Chan Hong,
once we get out of here...
can I eat at your place again?
What are you talking about
all of a sudden?
His mother makes
the best kimchi stew.
You'll keep wanting to have it
once you've tried it.
Especially on a day like this.
Don Hyuk.
- We should just...
- Let's get out of here.
We should first get out.
I'm really fine.
I know Seo Jung would've
done the same.
Stop having negative thoughts.
"I've made a mistake. This is bad."
"It's over. I'm dead.
It's all my fault."
"The Earth is going to crumble.
I should die beforehand!"
Stop being like that.
Mi Ra, when these thoughts pop up,
you should think
lewd thoughts instead.
That's more productive.
Mi Ra.
Let's live a long life.
Let's live long shamelessly.
Let's not die...
but live a long life with friends.
We could talk behind their backs,
get mad, and fight over it.
We could always...
turn a blind eye to each other.
So...
let's live long.
Mi Ra.
I like you.
I mean it.
Why aren't you...
a bit more...
What is it, Mi Ra?
Why aren't you a bit more
handsome?
What?
What can I do?
- You'll get used to my looks.
- No, I won't
What should I do about it?
Is Chan Hong with you?
He's not answering his phone.
Ninja, where are you?
The caller can not be reached,
please record...
Why is no one answering
their phones?
I feel like my indigestion
went away.
Let them go.
It's surprising to see an adult
keep her promise, isn't it?
Why did it have to be Seo Jung?
Why did Seo Jung have to suffer?
You're asking the wrong question.
You should've asked who showed...
where the fish flock.
That's what I'm wondering too.
If you find that person, make
sure to let me know.
I'll kill you.
- I'm going to kill you!
- Hello, congressman.
Of course.
Come back next time.
What's this?
Let's move him.
Kill him!
Go already.
Are you acting like a friend, now
that you have everything you need?
Stop bothering me
and leave already!
I'll get going.
Let's go together.
Don't be an amateur.
You need to walk Sae Yun home.
I'm going too.
Geez, my legs.
I can go by myself from here.
Let me walk you home.
My parents will be outside
waiting for me.
I see.
It must've been scary for you today.
I'm sorry I was late.
No.
Chan Hong.
I like you a lot too.
And I know
that you also like me a lot.
But...
what can we do for each other?
It's just like how we couldn't do
anything for Seo Jung.
So,
it's not your fault.
Don't be sorry.
Why didn't you answer your phone?
What happened to you?
What is going on?
Who did this to you?
Is it him again?
That Don Hyuk kid?
- Did he hit you again?
- No.
Obviously, it was him!
Give me his phone number. Right now!
I need to call him.
- That's not it.
- Tell me. Who did this?
Hey!
What parent would stay put
when their kid is in this shape?
Tell me right now!
I can't have this.
Honey, bring me the bat.
- Let's just ask him tomorrow.
- Bring it now!
Fine, I'll get it.
Stay right here.
I'll bring it myself.
He's hurt already.
There are some things
I can't tell you.
There are things...
I shouldn't talk about.
There are somethings...
that I can't explain.
Dad, you're a man too.
You should know
things happen like this.
Even though
we are all 19 years old...
we live different moments.
Park Chan Hong lives
Park Chan Hong's life.
(I'm sorry.)
I'm sorry.
Heo Don Hyuk lives
Heo Don Hyuk's life.
Um Sae Yun lives Um Sae Yun's life.
Can we ever...
fill that gap?
(New beginning for Gangpo.
An earnest worker, Cho Pyung Seob)
A persona indicates...
the main character of the poem.
This character can be the writer...
or an imaginary character.
It is a mean to show one's
actual self...
or to show what one imagines
things to be like.
Are you still sick?
Look at me. I'm all fine.
Ninja,
do you want to play games tonight?
I heard they'll be giving out
special items.
Are you up for it?
Oh Kyung Pyo.
- It's you, isn't it?
- Yes, that's me.
As of this time, you are
under arrest without warrant...
for violation of IC Network Act
and blackmailing.
Excuse me?
Are you arresting me?
Wait a minute.
- Why are you doing this?
- Watch it.
Chan Hong.
Chan Hong!
(Gangpo Police Station)
You know Kang Hyun Ku, don't you?
He requested us
for a police investigation.
(Report on Unauthorized
Social Media Account Use)
He said someone used his account...
to commit a crime.
I see.
That was a misunderstanding.
It's nothing.
You see, this is what happened.
There was a bad guy...
- with a tattoo.
- You met him to cover your tracks.
- Pardon?
- You ran away in the middle.
You made a fake account
to approach him.
That was...
Is it true or not?
- What you said is true, but...
- So it's true.
You know Shin Seo Jung
who died, don't you?
- Pardon?
- Why did you send her that message?
What message are you talking about?
You made fake accounts
to approach girls.
You lured them and took photos
to blackmail them.
You bypassed your IP too,
didn't you?
We couldn't catch you,
but your IP appeared once.
Your ID was Mithra.
That's you, isn't it?
Mithra? What is that?
I don't know.
He said I used that ID
to get information...
on girls and blackmail them.
Don't be so sad.
I didn't do anything wrong.
I'm fine.
My mom said...
she's looking for lawyers.
I'll probably be out soon.
I'll have another story to tell
when I go out.
Why the long face, my Mi Ra?
- My Mi Ra?
We're dating.
That's more shocking
than you being locked up.
Did you think you were the only one
who could get a girlfriend?
I'm going to announce it
when I go out...
so others won't hit on you.
Where are you looking?
Look at me, it's been a while.
It won't be easy.
If they arrested without a warrant,
it means the police are sure about this.
If the real criminal doesn't show up
or if he doesn't have an alibi,
he'll probably be handed over
to the prosecutor within 48 hours.
This is nonsense.
You know Kyung Pyo is innocent.
We don't have much time.
We need to look
for the real criminal.
That's right.
The fake one has to be arrested...
so they won't look
for the real criminal...
even if this becomes a problem.
It'll be a problem if they start
looking for a dead person.
Tell them he'll be transferred
to the main police station.
Okay, then.
(I knew that psycho pervert
would get in trouble.)
(He was strange. I heard he was
the one who took secret photos.)
(What if he took photos
of the girls' restroom?)
(He stared at girls
when they pass by.)
(It'd be too embarrassing to come
back to school if I was him.)
(He's disgusting.)
That psycho pervert jerk.
I knew he'd cause trouble.
I know.
He was always a bit strange.
I heard he was the one
who took the secret photos.
- It's hideous.
- Really?
What a complete trash.
What if he took photos
of the girls' restroom?
My uncle's a policeman
and I heard him talk.
What he did was filthy.
I knew it.
I didn't like the way he looked.
Did you see him doing it?
What do you know...
about Kyung Pyo
to be talking about him like that?
Did you see it?
Did you see him do it?
She said he first talked to her...
using the online forum.
The ID was...
Mithra.
What?
We started talking...
in an anonymous chat group
by chance.
(Online Forum)
(You have a new message
from Mithra.)
(You're Choi Mi Ra in Class 2-5,
right?)
(How did you know?)
As we were talking,
we had similar interests...
and we got along very well.
Kyung Pyo told me not to tell anyone
because it was dangerous.
But I thought
it'd wrong not to tell.
Also, he seemed to already know...
that I was Choi Mi Ra.
(Who are you?
You told Chan Hong, didn't you?)
(Don't you want to make him suffer
a little bit more?)
(What did you say?)
(Park Chan Hong? What about him?)
(What did he say?)
Don't you think...
- Mithra is from our school?
- Yes.
He reacted immediately
when he saw your name.
If he didn't know,
he would've asked who you were.
- But he seemed to know you.
- I don't think it's a girl...
- judging from the words.
- His words were harsh and rough.
No.
Mithra is not the violent type.
It's actually the opposite.
In my opinion,
I think he's a weak personality.
When I got beaten up
by Kim Dae Yong,
he wasn't the one I hated,
but I was the one
that seemed pathetic.
I thought everything was my fault.
I got mad over nothing.
(You killed Shin Seo Jung.)
(Do you want me to do the same
to you?)
Ans I became very sensitive.
He resembles me back then.
It feels like he's isolated.
He didn't press me
even when I responded late.
He was like...
a child who was asking
to have more playtime.
(He's isolated. What is
his relationship with Seo Jung?)
(He's behind a different identity.)
(Did he have a grudge
against Seo Jung?)
"(Mithra" as a solar deity? )
He knew me.
(Who's Mithra?
Why did he blame Kyung Pyo?)
He's weak and nervous.
He put up someone else.
Why would he do that?
It's because his face shouldn't
be seen.
I need to think.
(Shin Seo Jung)
Happy birthday, Seo Jung.
I'm sorry
that I came here so late.
(Shin Seo Jung)
I've really wanted to come here,
but I was scared
I couldn't look at you properly...
and that would've hurt you.
It took me a while.
I didn't know
it would take me a year.
I'm sorry.
(The last episode)
Today is the first day of the midterm.
Please take your seats.
(I am the happiest man
in the world.)
"Happiness."
(I don't worry about living thanks
to my wife who runs a teahouse.)
"I am the happiest man
in the world."
"I don't worry about my living..."
"thanks to my wife who runs
a teahouse."
(Shin Seo Jung)
"There is no lack of learning..."
"because I studied at university."
"I have a house..."
"so how comfortable am I?"
"I have no complaints..."
"as my wife always buys a drink
of rice wine..."
"for me."
"Moreover, I firmly believe
in the Lord..."
"who is the most powerful
in this Universe."
"Lord is my supporter,
what misfortune is to come for me?"
(Cheon Sang Byeong)
(I am the happiest man
in the world.)
Even if a poetic narrator uses
a negative and rough language,
it does not necessarily mean
he wants to convey a dark...
and hopeless message.
It is actually such
negative expressions...
that portray the mind of the poet...
who has a strong yearning
for happiness.
What I mean by that is...
no matter how hard you try,
you're only revealing yourself.
Sir,
may I leave when I'm finished?
- You finished already?
- Yes.
You may turn the answer sheet
and leave.
Mithra.
- I think I know who this is.
- You do?
It's someone who is...
the weakest,
the loneliest,
and the most anxious
in our school.
The only person...
who doesn't have anyone around him.
And...
someone who could give us
information...
about Cho Pyung Seob's hideout.
What did you say?
What did you say just now?
I'm Mithra.
I'm the one who took
your friend, Seo Jung,
to Pyung Seob and got her killed.
Is it hard to believe...
that a jerk like me...
is Mithra?
How could you?
Why would you do that?
Chan Hong thought of you
as a friend.
A friend?
Don't follow in after me
if you want to live.
Don't ever think
about coming in here.
(Chan Hong, 34 Missed Calls)
(Dialing Chan Hong)
(Shin Seo Jung)
Bring back all the information...
that Mithra still has.
And make sure you leave
nothing behind.
Are you okay? Did you get hurt?
I'm okay.
But Sung Do went inside.
- Sung Do is Mithra.
- I know.
Let's go in.
Sae Yun, I told you not to come in.
- You should've just let me die.
- Why you...
Who told you that you could
take your life so easily?
I didn't come here to save you.
I wanted to keep you alive
so I could hear why you did this.
Why did you do this to Seo Jung?
Why did you do it?
You guys and I are no different.
The most popular girl
in Jaeil High School...
and you guys flocking to her.
I wondered how solid
your connections would be...
but it broke down
as soft as a sandcastle.
I realized...
I wasn't the only sucker.
A friend by your side is nothing...
but useless.
Nothing ever broke down among us.
Don Hyuk...
came all the way here.
The same goes for Sae Yun.
Everyone...
did their best...
to stand by Seo Jung's side.
It's not a sandcastle.
Fine.
Then what about me?
What about me who's always been
outside that castle?
You guys all saw
how Dae Yong bullied me.
Please stop.
Did you get it?
Give me your backpack.
Come on.
Stand straight.
Any one of you guys...
could've helped me if you wanted to.
Yet you just left me alone.
Because you didn't want
to end up like me.
The friendship that only
you guys have.
That worthless friendship.
I tried to break that because
it was so meaningless.
I...
Well, even I don't...
really know
what friendship is. But...
I want to ask you one thing.
Did you ever...
try to reach out...
to anyone?
When I saw Don Hyuk
for the first time,
I thought I'd never want
to be involved with the guy.
I talked behind his back
with Kyung Pyo...
even though I knew nothing
about him.
But...
he wasn't who I thought he'd be.
On the outside, he looks like...
the toughest guy in the world.
But he wasn't much different
from me.
He gets anxious every day,
full of things he doesn't know,
and gets hurt easily.
We're all the same.
Seo Jung...
who you thought had everything...
was just a girl
who was no different from you.
She was just a 19-year-old girl...
who wanted to be loved and happy.
That's all.
Darn it!
I know that.
I try to turn it back...
but I was too late.
I just hoped it wasn't just
because of me.
That's how I thought
I could survive.
I'm sorry.
Let go. Please!
- No one cares if I die.
- Live.
Live and endure.
This isn't because I worry
about you...
or because I forgive you.
Live anyway.
Live no matter what.
Let go.
We're merely a 19-year-old.
We're imperfect.
We don't know...
what true friendship is.
So sometimes things end...
with only wounds, even when we
think it was friendship.
Would we become perfect...
if we become adults?
I just wish...
we could look at each other.
A bit longer,
a bit more sincerely,
a bit more...
kindly.
It was revealed that Ms. Cho,
a candidate for Gangpo city office,
kidnapped a teenager and forced
her to take revealing photos...
- and made money by threatening...
- You see?
I knew this would happen.
I didn't like how she looked.
She looked shady.
I voted for that other person.
- The chief of police...
- Oh, my.
brought in Ms. Cho today,
for sexually trafficking
a teenager...
who had also bribed the police.
Okay. That's it.
I wish people could be fixed...
just like this little thing can be.
Son.
You don't need money nor power.
Just be kind and sincere.
That's the best.
But your mother would like it very
much if you could make money too.
Yes, ma'am.
That's nice.
Aren't you hungry?
Is it time to eat already?
I'm thinking of cooking
your favorite menu.
My favorite? Son!
Your mom's going to cook
my favorite menu!
Thank you, madam.
I'm so happy. I love you.
What kind words, sir.
I can't let this feeling pass.
Let's play a song.
If you play music,
I'll be roasting the meat.
That's nice.
Will you visit me
when the sun rises
You'll just leave me
when the wind blows
When I look back in high hope
I see you ignoring me
Oh, wind please stop blowing
That's not how you sing that part.
Try harder.
That's good!
Are you done?
Yes, almost.
Don Hyuk, I guess you'll be
eating home-cooked meals now.
You're going to miss
my mom's cooking.
What will you do?
My mom's a good chef too.
Come visit.
Have a meal and sleep over
at my place.
- Don Hyuk.
- What?
Don Hyuk!
What is it? What are you doing?
- Let's hug one out.
- Are you crazy?
You've gone crazy.
If you pull anything strange...
I will kill you this time.
Don Hyuk.
You did a good job.
Hey, people might think
you're older than me.
- I get it now. Let go.
- No.
You don't know anything.
I said let's stop.
Don Hyuk.
Let's just...
let Seo Jung go now.
She would have forgiven you...
after what you've put
yourself through.
Don't you think
she would have been...
heartbroken in heaven?
Forgive yourself now.
Come out of...
your cave now.
It's not your fault, Don Hyuk.
(Grade card)
Yes.
No, my scores dropped.
Please...
listen to me first this time.
Honestly,
I don't know if I'm good at arts,
or if I’m good enough to make
a living from this, Dad.
How would I know?
But, at least...
I know how I feel when I draw.
While I'm drawing...
I feel like the world is a fine and
beautiful place to live in.
I feel like I'm inside that
pretty canvas.
So I'm going to keep on drawing.
Isn't me being happy enough?
I don't care whether you
like it or not.
I'm going to keep telling you...
and I won't...
lock the door up first anymore,
at the very least.
(Home notice letter)
(The desired subject of study:
Creative Writing)
You've made a big decision.
Yes.
Chan Hong,
you need to maintain your balance.
Pardon?
Do you know why I didn't become
a poet but stayed here?
There was a time...
when I thought
poetry was everything.
I gave up everything
and held on only to poetry.
As a result,
my life crashed...
and I was destroyed.
How could I write poems
when my life was ruined?
Fortunately, I started
liking this school very much.
I like having my pupils like you
than reading poems now.
Chan Hong,
you can't let the things you love
destroy you.
Do you understand?
- Yes.
- Also,
the more important thing
than that is...
Ms. Choi.
Let's talk later.
What are you doing after work today?
- Why do you ask?
- Why else would I be asking?
I'm planning to live our lives
to the fullest...
and go sightseeing
before the flowers fade.
We'll have a meal
and watch a movie too.
- The course sounds pretty okay.
- I know, right?
But the man isn't...
- quite my style.
- Pardon?
You make funny jokes.
Did you put on a wig today?
- I think it's a wig.
- Oh, my gosh.
- Come on. Let me touch it.
- Stop it!
The cherry blossom represents...
evanescent beauty and purity.
It means vain life and death.
Canola flowers represent...
cheerfulness and hope.
Being 19 is like...
walking between cherry blossoms
and canola flowers.
It's like walking on a tightrope
between death and hope.
Your hair is falling.
Hey, Mi Ra.
Do you like me or not?
Am I good-looking or not?
Am I pretty or not?
- Kyung Pyo doesn't have...
- Am I cute or not?
good grades or good looks.
- He's not good at sports too.
- I like you a little.
He wasn't interested...
- in what Mi Ra did.
- Hey.
- I can't say you're cute.
- That was...
- who Kyung Pyo is.
- Mi Ra.
- You got something on your face.
- That is...
- because he's King Psycho.
- Beauty's on your face.
Hey, why did you do that for?
As for Don Hyuk,
he goes to visit Sang Pil
once a week.
It's his friend whom he found...
(Heo Don Hyuk)
not so easily.
(Friend)
I've brought some snacks,
underwear, and socks.
You can't dress cool there,
so your status is based on that.
Stop being a know-it-all.
Hey, the youth detention center
you stayed was...
a place with high school boys
talking about girls.
This is a place...
where adults share concerns
about the country.
Judging by the way you talk,
life in jail must be comfortable.
That should be my line.
You're looking good, Heo Don Hyuk.
Sang Pil.
Leave if you're going to thank me
or say you're sorry.
I'm not that crazy
to say such things.
Use this opportunity
to get a hold of yourself.
- I'll get going.
- Hey, Don Hyuk.
When I leave this place,
I'll change as you did,
won't I?
You can't do it.
It's only possible because it's me.
(Dear, Sung Do)
I write...
to Sung Do once a week.
He's not accepting visits yet.
But still,
he sends me back
every once in a while.
(From Sung Do)
Don Hyuk, have breakfast.
I'm not eating.
Hurry up and eat.
Geez, I said I was on a diet.
I told you my friends were
coming over.
Chan Hong's mom prepared
a table full of dishes for me.
Don't hit me!
Geez.
Should I make this thicker?
I think it looks great now.
It's natural.
It'll stand out if it's too thick.
You think so?
The colors are beautiful.
I think it's good that the tones mix
with other colors.
You think so?
Chan Hong.
(Dear, Seo Jung)
Is this all?
"You're pretty and lovely."
Isn't that enough?
Here.
(Don't hate Mi Ra so much, please.)
- Oh Kyung Pyo, you passed.
- Yes!
Look at you, Don Hyuk.
(Title: You, painted by us)
(A fun and happy school
with proud Jaeil students)
Hey, Kyung Pyo.
(How to Buy a Friend)
(The real end)
(Thank you for watching
"How to Buy a Friend.")