(Gangpo area, Turned 20 in 2018,
soft SM, Long-term, Pretty)
(I'm looking for
a long-term relationship.)
(Near Noodles and Gimbap...)
This is what Seo Jung wrote
on the dating board.
It's not her.
What do you mean it's not her?
I even checked the IP address.
There's no denying
that the photo is real.
She even asked my guys
to collect money for her.
Stop it.
Look at yourself in the mirror
and see if I can stop.
Don Hyuk, get it together!
Just admit that this is
who she really is, you jerk.
Shut your mouth!
- Let go of him!
- You know nothing about her.
Don't ever come here again.
I regret that I ever thought
of you as a friend.
All right. You'll never
be seeing me again.
I'm telling you,
my account got stolen.
Sure.
They came over and hit me
without checking.
You just said that before.
Calm down, sir.
Give me your mother's phone number.
Will you?
How stubborn.
- Is Chan Hong here?
- Where's Chan Hong?
He's there.
Oh, dear.
- I appreciate your work, sir.
- Thank you for your work.
Are you okay?
What's happened?
Let me see your face.
- My goodness, Chan Hong.
- You're pretty hurt.
Are you mad? This is not like you.
Were you involved too?
I am sorry.
Are you his parents?
Can you handle this quickly?
Hold on.
- I don't have time for this.
- Yes, sir. Give us a minute.
Sir,
what's happening to the boys?
Your son was beaten...
so you can sign here and take him...
but we have a problem with this guy.
Someone in his family should show up
to work out an arrangement.
He also spent time
in the detention center.
It's not going to be light for him.
- Is he your friend?
- Yes.
Are your bones okay?
- I appreciate it.
- It's okay, sir.
Thank you for your understanding.
I'll teach those boys.
- Yes, sir.
- Why did you open these buttons?
This is the fashion these days.
Geez.
All right. I got you.
You'll freeze to death
trying to look cool.
I'll make you a jacket.
Don't worry I'll get the material
and make it myself.
You just stay still.
(ChungGyver)
(Always in your service, ChungGyver)
You should sleep over. It's too late.
You went through a lot today.
It's okay, sir.
Please don't refuse.
I don't intend to punish you.
It's really okay, sir.
I'll make sure to pay back
the settlement money.
Just have dinner with us, will you?
What do you like to eat?
Gosh, it's hot.
Here.
Eat up.
It could've been better
if I had more time.
If we had time, we'd be feasting now.
You should come over often.
So we could have
some nice food thanks to you.
I love this soup.
It's so delicious, darling.
I don't know if you'd like it,
but you should eat up.
We never leave food over
in this house.
Why are you not eating
your tofu pancakes?
I told you I don't like food
made with beans.
You know that.
Your father raised you so well.
It's for your health!
Help yourself.
- Gosh.
- Look at you.
That's a white shirt.
- Look at what you've done.
- Well done.
Geez. Look here.
You brat.
It's okay. It'll wash out.
When will you grow up?
Look at your friend.
He's so mature and reliable.
Stop with the word "mature."
It's a burden to the mature adult.
Not many people are so mature
these days.
They just pretend they are.
Aren't I right?
Chung Chae, that wasn't cool at all.
- This is a bit salty, son.
- It is a little bit.
Is it?
Don't eat it, then.
You should have all of it.
No, Mom.
The meat should be salty too.
Get your hands off it.
He's going to have it all.
Just have your tofu pancake.
Don't touch it.
It's not salty when you eat it
with rice.
It's not that salty. It's good.
Let me try it.
It's just right.
Don't mind them.
Eat all you want, son.
Eat now and come over often.
Look how well we're eating today.
Traitor. How can you run away
like that?
Someone should leave in order
to report.
What happened?
Don Hyuk is at my place.
My parents keep telling him
to sleep over.
What? He's at your place?
Yes. I think he's really
going to sleep over.
Can't you come over now?
Your message has been denied.
Are you kidding me?
What a psycho.
Chan Hong!
You said you're not
wearing this, right?
Yes, it doesn't fit me.
I thought you'd be taller.
Even if I were, I won't be
wearing this.
I got the material and made it
myself. Isn't it pretty?
Yes, ma'am.
Those are pearl buttons.
Make yourself at home
and stay comfortable, okay?
Sleep well, son.
- You too, Mom.
- Okay.
I'll close the door for you guys.
I told you I'll kill you if you lied.
I'm sorry.
I had my reasons.
How did you get that?
Was it fun to play around with me?
Sae Yun said...
- Seo Jung have Sae Yun...
- Um Sae Yun?
Seo Jung gave it to Seo Yun?
I almost forgot.
So this is how I twist it.
That's right.
I see.
I broght these.
I saw it on "Morning Forum."
Eating kiwi...
before you go to bed is good...
for you.
All right. It might not be cozy...
but sleep tight.
Are you learning something?
I am.
I see.
Goodnight.
Jung Hee,
you went through a lot today.
I don't want to be worried...
but I am.
But...
I think it was a good idea
to bring him over.
Isn't it?
You're right.
Why do you think he went
to the detention center?
He knows how to respect
his elders.
He must've had his reasons.
Sae Yun didn't...
hide it on purpose.
Sae Yun said Seo Jung left it...
in her cabinet.
Why?
No one knows that.
Just like no one knows why...
she left that sentence to...
you, me...
and Sae Yun.
It seems like Sae Yun went
through a lot too.
She must've felt like
Seo Jung blamed her.
That's the scariest thing.
(Seo Jung, what are you up to?
(Nothing. I miss you, Don Hyuk.)
Are you going out?
Good morning.
What a coincidence!
Stay right where you are.
Chan Hong! Let's go take a bath!
(Won Jam Bathhouse)
(Cold bath)
In lane five, Oh Kyung Pyo.
Thank you, Mom.
You sometimes tend to
make people cowardly.
Do better then.
Don Hyuk, even your skins is fair.
Come on. If I made the call later,
you would've been more hurt.
Not you, them.
I'm worried about them.
I thought your punches
might kill them.
- Can I throw up a bit?
- Go ahead.
Look at this. Are you an eraser?
Take them home. I'll wrap
them up nicely for you.
I feel squeaky clean.
- I'm going to work.
- I'll see you at home.
See you again.
This is from Mom.
Please tell her I said thank you.
A venti for Don Hyuk.
Ninja, you get a tall sized one.
- And a grande for me.
- Hey!
I'm taller than you.
I'm not talking about our heights.
Don Hyuk, you're the man.
Watch yourself.
(What rhythm has taught me)
Rhythm.
It is chemistry made from
words that go well with one another.
If you were to leave me,
for I disgust you,
I will send you off...
quietly.
The poem has a certain rhythm to it.
It has a sonnet's rhythm.
This goes for you too.
If you keep writing poetry...
you will develop a rhythm.
Your very own rhythm.
So this rhythm...
We are at a roadblock.
Is there a way?
If you get used to this breathing,
it will stick with you...
so you can't change it.
I thought of something while reading
through the chats.
So even without a base, you can
develop a rhythm. Isn't it amazing?
Hello.
- From yesterday...
- I see.
Hey, the runaways.
Go make the world a cleaner place.
Go on.
Wait, look at them.
This is a total cacophony.
But how is it?
There is an exquisite rhythm
to them.
Sometimes, the things that are
so finely mismatched...
create an exquisite rhythm.
So, they stole
someone else's photo...
and pretended to be like them?
But their faces must be different.
Seo Jung would have been more alert.
That's simple.
You were going to meet
with Hyun Gu, right?
Yes.
Are you the friend that
he mentioned?
Yes, I'm his friend.
He must have looked nice.
But Seo Jung seemed a bit drunk.
She can't drink at all.
They must have drugged her.
Have this while you wait.
He'll be here soon.
Okay. Thank you.
Then they took a photo
and exploited her.
Let's go catch them.
High schoolers have no money.
How did she make it through?
I would've done anything
to come up with the money. Right?
- Be quiet.
- What?
Let's split up and clean.
Don Hyuk, you should get some rest.
Ninja and I will do it.
Please!
What?
There's been...
something at the back of my mind.
This is what Seo Jung wrote
on the internet.
I wanted to think that she didn't
write this...
but the ID and IP match.
If this was Seo Jung...
Well...
- That is if..
- She didn't.
She was someone
Sae Yun looked up to...
and she was someone you liked.
Don Hyuk, it can't be.
You don't come
to cram school these days.
Is there something going on?
No, there isn't. Nothing's going on.
That's good to hear.
I thought maybe
giving you the phone...
caused you harm. I was worried.
Don't be. I have it nice and safe.
Come to cram school today.
I'll see you there.
Sae Yun.
Yes?
I won't be going there for a while.
Why?
I don't have any money.
The thing is...
If my mom finds out, she'll kill me.
Are you going to become
a full-time writer?
- No, that's not it.
- That must be it!
Chan Hong, that's great!
I'll root for you. Happy writing!
I'll get going.
You've improved so much.
The student has become the master.
You know what most surprising?
Even if I read this with
your name covered,
I can still feel Chan Hong's rhythm.
This is very good.
I'll keep this safe.
This is such good writing.
You know Seo Jung, right?
Yes.
She used to be a good writer, too.
Do you want to give it a read?
The child who had
a beautiful and pure laugh.
The child who was sad one moment,
and happy the next.
The child who had...
a three-year-old cuddled up
inside of him.
He doesn't know...
how lonely his stiffed back looks.
how sad...
his wide-opened eyes look.
The child doesn't...
know it at all.
He doesn't.
He doesn't know.
(Poem-writing)
What is it?
Chan Hong.
What's going on?
Hey, where is it?
What do you mean?
Chan Hong, what is it?
The post
on the dating board was not...
written by her.
Pardon?
(And, so)
The teacher kept telling me.
These are redundant. Remove them.
Get rid of this.
These conjunctive adverbs make
the sentences loose.
- Cut them off boldly.
- Also,
look at the words "soon",
"somewhat", and "will be."
She never made these mistakes
in her writing.
There's a saying that says
simple sentences are noble.
Sentences should be written...
- as short as possible.
- I don't think...
she would've written sentences
this long.
She has a habit of making commas...
when her sentences were long.
But this one doesn't have commas.
But this wasn't formal writing.
It's on the Internet...
The finishing touch is this one.
(The reason for this is...)
"Reason" and "because" are synonyms.
It's better to remove one of them.
(Because that was the best. The
reason was the emptiness it gave.)
This is indisputable.
Someone else wrote this post.
This post wasn't...
written by her.
Another thing.
Here.
I think she was talking about you.
("The Child")
(He doesn't know
how lonely his stiffed back looks.)
It's chilly.
Go put on something.
I'll take you home.
It's already late. Please move aside.
I feel great.
This is fast.
Hold on tight.
Sure.
By the way,
are you sure this is the right way?
Do you want to get off?
I'm sorry.
Sae Yun, I'm coming.
Be quiet.
Sae Yun!
Thank you.
How do I take this off?
Let me do it.
Thanks.
See you later.
Chan Hong,
thanks.
I mean it.
(Delivery)
Hey.
I found him.
Are you sure?
All right.
I got it so hang up.
Don Hyuk,
can't you trust me?
I really didn't do it.
What were those posts then?
Seo Jung,
I don't care about these. I'm fine.
I just...
need you to be honest with me.
I think...
I'll be okay...
if you believed in me.
Seo Jung.
I'll find them.
I'll make sure to find the people...
who did this to you.
When I told them
I'll continue painting,
they became very mad.
That's why I'm in these
this late night.
You are something, Chan Hong.
I took courage
after seeing you write poems.
I'm already wavering.
But I'm not going to give up.
I won't.
Aren't you going to cheer me up?
Sure, cheer up.
That sounded soulless.
It's not like that.
You're already doing so well.
So you don't have
to push yourself more.
For me,
I just want you to feel comfortable.
That's my dad's car.
(Episode 6)
I think he's gone now.
Yes.
Kiss.
Kiss is all about the timing.
When a girl gives you a sign,
you should catch it right away.
If you go in offbeat,
she'll slap you and it'll be over.
How do you recognize the sign?
Have you heard
about Edward Hall and Proxemics?
What?
You should write it down
if you don't know.
According to Hall,
people have an interpersonal space.
It's about 45 centimeters
or a step and a half.
It's not open to everyone.
And if she doesn't move back
when your in that space,
that's when you go in fast.
Then slow down right after.
Why's that?
You shouldn't be
the only one to go in.
She should lean in too.
Love is not a one-way street.
It reminds me.
The scent of flowers,
the sound of her breathing,
and her sweet lips.
You've never kissed before.
Y♪♪tube.
You should write it down.
You were supposed
to meet her in front...
of Noodles and Gimbap
at Boram intersection.
Noodles and Gimbap?
(Noodles and Gimbap)
It's short for buckwheat noodles
and gimbap.
The name of the place is
Woori Snack Stand...
but that dish is just so popular.
So everybody calls it like that.
Only guys at our school call it
that way.
So that person is
within this school.
How do you know who wrote it?
There is a way.
The cabinet is...
at the center of the teacher's room.
Just get their attention
and I'll take it out quickly.
- Sir.
- You're here again.
Can't you show me the works of other
guys just this once?
As I said, I can't do that.
You know how they write. Why would
you want to read it?
No way. These are
confidential documents.
Geez, you scared me.
What is it, Don Hyuk?
May I please have a word with you?
With me?
Yes, sir. Can we go somewhere quiet?
Somewhere quiet?
You don't have anything
against me, do you?
No, sir.
(Confidential Documents)
- I got you. Are you helping out?
- Geez.
What is this?
What's the problem?
Hey, what's going on there?
Sorry?
What are you doing?
It's nothing, sir.
You punks.
Ms. Choi, what is it?
- Please have a seat.
- I have a headache.
Miss, my goodness!
Don Hyuk!
Hey, Chan Hong!
- Yes, sir.
- Can you call the school nurse?
- I think she has a fever.
- Oh, my.
- Why are you touching?
- Chan Hong!
The school nurse, now.
Hurry up!
Please stay still, Miss.
Take a deep breath.
- That's good.
- Chan Hong,
it's all right.
No, please ask her to come here.
Hurry up now.
Please sit still.
- Chan Hong, I'm fine.
- Please hold still.
Take a deep breath.
- When did this start?
- Yesterday.
Did you have
something bad yesterday?
I had chicken feet dish with soju.
You should've called me.
Sorry?
It's nothing. What are your
symptoms?
I have such a bad headache.
A headache...
I think the nurse's office is
that way.
I'd stolen something for the first
time in my life.
You make ramyeon so well, Don Hyuk.
Why did you fold all their names?
I didn't want to be biased.
Do you really think this is possible?
This is yours, isn't it?
How did you know that?
It's moist and filthy.
Geez.
(Soon)
(Somehow)
(Will be)
(The reason)
(Is because)
(Choi Mi Ra)
Choi Mi Ra.
You know...
I want to talk to you about Mi Ra.
You are sensitive.
I guess it's because you're a writer.
Mi Ra's not doing well these days.
It's kind of awkward with her.
She looks somber.
You know...
It's nothing.
I'll tell you later.
- We'll talk about it later.
- I wonder what it is.
Your birthday's in November, right?
Yes, how did you find out?
That writer has the same birthday
as you.
November 22nd.
I thought about waiting,
but it's such a long time from now.
Thank you. I didn't prepare
anything for you.
You can write me a letter.
I want to get a letter from you.
Okay.
- I'll write you one.
- That's a promise.
It was my first kiss.
The world came to a stop.
All my senses became keen,
that night.
I'll forever cherish...
every bit of this moment...
until the day I die.
Come here.
You jerks!
You scumbag, are you
out of your mind?
What do you think you're doing?
Are you okay?
Yes.
You pathetic loser.
Do you not feel anything
after seeing this?
The one you were bullying
just saved you.
You should say thank you, not be
angry, you dumb jerk.
You've been coming here a lot.
Thank you.
Are you okay?
Yes.
Luckily, it wasn't a deep wound.
Hey.
Here.
Thank you for the drink.
Thank you.
Take some rest.
Chan Hong.
Yes?
You're close with Sae Yun,
right?
Yes. Why?
Well...
Dae Yong is...
looking for the pink phone
that Sae Yun has.
There was nothing special,
no matter how much I looked.
There must be something
like you said.
That's why they want the phone.
Why are there two calculator apps?
- What?
- Look at this.
There are two calculator apps.
I opened them, and they
both have similar functions.
(Enter the password.)
What is this?
What did she record?
Who is this woman?
I think Dae Yong wrote that post.
That's why you couldn't
find it last time.
He would never have
done his homework.
Don Hyuk.
- First, et's calm down...
- This is our chance.
We can...
catch their trails.
If we follow the people trying to
kidnap Sae Yun...
- we can find...
- We can't do that.
That puts Sae Yun in danger.
- She's already in enough danger.
- I...
I will protect her with my life.
Please trust me this once.
Heo Don Hyuk.
This really isn't right.
Just one day.
Let's just wait for one more day.
What if something happens tonight?
Chan Hong.
I said I'll protect her
with my life.
Come on.
You're still just a high schooler.
You are a high schooler.
I'll do it alone
if you're not coming.
I'll do it by myself.
Thumbs up, thumbs up
An honest and hard-working candidate
The more you get to see her,
the more you get to know her
She has so much charm
Cho Pyung Seob
Park Kwang Il, who used to be
a college professor...
lowered his head in front of me...
and called me ma'am.
What do you think it means?
It means I, Cho Pyung Seob,
am close to winning the election.
Don't you think?
Even though
everyone says I'll win...
why am I still so nervous?
That's right.
That cellphone.
If the video gets out...
it's not just about the election.
You and I will go to prison.
Isn't that right?
I'm sorry.
Did I ask you to get me funds?
Did I ask you to get me votes?
I told you to get the phone
that will win my election...
and get you a brand new suit.
Is that so hard to do?
I'm begging you.
Help me.
Please?
Sae Yun.
There you are.
Hi, Mi Ra.
I'm sorry everyone.
I was a bit on the edge lately.
The thing is...
I had something going on with my
parents, and I was a bit sick.
So I was a bit down. I'm sorry.
I'm sorry everyone.
- It's okay.
- It's fine.
I'm sorry. That's right!
This is a new camera app. Did you
try it? It's absolutely cute.
Let's give it a try.
Gather around.
Come closer.
Smile.
In 1, 2, 3.
It's good, right?
Come closer.
(- Send me Sae Yun's photos.
- Please stop doing this.)
(Stop? Are you fine with revealing
what you did to Seo Jung?)
(Do you want to go through
what she did?)
What is it?
I have something to ask you.
When you text someone...
you use a lot of ellipses, right?
What?
I do, but why?
Let me see your phone.
Why would I show this to you?
Mi Ra.
It's you, isn't it?
What?
The post on the dating board...
you wrote it, didn't you?
No. I didn't do it!
- It wasn't me!
- Stop lying.
You wrote it.
No, I didn't. It wasn't me!
The post on the dating board...
you did write it, Mi Ra.
- Hey, let's go to the cafeteria.
- Okay.
(Reply to me. I know what you
did to Seo Jung.)
(Are you happy now?)
(Who are you?)
(You told Chan Hong, didn't you?)
(Power off)
Why didn't you tell me?
I didn't want you to worry.
(Mi Ra)
The caller can not be reached
at the moment.
Please record a message
after the beep.
Why won't she answer the phone?
I want to go home alone tonight.
- Let me walk you home.
- Just go.
I want to be alone.
I'm...
just worried about you.
That's all.
I don't want you to be in danger.
Don't you look at me as a liar too?
What difference do Mi Ra and I have?
I was wrong.
Give me back Seo Jung's phone.
I'll hold on to it.
Hello?
What? Mi Ra?
(Gangpo University
Psychiatric Hospital)
They cleaned out her stomach
quickly, so she's not in danger.
Go ask if we can apply
health insurance to this.
Why are you blaming me?
Did you even check up on her once?
When I was in middle school,
I was very happy...
when you talked to me...
after you saw my scribbling.
You told me that I too was good
at drawing.
You know,
I've always been so small
and timid...
that I didn't have many friends.
You were popular back even then.
That's why...
I kept asking my mom
even when I knew it was hard...
to send to me to an arts academy.
Everyone treated me differently...
because you were friendly to me.
I was the small one beside Sae Yun.
I was Sae Yun's friend.
Maybe I was...
a bit anxious.
Make this part a little brighter.
I was afraid things would...
- Over here.
- Go back as they were.
This is great.
- Did you have breakfast?
- No, I didn't.
Did you?
- I'm hungry.
- Me, too.
I want to eat something.
I started hating her.
I hated her more...
because there was nothing
hateful about her.
I really...
didn't know she'd do that.
I'm so sorry. I didn't know.
I didn't think
things would turn out that way.
I'm sorry.
I never meant to do that to her.
I think it's every Wednesday.
He calls them out anytime
in the evening or dawn.
But it's silent that day.
That's why I keep waiting
for Wednesdays.
I found it, Chan Hong.
I think it's over there.
Look at his face closely.
I think this is related to him.
Who is he?
Do you know him?
I used to.
He showed me that post too.
I think he has something
to do with this.
I don't know.
I want to stop now.
I'll report this to the police.
No!
I explained it.
I'll make sure
that Sae Yun won't get hurt.
I'll risk my life to protect her.
- Chan Hong.
- Protect her?
How are you going to do that?
Mi Ra almost died.
Something might happen to Sae Yun.
Who almost died?
What are you talking about?
Chan Hong.
I'm asking you a favor like this.
Can't you do this for a friend?
Friend?
Were we friends? We are...
under a contractual relationship.
Park Chan Hong!
Stop it already.
If Sae Yun leaves me,
what am I going to do?
Of course, she'll leave you.
Why would Sae Yun stay
for a ninja like you?
Yes, you're right.
There isn't...
an answer to our lives.
(Life Bar, Friends for 24 hours)
But I still have...
a friend beside me.
Let us comfort ourselves
with a bowl of wine.
I heard you were a poet.
Those are some strange words.
Don't you know this?
It's a signboard game.
- Signboard game?
- I heard Seo Jung...
and Sae Yun used to do this a lot.
No wonder.
What would you know
when you're so busy fighting?
(Footprint)
I remember...
(Memory)
the footprints.
(Cafe Sand)
Wet sand...
Remembers one's footprints.
(Footprint, Memory, Cafe Sand)
Sae Yun.
I left a handwritten note...
under the public phone.
You wanted to have it.
(To Sae Yun)
("A Girl")
There is a girl.
She resembles the spring.
(Cafe Sand)
She resembles a red flower.
Even during the summer...
when the flower fell
and the buds turned red,
the girl was not forgotten.
But that was not true.
The girl resembles the summer.
The girl was afraid...
that she might resemble
the cold winter...
and that she might be cut
by the chill.
In 1, 2, 3!
When the spring comes,
will you be...
the spring one more time?
(What rhythm has taught me)
(The end.)
Where is the phone?
Don't say it.
We're all going to die if you do.
You need to save your girlfriend,
Um Sae Yun.
- Chan Hong.
- Sae Yun!
Let's not die but live a long life.
Let's live a long life
with our friends.
Let's talk behind their backs,
get mad, and fight over it.
But let's just live a long life.
Why did it have to be Seo Jung?
It's the wrong question.
You should've asked who showed...
where the fish flock.
You know Shin Seo Jung
who died, don't you?
Why did you send her this message?
You're ID is Vitra, right?