HYENA
THIS DRAMA IS PURELY FICTIONAL
AND IS NOT ASSOCIATED WITH
ACTUAL PEOPLE, INCIDENTS, ASSOCIATIONS,
OR LOCATIONS
EPISODE 15
Was it really necessary to come back here?
Checking the scene could give us
a new insight.
We can go and check
if they really don't have CCTV cameras.
Why don't you just become a detective?
Why can't you handle this like a lawyer?
I'm doing it my way.
I really need that room today.
Well, the thing is,
-that room is...
-Sir.
We have a similar suite
on a different floor--
That room is very special to us.
Today,
I'm going to propose.
Well, if that's the case...
She's one lucky woman.
Goodness.
She was married once.
But for me, it's my first time.
There are lots of couples like that
these days. Right?
She can be very fussy though.
She's fussy and a bit of a clean freak.
She's a little bit of both.
So I'm worried about
what might bother her later on.
You don't need to worry at all.
We only provide the best service.
Yes, I expect the best.
Today's a very special day for us.
Right.
Hee-jae, come here and push me.
I'm Seo Jeong-hwa, and you're the culprit.
These kinds of things
should be done properly.
-Hey!
-What?
But do you think that'd be enough
to shatter the glass table?
I'm not sure.
This time, you're Seo Jeong-hwa.
Shouldn't it require
at least this much strength?
I guess it wasn't
involuntary manslaughter then.
The culprit who banged
Seo Jeong-hwa's head on the table
surely would've injured his or her hand.
But Ha Chan-ho's hands were fine.
They were only covered in blood.
Then here's a second question
assuming that Ha Chan-ho is innocent.
The alcohol spilled on the table.
But at the scene of the accident,
there were no signs of alcohol on the rug.
That means the rug
came from somewhere else.
In order to move a corpse
and a heavy rug covered in blood,
there should be at least two guys.
And somewhere nearby...
There has to be a place
that has the same rug and table.
Look at this stain.
Do you see this or not?
I can't see anything.
So I'm the only one who can see this?
Oh, my god.
Honey, you see this stain, right?
It's so dirty.
And look at this place right here.
Look at that and that.
I don't like the layout of the furniture.
I personally think
it sucks.
Oh, I see.
My goodness gracious.
Look at this hair. Oh, my god.
What is this hair?
Are you serious right now?
I have very sensitive bronchi.
-Right, honey?
-Right.
A single speck of dust
and a strand of hair can be fatal to me.
Then what can we do for you?
We can give you a refund if you want.
There's another suite next door, right?
I'd like to switch to that one.
Ma'am, that suite isn't
for ordinary customers.
It's for one of our VIP customers,
and it's reserved all year long.
SS Group sold all their hotels.
But apparently, Chairman Son still has
exclusive use of one of the suites.
What? Can you repeat
why we can't switch rooms?
That suite isn't for ordinary customers.
"Ordinary"?
Did you just call me ordinary?
Oh, my god.
Honey, did you hear that?
She called me ordinary.
Am I an ordinary person?
Did she just label me as someone ordinary?
No, that's not what I meant.
You know what? Forget it!
Bring me the president of the hotel.
This place has terrible hygiene,
but you call this a suite
and expect us to pay a fortune?
I'm going to upload a national petition
on the Blue House website today.
I'll show you what happens
when you mess with an ordinary person.
Oh, my god. Me? Ordinary?
You called me ordinary? Really?
No one has ever said that to me.
I'm going to tell my mom.
I'll leave as soon as I propose to her.
I went through so much to get this.
This diamond was found in 1905
in South Africa.
It's called the first star of Africa.
-But still, it won't be possible.
-Me? Ordinary?
CASHIER'S CHECK
1,000,000 WON
I'm so upset!
-Please do me a favor.
-How dare she call me ordinary?
The room is empty today.
-And if you make it quick...
-I'm ordinary?
Okay. Two hours will be enough. Thank you.
No more than two hours.
-Otherwise--
-Got it.
Oh, my god.
She thinks I'm ordinary? "Ordinary"?
Honey, I settled everything.
Really?
VIP ROOM 1328
CHAIRMAN SON'S ROOM
The furniture and the layout
are exactly the same.
You're right.
Look at this.
Someone must've bought this in a hurry.
Okay, then. Let's order room service.
I threw a huge fit, and now I'm starving.
Seo Jeong-hwa used an ArtSky credit card,
and it was mostly used at White Hotel.
But here's what's weird.
I couldn't find a single painting
in the hotel lobby and hallway.
Isn't it strange
how there's a really expensive painting
in this suite?
ArtSky's paintings and White Hotel
which belonged to Chairman Son.
And Seo Jeong-hwa.
Maybe Seo Jeong-hwa
managed ArtSky's paintings.
Using Son Bong-u's slush fund, right?
It's pretty common for conglomerates
to use art galleries for their slush fund.
Okay, then.
It's time for the last step.
Honey.
Will you
marry me?
No.
You lost the ring?
Oh, my god. My ring.
Gosh, it's worth a fortune.
Where in the world is it? Oh, my god.
We ordered room service
and had the room cleaned up afterward.
We had a lot of people come and go.
So I'm embarrassed to say this,
but we can't help but be suspicious.
-But sir--
-Like I told you earlier,
-that diamond ring is--
-Yes, I know.
You told me it's a very expensive ring
from Africa.
It was from Africa. Oh, my god.
Should we call the cops?
Sir, please don't do that.
One of our guests
has exclusive rights to this suite,
but I let you use it.
That will put me in big trouble.
Then let us check
the surveillance footage.
There aren't any CCTV cameras installed
on this floor.
You don't have CCTVs? Oh, my god.
Then I'll just have to call the cops.
-Sir.
-Gosh.
I'm sorry.
We can't have any more cops
come to our hotel.
But there is one thing I can do for you.
There aren't any cameras in the room,
but you can check the one in the hallway.
There's a CCTV camera in the hallway?
The main concept of our suite
is to protect our guests' privacy.
So we keep the hallway CCTV confidential.
After 24 hours, the footage gets
sent to the security company.
But you lost it a few hours ago, so
you'll be able to check the footage here.
There aren't any CCTV cameras
in front of the VIP guest room.
Gosh, that's not good.
We can't see anything.
-What?
-Gosh, forget it.
How can we find the ring with this?
Where is my ring?
Where is my expensive ring?
You know what?
Call everyone that came into our room.
I want my expensive ring back!
-Honey, wait.
-What?
After I gave you the ring, you went
to the bathroom to wash your hands.
-Yes.
-Where did you put the ring?
A while ago?
I put it in my cute mini bag.
There's your ring.
The famous ring you got from Africa.
It really does look expensive.
But this whole experience
completely ruined my mood.
Let's go somewhere else, honey.
About that CCTV camera in the hallway...
Do you think the cops didn't know?
It wasn't on the evidence list.
We'll find out once we check.
Let's call the security company--
Yes, I already asked Ju-ho to check.
What's your relationship with Park Ju-ho?
By any chance, were you guys a couple?
Like us?
We might actually get disbarred
because of what you did.
-I'm surprised you're making jokes.
-My goodness.
You shouldn't have gotten fooled.
You should go without me.
You're not coming? Where are you going?
Can't you at least let me know?
LAW OFFICE CHOONG
What took you so long?
I felt so suffocated
that I almost killed myself.
We'll be outside.
Call me once you're done.
ATTORNEY YOON HEE-JAE
What brings you here?
You could've found a better place.
It's not like you're short on money.
I like vintage.
Since when?
People change according to whom they meet.
I heard you're going to defend Ha Chan-ho
for his appeal.
Yes.
If you need stuff from his first trial,
you can ask Mr. Ga.
I'm sure he'll help you out.
Sure.
But I'm sure you're not here
to tell me that.
Hee-jae.
The fact that I refused
to defend your father
doesn't mean I plan to neglect him.
Everyone knows Song & Kim was in charge
of defending Issume throughout the trial.
So if we get involved
with your father's case,
it'll only cause people
to suspect him even more.
He made a verdict
based on his legal consciousness.
Even if the prosecutor accuses him
of abusing his authority,
he'll quickly get released
considering the independence of judges.
That was a very long
and detailed explanation.
I'm relieved to know
that you're representing him.
He's your father,
so I know you'll do your best.
Yes.
You're right. I'm going to do my best.
I'm up against a guy who thinks
he has power over the entire country
and is coldhearted enough to abandon
a 30-year-old friendship
without even feeling
the slightest bit of regret.
Hee-jae.
Life can be very difficult.
Things don't always go your way.
This is my advice as your mentor,
so keep that in mind.
I can't stand this bullshit.
Do you still expect me
to think of you as my mentor?
I've only seen you play dirty tricks
and heard you give lame excuses.
You punk.
You're going to get a subpoena.
I can't wait to see you in court
as a witness.
You're going to have me summoned?
Why? Are you suddenly scared?
I'm guessing it's because
you're hiding something.
Some people lack competence
regardless of how hard you try
to help them grow.
I must've misjudged you.
I'm very disappointed.
Yes, I'm disappointed as well.
Some people make me gag
even though I try so hard to respect them.
Please leave if you're done.
Didn't you hear what I just said?
Do you want me to walk you out?
I'm sick of getting disappointed in you.
So please leave.
-Isn't that Ms. Jung?
-Hey, that's Ms. Jung.
I thought she got fired.
-Is that really Ms. Jung?
-Yes.
Come in.
Hey.
You look stunning.
-Have you been well?
-Ms. Jung.
Are you here alone?
Yes, Hee-jae isn't here.
Is he doing well?
-Why don't you ask him yourself?
-What?
Shouldn't you know why I'm here by now?
It's about
Hee-jae's father's case.
I need another attorney.
We're very short on manpower.
Does Mr. Yoon also know about this?
I'm hiring you because I need you.
Don't you think you'd be bothered by me?
What do you mean?
You know I like Mr. Yoon, right?
Give it your best shot.
Hey, it's burning. Get off the phone
and focus on grilling the meat.
It's smoked meat, so you can just eat it.
-Oh, really? Nice
-Here.
-It looks so good.
-We're at
your favorite restaurant
in the chicken feet alley.
-Eat up.
-This place is nice.
We just started eating.
I don't want to hang up.
Why don't we talk on the phone
until you get here?
-Hello?
-Yes, you can eat it now.
My gosh.
Don't we normally have beef
for team dinners?
We're working at Choong, not Song & Kim.
-Eat up.
-Oh, right. What about the CCTV footage?
The detective in charge took the footage.
Detective Lee?
But it wasn't on the evidence list.
We'll have to look into it.
-Will you stop hanging up on me?
-I was right outside. Come on.
Ms. Boo.
Have you all been well?
It's nice to see you.
-Are you going to join us?
-Yes.
Have a seat.
-Sit down.
-Take a seat.
-Give her a spoon and chopsticks.
-Here you go.
-You scouted Ms. Boo?
-Yes.
She'll be in charge of your father's case.
The others are too busy
with Ha Chan-ho's case.
What's wrong?
Will you be okay?
I'll be fine.
-Why wouldn't I be okay?
-Have this.
-Ms. Boo, he's our investigator.
-Your chopsticks.
-This is nice.
-My goodness.
What kind of team dinner is this?
Ma'am, can we have 12 bottles of soju?
Here I go.
Choong!
Thank you.
No, don't.
-Let's all drink. Cheers.
-Just drink water.
-Cheers.
No!
-He swallowed it already.
-What's wrong?
We have exactly one minute.
"One minute"?
-You'll see.
-My god.
It's going to begin.
Hyenas!
You hyenas!
-What's wrong with him?
-He's crazy.
Yes, I know we need to be like hyenas.
Right? After all, this is a jungle.
We're living in a jungle
where people gobble each other up!
-Yes, you're right. This is a jungle.
-Bring it on.
I'll show you
how I survived in the jungle. Bring it on!
Here.
Let's get wasted tonight.
I heard hyenas are actually very clean.
-Really?
-Yes.
-Are you okay?
-No.
LAW OFFICE CHOONG
Have some scorched rice.
Hee-jae.
It's hot, so blow on it a little.
I heard Mr. Song came by yesterday.
Did you guys have a nice talk?
What did he say about your father?
Do you know what Song & Kim is good at?
They're really good at
secretly representing both parties.
They hold information from both sides
and weigh their options.
And I was the best at that.
He can't represent my father
because he's representing Issume?
That's fucking bullshit.
He says he's going to get acquitted,
so why not?
What do you want to achieve
through your father's trial?
I want to bring Song Pil-jung down.
I want to prove that he set things up
between Issume and my father
and that he planned this
from the very beginning.
I know it's going to be hard.
That's precisely why
we're here right now.
Just trust me.
PARK JU-HO
What do you have for me?
Lee U-tae,
the detective who took the CCTV footage,
recently quit his job.
So we came to his house,
but we got here too late.
He moved already.
Then do what you're good at.
Use your knowledge as a former detective,
and do everything you can
to find that guy.
I'm talking to Ms. Jung.
We already lost the room service staff,
so we can't afford to lose Detective Lee.
Ask all your detective friends for help
and search everywhere.
You have to find him no matter what.
Okay.
Do you think
Detective Lee destroyed the CCTV footage?
That depends on what kind of person he is.
It'd be great if we could
check his bank account.
Can't you do that?
How am I supposed to do that?
Do you think that kind of stuff is easy?
I'm not capable
of doing everything you ask.
Why are you talking informally to me?
We only have
circumstantial evidence and assumptions.
We don't have any conclusive evidence.
If we fail to obtain the CCTV footage,
that will bring us back to square one.
Hi.
I heard the news.
What?
That I got dismissed?
I know it's not good news.
Song Pil-jung, that son of a bitch.
Have I told you about my sister?
You see, Song Pil-jung...
He married my sister because Chairman Ha
and my father pushed ahead with it.
At first, it seemed like
he was in love with her.
But his true colors came out
when he inherited the law firm
after my father passed away.
She's still at the nursing home, right?
It's been 15 years since she collapsed.
She wouldn't be in that situation now
if she were taken to the hospital quickly.
I think
Song Pil-jung did that on purpose.
I found out something recently.
He visits the nursing home every week
and acts like a romantic, you know.
But on paper, they're already divorced.
I wanted to teach that dirtbag
a lesson somehow,
but I got ousted.
Judge Yoon Chung-yeon's trial
will be held soon.
We can't take him down
with something like that.
All he has to do is deny it.
First,
let's save Issume, okay?
I need you.
Finally, we meet, Ms. Jung Geum-ja.
It'd be wise not to meet up
for the time being.
You must show up if I summon you.
I decide whether
we need to meet up or not.
I want to get rid of those paintings
as soon as possible.
I feel like they're already jinxed,
so I don't want to keep them.
-Sure.
-Try to sell them at good prices.
And make sure you give enough money
to Congressman Lee.
Okay, sir. I'll take care of it.
Good night, sir.
Hi, Mr. Ma.
There's something I need you to do.
-Me?
-Yes, here's the list.
So you'd like me to check the things
in the warehouse
and send them over to AP EON, right?
Yes, you got it.
Isn't AP EON an important client to us?
-Yes, they are.
-We do whatever our clients ask of us.
-Now, get back to work.
-Yes, sir. Have a good day.
Mr. Ma.
Will I be in charge of Issume's account
or AP EON...
For now, just do a good job with that.
Just excel in the things
that you were told to do.
That is your duty and responsibility
as a lawyer at Song & Kim.
Yes, sir.
I'll remember that.
Thank you. Have a nice day.
Honey.
I have nothing to do. The only task I have
is doing something at the warehouse.
What the hell?
Knock them down or something.
Maybe they're just using you.
Instead of helping you
advance your career,
they'll fire you after using you. Right?
Honey, don't say things like that.
You're going to make me cry.
I heard Hee-jae and Geum-ja
started their own firm.
-You mean, Choong?
-You should go work with them.
You should at least feel at ease.
Hey, how have you been?
There's a freight container
at the harbor at Yeonan Pier.
Back when we were working
on that case together,
I followed Seo Jeong-hwa's navigation
and went to Yeonan Pier.
That day, I didn't even know
what I should be looking for.
But...
Now, I know. It all makes sense.
My gosh, what is all this?
Not sure.
So, this will be managed by Song & Kim
from now on, right?
Oh, yes. That's right.
Were these left by the person
who was previously in charge?
What's going on?
Who's that person?
Ms. Seo Jeong-hwa.
What? Who?
Seo Jeong-hwa. That lady.
She owns a gallery.
The paintings that
Seo Jeong-hwa used to manage
were all purchased by White Hotel
through ArtSky.
In other words,
they're owned by Chairman Son.
Why are you telling me this?
Because I'm a lawyer too.
You see,
I also regret wrapping up
Ha Chan-ho's first trial like that.
Thanks.
I'll be off, then.
Hee-jae.
I...
I'm not sure when and how
things started going wrong.
I also don't know why I'm still
at Song & Kim when you guys are all there.
Gi-hyeok.
Don't beat yourself up
for something that's been done.
It's not like you can change
what's already been done.
Just
focus on the present.
And what you should do from now on.
If we start regretting
what we did in the past,
I should go jump
into the Han River or something.
When you jump,
-I'll do it with you.
-Jeez, you fool.
What I'm saying is, we shouldn't do that.
I just want to do things with you,
no matter what it is.
Jeez.
These guys are our staff.
Yes, that's right.
B1 PARKING LOT
I don't recognize that car though.
Isn't it from a cleaning company?
It's not you guys?
No, it's not us.
Does White Hotel work
with another cleaning company?
No, we have an exclusive contract
with them.
Who are these people?
You couldn't find any information
on this company called Cleaning?
No. I did a thorough search online,
and this company doesn't exist.
I called every company
that has a similar name,
but none of them has any connection
with White Hotel.
Okay. Thanks.
Reorganize the list of cars
that entered the hotel.
-What?
-Goodness.
-Gosh.
Let's cheer up.
Issume has been financing
presidential campaigns,
and Song Pil-jung has been the middleman
between Issume and the candidates.
And after taking office at the Blue House,
they had to repay Issume and Song Pil-jung
during their terms.
That's how Song & Kim has managed
to stay at the top all these years.
And they're planning to do
the exact same thing again
for Lee In-yeop,
the presidential candidate.
Then it's true that
Judge Yoon gave Issume special treatment.
They even made him
the Supreme Court Justice.
But at a critical moment, my father...
No, I mean...
Judge Yoon Chung-yeon rebelled.
I understand all the facts.
However, we should still say
he was never bribed
for the verdict in favor of them,
and he had no say in being appointed
Supreme Court Justice.
The verdict was at his sole discretion,
and it cannot be considered
abuse of authority.
That will be our argument, right?
No, we'll do the opposite of that.
We'll admit everything.
And during the trial,
we'll uncover the truth behind it all
and reveal their connections.
Isn't that prosecutors' job though?
You said you'll defend your father.
The current and former CEOs
of Issume's subsidiaries
violated the law to make sure
Ha Chan-ho could inherit the company,
yet my father acquitted them.
That is wrong.
And it is considered
abuse of authority.
The court is at recess,
but it got scheduled right away.
The key is,
will your father admit to it?
That his verdict was wrong.
He will.
He promised me
that he will.
I'm so confused right now.
What is the goal of--
That will be the beginning.
He must admit
that he abused his authority.
Only then will his motive gain importance.
And only then
can we take Song Pil-jung down.
Yes, Dad.
Don't worry too much.
Remember what we discussed?
That's all you need to do.
All right.
I'll need Ha Chan-ho on the witness stand.
After all, he benefited the most
from that trial.
Will he do it though?
We'll be defending him
in the court of appeal,
so I'm pretty sure he's desperate
to get on our good side.
Because he'll have to spend
eight years in jail otherwise.
Are you going to strike a deal with him
or something?
If that's our only option.
I learned it from you.
But revealing your father's wrong deeds
will disgrace your family,
which has produced several judges.
-Will you be all right?
-Are you worried about me?
I'm doing it for my family's honor.
Admitting your mistake
is harder than making one
in the first place.
My brother told me
that I should never dishonor the family.
Yes, that's the spirit.
This confidence. This is you.
Best of luck.
Thanks.
Now, tell me what you said.
At the disciplinary hearing
held by the Bar Association.
-You want to hear it that much?
-Yes. I want to know.
I told them I loved you. Happy now?
JUDGE CHOE
Hello, Judge Choe.
Who will be on the witness stand?
COURT OF LAW
Ms. Jung, the four main newspapers,
including Daeguk Daily,
aren't sending reporters.
They've pulled some strings.
I was only able to gather reporters
from a few online news outlets.
Even though Ha Chan-ho
will be on the witness stand?
What about Mr. Song?
He won't show up, for sure.
TRIAL IN SESSION
Dad...
decided to admit everything.
And that's only right.
COURT OF LAW
WITNESS APPLICATION
WITNESS: SONG PIL-JUNG
WITNESS: HA CHAN-HO
Is witness Song Pil-jung here?
No, he's not here.
So I'd like to have the other witness,
Ha Chan-ho...
DEFENDANT
Now that the witness is present,
we will begin the examination.
Witness, please come forward.
WITNESS STAND
Mr. Song,
during the past month
up to the day of the first trial,
you met numerously
with Issume's Chairman Ha
and the defendant Mr. Yoon.
I don't remember.
You introduced the defendant
to Chairman Ha.
The defendant never met
with Chairman Ha alone.
You were present at every meeting.
Is that so?
I don't recall.
Wasn't it to request a favorable ruling
in the Issume's succession case?
And that request
came from you, not Chairman Ha.
Counselor, are you sure
about this line of questioning?
No.
I did no such thing.
Mr. Yoon. Did Chairman Ha
solicit such a deal
regarding Issume's succession case
or was it Mr. Song?
Counselor, you're supposed
to ask the witness the questions.
This is the statement
written by the defendant.
My client, Yoon Chung-yeon,
wrote down the dialogue that was exchanged
between him, Chairman Ha, and Mr. Song.
"May 3.
Received information from Song Pil-jung
regarding Issume's succession case.
May 7. Song Pil-jung
discussed the tendencies of the judge
in charge of the first trial.
May 15. Had dinner with
the judge of the first trial
and discussed details of the case."
Counselor, that evidence
has already been reviewed.
Direct the questions to your witness.
"July 16. Told Song Pil-jung
that I would be ruling the second trial
and they discussed
if an acquittal could be possible."
-Counselor!
-"September 4.
Was told by Song Pil-jung
that an acquittal
could lead to the position
as Supreme Court Justice."
-I want this off the record.
-Yes, Your Honor.
The defendant's statement
will be verified at another time.
Let me speak up.
This trial is to determine
whether or not Yoon Chung-yeon
abused his authority.
Did he coerce
the judge of the first trial?
Did he betray his conscience
as an officer of the law
and rule in the favor of Issume?
I'm not asking these questions
because I don't know the answer.
It's plain and simple really.
Defendant Yoon Chung-yeon,
did you coerce
the judge of the first trial in any way?
Did you make a ruling in the second trial
that goes against your conscience?
What game are you playing?
The defendant will answer.
-But Your Honor!
-The defendant will answer.
I have done
no such thing.
Mr. Yoon,
did you just testify that you never
abused your authority as a judge?
Chairman Ha and Song Pil-jung
never made a request?
I made a ruling
based on my conscience.
Let's give Mr. Yoon a moment.
You guys even jumped ship.
We don't regret it though.
Judge Yoon's decision
was a surprise to all of us.
We'll do our best on Ha Chan-ho's case.
Yes, it's me.
I found the car you mentioned!
Send me the photos right now.
It was my best option.
Only this
would benefit me.
You chose to stay loyal to the man
who abandoned you.
Honestly,
can you proudly say you made the ruling
according to your conscience?
"Judges aren't gods.
They can make mistakes
and also false judgments.
But
what's important
is that they own up to said mistakes."
Ever since I was ten,
you've been saying that to me
so that it'd be etched in my brain.
And now,
here I am saying it back to you.
As a judge,
and as a father,
you're no longer qualified.
I bet you want to erase it all.
Anyway, I know a spectacular way
to dig yourself out of a miserable state.
And what may that be?
CAR OWNER: KIM MIN-JEONG
What about this?
License plate and address.
These were a dead end.
I was struck with a question
when we came back from White Hotel.
The Entrepreneur Federation
met at White Hotel that day.
Chairman Son was present
and he stayed in the VIP suite.
Then Seo Jeong-hwa must've been there
to meet Son Bong-u that day.
Only that makes sense.
Seo Jeong-hwa's friend said that
she was going to leave the country
with Ha Jun-ho after selling a painting.
Let's say that
Chairman Son killed Seo Jeong-hwa.
Who would he first call?
His lawyer.
Just like how Ha Chan-ho called you.
35 Iyeok-dong, Gangnam-gu.
It's where Song Pil-jung lives.
WHITE HOTEL CCTV FOOTAGE OF VEHICLES
The car belongs to Kim Min-jeong.
Song Pil-jung's wife
who's at a nursing home.
Ms. Kim Min-joo verified that.
Let's go and do what you do best then.
-What? Right now?
-Yes.
How was that for a distraction?
You're right.
That was spectacular.
Let's go and catch Song Pil-jung
for good this time.
You can't barge in here unannounced.
My apologies, sir.
CAR OWNER: KIM MIN-JEONG
B1 PARKING LOT
And what do these prove?
Why were you at White Hotel?
I was never there.
Are you saying that Ms. Kim Min-jeong
drove this car herself?
You should've just admitted
that you went to White Hotel
and came up with a lame excuse
about needing to take a dump.
Well,
kudos to us for catching you off guard.
I have nothing more to say,
so please leave.
Did you see that?
That flustered expression?
You don't look as confident
as you did in court earlier.
Hee-jae, it seems like the outcome
of the hearing got to you emotionally,
but it isn't like you
to present inadequate evidence.
Aren't you ashamed of yourself?
This is only the beginning.
Chairman Son Bong-u, you,
and Seo Jeong-hwa.
Sounds fun, doesn't it?
Look forward to it.
That was a thrilling sight.
That's the taste of being a lawyer.
-I don't agree.
-Save the attitude.
Your father...
That is what he believed in all his life.
He won't change.
If he does, he'll crumble.
Changing means denying the life he lived,
his principles, and values.
So?
I'm supposed to understand him?
I'm just saying.
We all live different lives.
I have somewhere to be.
-Take a taxi, will you?
-Again?
Who is it this time?
Someone else who'll never change.
I'm going to end this once and for all.
Good night.
Could you...
Just a second.
It's me.
I had to ask.
Are you perhaps off to see your father?
Stop calling him my father.
Why would you go see him?
Because I want to end this
once and for all.
At least let me come with you.
I'll be fine.
ATTORNEY YOON HEE-JAE
Geum-ja? Jung Geum-ja!
INVESTIGATOR PARK JU-HO
Mr. Park?
Eun-yeong, can you give me one last chance
to beg for your forgiveness?
This will be the last time I bother you.
ATTORNEY YOON HEE-JAE
I said I got this.
I'm almost there, so sit tight.
Don't meet him without me, okay?
Answer me!
DAEJONGSEON CHURCH
What is it?
Talk to me.
Geum-ja? Jung Geum-ja!
Subtitle translation by Liya Choi