HYENA
THIS DRAMA IS PURELY FICTIONAL
AND IS NOT ASSOCIATED WITH
ACTUAL PEOPLE, INCIDENTS, ASSOCIATIONS,
OR LOCATIONS
FINALE
ATTORNEY YOON HEE-JAE
I said I got this.
I'm almost there, so sit tight.
Don't meet him without me, okay?
Answer me!
DAEJONGSEON CHURCH
What is it? Talk to me.
Geum-ja?
Jung Geum-ja!
Hey, who's there?
Who are you?
Hey, who are you?
I asked you a question.
If you're here to ask the Lord
for forgiveness, I will pray with you.
I'm sorry, but can you drive a bit faster?
Geum-ja!
What happened? Are you okay?
He went that way.
Did you get hurt anywhere else?
Is this all?
Call the cops. Do that first.
And call an ambulance.
My stepfather wasn't the one
who stabbed me. It was some other guy.
Is this 911?
Oh, my goodness.
What happened to Ms. Jung?
Oh, my goodness! Oh, no!
-No, it's not--
-Is it possible that she might die?
It was her stepfather, wasn't it?
That fucking jerk!
-No, it wasn't--
-Goodness.
What if Ms. Jung passes away?
I'm fine.
Ms. Jung!
-Oh, gosh.
-Ms. Jung.
Are you okay?
Did you get severely injured?
No, I only injured my hand.
Mr. Yoon quickly took care
of the situation, so I'm okay.
-How's he doing?
-He's in the ICU.
I thought it was that bastard.
But this time, he saved your life.
Gosh, I really thought you might die.
How could you think
of grabbing a knife with your hand?
Then should I have used my foot?
You must be okay
seeing that you're making jokes.
I always thought he might
try to stab me again one day.
really try to kill me
this time around.
It's always been on my mind.
Then why would you go there by yourself?
I grabbed the knife so I could live.
That's all I could do.
Okay, I get it.
I get what you mean.
I really do.
But I don't want you to get hurt anymore.
Just stop
getting injured.
The scars on my body show me
what I've been through.
It's time you stop
going through that kind of stuff.
Who could it be?
It wasn't my stepfather.
So who else would want me dead?
Right now, there's only one person
that comes to my mind.
LAW OFFICE CHOONG
Are you sure
you'll be okay on your own?
I grabbed the knife so I could live.
That's all I could do.
LEGAL COUNSELING
LAW OFFICE CHOONG
Dad, stop it!
Die!
Geum-ja!
What's wrong?
I think I had a bad dream.
What a fucked up nightmare.
Let me lean on you for a moment.
I'm a little dizzy.
I'm sure you also had a long day.
You should've gotten some rest.
Why did you come?
So I could do this.
So I could be with you like this.
My gosh, it's so cramped.
Is this really what you want?
Just go home already.
I'm tired. I can't be bothered
to go all the way home.
I admit that you went through a lot today.
I'll cut you some slack.
My day was nothing compared to yours.
Physical injuries recover quickly.
Emotional injuries don't.
It lasts quite a while.
I should get a bunk bed or something.
That's better.
Yes, this is better.
LAW OFFICE CHOONG
We have no conclusive evidence
to prove that Son Bong-u
and Seo Jeong-hwa met up with each other.
What about the CCTV footage?
Even if we find that, nothing will change.
It doesn't even show the entire hallway.
It only shows Seo Jeong-hwa's room.
And her other cell phone?
No one knows
what's inside that cell phone.
Where is our investigator?
He went to Daejeon.
Detective Lee's parents live there.
He's our only way
to obtain the CCTV footage.
I should also get going.
Where are you going?
To do some field work.
Hey, it's me.
How do you feel? Are you okay?
Yes, I feel great today.
I'm almost done. See you later.
PROSECUTOR KWON YONG-UN
Take a look.
You recovered a lot faster than expected.
Your father's trial didn't go your way.
No, it didn't.
There's nothing you can do.
He can't change overnight.
What are you here for?
Detective Lee U-tae.
He recently quit his job,
and he investigated
Seo Jeong-hwa's murder.
-He hid evidence, received money, and--
-I'm not in charge of this case.
Yes, I know. But the prosecutor in charge
will never give me what I want.
What's that?
A warrant to seize and search
Detective Lee's bank account.
Hee-jae, are you serious?
Don't even think of lecturing me
about morality again.
PERSONAL INFORMATION
NAME: LEE U-TAE
-Ha Chan-ho didn't murder her?
-Come on, Yong-un.
I know you're curious to find out
whether or not Ha Chan-ho is guilty.
I'm right, aren't I?
You had Song Pil-jung stand as a witness
even though you knew it'd be hard,
so I'll do it to give you credit.
-Take this.
-Okay, sir.
I found Detective Lee.
He's going to leave on a boat.
Got it.
Mr. Kim, the Passenger Terminal.
Go right now.
Excuse me.
Please don't run away.
I just need to ask you one question.
Who are you? Let me go. Are you crazy?
I'm not a bad guy. I'm a lawyer.
Please don't run away.
Why would I run away?
You're not a loan shark.
Just one minute will do.
You worked at White Hotel, right?
She stayed at a suite there.
-What about her?
-Did she order room service?
Yes, she ordered
the most expensive whiskey at the hotel.
Did you also give her sleeping pills?
Yes, she asked for some.
-But why do you ask?
-She asked you to bring them?
Yes.
Okay, then. It was a pleasure to meet you.
I didn't know AP EON
had this much interest in paintings.
As an international investment company,
you really bought a lot of paintings
and signed a jaw-dropping contract.
Right. I should go now.
My gosh, I guess he doesn't know much.
What's with that smile?
Sorry, sir.
Once we get the money from AP EON,
make sure you cash everything.
Okay, sir.
Hey, it's me.
How much for a painting?
He asked you to cash everything?
That means they plan
to give it to him in person.
Okay, thanks.
WILL THE GLOBAL PRIVATE EQUITY FUND,
AP EON, REALLY TAKE OVER ISSUME?
AP EON'S REASONABLE
AND TRANSPARENT MANAGEMENT
WILL OVERCOME THE LIMITS
OF KOREAN CONGLOMERATES
ISSUME'S SHAREHOLDERS CHOOSE AP EON
FOR GLOBAL COMPETITIVENESS
Issume is easily getting handed over
to AP EON.
The money they're getting
from selling the paintings.
It's for Congressman Lee, isn't it?
It's not a bad deal for AP EON
since it'll be
going to the next president.
Congressman Lee's approval rating
is over 30 percent now.
Mr. Song must be very proud to have
control over the country.
Seo Jeong-hwa
got in the middle of all this.
She probably used the slush fund
to blackmail Son Bong-u for money.
And then...
-Let's go.
-But do you think
it'll do us any good
to meet Son Bong-u right now?
Let's stir him up and see.
Did Mr. Song urgently send you here?
No, we no longer work at Song & Kim.
We work at Choong now.
I represent Ha Chan-ho
for his second trial.
I think you should go.
You stayed at White Hotel
on the day Seo Jeong-hwa died, right?
You stayed in the suite
right in front of hers.
What?
You even
talked to her over the phone that day.
What? What are you talking about?
It's all saved on her cell phone.
Your name is on her call log,
and she even left a recording
of the phone call.
How dare you?
Why did you
kill Seo Jeong-hwa?
Was it because of the paintings
that she was managing for you?
Leave right now!
Mr. Kim!
I want them out of here!
I'm going to have to ask you to leave.
He didn't deny it.
It looks like we really stirred him up.
Song Pil-jung's cell phone
will be on fire.
PARK JU-HO
Hello?
Okay.
He caught Detective Lee.
As for the international arbitration team,
I want Mr. Park to leave in June
and talk to the...
CHAIRMAN SON BONG-U
However,
we still need to discuss
what we're going to do with the team.
Let's move on.
CHAIRMAN SON BONG-U
The next agenda is about
the investment management company.
We need to decide
on their stock allocation.
I'd like to ask the steering committee...
What do you think you're doing?
This is kidnapping!
Uncuff me. Uncuff me right now!
Sit down.
Who is he? Is he a gangster?
Detective Lee.
No, you're not a detective anymore.
You're awfully brave for a lawyer.
You're the one who did
all sorts of shitty stuff as a detective.
-Like what?
-You hid evidence and received money.
What?
I never did such a thing.
We already checked your bank account,
so cut the bullshit.
I have nothing to say.
Where did you hide the CCTV footage?
Do you want to get charged
for destroying evidence?
Let me talk to him privately in my office.
What do you think this is?
A few days ago,
I got stabbed and almost died.
This bastard stabbed me.
I think this kind of looks like you.
It was really dark there.
I'll just use you as a model
and draw another one.
You're going to go to jail
for attempted murder.
Cut the bullshit!
Yes, I know it's bullshit.
But I hope you understand.
That asshole didn't leave behind
a single trace of evidence.
I'm the only witness and victim.
My testimony will mean everything.
He actually stabbed one more person.
Let's see how he's doing.
I called to ask about Mr. Jung Chun-su
who's currently in the ICU.
He's my dad.
I see.
Okay.
You'll be sent to jail
for attempted murder
and homicide.
How many years do you think you'll get?
Where is
the CCTV footage?
-I threw it away.
-Damn it!
Guys like you never throw away
that kind of evidence.
Because you know
that it will come in handy one day.
Without the CCTV footage,
you'll become a murderer.
Darn it.
Uncuff him.
You also need to visit
his parents' house again.
Okay.
That's where he hid
the CCTV footage.
What got him to talk?
I used my life
and
my stepfather's life.
He apparently died a while ago.
How could you let them come to my house
and say that to me?
They just went there to stir you up
because they have nothing.
I don't feel safe.
-Give me the money from AP EON.
-Sir.
I'll decide once things get settled,
so give me my money!
Let me tell you something
about Seo Jeong-hwa.
How dare you mention that name?
Seo Jeong-hwa
left a recording of the conversation
she had with you.
-What?
-I've been
keeping it very safe.
Would you like to hear it?
SEO JEONG-HWA'S RECORDING FILE
-I'm going to go.
-What?
How dare you threaten me?
-Are you crazy?
-Hey!
How dare you try to blackmail me?
Who do you think you are?
I have the money.
And I'm going to use it
exactly as planned.
If you want things to stay quiet,
you just need to stay still
and not do anything.
SEO JEONG-HWA ENTERS ROOM 1325
ROOM SERVICE ARRIVES
HA CHAN-HO ENTERS THE ROOM
Ha Chan-ho entered the room
about an hour after she checked in.
SEO JEONG-HWA MOVES TO ROOM 1328
WHERE CHAIRMAN SON IS
She entered Chairman Son's VIP suite
at 8:35 p.m.
It only shows Seo Jeong-hwa's room.
There's no way to see what happened
in the other room.
MOVED THE BLOODSTAINED RUG
TO ROOM 1325
So that's how they staged the scene.
Who are those guys?
That's Seo Jeong-hwa.
MOVED SEO JEONG-HWA'S BODY
TO ROOM 1325
Is she dead?
They're coming out.
Who's that?
He's checking Seo Jeong-hwa's phone.
That's her second phone.
Do we recognize that man
because we know him?
So Mr. Song called the cleaning company
and took Seo Jeong-hwa's second phone?
Like Mr. Na said, we recognize him
because we know him.
To get Song Pil-jung,
this footage isn't enough.
The circumstances tell us
that Son Bong-u is the culprit,
but we don't have firm evidence.
Not even any CCTV footage.
We're screwed.
But we know one thing for sure.
The fact that Ha Chan-ho is innocent.
Can we see the part where those guys
are moving her body?
Sure.
Right there.
It's that bastard.
The asshole who stabbed me.
-What's up?
-We can get Ha Chan-ho acquitted,
but the other stuff will be hard, right?
As for Song Pil-jung...
He'll weasel his way out of it.
I'm meeting Gi-hyeok for dinner.
Do you want to join us?
I'm busy. No, thank you.
I'm busy too.
-Did you look into it?
-You mean, Cleaning?
If Mr. Song hired them,
they might have something to do
with the legendary Team H.
Hey, stop writing a novel.
The archive only a few higher-ups can use.
Only a select few can go in because of
the fingerprint identification system.
In that room,
Seo Jeong-hwa's second phone
and information about Cleaning...
-They're there?
-No, they might be there.
Hey!
What? It's not like I can go in there.
My fingerprints won't work.
Shall I cut off
Mr. Song's thumb or something?
That would be nice.
Ms. Jung.
You said you weren't coming.
I got hungry.
The food here is pretty good.
Well, I heard you got hurt.
Are you all right?
It makes her look even tougher.
What about him? I heard he's hurt too.
He died.
-Shouldn't you be there?
-Why should I?
He died, and that was his fate.
Thanks to me,
he went to jail and found God.
And he saved me,
although it was unintentional.
He won't end up
in the worst place in hell.
Eat slowly, or you'll end up
with an upset stomach.
I guess she likes the pizza.
-Mr. Ga.
-Yes?
I have another favor to ask.
We might actually need
Song Pil-jung's finger.
His thumb?
How are you feeling today?
It's our D-Day, you know.
Just focus on Ha Chan-ho's second trial.
I got this.
I'll make sure this shareholders' meeting
will go down in Issume's history.
Today, we'll find out who the winner is.
Either Song Pil-jung will get crushed...
Or Choong will be destroyed.
Don't make such an ominous remark.
Let's do our best.
That's not enough.
We must win, no matter what.
All right, let's win.
We'll win.
THE 12TH EXTRAORDINARY
SHAREHOLDERS' MEETING
We're counting on you, Mr. Song.
Gosh, I'm flattered. I'll see you inside.
-Okay.
This day is finally here.
I owe it all to you, Mr. Song.
Everyone eventually goes with the tide.
Am I the one leading the tide
at the moment?
About Ha Jun-ho...
You're sure, right?
Yes, of course.
I've already persuaded him.
And he's just a puppet anyway.
I heard those two ladies
have gotten very close recently.
Is that right?
But what can they do
other than just hanging out together?
-Let's go in.
-Okay.
The defendant was tested positive
for zolpidem, a sedative.
Seo Jeong-hwa got it
from the room service waiter.
The defendant fell asleep against his will
because of zolpidem in his drink,
which Seo Jeong-hwa gave him.
When he woke up, he found himself
next to her, who was dead.
He got her blood on his hands and clothes
while checking
whether she was alive or not.
Gosh, you made it. Thank you.
-Congratulations.
-Thank you.
-My gosh.
-Congratulations.
-It's good to see you, sir.
-Hello--
Ha Chan-ho's second trial
is in session right now.
-So what?
-Aren't you curious?
It doesn't matter
even if he gets acquitted.
That card is no longer useful,
so I don't care.
You still have a long way to go,
Ms. Jung Geum-ja.
-My gosh, you made it.
-Congratulations.
Gosh, hello.
Thanks. Gosh, thank you.
The defendant's DNA found
underneath Seo Jeong-hwa's fingernails
can be explained by the fight they had
while drinking together before her death.
I suspect that was when his DNA
got underneath her fingernails.
As you all saw in the CCTV footage,
Seo Jeong-hwa was alive
when she left the room,
where the defendant was,
of her own accord.
Then she returned to the room as a corpse.
Those people even brought the rug
to stage the scene.
Defendant Ha Chan-ho did not kill her.
Your Honor.
Defendant Ha Chan-ho is not guilty.
Gosh, thank you.
-Thank you.
-Congratulations.
We will now begin
the shareholders' meeting.
-Please be seated.
-Let's sit down.
You're still here.
If you want to watch the finale...
Mr. Song Pil-jung, please be seated.
You must know Detective Lee U-tae.
Hundreds of millions of won
was deposited into his account.
The thing is...
Do you know who sent the money?
Your wife,
who's been bedridden
for the past 15 years.
You're using her in every possible way,
aren't you?
What are you talking about?
Mr. Song, please be seated.
Here's the finale I put together for you.
Song Pil-jung, you're under arrest
for concealing Seo Jeong-hwa's corpse
and destroying evidence.
You have the right to remain silent
and the right to an attorney.
You may refuse
to give an incriminating statement.
Do you understand each of these rights?
Take him.
You really have a knack
for surprising others.
You told me to just trust you and wait.
You want to thank me?
Then you know what to do, right?
Hire Choong to get Issume
back on the right track.
Bravo.
That was an amazing show.
You don't look as upset
as I thought you would.
I guess you enjoyed it.
If the meeting took place,
I wouldn't be
smiling at you like this now.
That's why you should've selected
your business partner more carefully.
The global business hunter, AP EON,
got a little too greedy this time, right?
But this won't be the end of me.
Of course not.
You'll find another target
and rip it off big-time.
I'm just doing my job.
I know.
Same here. I'm just doing my job.
Had we not met through work...
Here.
Would things have been
a little different?
I only put up with you
because we met through work.
I can give you only 30 minutes.
The lawyers from Song & Kim
must be rushing here now,
so finish it before they come.
Did I hire you to represent me, Ms. Jung?
Acting up like this can get you
in trouble, Prosecutor Kwon.
Concealing a dead body
and destroying evidence.
Can you prove it?
Are you saying this is me?
Who'd believe that?
The presiding judge?
The prosecutor?
What?
Are you suddenly drawing a blank?
You showed up at the shareholders' meeting
and caused a scene.
Song Pil-jung got arrested too.
There's no way you can get out of this.
The lawyer who always
solved problems like this for you
is in the other room right now.
Concealing a dead body
and destroying evidence.
Are you repeating that because
you don't think I know what I'm here for?
No.
They're not the only charges
you're facing.
There's more.
That's why I keep saying that,
Mr. Song Pil-jung.
The main cause of Seo Jeong-hwa's death
was hematogenic shock
and traumatic subdural hemorrhage.
POSTMORTEM REPORT
So she bled to death
because of her head injury, right?
But on the report...
"The frenulum
and buccal mucosa were damaged.
Petechial hemorrhage found
on the conjunctiva."
That needs an explanation.
The expert opinion is that such wounds
are formed when someone tries
to cover your nose and mouth.
It also proves that her blood was pumping
when the pressure was applied.
So when Seo Jeong-hwa
was dying from exsanguination,
while she still was
conscious and breathing,
someone covered her mouth and nose
to suffocate her?
Who?
It wasn't only Ha Chan-ho's DNA
that was found underneath her fingernails.
There was an unidentified DNA sample.
Son Bong-u's?
No, not his.
His numerous paternity tests
made it easy to verify.
Then...
That leaves only one person.
How dare you pinheads
make me sit in this chair?
Murder,
fleeing the scene of a crime,
and ordering the disposal of a body.
If you're sentenced to prison,
you might have to end your life there.
It was all Mr. Song.
My anger just got the best of me.
It was an accident.
That ungrateful bitch
blackmailed me with my painting.
How dare she!
Then I guess it could be downplayed
as involuntary manslaughter.
Considering your age and social status,
you might only get probation.
Your lawyer is the one
who turned this into a murder case.
I'm now offering you
a way out of this mess.
What if she was still alive
when you thought she had died?
What if it were Song Pil-jung
and not you who killed Seo Jeong-hwa?
Hey.
Where are you right now?
Right.
You need to get over here.
Yes.
That's right.
I'll handle this mess, so get out of here.
This is the VIP suite at White Hotel.
Get over here quickly and bring the team.
Mr. Song...
That's quite a story you concocted.
You of all people know
the difference in punishment between
a cover-up and murder itself.
Ms. Jung,
I'm not at all like the punks
and idiots you normally deal with.
I am not your match.
Why do you think there's no evidence?
Because I didn't do anything.
It's funny, you know.
When backed into a corner,
a hotshot lawyer acts the same
as thugs on the street.
Their first instinct
is to deny everything.
-Watch your mouth!
-You...
could've saved Seo Jeong-hwa.
But you didn't.
If you had let her be,
she would've died
from excessive blood loss.
But that's not what you did.
You chose to end her life
right then and there.
Mr. Song...
Help me.
-Your evidence?
-Another set of DNA
other than that of Ha Chan-ho's
was found underneath her fingernails.
Who'd even imagine
it being a match to yours?
No one thought to check
since you were never a suspect.
That's why it came back as unidentified.
However,
I had it verified.
This is hair from your razor.
You will
have to prove
that I was even there to begin with.
A DNA test can't be ordered
unless I become a suspect.
One that's legal, I mean.
I wonder if Chairman Son agrees.
He's talking to Hee-jae as we speak.
-You two--
-He'll speak the truth
about
who
called you there.
What are you playing at?
Get me the senior prosecutor right now!
He'll sing like a bird
since it'll get him off the hook.
He'll make sure
you become another prime suspect.
That good-for-nothing geezer.
It's over for you.
Anyway, we're thinking about
representing Chairman Son.
Shit, it already sounds like a blast.
What do you say?
-Sounds fun, doesn't it?
-Actually,
you have it all wrong.
It's over when I say it's over.
Let me ask you this though.
Why are you taking it this far?
Why?
Have you forgotten
that you tried to kill me?
I may have let it slide,
but you should've never forgotten that.
This is the price you pay
for messing with me.
You see, I'm none other than Jung Geum-ja.
Jung Geum-ja...
Law Office Choong
will now represent you, sir.
LAW OFFICE CHOONG
ATTORNEY YOON HEE-JAE
INTERROGATION ROOM
Issue a warrant
for Song Pil-jung's arrest.
For a cover-up
and tampering with evidence?
Add a murder charge too.
Sorry?
Goodness. How sluggish of you all.
What is the meaning of this?
What did you do?
Our jobs.
Will we finally get to see
your talent as a lawyer?
As the top lawyer
at Korea's finest law firm--
It won't be easy representing Mr. Song.
Make sure you're ready for us.
We're excited to see what you're made of.
Good luck!
Good.
Have they both lost their minds?
What has gotten into them?
Beats me.
There they are.
One, two, three.
-Eun-yeong, take a seat.
-Sure.
What's with the feast?
You calling Ms. Jung that fondly
seems a little too corny.
Could we be professional at work?
It's not like I can call her "Dude."
-But in the office--
-Whatever.
I'll call her any way I want, so be it.
You all did great.
-How about a drink?
-Let's do this.
Cheers, everyone.
-Cheers.
Honey, hurry.
Geum-ja! Move over.
I heard you almost died.
That's not the case.
Life throws you curveball after curveball.
Born as an orphan,
abused by foster dad, foster mom dies,
then foster dad dies too.
-Why would you say that on a good day?
-Did I do something wrong?
I shouldn't have told her.
I'm just proud of Geum-ja, that's all.
You overcame all those obstacles.
Right, I should be proud of myself.
Why don't we
raise our glasses?
-Cheers.
-Here you go.
-Honey, don't drink too much.
-Your sperms might get tipsy.
-My gosh.
I'm the one who must be drunk.
How tasteful, right?
I can't believe it.
Anyway, he's the type that gets boring.
THE FALL OF THE TOP LAWYER
SONG PIL-JUNG INDICTED FOR MURDER
AND MANY MORE
KBA CONSIDERS DISBARMENT
IRONCLAD ALLIANCE SHATTERED
Did you hear
the Ministry of Justice's decision?
The KBA's ruling was overturned.
Our suspension has been lifted.
Song Pil-jung has no power
over authority figures in Korea now.
That's what I call justice.
Why do you
follow me around everywhere though?
I just wanted to see
where you were abandoned.
Just so you know,
I've been getting to know you
by studying harder
than I ever did when studying for the bar.
I'd get adopted, abandoned,
and then brought back here.
Again and again.
Then one day,
this big-ass building was erected.
One that I could see from miles away.
Misery swept over me every time I saw it.
It was where I came back to
every time I was abandoned.
That's why I changed my mind.
I decided to buy the building
and make it my own
so that it'd no longer be
a gruesome memory.
That's the Jung Geum-ja way.
You never go small.
Setting that goal
made life
a little bit more tolerable.
Okay, I get it.
I do,
but have you any idea
how expensive this building is?
Only those chosen get to own a building.
Exactly.
So that's what I'll do.
I'll own a building.
Sure, let's do it!
HYENA
Subtitle translation by Ja-won Lee
THANK YOU FOR WATCHING HYENA
AND LOVING THE HYENAS WHO WORK HARD,
FIGHT HARD, AND LOVE PASSIONATELY.