(All characters, organizations, places, and events are fictional.)
The first thing I realized after scanning Jin Jae Gyu's memory...
is that throughout his 57-year-long life,
he was happy...
only for a few years.
The only time he was truly happy...
was when he was a little boy.
Why must you kill the goat?
To save others.
How can it when it's dead?
It'll be offered as a sacrifice to save people.
Are you saying that a human's life is more precious than an animal's?
I haven't learned enough to fully understand the cosmic ways,
but these animals are going to a better place...
after living a virtuous life.
Go where?
Somewhere nice.
Once we get home,
you can pay your respects to the goat with me.
Don't bring in bad luck and stay away from the shrine.
Let's go.
Take it.
I want to become just like you and save people.
No!
I've been constantly praying for the spirits not to disturb you.
You know that.
I meant something different.
I wish to become a savior like prosecutors and judges.
Does that choice please you?
Of course.
Her wishes never came true though.
Hwang Pil Seon. You will die a brutal death.
- The day his mother died... - Mom!
- Mom! - The spirit she served...
attached itself to her son.
Hello?
Is anyone here?
What on earth?
He prayed for his mother to wake up but to no avail.
It ended along with his happy childhood.
(15 years later, 1986)
- What's going on? - Mr. Jin has something to say.
What...
What did I tell you? I said I wasn't going to marry!
He's an elite prosecutor...
and his parents work at the Supreme Court Justice.
What on earth?
My gosh!
- It's me. - Should I know you?
Stay put.
What do you want from us?
I guess you forgot about me.
The son of the shaman you poisoned.
That...
That shaman brat?
Because of the hospital director you bribed,
I spent 15 years locked up in a mental institution.
Since I was eight, I lived in solitary.
Ma'am, I'm truly sorry.
He threatened me with a gun.
- I had no choice. - Nonsense!
There seems to be a terrible mistake...
The gunshot was loud.
Louder than I imagined.
All I have left is one bullet.
I want to live.
I want to forget my past and live a normal life.
Either let me go...
or just kill me.
Pil Seon!
What...
What is this?
Father.
What?
Father...
What did you do?
It took me too long to figure this out.
Why was the Eraser obsessed with having...
Jin Jae Gyu as his partner?
It was because they had a common enemy.
The one who started it all.
Hwang Pil Seon.
You people...
are in big trouble.
What do you think you're doing?
Did you know that the Eraser is after you?
Don't tell them everything.
What do you mean?
What do I mean?
I'm saying that we're in this mess because someone committed murder...
20 years ago while under the influence of drugs.
And then his mother faked a suicide note...
which led to the death of the bereaved.
- What the... - It's news to me.
You'll play dumb with me?
How dare you.
No one has ever raised their voice in front of me before.
You'll be experiencing a lot of "firsts" this time.
If you're lucky, you'll go to prison.
If not, the Eraser will end your life.
- Shut your mouth. - Quiet.
Let me get this straight.
The ultimate targets of this so-called Eraser...
are me and my son?
And that's why he abducted my daughter-in-law.
You hit the nail on the head, lady.
"Madam Chairman".
Even if that were true,
why are you bringing up something from 20 years ago?
How would I know what a psycho is thinking?
He's taking out those below you...
so that you two will shudder in fear.
Fear?
You know nothing about me.
He's killing innocent family members like Ms. Eun Soo Kyung.
What are you talking about? We all know it was his fault.
Yes, I'm enemies with the Eraser.
We're dying to kill each other.
Should I be more honest?
I couldn't agree with the Eraser's psychotic acts...
at all until now.
But I'm starting to understand him now.
Especially...
his contempt toward you.
Because I saw what you did to Jin Jae Gyu.
Hey, you're not making any sense.
What? Should I be more honest?
I couldn't care less about what will happen to you people.
The only person I want to save...
is the innocent Eun Soo Kyung.
I don't expect you to have a conscience, but...
if you want to save your wife and unborn child, come clean...
about the truth...
behind Moon Yong Dae's death 20 years ago.
The only things I'll protect...
are our family and my son's reputation.
Reputation?
Is that more important than your daughter-in-law's life?
People without a reputation to protect...
would never understand.
Anyone who harms my son's reputation...
in the slightest...
will pay heavily for it.
You must not know about me.
Hand him over to the prosecutors.
What? Are you really just leaving? Are you letting us go?
(Memorist)
(Ep 14, Two Layers of Evil)
Why that...
Move your car! Get out of my way!
Please, have mercy on him and protect him.
Please heal him.
Lord.
Dong Baek got away.
Get him.
Get every available man on him.
Yes, sir.
- Where is he? - In a room downstairs.
Let's go.
Tell me who the Eraser is.
Then you will live.
I'm already dead. I died 20 years ago.
At the morgue where I saw...
my brother's body.
No.
Yong Dae...
No, right? Yong Dae.
It can't be.
His suicide note that said he died because he was sick of poverty.
- No... - Please.
Those horrible words made my mom kill herself too.
Honey!
Honey.
My dad got depressed and left home.
He's probably...
in the bottom of a lake in a mountain somewhere,
unfound and untouched.
I had a gut feeling...
that the suicide note was forged.
If my brother really wrote it,
he would've at least left me a message.
Bang Joon Seok killed my brother,
but you killed the rest of my family. All three of us.
But what? You'll let me live?
How?
I already died 20 years ago, so how?
You found out everything,
but you let Bang Joon Seok live?
That rat can't die a comfortable death.
Same goes for your son.
- What? - Did you think he missed...
the vital points out of luck?
It's just the beginning...
for your son.
Who's the Eraser?
I don't know.
My memory has been erased.
Fine.
You...
need to die.
Oh, I see.
Will you kill me yourself?
Please let me see him for a minute.
You can't.
This isn't right.
You should let me see him.
You said you weren't in any relationship.
Where's the Eraser?
Did you enjoy the show?
Did you enjoy watching your son burn to death?
- What? - Well,
my brother...
was also burned and pushed off a cliff.
The Eraser said he'd do the opposite.
He said he'll make you hit rock bottom first,
then he'll burn you to kill you slowly.
He said it would be lame if you died too quickly.
Die.
I didn't want to say this,
but he's a murder suspect.
Bring a lawyer. You can't see him otherwise.
Why are you out here? What about Moon Yong Gang?
The Intelligence Bureau is standing guard.
- What? - They don't have jurisdiction.
Chief Byun.
Long time no see.
What brings you here all the way from the Intelligence Department?
- Can we talk? - Maybe next time.
Check the patient's room.
- Yes, sir. - Yes, sir.
It's the deputy chief's orders.
The director and deputy chief are both upstairs.
We'll be out of your hair soon, so give us a few minutes.
He's being interrogated.
By whom?
Corporal Chun Ki Soo from headquarters.
Just act like you don't know anything.
You let the victim's family meet the suspect?
Young Soo, you also work for the deputy chief.
What's the matter with you?
I don't work for him.
We just need to do what we're told.
Check the patient!
- Just push through! - Let's go!
Stop them.
- Move! - Get out.
Get off!
Who is the Eraser?
The pain of having lost your son...
will only worsen with time.
The pain will eat you up...
and make you feel miserable.
You don't even deserve a trial.
I'll just kill you myself.
- Move! - Move back!
- Stop them! - Move!
- This way, sir. - Hey, stop!
Nothing's going on!
(Moon Yong Gang)
- You can go first. - Okay.
My goodness.
Hey, you know I used to serve in the Marine Corps, right?
We're known to be very brave.
I can even eat a raw snake.
Why are you telling me that?
Can you look out for mice?
I really hate mice because of their long tails.
What about ones that don't have a tail?
What about Mickey Mouse?
What about Jerry from "Tom and Jerry"?
I don't like any of them.
Hey, did you hear that?
He may be huge, but he's like a little kid.
What's the matter?
He saw a mouse.
I really hate mice. I really do.
- Was anyone following you? - We used an unknown route.
No one would know that we used the route created by a murderer.
- And your cell phones? - It's turned off.
Are you sure you didn't call your son?
I'm not an amateur. Just worry about yourself.
Chairwoman Hwang Pil Seon is the final villain?
She even fabricated Moon Yong Dae's death...
and led his family to die.
Bang Joon Seok was the leader among those eight guys.
He was the one who killed Moon Yong Dae.
Then why wasn't he at the warehouse?
Hwang Pil Seon sent him to study abroad.
What a piece of trash. How could he dream of becoming the president?
And Chairwoman Hwang made Deputy Chief Lee...
- cover things up. - That's right.
I never liked him from the start. He always looked so cunning.
Didn't you say he made it that far because of his good looks?
I was just saying he had what it takes to succeed.
But he has a wicked personality.
"Why don't you read my face?"
- "Do I have the face of a king?" - Shut it.
So now that we know all this, what are we going to do?
We still need to figure some things out.
First of all, why did the Eraser wait 20 years?
You're right.
He must've been dying to punish Hwang Pil Seon and her son.
But he didn't even do anything.
Do you think he was in jail?
- You're clever. - Right?
Should I look through the list of ex-convicts?
Second of all, why did Jin Jae Gyu...
let Hwang Pil Seon live?
Why didn't he kill the woman that killed his own mother?
You're right. Then it would've been an execution-style murder.
She's a piece of trash who didn't get punished.
Do you think his memory got erased?
Or maybe he let her live because she's his stepsister.
No. It's because he received an oracle.
- "An oracle"? - A prophecy.
Hwang Pil Seon.
- He had already seen her future... - You're even worse...
- when he was young. - than your own mother.
You will die a brutal death.
And he had a revelation when he was confined in a mental hospital.
Killing her early would've been a blessing.
He truly believed that she will have a brutal ending.
(Newsroom Team 2, Reporter Kang Ji Eun)
What are you doing? Did you get some scoops on Dong Baek?
"The lonely fight of a telepathic detective"?
Are you crazy?
"The lonely fight of a telepathic detective".
Are you trying to get someone killed?
I wrote that based on the information I collected.
How is it an article if I just write...
- what I'm told to write? - Hey.
A reporter should write what the company wants.
If you don't like that, just start your own YouTube channel.
You know...
that even elementary school kids badmouth our broadcasting company.
There's not a single media that's on Dong Baek's side.
Then you should just resign.
Why would I do that?
So you won't do what you're asked, but still want to get paid?
I'll sue you for firing me for unjust reasons.
What? Have you lost your mind?
Fine. Go ahead.
Ji Eun!
- Did you get the photos? - What photos?
Did you get them or not?
Reporter Kang.
Move.
Sir, wait. We need to film this.
A guy altered his voice and called us...
saying he'll give us a scoop.
The Eraser?
But on one condition.
He wants you to give an exclusive report.
Ji Eun! This is a jackpot. How could you refuse to do this?
If we report this, we'll only be giving the Eraser what he wants.
We'll be pushing Detective Dong to a corner.
That's exactly why we should do it.
(I will drive a nail into her body every day until Dong Baek dies.)
Sir.
I'm not going to do it.
And here's the most important question of all.
What does the Eraser have against them?
We know what Moon Yong Gang has against them.
Bang Joon Seok and his friends killed his older brother.
And Hwang Pil Seon fabricated his brother's will...
and made his parents die as well.
But in the end, the Eraser was the one who took revenge.
He took revenge on his behalf.
The problem is that we don't know...
why the Eraser was so motivated to take revenge.
Are you sure Moon Yong Gang isn't the Eraser?
No.
He showed up after he used him as bait.
That means if we find out why the Eraser took revenge...
We'll be able to find out who he is.
Maybe he's someone who used to know Moon Yong Dae.
A friend or something like that.
My team is looking into it, but they don't have anything yet.
Then why don't we look into Dong Baek?
The Eraser killed your mother at Shimbae City...
(Eraser)
We probably won't find anything...
from Detective Dong's childhood at Shimbae.
Not a single person knew...
the telepathic celebrity for over seven years.
Where in the world is this guy from?
North Korea?
That makes sense.
- Maybe he was a secret agent. - Yes.
We only have one clue.
What was our first question?
"Why didn't the Eraser do anything for 20 years?"
He waited 20 years to take revenge. That's our clue.
So it wasn't because he wanted to take revenge for Moon Yong Dae?
There has to be a bigger resentment.
He was extremely patient and put in a lot of work for this revenge.
It can't be something that simple.
- Then what do you think... - The Eraser holds...
a deep grudge against Hwang Pil Seon's family.
We need to find out what happened between them.
Why didn't you tell me earlier?
Then I would've done my best to scan her memory.
No more memory scans.
Our hands are tied, so what other option do we have?
Anything's better than cleaning up a corpse.
- What? - Will someone die?
He will if he keeps on scanning memories.
Dr. Ahn is being paranoid, that's all.
- Call the medical team. - Got it.
Don't do anything silly. We're being wiretapped.
I'll lose my badge if you die.
You're going to anyway, so don't let it concern you.
I'm not being this way just to keep my job, you know.
Don't you care about those looking out for you?
We're not all cold-hearted like you.
This selfish act of yours is getting old.
Baek.
We have breaking news...
regarding Eun Soo Kyung.
Two photos of the abducted Ms. Eun...
were handed over to the media today.
What he wrote is gruesome to even repeat.
In the first photo, he wrote that he'd...
drive a nail through her every day...
until Dong Baek dies.
- Mr. Park. - Yes?
Dong Baek must be the telepathic investigator.
That is correct. The warning seems to be...
forwarded to Detective Dong.
What about the second photo?
The second photo is too merciless...
to reveal to the public as is.
However, since the people have the right to know...
Behind us is a blurred photo.
What are we seeing?
It seems to be the photo of Ms. Eun's feet.
They're your wife's feet.
Are you sure?
My son was assaulted in the same way.
The focus of the investigation is naturally shifting toward...
the killer's grudge against Detective Dong.
Could it be because...
- of a crime Dong Baek committed? - Scumbags.
It's hard to make that conclusion,
but many believe...
that Detective Dong earned the wrath of the Eraser.
In other words, Detective Dong's actions...
could've led to all these crimes.
That's right. Many are reasonably doubting...
that the Eraser is trying to get revenge against Detective Dong...
in the most twisted way.
Even after the first warning,
Detective Dong didn't explain himself,
which is why many are assuming that he may have...
possibly contributed to the Eraser's actions...
or that he's even aiding and abetting...
the killer himself.
Nicely put.
He's good, isn't he? He knows how to make it intense.
Sources tell us that authorities are speculating...
Dong Baek as the Eraser or at least an accomplice.
Citizens are quite baffled...
since Detective Dong has always promoted justice,
but is failing to serve it...
when he's the one at the center of the investigation.
He chooses what sits best with him, doesn't he?
Our online bulletin board...
is being bombarded with criticism against Dong Baek...
- Look at his slimy face. - They also...
want the network to release the photos of Ms. Eun.
We will dive into it further after the break.
They'll do anything to get high ratings, won't they?
I don't get it. Why does the Eraser keep provoking Baek?
To strike me mentally. He's trying to make me anxious.
Are you all right?
Of course. If that's how he'll be, we'll take it even slower.
Don't they seem to have switched personalities?
Let's get some sleep and head out in the morning.
- Head where? - To Hwang Pil Seon.
It's just like Ms. Han said. Cracking her will give us...
all the answers.
The Eraser's grudge and his true identity.
What on earth is this?
You shouldn't blame yourself.
I see you've grown a spine.
You have too, thanks to me looking out for you.
But yet you made this mess,
because you couldn't handle some telepath.
Truth be told, it isn't because of Dong Baek.
Your mistake 20 years ago...
brought out the devil we know as the Eraser.
I bet you're dizzy.
How can you not be...
when you're up somewhere too high for a lapdog?
Mr. Bang.
I didn't help you get out of trouble because I'm loyal to you.
It's because I believed it was right.
It was the best ending...
for the victims and everyone involved.
Unfortunately, it just led to some unexpected sacrifices.
- So? - I'm saying that loyalty...
isn't most important.
What matters is competence and it's why the chairwoman...
appointed me for the job.
Is this what you call competent?
You think you have all the power...
just because you have leverage over me.
Of course not.
It may sound like a cliche,
but I guess you can say our fates are tied.
First,
I don't care if his wife survives.
Mother!
Second,
my son...
must not be hurt from this scandal...
in any way.
You could turn it your advantage.
The biggest asset for any politician is sympathy votes.
Shut your incompetent mouth.
Third,
the killer who knows the truth must not walk into a courtroom.
Never.
I'm fully aware of that.
Lastly,
the one being criticized...
must be buried too.
You mean, Dong Baek.
Anyone who can be a threat to my son...
must be eliminated.
My wife must return safely.
If she doesn't, you'll pay with your life.
I'll do my best.
Just so we're clear,
his wife's safe return isn't a concern of mine.
I wouldn't mind it going the other way.
Keep that in mind.
We may not share the same views,
but our goal is the same.
Eliminating both the Eraser and Dong Baek...
is the only way...
to protect our children.
Cho Won!
How can you eat Dong Baek's as well?
Unbelievable!
Darn.
Going on a midnight run?
Did you stay up all night to keep an eye on me?
- I'm a light sleeper. - Please turn a blind eye.
Those crushed by the weight of guilt...
jump into the flame of death all by themselves.
- I'm not going to die. - It's not Cho Won.
Ms. Eun's unborn baby isn't your old friend.
- That's not why... - That's exactly why.
You're still haunted by the guilt from seven years ago.
I'm only trying to stop others from being hurt because of me.
How is any of this because of you?
He's messing with your head.
- I'll get going. - You'll end up dying.
I don't care.
I hate others getting hurt because of me even more.
What... What's this?
What's going?
Baek. Seriously.
I knew it. I knew he'd do that.
People don't change. Good thing we installed that.
Cuff him so he can't run away.
You've done all you could.
- It's my fight now. - What garbage.
Your protagonist syndrome is incurable.
Stay out of it.
You should see Peanut get married.
Shut it, punk.
Even if it's to the fiery pit, we're all going together.
If you'd listen to me and not stress me out,
I can live till 100 no problem.
You stay out of it too, Se Hoon.
I'm hurt.
Where Batman goes, Robin should go.
Who am I then?
Alfred?
"Alfred"? Isn't that a dog?
The butler who guards the house. That's perfect for you.
We're a team.
Let's go to the bat cave. I'll be the commissioner.
Superintendent Han has the highest rank here.
She's the captain, punk.
Captain, aren't you hungry? We're wide awake anyway.
The sun hasn't even risen yet.
Why are you being a busybody when the sun isn't even out?
You're such a pain in the neck. You annoying punk.
How about instant noodles?
Captain, how do instant noodles sound?
- Sounds good. - Okay.
Loser goes and buys. Rock, paper, scissors.
- I won. Go buy them. - Go.
Son.
- Dad. - Yes.
- Can you see me? - Yes.
The worst is over.
We should focus on recovery now.
Thank you.
Thank you, doctor.
Honey.
Sweetheart.
My gosh.
How's your son?
The worst is over.
He's critical.
Where did it all go wrong?
Do you resent me?
You were my savior...
until a few days ago.
I should've been fired long ago, but you made me a deputy chief.
- And now? - It's meaningless...
since my son's dead.
Take a break.
I'll get revenge.
The Eraser's identity.
- That's not your burden. - Yes, it is!
It's for my son's life.
Dong Baek.
Are you positive?
At least an accomplice.
This was taken at the safe house.
He used that item on his back...
to do that to my son.
I hear he's after Chairwoman Hwang.
(20R 9431)
Metro's surveillance truck.
Intelligence is staking out too.
- What should we do? - What else? We have to withdraw.
No.
No? How can we get through that?
(TVC News, MBS Daytime Briefing, CBC Today's News)
Look at the ratings.
What if the Eraser gives his next tip to someone else?
That's out of our hands.
It's better than dragging our heels and losing an exclusive.
Take care of Kang Ji Eun.
Yes, sir.
Excuse me. What are you doing?
Excuse me. Hey.
You can sit here and wait from now on.
- Where's my laptop? - That's a company asset.
Get permission before leaving your designated area.
Even when going to the bathroom.
Otherwise, you'll be disciplined for violation.
(Restricted Caller)
Hello?
What?
Former Assemblyman Bang Joon Seok will address the nation shortly.
Most predict he will appeal to his wife's abductor.
At the same time, many think he'll ask for a rightful decree,
given his leadership in caring for the disadvantaged...
and his view on strict adherence to the law to fight injustice.
Did you memorize your lines?
If I say those lines, everything will be fine?
No. Soo Kyung won't come back.
Mom.
Do you think the abductors wouldn't have said anything to her?
Still, how can you dump her?
No. She'll probably dump you.
If she does come back safely, would she still be on your side?
Knowing her personality?
It's simple to discern who's on your side.
People who won't change their minds...
even if they find out your dirty secrets.
Servants like this one are more trustworthy to be on your side.
Still...
I guess you're not.
You're capable of betraying us.
- That's not true, ma'am. - Mr. Jo.
Now, that's what you call loyalty.
He's willing to kill her the moment I tell him to.
I don't like the look in her eyes.
I still can't abandon Soo Kyung.
I told you already. She'll abandon you.
We should try to convince her.
She's pregnant with my baby.
My son.
Don't be scared of what you'll lose.
You should be scared of not being able to have more.
You'll continue to lose stuff from now on.
You might even have to share your power...
with the people around you.
But every time you lose something, remind yourself...
that what you lose...
will only help you gain more.
If Soo Kyung dies,
you'll be able to get the chance of a lifetime.
It'll be the most successful investment ever.
Do you understand?
- Let's go. - Hurry.
- Come on. - Let's get moving.
Let's go.
Come on.
- There he is! - Who is that?
Dong Baek is heading toward the trap.
(Taechul Distribution)
- You can't shoot. - Ms. Han.
The Eraser is after Chairwoman Hwang.
- We'll catch him, sir. - Just kill him.
If Dong Baek really is the Eraser, we can't just kill him.
How will we handle the aftermath?
The higher-ups will take responsibility.
We still haven't proved that he's the Eraser.
Whoever attacks Chairwoman Hwang is the Eraser.
On what basis?
Just believe what I tell you!
You parked this truck here on purpose, didn't you?
You wanted to warn Detective Dong because you know he's innocent.
(Former congressman, Bang Joon Seok, Urgent Press Conference)
My fellow citizens.
Today,
I stand before you for personal reasons.
And I hope you understand that.
For the past 12 years of my career in politics,
I've never compromised my principles for my own personal interest.
Not ever.
But I have decided to go against that...
just for today.
I beg the person who kidnapped my wife.
Please don't do anything...
to hurt my innocent wife.
I don't know what you have against Detective Dong.
But I am willing...
to endure the pain on behalf of my wife.
Give him a chance.
Give Detective Dong some time to find conclusive evidence.
I've already given my orders.
Sir.
I told the guys not to shoot regardless of whom it may be.
What are you doing here?
I know, right?
I beg once again to the person who kidnapped my wife.
If you want me to retire and donate my entire fortune,
I will do so.
If you need to take someone's life,
you can take mine instead.
I'm willing to abandon everything...
as long as I can...
save my wife.
It's Detective Dong.
- It's Detective Dong. - It's him, right?
Yes, it's him.
- What's going on? - What is he doing?
- What is that? - It's a gun.
- He's holding a gun. - That's a gun.
- Put the gun down. - Put the gun down.
- Put the gun down! - Put it down!
- Put it down! - Put the gun down!
- Let's go! - Are you okay, sir?
Catch him! Hurry up and catch him!
- Catch him! - Put the gun down!
Put it down!
- Put the gun down! - Put it down!
- Put the gun down! - Are you okay?
My goodness, what's going on?
- Put the gun down! - He's leaving!
- Catch him! - Go!
- Hurry! - Catch him!
- He's going! - Let's go!
Get moving!
Where did he go?
It's a gas pistol.
Wait.
Come on. It's okay.
- You'll be fine. - Find him!
- Hurry! - We need to catch him!
Take him with you.
Let's get moving!
I'll bring the car.
(Officer Dong Baek)
I'm listening.
There was another victim...
on the day that Moon Yong Dae died.
She died due to rape.
Yoo Ah Young. 20 years old.
Her... Her dad.
The fire station chief.
Shimbae Fire Station.
We have a special guest, so hurry up with the big welcome.
It's him.
He's the Eraser.
Former assemblyman Bang Joon Seok...
held a press conference regarding his wife, Eun Soo Kyung.
Mr. Bang appealed to the abductor and asked him for her safe return,
but Detective Dong's sudden appearance...
cut his press conference short.
- Dispatch units to his house. - Yes, ma'am.
Two young souls were taken that day.
Please don't hurt me.
We must stay alert.
You have too many enemies at the moment, Detective Dong.
Detective Dong isn't a criminal yet though.
We'll see about that.
Now that we know the killer's identity,
he'll soon be put down.
If something happens today, you can go ahead...
and read all of my memories.
I wish to testify.
The truth matters the most to a true journalist.
Could things really change?