(All characters, organizations, places, and events are fictional.)
(2 years ago)
How is Dong Baek doing?
Is he adjusting well?
Yes, he's been quiet lately.
It hasn't been that long since he got kicked out of Metro.
Is that so?
Then how about from now on?
- Pardon? - How do you think he'll behave?
Well, he's known to be very unusual.
- And he does whatever he wants... - He's hard to control, right?
But he's kind at heart, so with a little bit of help...
And what?
The support of the police...
will act as a stepping stone...
to help him succeed even more.
- Captain Koo. - Yes, sir?
How about this?
Let's not become someone who supports him.
Let's be the person who receives his help.
- Okay? - But sir...
That will be good...
for both the police force and Dong Baek himself.
Do you understand?
Yes, I understand what you mean.
If that's the case,
make him write a resignation letter.
Let's have him get dismissed...
and only use him when we need his power.
He can help solve violent crimes...
Detective Dong won't accept that.
From what I heard, he's always been very fond of you.
I'm also not sure if that's the right thing...
Captain Koo.
There's no right or wrong when it comes to the organization.
It's just a matter of making a choice.
Let's drink.
Gosh, come on. This isn't fair.
Old Man, I brought some guests.
- My gosh. - Shut it.
Gosh, that stings.
Is it fun to play detective?
I'm having a blast.
Do you know that people with power are scared because of you?
Why? Is someone scared about getting caught?
Those guys lived comfortably all their lives.
But they might lose everything because of you.
So of course, they're nervous.
Are you telling me to quit my job so the bad guys...
- can live in peace? - No, it's not that.
There are lots of other fun things to do.
If you become a celebrity,
you can get all the attention you want.
You can't kick me out.
I'm not trying to kick you out.
I'm not going to quit until you retire.
Because of you,
I even gave up trying to fix my hair loss.
I might die early because of stress.
That hurts. Can you take this off for me?
Come here.
Why are you trying to caress me?
Caress, my foot.
Do it gently. It hurts.
Gosh, it's cold.
Don't try to fight against those who hate you...
and just find what makes you happy.
You can hate me if you want.
No.
Detective Dong.
Catch them!
Sir!
- Sir! - Darn it.
- No... - Run.
Sir!
- Sir! - Oh, gosh.
- Sir, are you okay? - Wake up.
What are you doing? Call 911!
- Are you okay? - Please hurry up!
- Is this 911? - I'm okay.
- It doesn't hurt at all. - Someone got hurt.
Please hurry.
His condition? Just get here as fast as you can.
Sir!
(Operating Room)
(Restricted Area, Operating Room)
(Officer Oh Se Hoon)
The receiver cannot be reached. You will be directed to voicemail.
You will be charged after...
(The innocent shall be crucified in place of the sinner.)
(Restricted Area, Operating Room)
He'll be okay.
Dad!
Mom, what are we going to do?
Where is Uncle Baek?
He'll be here.
But right now, he's busy.
What are we going to do?
Se Hoon.
We got paged, so we need to go.
Okay.
Call me once the surgery ends.
The doctor doesn't know yet.
We'll need to wait and see.
We're all cops here. Show some respect.
Is this really necessary?
His life is at risk.
That's enough.
Gosh, that darn old man.
He's so slow. I can't believe he couldn't dodge that.
It's like he's trying to make me feel guilty.
This is all because of Dong Baek.
It's not because of him. I'm the one who volunteered.
Why would you volunteer?
You're about to retire soon.
Do you expect me to sit back and watch a kid fight by himself?
He's not a normal kid.
Yes, he's not normal.
He's a real pain in the neck.
- My gosh. - But you see,
he's no different from our kids.
He laughs when he's in a good mood,
and he cries when he's sad.
Then he shouts when he gets angry.
He may be different, but that's only a small part.
He's a normal human being just like us.
Plus, he can't do anything without me.
My goodness, you're unbelievable.
I'm serious.
- My gosh. - Baek.
What? Why?
Come on. Let's go inside.
- Sir. - Hey, it's Dong Baek.
We came to watch your interview.
Gosh, we don't need to watch that.
There it is.
What kind of person is Detective Dong?
He's an amazing young man.
Oh, I see.
How exactly is he amazing?
Well, you can say that we're like father and son.
We care for each other like any other family...
The medicine I took is making me drowsy.
Goodness.
Father. Father?
What was up with that interview?
- Father, get up and talk to me. - Just let me rest.
Dad?
Give me back the remote control.
Dad, come on.
(Memorist: Ep 15, Flesh and Blood)
- Dad! - Honey!
- Honey, open your eyes. - Dad...
Honey, please open your eyes.
- Coming through. - Wake up, will you?
Open your eyes.
Honey!
He passed out the moment he got here.
Isn't Detective Dong overexerting himself?
He's awake.
Sure, I'll get back to you.
Are you all right?
You should rest a little more.
What about the old man?
The surgery went well but...
I can take it, so tell me.
He hasn't gained consciousness.
I'm sure he'll soon wake up though.
You can't. The hospital is crawling with prosecutors...
and officers from the Intelligence bureau.
And Ms. Eun Soo Kyung?
They're looking for her. I just talked to Superintendent Han.
Detective.
Don't worry. I'm not going anywhere.
I'll be in the next room.
Give me some time alone.
Let me go there instead then.
No, you should get some rest.
It might be your last for a while.
Thank you.
Prosecutor Woo Seok Do?
I was hoping to introduce myself in a formal setting,
but I guess things are too urgent for that.
Could we perhaps have a few words?
Go ahead.
I know you have grave interest in Detective Dong,
but I'd appreciate you turning it down a notch.
The prosecution being interested in a criminal...
isn't the NIS's concern.
Detective Dong isn't a criminal.
We'll see about that.
I also know of a criminal.
There's this guy who got a victim killed...
by trying to cover up a chief prosecutor's scandal.
I'm just saying since you're interested in criminals.
It's a pleasure to meet you, Deputy Chief Lee.
I'm Chief Kim of the NIS.
Ms. Son, what brings you by?
I didn't take you for a coward,
but here you are lying about your identity.
Is this about Dong Baek?
I knew you'd figure it out.
I'm afraid there's nothing I can help you with though.
Shall we?
This won't go your way.
It won't.
(Chairwoman Hwang Pil Seon)
I'm Prosecutor Woo Seok Do of the Central Prosecutors' Office.
I was told by the prosecutor general to help you in any way I can.
The culprit has been identified, so he'll be put down soon.
- And the brat? - The same goes for Dong Baek.
But first, there's something we need to sort out.
It requires a promise from the prosecutors' office.
- A promise? - A non-indictment.
Dong Baek's death will turn the world upside down.
The press will have a field day...
and the prosecution will use this chance...
to point its swords.
So you need me to guarantee...
a non-indictment?
This isn't something I can decide on my own.
I already cleared it with your boss.
Then why do you need my word too?
Incompetent.
- Sorry? - Your boss is incompetent.
He shouldn't have let this get so far, but look at this mess.
It's like we're criminals discussing our next crime.
- I apologize, ma'am. - Save it.
So what'll it be?
Do you really want the prosecution to spend its resources...
cleaning up after others?
No, ma'am. That ends right here.
I'll handle the situation myself...
so that you never have to be concerned anymore.
That's the spirit.
I hope you'll keep it that way.
You remind me of...
how your boss was six years ago.
Once you lose your drive,
your power and authority disappear with it.
Former Assemblyman Bang Joon Seok, who was assaulted by Detective Dong,
went back to helping the police...
find his wife despite recommendations from his doctors.
If Detective Dong truly is an accomplice,
then I plead to him.
Please let my wife go.
The police have declared Detective Dong's assault...
as an act of terror...
and announced that they'd arrest him immediately.
Detective Dong's assault on Mr. Bang added to the suspicion...
of him being the Eraser's accomplice.
The serial killer known as the Eraser...
made a threat against Detective Dong,
but many suspect that it was a trick...
to mask the relationship between them.
Fear is now increasing among the public...
Let me attend to your bruise.
What's your relationship with him?
Sorry?
You and Moon Yong Gang.
I don't think I follow, sir.
Did you think I wouldn't know?
- There's nothing going on. - Then why...
did you visit him at the hospital?
Well...
Have you been scheming with him?
Did he offer you money...
for helping to kill me?
Look at me.
Look at me, darn it.
If you're not working together,
are you two intimate?
We are not.
There's really nothing between us.
I knew from the get-go.
At first, you looked like...
you wanted something from me.
Gosh. But you got together with a lowlife like him.
You're so cheap.
I'll go now.
What a shame.
I would've put you in the pool...
of potential second wives once my wife died.
Keep an eye on her.
Yes, sir.
What are you doing?
I was just...
Just what?
Just... Well... Thinking?
Should I take a guess?
What are you doing?
You were thinking about me.
Am I wrong?
Yes.
Darn it.
I'm jealous.
I wish I could read people's memories like you.
It's not good at all.
Why not? I think it would be awesome.
It isn't.
People's memories...
aren't as nice as you think.
There are so many things I wish I never knew.
I'm sure there are some that you're happy about knowing.
I'm not sure. Were there any?
Here.
Take it out if you need.
All of my memories.
I've been...
thinking especially more about you recently.
Made you smile.
See? Your ability made at least two people happy.
Baek.
Your ability...
may be able to make a great number of people happy.
Then eventually...
the world may change and become a better place.
Can it...
Can it really change?
I'd like to make a statement.
Please don't kill me.
Please?
I've already...
saved many people.
I know you're a good person.
So please...
There's no rule...
that says a good person can't become bad.
Rather, I've been too good a person.
So the pain that I've suffered...
feels even more unfair.
Things like that...
shouldn't happen...
to me...
and to my baby.
Don't you agree?
20 years ago,
I went abroad to rescue people after an earthquake.
I suddenly had to rush home.
They said my daughter had died.
But it wasn't a natural death.
I had seen many deaths...
during my years as a firefighter.
Even when my wife died,
I wasn't as afraid as I was that day.
They said...
she had committed suicide.
However,
that wasn't true.
I wish...
I never found out.
Yoo Ah Young?
So Philip?
Darn it. What are you doing here?
I'm taking pictures.
What about you?
My friend owns this land.
All of this...
is his.
Bang Joon Seok.
Don't you know him?
That's right. We go to different schools now.
Darn it. What's wrong with me?
Were you...
drinking?
Something much better.
See you later.
Darn it.
You should pay an access fee for entering someone else's land.
What?
Want a drink?
It'll take you to paradise.
Those jerks trampled on Ah Young.
But that wasn't where their sins ended.
Hey. Look at this.
Here are some more.
Come on.
What is it?
Come on, don't do it.
I asked, what is it?
Moon Yong Dae?
Darn it.
Where's Ah Young?
Why you...
Get him!
I can't stand your eyes. They annoy me.
He burned Yong Dae.
And while he was still alive,
he threw him off a cliff.
That day,
two children were killed...
by your husband, Bang Joon Seok!
My child's friend died that very day,
but my child...
Hey.
Detective Lee, what brings you here?
You really need to come to your senses...
if you don't want to rot in prison.
My daughter lived.
Both her body and mind...
were completely destroyed.
But she didn't die.
(Gynecologist, Jeong Hyeong Sik)
I don't see any signs of resistance.
Ah Young, I believe you.
But some people could take this the wrong way.
Imagine how sad your dad will be if he finds out.
Don't you agree?
You know Moon Yong Dae, right?
I'm not supposed to tell you this.
But he died.
He committed suicide.
Remember that place where you had fun with those guys?
He died nearby.
I wonder if he saw something there.
She survived that day.
But she died inside...
every single day.
I also have a child.
If you let me live, I'll do anything you ask.
But you see,
after having gone through something like that,
I finally realized something.
I realized that there's no reason...
behind our misfortunes.
I heard about what happened to Captain Koo...
and the guy who did it.
Chun Ki Soo...
tried to hit me.
Deputy Chief Lee gave permission to shoot.
He gave permission to shoot and kill.
- Detective Dong. - What?
Why do you think I'm telling you this?
It's not just the Eraser...
that we're fighting against.
You have way too many enemies.
- I know. I'm used to it. - Don't be.
You need to stay alert.
And there's no need to blame yourself.
If I could have things my way, I'd keep you off this case.
But you know I won't listen.
Yes, I know. That's why I'm telling you this.
I'm telling you so you'll watch out.
Are you being considerate?
No, I'm giving you advice based on the information...
I've gathered about you.
So you're giving me advice out of consideration? That's nice.
I'll keep it in mind.
Thanks a lot.
- Where is Yoo Soon Nam? - We're trying to trace him.
All we know for now is that he left the city.
(Situation Room)
Hello?
Let me go with you.
No, I need you to stay and do something for me.
Please do me a favor.
I think I know where Yoo Soon Nam is. Let's go.
Tell me the specific location.
Yoo Soon Nam's father-in-law owns a warehouse near the river.
And that's where his car went.
We sent you the address via text.
The SWAT team will be there in 20 minutes.
Okay, thank you.
What's the scoop?
Detective Dong's testimony regarding the truth...
behind the Eraser's murders.
- "Testimony"? - What if Detective Dong was framed?
- What? - And what if the murders...
were caused by a certain conglomerate family?
We need to watch it first.
Where is the video?
I'm worried you might get rid of it so you could destroy Detective Dong.
- Are you kidding me? - Answer my question first.
Will you release the video...
exactly as it is?
Have you lost your mind?
- Ji Eun. - Yes?
What do you think is most important to a reporter?
The truth.
The truth is what matters.
And we're all reporters.
That's why we need to tell people that Detective Dong was framed.
The truth...
doesn't come from outside. It starts from here.
We're the ones who create the truth.
And the truth we need to create right now...
is to make sure that mutant disappears from this world.
Okay?
Ji Eun, you're still a rookie, and you don't know much.
We'll give you one more chance.
So stop being so stubborn and bring us the video clip.
- I can't do that. - My gosh!
You could go to jail for using your position to gather information...
- and keeping it to yourself. - You must be mistaken.
I'm the one who just offered to give you one last chance.
I'll be off now.
Ji Eun!
Ji Eun, wait.
Hey! Your life will be over...
once we sue you for compensation and have you end up in jail!
Ji Eun!
Darn it.
The SWAT team is approaching the place,
but we don't see a hostage anywhere.
You may shoot and kill if an emergency breaks out.
Yes, sir.
You have permission to shoot and kill.
He's never been this obvious about his whereabouts.
This isn't the place.
(SWAT)
There's no one at the location.
What on earth?
- Let's go. - Where?
There's one more place I suspect.
I looked into it and the professor was right.
It's nearby where Yoo Ah Young killed herself 20 years ago...
by carbon monoxide poisoning.
Got it. Text me the address.
Sure.
Should I call for backup too?
Just Metro. Leave the others in the dark.
Got it.
How did you know?
It's the same for most serial killers.
Murder is a ritual to the Eraser as well.
I knew there was a reason he came all the way here...
even though it'd leave a trace.
Right.
Uncle Dong Baek...
You see...
I know. He's busy, right?
Yes.
Mom said...
that he's 10 times busier...
because my dad got hurt.
Yes, that's right.
Just so you know, my dad can't do anything...
without you and Uncle Dong Baek by his side.
Yes, that's right too.
(Ms. Kang Ji Eun)
Just a second.
Detective Oh, I need your help.
It's for Detective Dong.
Of course.
(57H1019)
Where's Eun Soo Kyung?
Darn him.
- She's still alive. - Let her go.
Take her from me if you can.
Yoo Soon Nam.
What do you achieve by hurting Eun Soo Kyung anyway?
Detective Dong Baek...
and Superintendent Han Sun Mi.
What do you achieve...
by saving her life then?
A sense of relief for saving an innocent life?
A sense of justify that's more like a mirage?
What are you trying to say?
There was a time when those were important to me too.
But you see, those emotions...
only mean anything for us humans.
Just cut the crap.
People forget too easily.
A police officer who arrested a perp?
A firefighter who saved a life?
How long do you think people remember that?
I doubt it even lasts a day.
So why would you put yourself in danger...
for something that'll easily be forgotten?
Isn't it a waste?
No, I'd never think that.
Actually, you've already realized...
that your sense of justice can't change the ways of this world.
The more you try to help,
the more the world will turn against you.
Remove Detective Dong!
HQ just disassembled our team.
This is not acceptable!
This is to humiliate you...
in front of the camera for the whole world to see.
Dong Baek.
Han Sun Mi.
In order to create a better world,
a true leader must emerge.
Her husband, the former assemblyman.
His crude mother who thinks money can buy everything.
And the parasitic prosecution, police, and media outlets!
Not those countless scumbags.
Not those animals behind masks,
but a true leader.
A worshiped idol...
and the fear that'll be brought upon...
anyone who goes against that said hero.
The fear generated by that hero...
is what will give birth to true justice.
Eun Soo Kyung...
is actually dying an honorable death.
You scumbag...
What are you thinking?
Why is he using her to bargain with us?
That's not the only odd thing.
All this time, he avenged Moon Yong Dae...
and Yoo Ah Young in the way they were wronged.
No!
Murder is a ritual to him. One that he's obsessed about.
He wouldn't suddenly change his way of killing.
Eun Soo Kyung isn't in there.
Then where could she be?
Should we make our move?
But what if he really is the Eraser?
Sure thing. Go ahead and kill Ms. Eun.
I'll follow your ways.
- Do you mean it? - Yes.
On one condition though.
Before you kill her,
I'd like to do a memory scan.
Bang Joon Seok and Hwang Pil Seon have messed with me too...
and I need information in order to deal with them.
You can do whatever you want afterward.
So what do you say? Do we have a deal?
Did you really think I'd fall for your trick?
Come on.
If you truly are the Eraser,
you'll incapacitate us no matter what we do.
Aren't I right?
So open the suitcase. It doesn't seem too hard to me.
You're not the Eraser.
Take another step...
and I'll push her over.
It's fine. She's not in there anyway.
Eun Soo Kyung is in the building!
Tell me. Who's the Eraser?
It's me.
Tell me the truth.
It's me. I'm the Eraser!
- Yoo Soon Nam! - All that I said to you...
was what I heard from him.
I wasn't here today.
It was him...
who was here.
You just won't give up.
Remember...
what you heard today.
The world cannot improve using your methods.
And if the world doesn't improve,
you will be nothing but an outsider...
who is persecuted forever!
- Chun Ki Soo, drop your gun! - Drop it!
Drop your gun.
No!
Hey.
Baek! Baek! Are you okay?
Darn it. He was shot. Hurry. Call an ambulance.
We need a medic. There's a gunshot victim on the roof.
Baek! Wake up!
- Press on the wound! - Yes, on the roof.
Wake up!
Press on it!
Yes.
The Eraser died. Dong Baek was shot and is being transported.
- How is he? - It won't be easy.
- Confirm. - But...
the NIS suddenly showed up.
What should we do?
- Follow them discreetly. - Yes, sir.
Where?
- Right now? - Take it down right away, please.
Please. We need it down by this evening.
Oh no.
That's...
In this video, Detective Dong Baek tells us the truth...
- regarding the Eraser. - Hello, Madam Chairman.
I'd like to make a statement.
Based on the memories that I saw while hunting the Eraser,
it's a story that began long ago.
20 years ago.
The scumbag who trampled on and killed innocent young people,
and the mom who caused the deaths of their surviving families...
in order to hide her child's sins.
They are...
the real cause that brought about Eun Soo Kyung's suffering.
Former assemblyman Bang Joon Seok...
and Chairwoman Hwang Pil Seon.
And...
Deputy Chief Chun Ki Soo,
who followed their orders and covered up the crimes,
(Detective Dong Baek's Statement Regarding the Eraser Case)
and Lee Shin Woong,
the deputy chief of the National Police Agency.
They bribed many people in order to cover up the murder...
and rape committed by Bang Joon Seok and his friends.
They fabricated false testimonies and disguised a murder as a suicide.
Moreover, they said unspeakable things to the rape victim,
who was just a student at the time,
and killed the girl...
over and over.
Chun Ki Soo, who covered up the murder on their orders,
and Lee Shin Woong,
the deputy chief of the National Police Agency.
Take down what you posted online right this instant.
No, I will not.
Ji Eun. Do you think you'll get away with this?
I have no choice.
The most important thing for a journalist is the truth.
Hey, Ji Eun!
Nice.
You're super cool.
I'm cool and unemployed.
I should do that too.
To Baek...
and to Captain Koo. I should talk to them like that too.
Call me when you get fired.
Okay.
(Dong Baek's Statement)
Do you think Baek will be okay?
Well, he looks completely not okay, but still.
He'll be okay.
He has a lot of people rooting for him.
Still, Had I known he went to the scene, I would've gone too.
He needs someone there to hold him back.
You're worried he'll get hurt, aren't you?
No. In case he beats someone up.
He doesn't get hurt easily.
Even if he does, he gets right up and yanks out the IV needle and...
And...
Superintendent Han went with him, so I'm sure he's fine.
I guess so, right?
What are you doing?
Take that video down right now!
It's on servers in other countries too.
We'll find a way.
Darn it.
Mr. Cho.
What do you think you're doing?
I warned you 20 years ago.
That if you don't get your act together,
you'll rot in jail for the rest of your life.
Do you think you'll get away with this?
Stop.
We need to fix it first.
It's impossible...
to make it like none of it happened.
Nothing is impossible for me.
Not in this country.
Just do as you've always done. Just follow my orders!
- I make the decisions. - No.
I'll take care of it using my methods.
This is...
no longer just your family's problem.
It's my problem as well.
You're going to cut ties with me...
now that the situation isn't in your favor?
Do you think you're the only person who works for me in this country?
Did you forget...
who helped you get this far?
Detective Dong, who fell unconscious after he got shot 15 days ago,
is known to be in a very critical situation.
According to his doctors,
Detective Dong still hasn't regained his consciousness.
And the foreign doctors who came to treat him...
are also very pessimistic about his recovery.
Are you going to keep staring at me like that?
Are you okay?
Of course.
Did you think...
I wouldn't be okay?
But according to the news...
Did they say I'm going to die?
You moved the public.
It looks like there's going to be a special prosecution...
for Hwang Pil Seon and Bang Joon Seok.
But of course, it won't be easy.
Everything will turn out great.
Your testimony played a big role.
What's the matter?
Something suddenly came to mind.
What?
I started to wonder if things would've come this far...
if I didn't end up getting hurt.
I tried so hard to make this happen.
But it's proceeding a lot faster...
now that people think I'm about to die.
Do you really think...
The more you try to help,
the more the world will turn against you.
You will be nothing but an outsider...
who is persecuted forever!
Do you really think I'll be loved once I disappear from this world?
I couldn't stop thinking about what he said to me.
You should get some rest.
Stop worrying about that. It doesn't suit you.
Just focus on recovering so you can return to work.
Hey.
Hey!
What?
Are you Detective Dong?
(If you want to know the truth, let's meet where it all started.)
Seo Hui Soo.
I will start by telling you the truth.
Dong Baek.
My little brother.
(Memorist)
This document is about a person with supernatural powers.
Someone other than Detective Dong.
Trace Detective Dong's location. Hurry.
Tell me everything you know.
How can I believe you?
That's when...
I realized something.
That's why you killed people...
and started taking revenge?
If you think I'm a monster,
just kill me. Kill me!
It's over now.
Shut your mouth and watch. This is just the beginning.