(All characters, organizations, places, and events are fictional.)
(The night of April 20, 2000)
(Abandoned Warehouse in Shimbae City)
I'll let you talk if you promise to be quiet.
You dare abduct a high-ranking police officer?
Did Kim Ju Kyeong put you up to this?
No.
Then was it...
Mr. Hwang?
Tonight, you will die.
- What? - That's all I know.
My memories aren't completely intact.
All I know is that, just like me, you've become the kid's target.
What kid?
The young devil.
- Who are you? - He's young but evil.
I only cooperated to protect my daughter.
Although, even these memories will soon be erased.
Let's go. Let me loose...
- and we'll find a way. - Quiet.
He's here.
Don't underestimate him...
or you'll die a gruesome death.
What did you do to Sang Ah?
But I did everything you asked.
I'll kill you!
There is going to be a party?
Unbelievable...
Who are you?
What...
Kid. Hey, kid?
Are you all right?
Kid!
Hey, kid. Are you all right?
It was you.
You liar.
You were the one who killed seven people in Shimbae...
20 years ago.
No. No.
No! No, that can't be!
You're the Eraser who killed...
all those people.
Where's your proof?
All the people he loathed...
fell victim to the Eraser.
Park Ki Dan,
Oh Yeon Tak,
Jo Sung Dong...
No.
You were the one to identify Yeom Hwa Ran...
as the suspect in the DUI hit-and-run case.
Choi Won Yeong and Yeon Mi Ji.
The two psychopaths killed a poor girl...
whom you grew up with at the orphanage.
(Attached file)
You're lying.
You're the one who ordered Chun Ki Soo...
to cover up the incident 20 years ago.
I don't know what you're getting at,
but that's a meaningless detail...
considering how you're the murderer.
Who was it?
Who ordered the cover-up of Moon Yong Dae's death?
Why do you ask?
To add another name to your list of victims?
I'll just scan your memory myself.
- Freeze! - Freeze.
- Arrest him. - Lower your weapons.
We're here to investigate...
Deputy Chief Lee's alleged corruption.
He's a killer.
- That's enough. - Shoot him if he makes a move.
Did you really believe you'd get away with this?
Even though a mistake was made in the process,
the statute of limitations has expired now.
A mistake?
The murder of a young man was covered up as a suicide!
I've been handling a murderer through proper procedure.
How dare someone like you question my conduct?
You foolish girl.
You couldn't see the murderer in front of you...
even with the hint I handed over.
This is your job now.
It's up to you to fill in the blanks.
Actually, I figured it out a long time ago.
The relationship between Detective Dong and the victims...
and how you tried to get rid of him without making the move yourself.
What I couldn't figure out was the motive. But now I know.
It was to hide your own crimes.
You kept silent even when you knew he was the killer?
Where's your evidence?
Only Dong Baek's enemies were murdered.
At the very least, Dong Baek is the Eraser's accomplice.
What about Chun Ki Soo's son...
- and the firefighter? - Them too!
Dong Baek's taking revenge...
on what happened in Shimbae 20 years ago.
No, that's only what you want to believe.
You're trying to crush Dong Baek because he figured you out.
He found out how you covered up...
Moon Yong Dae's murder and the incident in Shimbae.
You'll have to at least kill one more person...
if you wish to keep your crimes hidden.
(7 years ago)
(Sul Cho Won missing 3 days)
Candidate number one, Ko Hyun Ah.
- Ko Hyun Ah. - Ko Hyun Ah.
- Ko Hyun Ah. - Please vote for me.
Candidate number one, Ko Hyun Ah.
Ko Hyun Ah.
- Please vote... - Candidate number one, Ko Hyun Ah.
What are you doing?
- Please stop. - You shouldn't do that.
- What is he doing? - Hey.
Ma'am!
(Memorist)
(Ep. 13, The Name of The Prophesy)
(Year 2013)
A young man standing trial...
has stated that he has telepathic powers.
He is making an outlandish assertion that he can read memories...
simply by touching a person.
During the trial for the assault on Assemblyman Ko Hyun Ah...
held at a district court in South Gyeonggi,
the suspect Dong asserted that he has telepathic powers.
He made an outlandish assertion that he can read people's memories...
simply by touching them.
In a shocking turn of events, contrary to expectations,
the justice department appears to believe him,
and has closed the trial from the public.
According to sources,
the NIS had been investigating
the truth behind his telepathic powers...
since the onset of the trial.
This series of events has been interpreted...
as accepting Dong's assertion regarding his telepathic powers,
thus increasing the interest of the public.
It's a warning found in the firefighter's nose.
"The innocent shall be crucified..."
"in place of the sinner."
Dong Baek and Superintendent Han Sun Mi...
are digging into a case in which the firefighter's wife was involved.
The Eraser appears to have targeted the firefighter...
because of his wife, who is a doctor.
Targeting innocent family members.
My son's inside.
Joon Young!
Move my family to a safe house.
Excuse me?
Get the NIS, the Secret Service, everyone,
and evacuate my wife and son immediately.
Yes, sir.
Dong Baek fled last night.
That is all we have on the case.
From this moment forth, Dong Baek is our prime suspect.
Concentrate all our forces on arresting him.
We will also locate and monitor those who may help Dong Baek.
Superintendent Han Sun Mi,
Captain Koo Kyung Tan, and Officer Oh Se Hoon.
It's bad enough Superintendent Han was suspended,
- but what? Monitor her? - This is nonsense.
Dong Baek? The Eraser's accomplice? You know what he's like.
He loathes murderers with a passion.
- Hey. Am I right or not? - It's true.
It's understandable to suspect him.
What was that, punk?
Who would instruct you to give us such an order without any evidence?
If he resists arrest,
you may use any and all necessary force.
Even guns?
Sir. Whose order is this?
Even those ignorant prosecutors can't give an order like that.
Dong Baek is a hothead, so he'd never come readily,
but you want us to shoot him?
You know his temper. This is an order to kill.
- Am I right or not? - You're right.
(Byun Young Soo)
Please show me the evidence.
Hey, you. Young Soo. Are you defying an order?
It's not defiance. I'm requesting evidence.
The prosecutor's arrest warrant wasn't a request for cooperation.
Your job is to catch him before the prosecutors and find evidence.
Don't be a rude punk...
and demand evidence, you jerk!
(Media Policy)
(Media's unsubstantiated statements are harming the police's reputation)
Make the media hostile toward him.
None of the media companies are favorable to Dong Baek.
Captain.
What's with the rain?
It looks like it'll pass. Did you find Moon Yong Gang?
He disappeared without a trace. What about Chun Ki Soo?
He hid himself well.
What do we do?
I'll do as Superintendent Han said and stay with Assemblyman Bang.
You keep trying to locate Moon Yong Gang.
I don't know where to start.
We don't have time. Look at this.
Every news agency is bent on catching Baek.
(Despicable Serial Killer Suspect Dong Baek, Did He Fool the Nation?)
This is the agency where Kang Ji Eun works.
No one in media is on Baek's side.
We're the only ones on his side, so stay on top of your game.
I'm going to meet with Ms. Kang.
For what? She's powerless.
I'll call you.
Se Hoon.
So you're alive.
How did you know I was here?
Sit.
This feels like an interrogation.
Because I'm going to interrogate you.
About what?
The truth about you.
You're interrogating me from a murderer's desk.
Why? In case I'm the Eraser?
That too.
If I'm really the murderer, your life is in my hands.
I told you. The moment I die,
this will record everything and send the file to my colleagues.
Shall we begin?
You'd better be nervous.
You'll get arrested the moment you say anything suspicious.
How did you know I was here?
Was Jin Jae Gyu really a shaman?
Why do you want to know?
I need to know who he really was in order to answer your question.
What did you see when you scanned his memory?
He was definitely psychic.
"Psychic"?
It ran in his family.
(1971, 8-year-old Jin Jae Gyu)
Jin Jae Gyu's mother...
was a shaman.
Stop!
But Jin Jae Gyu was a normal kid. At least until he met...
his worst enemy.
Pee on him.
Pil Seon, he's just a kid.
Should I do it myself?
Do you think this is funny?
Your brother in Vietnam...
was killed by a Vietnamese soldier two days ago.
- What? - He died a miserable death.
What did you just say?
You darn little...
Yong Sik!
Tell Dad to stop smoking and drinking.
And Mom has weak knees,
so run errands for her whenever she needs your help.
And I want you to burn my guitar...
and bury it in the ground with me.
Yong Sik!
We should go.
Hwang Pil Seon.
You're even worse than your own mother.
You will die a brutal death.
You will face the most pitiful death.
(R 3 - 4671)
Mom!
Mom! Mom!
(For orchards and weeds)
What's wrong with you?
Why...
did you come home so late?
Mom, what's wrong?
Jae Gyu, my son.
I hope you become a great person.
Mom!
I cooked...
rice for you.
Eat it...
before it gets cold.
Mom! Mom!
- The day he turned psychic. - Mom!
Mom!
That's when his mom died.
She drank pesticide?
But why do you care whether he's psychic or not?
What does that have anything to do with why you're here?
Jin Jae Gyu's last words.
You will meet again.
He told me we'll meet again.
You will meet Dong Baek again at the foundation.
The foundation of the murderer.
You came all the way here...
because of that?
How many things did he tell you before he died?
Four.
He told me the Eraser is hidden deep inside your memory...
and that I'll end up meeting you again here.
And lastly,
he told me to find Cho Won.
- There should be one more. - It was the strangest one.
He told me...
someone came to the church the night Park Ki Dan got murdered.
And he told me...
that was you.
I saw a revelation.
I saw him standing there.
I just ignored what he said.
He was dying, so I thought he wasn't in his right mind.
But once everything started to come true, I changed my mind.
If Jin Jae Gyu could really predict the future,
I figured you really might've gone to the church.
Did you kill Park Ki Dan?
I wanted to.
And I wanted to ask something before I killed him.
I wanted to ask how it feels to be the victim.
Yes.
He's right. I was there.
I went there to scan his memory.
I was expecting to go to jail.
So I wanted to expose all his sins to the entire world.
So what happened?
I turned around...
in front of the church and went home.
After you went all the way there?
I remembered...
the view I saw a long time ago.
The view I saw from the window...
every single day after Cho Won went missing.
That's when I realized...
that she wouldn't want me...
to murder anyone.
Cho Won always wanted...
more and more people to find out about my power.
She thought that would encourage more people to be kind.
Ko Hyun Ah...
was driving back with the guy she was cheating with.
My gosh.
- What happened? - What happened?
- What are we going to do? - Let's put her here.
- Hurry. - Don't rush me.
My goodness.
Help me.
- I think she's alive. - Darn it.
Help.
Darn it. Hey, what are you doing?
- What are you doing? - Move!
No, don't. No!
Hello, I'm Ko Hyun Ah.
I met her...
the day after the accident.
If only I had...
shaken her hand.
If I shook her hand that day...
You exposed your power to the public to punish those murderers.
How did you know that?
My trial records are classified as a national secret.
You owe me one.
The NIS?
You have a good hunch. I'll give you that.
You knew everything and still kept your eyes on me?
So what? Are you going to arrest me now?
No, you're not the type to kill anyone.
What I've been doubting all this time though...
was a separate personality.
The evil personality that killed seven people in Shimbae City...
20 years ago.
What if that evil personality became the Eraser...
along with the help of an accomplice?
I don't have the energy for jokes.
Every scenario hit a dead end and the possibility was close to zero.
Unless you used a trick that was beyond my comprehension, that is.
So?
I trust you.
Actually, it's my judgment I believe.
Is the interrogation over then?
For now.
I guess I should be grateful.
It's why we'll work together until we find the Eraser.
So all that's left is the incident at Shimbae.
Someone other than me was at that warehouse.
Someone taller than 170cm.
When he killed seven people that day,
you were there as well.
Mom!
He then went on to kill your mother.
You lost your memories and ended up at Dongbaek Station.
Why was the Eraser called the young devil?
He was probably young.
Moon Yong Gang was only 17 at the time as well.
You think Moon Yong Gang is the Eraser?
The Eraser is an enemy of your family...
and he killed seven people.
Two months before the incident though,
Moon Yong Gang's brother was found murdered.
He killed the seven people to avenge his brother...
by becoming the Eraser?
He's at least an accomplice.
How's that?
Because if I were the Eraser, I wouldn't pass up on...
Moon Yong Gang as a partner.
Just like he used Jin Jae Gyu.
Why did Moon Yong Gang inform us of Deputy Chief Lee?
Was it to fool us?
The Eraser is drawing a bigger picture,
but we don't even know whom he's ultimately after.
His ultimate goal?
The man who incited Lee Shin Woong.
There's an evil force that's been calling the shots...
and you think he's who the Eraser is ultimately after?
Then we have our answer. We either go after...
Lee Shin Woong or Moon Yong Gang, the Eraser's accomplice.
Who first?
You should stay out of it. This is my job now.
- What? - You'll only end up dead.
Dr. Ahn and her big mouth.
My health is supposed to be top secret.
The doctor is too much of a worrywart.
Get some rest.
The phone isn't traceable, so keep it on at all times.
You'll pursue the case without me...
You'll only slow me down.
This is my war.
One that death can't even stop.
I found a lead.
There's someone helping Moon Yong Gang.
Who?
Hold on. That phone's being traced.
It's on flight mode.
When did you record this?
- You'll end up dead. - Mr. Moon.
What seems off?
Please don't kill me.
She moved first.
Yes, Ms. Han.
Old man, it's me.
Where on earth did you go? Ms. Han was worried sick.
Where's Seo Hui Soo?
She's at Bang Joon Seok's residence.
We'll soon be there, so keep an eye on her. And Se Hoon?
He's not here.
- Why not? - He's trying to save you.
What do you mean?
Isn't it obvious? He's trying to be a good partner.
(Despicable Serial Killer Suspect Dong Baek, Did He Fool the Nation?)
I see it was published by my agency.
You know it's not true.
I'm sorry.
All I'm asking for is the truth.
Just write about who Dong Baek truly is.
I have nothing to say.
Detective.
- The day I joined the force... - Thank you for the meal!
Enjoy, guys.
It's when I first met Dong Baek.
On days you need extra energy...
Here you go.
I got an odd feeling.
- This is amazing. - Tell me about it.
What kind of feeling?
He seemed lonely.
What about the last one we had?
Salute!
It's an honor to meet you.
May I shake your hand?
Sure.
I'm Officer Oh Se Hoon.
What is he doing?
(Oh Se Hoon)
Gosh.
People called me Nutjob Number Two,
but...
I just felt so bad for Baek.
Here. You can have it all.
Really? Thank you so much!
No one would let Baek by their side.
Still, he was loved by countless people.
Do you know why he thrives on people's attention?
It'd be a lie if I said he never liked it,
but he needed it because of the criminals' memories.
The criminals?
Because the evil memories...
never leave him...
once they enter his head.
The victims' pain and agony...
are somewhat consolidated once the culprit is caught.
But that is not the case for the criminals' memories.
They become more vivid.
What got him through the torture every time...
was the people's love and support.
- Hello. - Gosh, you're here.
- I'm Ji Min's father. - Oh, right.
Thank you so much.
If it weren't for you, Ji Min might not have made it.
Ji Min, go ahead and thank him.
- Thank you so much. - Thank you.
- I made these macarons for you. - I see.
- Thank you. - The tears of the ones he saved.
Thank you.
The letters wrote by the bereaved families.
He may seem cocky and overly confident,
but he fought this battle by letting his heart get blackened.
I was called by the disciplinary committee too.
But I honestly couldn't care less.
How can I serve the people when I can't even protect my own partner?
If Dong Baek is thrown under the bus in any way,
I'll quit being a cop too.
I'll stay by his side...
even if that costs me my badge.
Thank you for your time.
Seo Hui Soo hasn't left Bang Joon Seok's house yet.
You couldn't find either Chun Ki Soo or Moon Yong Gang?
I'll have to look again.
Actually, Metro is probably on it,
so focus on Lee Shin Woong's family first.
His family?
The Eraser has been targeting the family members...
of those involved in the Shimbae case.
He'll go after Deputy Chief Lee's family too.
What? Why?
He's the one who buried Moon Yong Dae's murder.
- Murder? - The seven who died...
in the warehouse were Moon Yong Dae's murderers.
- Are you sure? - Moon Yong Dae died...
just before the seven died.
And there are commonalities between the incidents.
- Deputy Chief Lee? - No.
Chun Ki Soo.
Chun Ki Soo bribed a doctor...
and made her declare Moon Yong Dae's death a suicide.
He buried the mass murder in the warehouse as well.
My head's spinning.
But that's not enough to connect him.
The night the seven died,
Deputy Chief Lee was being held captive in that warehouse.
He was fated to be killed by the Eraser, but he escaped.
Chun Ki Soo was disciplined for bribery 20 years ago,
but he succeeded quickly and held high positions in HQ.
Deputy Chief Lee backed him.
They're in this together.
So, seven rich kids killed Moon Yong Dae,
and Deputy Chief Lee had Chun Ki Soo cover it up.
Moon Yong Gang, his brother, found out the truth,
and killed all seven kids who killed his brother. But...
that rage hasn't subsided even 20 years later,
so he became the Eraser...
and is harassing Deputy Chief Lee's and Chun Ki Soo's families.
Even if Moon Yong Gang is not the Eraser, he's working with him.
Why do you want to meet Seo Hui Soo?
We should catch Moon Yong Gang.
- It's a shortcut to catch him. - A shortcut?
Take Se Hoon and go to Deputy Chief Lee's home.
He'll show up near his family for sure.
Okay, yes, sir. Work hard.
Where's Moon Yong Gang?
How would I...
What are you doing? Put down the knife.
You moved first.
You stepped toward the stairs first, so that he could escape.
You're dating, aren't you?
No, we're not.
He used you.
He did not.
He's not like that.
Never.
It was to commit murder.
You know something.
What is it?
Moon Yong Gang is attacking people to kill for his revenge.
This is our only chance to stop him.
Where is he hiding?
We don't have time.
The resort.
The resort?
I beg you. Please save Yong Gang.
I'm begging you.
Wait.
Put men behind like last time.
They're Intelligence.
- Intelligence? - Lee Shin Woong's stooge.
He's the one who took the photos...
when I assaulted Choi Poong Won.
To get rid of you.
He knew Moon Yong Gang was hiding here.
No.
Moon Yong Gang isn't here to hide.
He's here to kill his next target.
- What's the boundary situation? - We blocked the entire floor.
- And the security office? - Four men are guarding it.
2 Intelligence agents and 2 security guards.
Double it.
Block external access to the security cameras.
- It may be hacked. - Yes, sir.
Get off your phone.
Dad. I'm getting cabin fever.
What's going on?
Just a minute.
(Restricted Number)
Hello?
The Eraser will target your family.
What?
You're next since you bribed Chun Ki Soo.
Did Baek say that? That he'll kill me next?
You should work with us if you want to protect your family.
Sun Mi. You don't get it yet, do you?
What the yardstick is for measuring...
how properly a person has lived.
It's the depth of power they can get to help protect their people.
I will protect my family.
Sir.
The Eraser will come here.
He's the Eraser, so who?
I see. His accomplice.
Cuff him and lock him up next door.
We'll interrogate him along with Moon Yong Gang.
- Yes, sir. - You'll regret it.
The lights.
What's going on out there?
We're checking now.
What's going on?
- He's here. - He's quicker than I expected.
He prepared gas.
"Gas"?
It's what doctors use for surgery.
Sleeping gas.
Don't scan him!
Baek.
Are you awake?
What? What happened?
What do you think? I'll end up getting fired for this.
Captain Koo brought you guys here.
Hey! Stop!
Hey!
What?
- You lost them? - Sorry, sir. I woke up too late.
What about Moon Yong Gang?
He's fine. The guys took him to the hospital.
I want everyone on standby to work on this case.
And tell the guys at the hospital to come back.
Okay, sir.
Let's start by interrogating Moon Yong Gang.
Got it, sir.
They're not on the same side?
No, let's reinforce security first.
This is a trick.
We need to go back. Get in the car. Hurry!
You should leave now.
Excuse me.
Sir?
Don't move.
Where are you?
- Moon Yong Gang was bait. - What?
The Eraser is going to kill your son!
No!
Romeo got injured. Don't let anyone in or out of the building.
The moment anyone sees the suspect, shoot him without hesitation.
- There will be no limits. - Baek.
Use whatever violence you can to capture Dong Baek and the suspect.
Will...
Will our son be okay?
My goodness. Oh, gosh.
He's still getting surgery, but the doctor says he'll live.
Fortunately, he missed the vital point.
"Fortunately"?
He nailed 20 nails on my son's body.
You think that's fortunate?
If my son dies,
you'll die as well.
I swear on my life...
that I'll catch him no matter what.
The culprit is someone else.
The guys who killed Moon Yong Dae.
There were more than seven.
There were eight guys in total.
Bang Joon Seok.
We finally solved the puzzle.
Ji Eun, what are you doing here?
Are you deaf?
What's wrong with a reporter coming to the news department?
I'm no longer going to take unreasonable orders from you.
What are you talking about? The country is in a mess.
I can't believe this.
- What's going on? - This is crazy.
Is it the Eraser again?
Is this for real?
- I can't believe this is happening. - It's absurd.
My goodness.
Please wait here for a moment.
Eun Soo Kyung, former congressman Bang Joon Seok's wife,
has been kidnapped by an unidentified assailant.
The kidnapper sent us a photo of Eun Soo Kyung...
holding a message that seemed like a forewarning.
Reporter Gong Cheon Mi will be reporting to us exclusively.
Please.
I'm six months pregnant.
I don't care if I die.
But please don't hurt my baby.
Detective Dong.
Please save my daughter, Soo Kyung.
Please. Please.
(Jeon Woo Jung)
My daughter did nothing wrong.
- I know you can save her. - Ma'am, please get up.
I know you can save my daughter.
My daughter...
is a fan of yours.
You have no idea how fond she is of you.
She wants nothing but the best for you.
So, please...
Please save my daughter and Cho Won.
Who?
- Cho Won? - We should go.
Cho Won...
It's the name of my daughter's unborn child.
You must find her.
Must find...
Cho Won...
Please save my daughter.
Please save my daughter, Detective Dong.
- Please save my daughter. - We should leave.
- Ma'am, please. - My daughter...
Please save my daughter!
It wasn't him.
- What? - The root of all evil.
It wasn't Bang Joon Seok.
- What are you saying? - The one that connects everything.
The killer who had Moon Yong Dae's death buried.
The Eraser's ultimate target.
The one who killed Jin Jae Gyu's mother...
and tore his life apart.
His half-sister.
What grudge is the Eraser harboring?
He appeared after using Moon Yong Gang as bait.
Your son? We're just getting started.
- What started this tragedy... - That's where the clue lies.
The one after Mr. Bang is the Eraser!
Everyone that is a threat to Assemblyman Bang...
must be eliminated.
Get him. Use any means necessary.
Give him a chance.
Give Detective Dong a chance to find the key piece of evidence.