(All characters, organizations, places, and events are fictional.)
It's the smell.
The smell of death.
This place reeks of it even at this very moment.
Do it now. Shoot! Hurry up and shoot!
Do you want to die?
Shoot!
Shoot him now! Don't care about me! Just hurry up and shoot!
Seal all the entrances and take the stairs.
You have no idea...
how much I missed you.
You got shot, so take off your mask and say hello.
Where are your manners? Let's see what you've got.
I'll aim properly this time.
I'm impressed. You win.
If you admit that you lost, get down on your knees.
Why weren't you able to do anything...
when your mom died right in front of your eyes?
Who are you?
Do you even remember how your mom died?
"Mom. Mom."
Mom.
You son of a gun.
I remember it very clearly.
You cried like a little baby in front of your dying mother.
Do me a favor.
Don't bother putting on those handcuffs.
and make a run for it.
I urge you to.
(SWAT)
Do not forget...
my last words.
Don't use your energy to talk and stay awake.
You must find it.
Don't forget...
the meadow...
(SWAT)
The meadow...
The meadow?
He fell from the roof. Send units to the back door!
The target is at the back door on the first floor.
He's in a SWAT officer's uniform.
To the first floor.
The suspect is dressed as one of us. All officers, take off your mask.
We lost them. The target and Detective Dong.
I'll take responsibility.
Responsibility?
Just know this.
No one will be able to take responsibility for this.
Even our dismissal from the force...
won't be enough to avoid the back blast.
(Memorist)
(Ep. 11, A Deep Wound)
(TVC takes the righteous path to bring you fair telecasts.)
A suspect in police custody died.
The serial killer, the Eraser.
Those two phrases must be aired.
Contact all your sources from the police department...
and draw help from our other departments.
This must be the headline news.
Which should we go after first?
The Metropolitan Investigation Unit, of course.
Make sure to add Dong Baek's name though.
Paint a picture of how this is all because of people...
like Dong Baek.
Sorry I'm late. Sorry.
You!
- Yes? - Who said you could come in?
Me?
Did she do as the director asked?
You're banned from the newsroom.
But...
Everyone said that Detective Dong is done for anyway...
- since he'll be found guilty... - So what?
Who do you think you are to make these decisions?
I apologize, sir.
Until you find hard evidence to bring Dong Baek down,
you are not to step foot in here again.
Now get lost!
(Captain Koo Kyung Tan)
(Officer Oh Se Hoon)
(Word Puzzles)
He's learning at a fast pace...
and his habits are still there.
Why won't he talk though?
He's probably experiencing an identity crisis.
He'll need time to adjust to this.
I'm sorry that I have to say this,
but he's an interesting subject from a researcher's perspective.
And that's why I won't stop trying to help him.
Thank you.
(Word Puzzles)
(The Executioner Dies in Police Custody)
He was murdered while in police custody,
but the police weren't able to identify the suspect...
or find even a clue as to who he can be.
Jin Jae Gyu, the deceased,
was the prime suspect of the Executioner serial murders...
that occurred 20 years ago.
He hurt himself during the trial validating his warrant...
and was murdered while being treated in the hospital.
There are only speculations of him...
murdering six victims including cult leader Park Ki Dan...
and former TBC president Jo Sung Dong.
No hard evidence has linked him to those cases.
Meanwhile, the so-called Eraser...
was once suspected as Mr. Jin's accomplice,
but the murder of Mr. Jin...
has kicked the case up in the air according to sources...
close to the police force.
An anonymous source...
informed us that Detective Dong was present at the scene too.
A high-ranking official within the police force...
The police weren't able to prevent the murder...
of a suspect who was in their custody.
During this morning's press briefing,
the police released an absurd statement...
about the Eraser who killed Jin Jae Gyu...
also being someone with supernatural powers.
But just two hours later, they changed their stance and...
- recanted their earlier statement. - I knew it.
Did they change their statement once again?
- How many times does this make? - The police...
- are once again scrambling. - They'll catch no one at this rate.
This fact has the public outraged...
and many are saying...
that lives are being lost due to their incompetency.
Hundred of thousands of citizens...
- I knew it. - Tell me about it!
Are you here to serve a search and seizure warrant?
- Is it because of Jin Jae Gyu? - Who is the suspect?
- Is it the entire unit? - Which office are you from?
- Northern Prosecutors' Office? - The Special Investigations Unit?
- Who is the suspect? - Let me through.
- Make way! - Please say a few words.
- Sir! - Any words?
(Metropolitan Investigation Unit)
Everyone, stop what you're doing.
As of this moment, your hands will not touch your desk.
Stay put. Hey, you!
Don't touch anything.
Don't touch anything. Don't you dare.
What is the meaning of this?
Isn't it obvious? This is a search and seizure.
Not even a single piece of paper can leave this room.
Move away from your desks immediately.
- Watch your manners. - Bite me.
- What? No, don't stop me. - Hey...
A prosecutor has no right to treat us this way.
And who said you can talk back to a managing prosecutor?
Abuse of power in this day and age?
(Search and Seizure Warrant)
I didn't know you were here.
Your team must be taught manners.
Do what you came here to do and leave.
You brought this on your team.
You let Jin Jae Gyu die in your custody.
- Then arrest me. - That doesn't sound so bad.
What did I tell you about being careful?
What is the meaning of this?
Deputy Chief Lee.
We finally meet.
What brings you here, Mr. Woo Seok Do?
I'm honored...
that you recognize a lowly managing prosecutor...
whom your underlings disrespect.
How could I not know the next Public Prosecutor General?
You were promoted to the Central Prosecutors' Office.
You survived Im Joong Yeon's scandal unscathed.
I forgot a warrant.
- Mr. Kim. - Yes, sir.
Go to the courthouse and get another warrant.
Include the deputy chief's office in the search.
What do you think you're doing?
- Should we talk in my office? - Why? Scared?
Why you little...
I understand you are passionate,
but you should show dignity.
We prosecutors don't care about dignity...
in front of suspects like them.
He isn't worth your time, sir.
- What? - Want to make a bet?
That you leave empty-handed...
Is that a joke?
I heard you were present last time...
when they came to arrest Detective Dong Baek.
- Move. - Hold on.
This isn't the time...
What about it?
You must know what the problem is.
I do not.
I won't make an issue of it if you leave quietly.
I can't do that.
Send them the documents they need later.
- Yes, sir. - You're quite the comedian.
You'll take responsibility...
for assaulting a suspect, is that it?
(Assaulting a suspect is punishable by up to 5 years in prison.)
And you have proof?
Shall we make a bet...
whether I'm bluffing without evidence,
or whether I have a high-resolution video?
There's no way you do,
but do you think they'd care even if you did?
True. The prosecutors solely have the authority...
to indict a suspect.
However, if that heinous video were aired on the news,
even if you evade indictment,
you'll lose your job for sure.
Prosecutors...
who get involved in scandals end up going into the private sector.
Are you challenging me?
Want to make a bet?
Whether you'll leave quietly,
or whether we'll duke it out, no-holds barred?
Pull out.
Excuse me?
- Remove the boxes. - Yes, sir.
You're just as I've heard.
I'll be seeing you again soon.
I'm sorry, sir.
Report to the Prosecutors' Office.
Resign before then.
I will, but please give me one week to investigate first.
- No, just three days... - Han Sun Mi.
- Yes, sir. - Do you know...
the top cause of the death of soldiers during a war?
Stupid leaders.
Just like you.
The Metropolitan Investigation Unit was humiliated because of you.
No. The entire police department.
And yet, you still can't let go?
You're a lawyer even if you quit, but not the others.
It's my duty to make sure they can feed their families.
If you keep resisting and holding on regardless,
Young Soo will be fired too. Is that what you want?
No, sir.
If you understood,
act accordingly.
You're home late.
Did you read my door code too?
What else did you peek at from my memories?
What do you take me for?
The four keys have your prints all over them.
You're such a careless profiler.
Stop scowling, will you?
I came because I was worried that the Eraser would be after you.
Once I die, everyone will know who the Eraser is.
You know you don't need to worry, so leave.
I have nowhere to go.
Woo Seok Do put out an APB on me, so they're at my home and at hotels.
He killed my mother.
I remember it very clearly.
You cried like a little baby in front of your dying mother.
I don't care who dies. I'm going to see an end to this.
How will you see an end to it?
He has been killing only infamous villains like the Executioner.
- But? - There was one exception.
Shimbae.
The decisive clue is in the Shimbae incident.
The reason the Eraser had to kill seven people.
Once I find that reason,
we'll be able to uncover the Eraser's real identity,
and why he had to kill them even if it meant revealing his power.
I need your help.
I've been kicked out...
thanks to somebody losing the perp.
You're the one who lost him.
I risked my life and chased him.
It's my fault for trusting you.
Such an attitude. Anyway.
What I need isn't your title,
but your brain.
Didn't you say your brain was the best in the world?
Of course, I'm as smart as Sherlock Holmes.
But you have your strengths too.
For example?
Knowledge of criminal law which I do not have.
And logical reasoning using an exceptional brain.
Do you admit I'm top-notch?
I'm saying you have strengths and weaknesses.
Jin Jae Gyu made a dying statement.
What?
The Eraser is hiding...
in Dong Baek's past.
What past?
The past?
Is that all?
All the leads led to dead ends.
Along with my childhood memories that I lost.
Anyway, what we need to dig into isn't my past,
but the Shimbae incident.
Do you really think that's the past where the Eraser is hiding?
If he meant your mom's death,
it would be meaningless since we all know about it.
- But... - But?
From what I saw...
Don't care about me! Just hurry up and shoot!
He wouldn't leave behind a meaningless dying message.
It looks like you're empathizing...
with Jin Jae Gyu's death.
The pain you had to go through...
is part of my karma.
He might be...
referring to a memory that was never erased.
So you're saying the Eraser might exist...
in my memory?
Does that even make sense?
You either didn't notice because it was so common.
- Or... - Or what?
Or it was too shocking...
that you failed to notice the surroundings.
That's where the Eraser is hiding.
I failed to notice...
because it was too shocking?
(8 years ago)
A shocking moment...
that made me forget about everything else.
The rooftop I went to when I was 19.
Can you do it somewhere else?
I heard taking off your shoes is a message...
asking people to notice your death.
Is that what it is?
No, that's not it.
Can you do it somewhere else? This is my spot.
Ms. Han, Dong Baek has put you through a lot, hasn't he?
You punk. Look how exhausted she is because of you.
He really has a way of tiring people out.
- You haven't eaten yet, have you? - Were you being tailed?
- No, of course not. - We're professionals.
Can you explain this situation?
You didn't ask her for permission?
I was just about to ask, but you suddenly showed up.
Ms. Han, we have new information.
Yes, we have important information.
I'm so starving.
So I forgot to tell you.
Excuse me.
It's an emergency situation.
We checked the people who died at Shimbae City.
Not everyone lived at Shimbae City,
and they were all going to different universities.
So it's weird that they all died on the same day and time.
And?
But they all had something in common.
- What's that? - Private tutoring.
It turns out they received private tutoring in a small group...
ever since they were in kindergarten.
Our team already knew that.
- That's amazing. - I see.
The family of the deceased are all pretty rich and powerful.
But none of them were willing to answer our questions.
- Why not? - How would I know?
So what is it that you found out?
Baek, isn't it weird?
They were only 20 years old, and 7 of them died.
But not a single family complained about their deaths.
And?
But there was one guy that caught my eye among the seven kids.
(Personal Details of the Deceased)
- "So Philip"? - Yes.
I remembered where I saw that name.
- Where? - Don't you remember?
You asked me and Captain Koo to find information on the cold case.
- The SMPA archives? - Yes.
I saw his name on one of the official documents.
(Suffocated to death, So Philip and 6 more)
It's an unusual name.
"So Philip".
(Special Investigations Unit for Cold Cases)
But it doesn't make sense.
No one did an internal investigation regarding the Shimbae City case.
Then why did they ask for the internal investigation results?
That means someone erased...
all the remaining traces of the investigation.
You need to be really brave...
to have the guts to erase police records.
I wonder what it was that the person was trying to hide.
"Chun Ki Soo"?
You're Kim So Mi?
The girl from six years ago?
What an interesting connection.
The team leader back then was a guy I know named Chun Ki Soo.
Old Man, you told me you know him, right?
I called him earlier, but he told me he took the day off.
So I agreed to meet him tomorrow morning.
Do you think he got rid of the investigation records?
We'll find out.
Maybe he was onto something.
Let's see how much of this he knows.
Good job.
Gosh, you're embarrassing me.
What about me?
What do you say? How about a joint investigation?
You guys can stay just for tonight.
Without her, we can't call ourselves the Avengers.
Oh, no.
Stop. No.
Help me.
Why do you keep following me around?
I didn't follow you around.
You're so lame.
Don't... Don't do it.
What?
Don't try to hurt yourself.
Hurt myself?
What a joke.
I'm not like you who tries to kill himself.
Stop following me and go home.
I know you also tried to jump a few times.
What?
You tried to die.
Did you ever see me try?
I scanned your memory.
You don't look like it, but you're really a jerk.
Go hit on the girls who go to the same school.
I know you were abused.
What?
You were saved right before you died and got adopted.
And you're still suppressed by that memory.
Who told you that?
Baek.
Baek. Baek.
Wake up.
- What's wrong? - Mr. Chun got into an accident.
What accident?
I don't know. We'll have to see.
Are you going somewhere?
- I'll go with you. - So is this a joint investigation?
Okay. Let's go, Avengers.
(Chun K Soo)
Sir.
What happened?
I can't remember anything because of my concussion.
What?
No matter how hard I try,
I can't remember his face.
He's fast asleep. Training must've drained his energy.
Sure, I'll be there shortly.
Our son is in the car, so of course I'm driving safely.
What do you take me for?
Do you remember the fried chicken he likes?
You could order that.
Sure. See you soon.
Her and her nagging.
Joon Young,
are you all right?
Joon Young, stay with me.
No, don't. Stay with me.
Joon Young!
Stay with me.
Son, stay with me!
Joon Young, stay with me.
Joon Young!
Joon Young, no.
Help us. My son's in the backseat!
Joon Young!
Please help my son.
Joon Young... No, get my son first.
No, my son. Joon Young!
No...
What are you doing? Someone's still in the car.
Someone's in the back seat.
My son's inside. Get him out!
Joon Young!
Joon Young, no.
I can't remember...
his face though.
Scan my memory so that you can catch him.
Do you have a headache?
No, it's nothing. I'm fine.
Joon Young, no.
Joon Young!
The Eraser!
The Eraser?
The murder who kills scumbags?
Why...
Why would he kill my son then?
He was a sweet boy.
He couldn't even kill an insect.
I'll rip him to pieces.
I'll kill him myself.
Hand it over.
That thing in your pocket.
His pocket?
What is this?
- His jacket button. - What are you doing?
He ripped it off and swallowed it.
Just find me any lead...
and I'll kill him myself.
I see a shape.
A shape?
It looks like a flame.
I think I know what it is.
What is this?
It must be a torch at the center of the petals.
I see it now.
Talk to me.
Did you cross-check?
Okay, good job.
The logo belongs to the fire department.
The fire department?
The torch at the center of a rose of Sharon borne by a bird.
It's the core of the fire department's logo.
How on earth do you know all this?
It's all thanks to the crime data center.
Does such a thing exist in Korea?
One is being established.
We're in luck to get that kind of help.
I'm the one who's been establishing it.
This is why we can't help but admire you, Ms. Han.
This is what you call the beauty of being clever.
Which alphabets are on it?
S and B.
There are a total of eight units in the fire department...
with the initials S and B including district stations.
There's no need to narrow it down though.
- It's that place. - That plce?
Where he first appeared. That's where he's been hiding.
- What? - What?
Let's see what's in store for us there.
What about Chun Ki Soo's other memories?
Was it really him who covered up the incident 20 years ago?
Why did the Eraser torch his son though?
- I don't know. - You don't know?
Did you only manage to see last night's events then?
Is something wrong with your head these days?
Should I contact the medical team?
Mind your own business.
But what if you pass out again?
Let him exhaust himself if that's what he wants.
Just know that everyone can die at any time.
Shouldn't we ask Mr. Chun about the case files again?
Have you become a psychopath?
How can we question a man who just lost his only son?
But this case is more urgent.
We're off to find answers right now, aren't we?
I'm sure we'll find a lead of some sort.
I can't believe you called me a psychopath.
(Shimbae Fire Station)
Let's go.
We have a special guest, so hurry up with the big welcome.
- Yes, sir. - I'm afraid we're in a hurry.
Things are urgent, so let us ask a few questions.
Could you take a look at this, please?
It's a button.
What kind of a button is it?
It's key evidence in a pressing case...
and the logo on it belongs to Shimbae Fire Station.
- A case? - A murder case.
- Sorry? - This isn't one of ours.
It came off a sleeve, so maybe your full-dress uniform or...
Over there.
There aren't any buttons here.
- The ceremonial uniform. - The ceremonial uniform?
It's on the uniform given to those...
who served the department for 20 years.
Yes, you're right.
Could we get a list of everyone who received the uniform?
Everyone gets a set after 20 years.
Let us check your list of employees.
Sure.
Sir, how long have you worked here at Shimbae Fire Station?
About 30 years.
Do you remember the abandoned warehouse from 20 years ago...
where victims suffocated in?
The one that took the lives of college students?
- So you know. - Of course. It was a big one.
Why didn't it make the headlines though?
I believe the bereaved families stopped it from being reported.
It would've made the news even more...
considering how the victims came from wealthy families.
There was this rumor.
A rumor?
Rumor had it that the kids did drugs.
Drugs?
Narcotics.
Is Detective Dong really here?
- Yes. - What for?
Remember the ceremonial uniform given to long-term firefighters?
The suit was found at a scene of a murder.
What? Our uniform?
Didn't you receive it too?
I lost it. I took it in for dry-cleaning,
but it got lost there.
The deceased youngsters got high, lost their minds,
and beat each other to death?
But the cause of death...
was reported as carbon monoxide poisoning.
They did die after breathing in the smoke from the campfire,
but many say that was only because they were high.
They got high and killed each other, but it was buried.
Here you go.
Including myself, 9 people were with the department for 20 years.
(Yoon Soon Nam, M, Park Chang Won, M)
There are six if you eliminate women.
May we meet with them?
Only three of them are here. The others are off today.
What is it?
Dong Baek's location was posted on social media.
He's at Shimbae Fire Department. We'll be there in five minutes.
Don't you dare lose him.
We'll get him no matter what.
Step on it.
(Lee Shin Woong)
(Kim Do Soo - Intelligence Dept)
- Hello? - Inspector Kim Do Soo...
of Intelligence reporting in as ordered.
Detective Dong Baek is currently at Shimbae Fire Station.
Shimbae Fire Station?
Yes, sir. The prosecutor is coming to arrest him.
- Keep marking him. - Yes, sir.
Clear my schedule for the rest of the day.
Yes, sir.
Poisonous gas leak at a factory in Shimpan-dong.
Rescue One. Rescue One head out.
Sorry.
You'll have to wait.
Do you not remember anything else from that incident?
Not really. It was so long ago.
That's right.
Never mind. It's nothing.
Please tell us. Anything.
I heard that a police officer was already there...
before...
our fire fighters arrived.
And?
He didn't do anything,
and just fled by himself.
Why?
He probably didn't want to get involved.
Was it a police car from a precinct?
I don't think so.
- Who saw that officer? - What?
Well... So... I'm not sure.
Why?
Only the fire department was notified.
The police weren't notified at all.
So it was only natural for the firefighters to arrive first.
Once the fire department is called, the police are called automatically.
But it wasn't a patrol car.
You're right.
The police could not have been faster than the fire department.
If he got there first...
Was that cop...
the Eraser?
If the Eraser is a cop, everything falls into place.
Was he able to erase all the records because he's a cop?
You're right.
The Eraser?
Hold on.
What about the button?
What?
We're here because of the button from a firefighter's suit...
that the Eraser was wearing.
If the Eraser isn't a firefighter,
but the cop who was seen at the abandoned warehouse.
Then who's the firefighter whose suit he was wearing?
That Eraser jerk...
stole a firefighter's suit and wore it intentionally. Why?
I don't understand what you're talking about.
Who was the person who saw that police officer?
- Please forget I said anything... - This is very important.
He was from a rescue team.
Noh Kwan Kyu, the rescue team captain?
Captain Noh?
I just asked him, and...
I lost it.
I dropped it off at the cleaners, and they lost it.
He said he lost the suit.
Where is he now?
He probably went to the scene.
He's in danger.
The suit the Eraser wore...
was bait.
The next murder victim.
Order Captain Noh to return immediately.
- What do you mean? - I don't know,
but the detectives say you're in danger and to return immediately.
What stupid nonsense is that?
If they need to talk to me, tell them to come here.
Okay. You will be forgiven if you fail to rescue victims,
but you will not be forgiven if you get hurt. Got it?
- Yes, sir! - Yes, sir!
His life is in danger!
He never leaves the scene first.
We'll go to him.
Chun Ki Soo led the investigation of the Shimbae warehouse case...
in which the Eraser killed 7 people 20 years ago.
That's right.
When he burned Chun Ki Soo's son to death,
the Eraser stole and wore what was probably Noh Kwan Kyu's suit.
- Then that was... - He was announcing his next murder.
That he'll kill the owner of the suit?
Eliminating a witness.
Captain Noh Kwan Kyu saw an unidentified police officer...
during the abandoned warehouse incident.
The real Eraser, who had arrived before he did.
So he's trying to get rid of him because he's a witness.
We need to find him and read his memory...
Freeze!
Baek, go ahead. Let's use our bodies to stop them.
We'll sacrifice our bodies.
See you soon.
Hey, you! Stop right there!
Stop, you jerk!
Stop the search. Let's pull out.
Victim needing rescue on the second floor, north side.
The second floor, north side. A victim requested a rescue.
This is the captain. I'm on the second floor.
- I'll go myself. - Copy that.
Help me.
Are you okay?
Captain.
Captain!
Darn it. I'm going back in.
Give me a new oxygen tank!
There he is!
Captain.
- Remove his belt. - Captain.
Giving him mouth-to-mouth now.
Captain! Sir!
Baek.
Baek, are you okay?
You lunatic! Why did you go in there?
He's... He's there.
- What? - He's... He's still nearby.
Hurry. Hurry!
What are you trying to do?
His memory from 20 years ago.
- Hurry! - Let's go!
Let's get going!
No, wait!
Be careful.
No, wait. Wait.
- Wait. - Watch out.
Wait. No.
Detective Dong?
We're the police. This is an emergency.
His vitals are back to normal.
Detective Dong, you're not well.
Just forget it!
(20 years ago, April, 2000)
Are you okay?
Hey!
Hey, are you okay?
Can you please call for backup?
Hello?
(Shim Sang Ah)
The Eraser.
He has a big scar on his right arm.
His right arm? Did you see his face?
No.
He was wearing a mask, so I couldn't see his face.
Your nose is bleeding.
He has a big... A big scar.
Detective Dong! Detective Dong!
Stay still.
Who do you think you are?
What? What's your problem?
Honey, put the laundry in the washing machine.
Detective Dong!
(Memorist)
(Epilogue)
Kim Yong Jin.
Jo Yeon Gyeong.
Lee Ho Rim.
Park Seung Hwan.
Lee Jun.
Lee Su Hyeon.
Park Hwan Uk.
Yoo Chang Hoon.
Kim Sang Soo.
Oh Gyeong Hoon.
Jo In Hye.
Jang Seok Chan.
Lee Geon Woo. Park Seong Min.
Lee Sang Hoon.
Kim Tae Hyeon.
Lee Jun Woo.
These 17 people...
died because of you, Dad.
They died because of us.
Dad, I know you can't say anything.
And I know you guys can't hear this.
But I'm still very sorry.
He loved justifying his murders, but that's not how he kills anymore.
- The innocent will be crucified. - On behalf of the sinner.
His purpose was to murder people.
Chun Ki Soo is the connection.
Who are you?
Your savior. The person who can save your son.
- Chun Ki Soo disappeared. - There isn't a single trace.
He was after the Eraser.
- What? - I saw the scar on his right arm.
- Who was that? - You were the Eraser.
You were at Shimbae City 20 years ago!