(All characters, organizations, places, and events are fictional.)
(April 19, 2000)
They're dead.
The doctor and psychiatrist assigned to Yoo Ah Young.
- So? - Ma'am,
there's this.
It seems like Yoo Ah Young sent a parcel to a friend before dying.
Her doctor and psychiatrist suddenly dying makes sense...
if someone figured out about them being bought.
Get rid of them.
Any soul, old or young, who speaks about this...
must die.
Yes, ma'am.
And Joon Seok's plans to study abroad?
Preparations are thoroughly being made.
(Son Soo Yeon)
Ms. Han.
(NIS Report, Sung Ju Ran)
- What's this? - A report on a telepath.
(Identity Report: Sung Ju Ran)
(Sibling: Sung Ju Ho)
Someone other than Dong Baek who has supernatural powers.
We believe this person to be...
Excuse me for a second.
- Hello? - Ms. Son, Detective Dong's gone.
What are you talking about?
Hurry and track down Detective Dong's whereabouts.
Have you known all along?
No, we don't have all the pieces to the puzzle yet.
So that person is the Eraser?
That's what we believe.
Then tell me everything you people know.
Seo Hui Soo.
I will start by telling you the truth.
My little brother.
(Memorist: Final episode, The Power of Memories)
I knew you weren't sane, but not to this extent.
We hung around here a lot...
when you were very young.
You were adorable back then.
What a load of crap.
Although, the last memory you have of this place...
is probably painful.
Seo Hui Soo.
I understand your denial,
but you'll soon believe what's true,
Dong Baek. I mean,
Sung Ju Ho.
Scan my memories if you wish.
How can I trust you though?
I had countless opportunities to hurt you.
The memories you want back.
Mom...
The memories you lost.
I'll return them all.
Go ahead.
- A police officer? - No way. How did you know?
I know everything, little brother.
- Mom! - You're back.
- Mom, you won't believe it. - What?
Ju Ran knew everything before I even told her.
I never told her that I wanted to be a police officer,
but she knew.
Ju Ran...
Okay, that's great. So wash up and get ready for dinner.
All right.
This too.
Don't forget to eat your meat too.
Yes, don't be a picky eater.
- I'm not a picky eater. - Aren't you?
No, Ju Ran's just making stuff up.
(With BFF Ah Young)
(Sung Ju Ho, Sung Ju Ran, Mom)
(Happy birthday, big sister. From Ju Ho)
(Welcome to Ah Young's website!)
(Is it true that you're dating Yong Dae?)
(Ah Young, what's up?)
(Are you ghosting me now?)
(Why aren't you picking up?)
(Ah Young?)
(Moon Yong Dae can't be reached either.)
(Did something happen to you guys?)
(Ah Young, call me when you see this.)
What's going on?
(Incoming call)
- Ju Ran... - Ah Young?
Is that you?
Help me.
Yes, it's me.
That's right.
Ah Young.
What's going on?
Don't come any closer.
You can talk from there.
What's wrong?
Did you get what I asked for?
Leave it and go.
Just go.
Something...
bad happened, right?
If you want, I can erase the memories.
- Bad memories are better gone... - Ju Ran.
Erasing my memories...
won't erase what happened.
I think that's when I finally realized it.
I should be erasing people,
not memories with my powers.
I'm sorry.
And...
thank you, Ju Ran.
(Shimbae High School, May your soul rest in peace)
(Funeral hall)
You know Moon Yong Dae, right? But he died. He committed suicide.
Remember that place where you had fun with those guys?
I wonder if he saw something there.
Imagine how sad your dad will be if he finds out.
Yoo Ah Young killed herself.
Wrap up the case neatly...
so that no one finds out about the rape.
- Don't worry, sir. - And Moon Yong Dae?
We're keeping an eye on him.
That's how I knew who I had to kill.
Is that why you started to kill people and took revenge?
"Revenge"?
That's not what this is.
I'm doing what I should with my abilities.
It's sort of like bringing justice.
And what that honorable justice brought you is insanity?
Justice goes hand-in-hand with pain.
You know...
that every time you use your ability to do good,
you get hurt.
What about Jin Jae Gyu?
He had nothing to do with this.
He was already doing the right thing as the Executioner.
He was keeping tabs on Bang Joon Seok's evil deeds...
in order to protect his daughter.
There were plenty of reasons to work with him.
There was a reason for the pain that followed.
You're home.
Just how you and I have, and just how you and I suffered.
That's right.
Ju Ran!
A box came for you. I opened it, but I didn't look inside.
Get out!
(From Yoo Ah Young)
If you want to save your daughter, bring me Lee Shin Woong.
You dare abduct a high-ranking police officer?
Hush.
(April 20, 2000, 8:11pm Abandoned warehouse in Shimbae)
Why did you tell us to come here?
What is it?
Where's Bang Joon Seok?
What's your deal? Do you like him?
- Where is he? - He's studying abroad.
Really?
What a shame.
You promised us something fun.
You're dead if it isn't.
It will be fun.
(April 20, 2000, 8:36pm Dong Baek's house)
(214-12 Simpan-2-dong, Shimbae City)
Gosh.
Mommy! Ju Ran isn't here!
Really? She didn't say she was going out.
Ju Ho, close the door.
The box!
I am Yoo Ah Young.
This is my testimony...
- Ju Ho. I said not to go in. - and dying message.
On February 9, 2000,
on a hill just outside of Shimbae,
Bang Joon Seok, So Phillip, and eight others...
raped me viciously.
The police officer Chun Ki Soo...
harassed me.
Who are you?
Mommy!
What is this place? Why is it so dirty?
- Gosh. - Hey.
- What could there be here? - I removed all of their memories...
- and left them only fear. - Let's just go.
Mommy...
Mommy!
Mom.
Why...
Let him go.
Ju Ho.
Ju Ran.
Why are you here?
Ju Ran, Mommy...
Ju Ho.
Go...
Go to Mr. Eun Gon's house.
I'll be right there, okay?
The one who erased your memories of that night...
was you.
You have the same abilities I do.
You can read memories, erase them,
and manipulate them as you please.
It's an incredible ability.
We've located Sung Ju Ran.
So you've been keeping her in custody ever since then?
What do you mean?
It was more like a cooperation.
Sung Ju Ran knew...
that killing them wasn't enough...
to take revenge.
Because of our powers,
we went through things we never had to go through.
What's the point of having supernatural powers...
when we can't even use it to achieve justice?
If we can't punish the bad guys,
what's the point of having these powers?
Humans are weak.
That's why they invented the law.
They thought it would help them achieve justice.
But you saw...
how the law is used.
It only helps those who have power.
We don't need...
to rely on something so useless.
Don't you agree?
You do it.
No.
I won't.
Just because I fight against scumbags...
doesn't mean I need to become one as well.
Ju Ran, no...
You're...
wrong.
You spent too much time reading the minds of monsters.
And that turned you into a monster as well.
You became a monster while fighting against them!
You think I became a monster myself while fighting against monsters?
Who do you think I fought against?
What exactly is a monster?
If I'm a monster, what does that make you?
If you think I'm a monster,
just kill me.
Kill me!
No!
How far are you going to go?
How can you do this?
What made you become like this?
Get to your senses!
People like you are so weak.
You can't do anything. You just suffer all the time.
That's what makes me strong!
Protecting people...
is what makes us strong.
We need to endure it until the end...
and make sure we don't get eaten up by their memories.
1, 2, 3.
- In a white canoe on a milky way - In a white canoe on a milky way
- Far beyond the blue sky - Far beyond the blue sky
- A cassia tree - A cassia tree
Where did you learn this?
Is that how you do it?
He's good.
What's that?
Is this it?
My goodness, good job.
Being able to remain as yourself...
is what proves how strong you really are.
My weak little brother.
Let's say the person who survives is the strong one.
Deal?
Sung Ju Ran, it's over. Stop.
"Stop"?
Stop what?
I'm not going to let you use me anymore.
No!
This is really bad.
It's not a bad injury.
She can live.
The injury isn't the problem.
She's very unstable just like you when you were hospitalized.
No, it's even worse.
She's dying.
I'll explain from there.
Will you please excuse us?
I'll go check on the patient.
The NIS has been in charge of supervising...
both you and your sister.
Let's just say we kept an eye on you.
We were encountered with something...
the whole world had never seen before.
Get to the point.
We kept your sister isolated for 20 years so we could protect her.
Her health deteriorated every time she used her power.
When she first came to our lab, her condition...
was out of control.
There wasn't anything we could do to protect her.
She was already in a serious state before things got this worse.
She's in her worst condition.
We can't be sure you'll experience the same thing she did.
So...
we'd like to protect you...
My sister and I never asked for your protection.
We're not this country's assets...
or monkeys in a zoo.
Let's negotiate.
I'll erase all the records regarding your sister.
"Negotiate"? No.
I'm going to blackmail you.
I've had a lot of physical contact with the NIS agents. Especially you.
Everyone around the world have their eyes on me.
What a great timing.
I'm guessing...
you want us to erase all our records regarding you and your sister.
That is above my paygrade.
I'll let your concerns be known though.
Since you don't care for negotiations,
let me blackmail you too.
All the information you retrieved...
must be taken to the grave regardless of what that may be.
Disclosing any of that information will put you in trouble...
on a national scale.
I don't trust a word you say,
but I'll try.
See? I told you this was a negotiation.
Then I'll uphold my end of the deal and get out of your sight.
The national petition moved the National Assembly...
and discussions of a special investigation...
are being held.
The fabricated investigation of the mass murder...
at an abandoned warehouse in Shimbae City 20 years ago...
was conducted by Deputy Chief Lee Shin Woong...
and the prosecution is focusing on him.
Back in 2000, Chun Ki Soo was bought off ...
- by Deputy Chief Lee. - They're throwing me out?
The prosecutors searched Chun Ki Soo's house...
- and announced... - To save themselves?
- to have claimed crucial evidence. - Dad?
- The evidence is predicted... - Tell me they're wrong about you.
to prove Deputy Chief Lee's crimes.
When Moon Yong Dae came to find Yoo Ah Young,
Bang Joon Seok beat him...
with a square bar embedded with nails.
He sprayed alcohol on him, made it catch fire,
and had him drop off a cliff.
In order to make his death look like a suicide,
Hwang Pil Seon conspired with Deputy Chief Lee...
Carry on.
Deputy Chief Lee bought Chun Ki Soo off...
and had him cover up Moon Yong Dae's case.
Captain Koo, can you hear me?
Just a second.
Over here, the patient is awake!
Se Hoon.
Do you recognize me?
Your wife just went to the convenience store.
And Dong Baek?
How is he?
Right. Well...
He's busy catching bad guys...
like always.
You're too sweet for your own good.
Sister.
It's been a while since you called me that.
You used to be a sweet person too.
I doubt you'll ever turn out like me though.
Why...
Why did you go to such lengths?
Such lengths?
Actually, I'm disappointed that I never...
got to do more.
You didn't have to kill everyone involved.
Who would've done it in my place then?
I'm still certain...
that had I not done what I did,
all those scumbags...
would be living their lives in peace.
But...
you could've taken another approach.
Yoo Ah Young left you her testimony...
and you could've used your ability to reveal the truth.
You...
should've made a better choice.
Ju Ho.
Memories don't hold any power.
People's memories...
are powerless.
Ah Young's memories...
and mine...
don't have the power to punish anyone.
All right. You don't have to say more.
Let me give you a memory...
that'll help you make up your mind.
Let me erase...
all your terrible memories.
The problem is this though.
There's enough circumstantial evidence...
to tie Bang Joon Seok to Moon Yong Dae's murder,
but there's no definitive proof.
He spent time abroad,
so the statute of limitations hasn't expired yet,
but we still won't be able to make an arrest.
When did we ever let that hinder us?
We should just do what we do best.
What about Deputy Chief Lee then?
First, arrest Kim Do Soo of the Intelligence Department.
- Yes, sir. - Yes, sir.
I was thinking about going to see Deputy Chief Lee.
Without a warrant?
There's something I need from him first.
I'd appreciate you still being polite though.
I'm asking you.
Got it.
- Are you all right? - Yes.
Mom, it hurts.
- Honey? - Sure.
There you go.
Good.
Here.
I'm glad to see your son doing better.
You came in for your first interview...
when you around his age.
That's right.
Why did you decide this line of work though...
instead of joining the prosecutors' office?
You already asked me that during my interview.
Did I?
Well, I knew that prosecutors spent their days...
going over case files at their desks.
Right.
Many weren't on board when we first hired you.
It was custom to only hire those over 30...
for special recruits who have passed the bar.
I'm well aware that you advocated for me.
In order to build a better system,
customs should be broken from time to time.
I'm grateful for everything.
Has the warrant been issued?
It will.
Inspector Kim Do Soo confessed too.
What's the charge?
The statute of limitations expired for the Shimbae incident,
but there are nine charges including abuse of power.
The total sentence will be quite long.
Don't be conceited.
I won't go down that easily.
I don't expect anything less.
Superintendent Han.
There must be a reason...
why you came alone first.
I came to ask you to make a decision that will protect...
the reputation of the force.
I'm dying anyway,
so you want evidence to catch Hwang Pil Seon, is that it?
Sun Mi.
When you reach out your hand to someone hanging off a cliff,
you need to give that person hope.
I don't see any hope in the hand...
you're reaching out.
Hope for my survival.
Sir.
We have a warrant.
Shall we go?
(214-12 Simpan-2-dong)
Step aside. We're here to see Chairwoman Hwang Pil Seon.
We said to step aside.
- You can't go. - Get out.
- We're the police! - Get out!
Get out!
- Get out! - Step back!
Please step aside.
Chairwoman Hwang Pil Seon, we're here to escort you.
How dare you come here?
- Attorney Im. - Yes, sir?
Report that woman first. Right now!
Superintendent Han.
You're putting way too much faith in that telepathic lunatic.
As you can see,
she's extremely busy dealing with those who spread wild accusations.
Including you...
Chairwoman Hwang Pil Seon,
you are under arrest for blackmail and murder-for-hire.
Superintendent Han! How dare you...
- Do you have a warrant? - Enough.
Don't be rude.
Yes, ma'am.
Superintendent Han. Choose your words carefully here.
That's how you must act in front of me.
I'll say it again carefully.
Hwang Pil Seon.
You are under arrest for blackmail and murder-for-hire.
That's fun. It is.
Okay, then. Shall we go?
Step back! You sewer rats.
You have no class.
You scum bags.
- Call the prosecutor general. - Yes, sir.
Madam.
Superintendent Han. Where's Baek?
Where did he go?
Mr. Prosecutor General.
Why was it so hard to reach you?
What is going on here?
How could you make the chairwoman come to the police station?
There are national petitions regarding this. My hands were tied.
Don't call me for a while.
- Goodbye. - Sir. Sir!
Darn it.
What's this?
Why is the criminal who should be interrogated, interrogating me?
I heard the prosecutors named you,
Deputy Chief Lee Shin Woong, as the prime suspect.
I'm here to be interrogated as well...
since I've committed so many crimes.
Dad.
I believe all of it is a lie.
I will trust you until the end.
Because you're a good cop.
"The guilty shall pay for his crimes."
I had forgotten for too long, but that was...
my conviction.
(Personal Data)
(Personal Data of Bang Joon Seok, Im Joong Yeon, Hwang Pil Seon)
You rat.
Were you...
always this fearless, Lee Shin Woong?
Let me educate you again from the beginning.
I won't be here for long.
You don't have to stay here for long.
We have ample evidence.
Superintendent Han.
The interrogation will be over soon.
Hwang Pil Seon.
Why don't we both guess how long...
you'll end up in prison?
You've been acting up for way too long.
I guess you don't know me very well.
I'll teach you a lesson so that you'll learn...
not to cross me...
ever again.
What a pity. You should know that things have changed.
A lot more people are like me these days.
Let's talk about the stuff we can still charge you with.
Sir, things aren't going as planned.
What do you mean?
The attorney general won't answer my calls.
And I might get investigated as well.
Why don't you try calling someone else?
What about me? Am I in danger too?
We need to get the chairwoman out of here in order to survive.
- You should make some calls... - Get out of there.
Pardon? But what about the chairwoman?
I need to survive in order to save my mom. Get out of there.
Assemblyman Bang.
Where are you off to? I'm here to see you.
- What do you want? - Baek!
We don't have anything on him yet.
Oh, you mean evidence?
What about this? What does this have to do with me?
Shut your mouth and watch. This is just the beginning.
- She's so cute. - It's water.
Drink up.
Here.
Do you know who I am?
I'm Bang Joon Seok.
I'm Bang Joon Seok, okay?
Drink up.
There's more, but I'll save it for later.
I'm having a hard time watching this.
Bang Joon Seok, you're under arrest for suspicions of murder.
- Detective Oh. - Yes, sir.
Take him where he belongs. I'll be right there.
Let's go, sir.
You have the right to an attorney...
and can request a review regarding the legality of the arrest.
Hey, you. Attorney.
Look to your front. Over there.
Are you crazy? Let me go!
You're just a police. How are you going to deal with the consequences?
Hey, stop filming me! Which broadcasting station are you from?
Sir, is it true that you left a kidnapping victim to die...
so you could cover up the former district attorney's scandal?
What are you saying? Get that out of my face!
Dong Baek, you punk.
Sun Mi, don't you know me?
Do you think you're all innocent?
You just wait. You're all dead!
Do you really think that would scare me?
Get yourself a good attorney and wait for your turn.
You're not that important, so you'll need to wait in line.
Sir.
Sir, will you please say something?
- They're trying to frame me! - We want to hear what you think...
as the former district attorney.
Did you ever ask him to do something unjust...
so you could cover up your scandal?
No.
Do you have any words for the family of the deceased?
No, I don't really know what you're talking about.
Hey, stop him. Stop him!
I only helped him do what he did. He's the guy you're after!
What are you all doing here?
I have a lot to talk about with you guys.
Take them upstairs.
I'll be off now.
Hey, what are you doing? How dare you?
Don't you know who I am? Let me go.
How polite of them.
They gathered here before I could even call them.
Hello, ma'am.
It's nice to see you.
The special prosecution starts today.
There's not much left for you to do.
I'm worried I might end up with all the work.
Yes, if you're still willing to be a star prosecutor...
like I promised before.
Will you guys be quiet? This is a public place.
Have some manners. You guys should know better.
I can't believe this!
You can't do this to me!
You must've made up your mind...
seeing that you're here.
What? No, there was nothing to decide...
because I never got swayed.
Where did you find the evidence?
Inside someone's memory.
What are you doing with that rag?
It's not a rag. It's a towel.
I don't care if you washed it. It's still a rag.
I made sure I washed it clean.
Old man!
Hey, you're here. Good work.
Do you know how worried I was?
Old Man!
I'll live until I'm 100 if you don't stress me out.
And will you take Se Hoon home? He cries so much. It's annoying.
This is so upsetting.
Do you know how hard I tried to take care of you? Forget it!
Did you think I'd say that?
- Old Man! - Old Man!
- My Old Man! - I was so worried.
I can't believe you're both doing this.
Look at how swollen he is. What are we going to do?
- It must've hurt so much. - He's always swollen.
It's not because he's sick. It's just his fat.
Did you think this through?
I should've done this earlier.
It's a very big loss for the police force...
to lose a competent police officer like you.
My job as a policewoman is over.
(Resignation Letter)
Good luck.
Attorney Han Sun Mi.
Thank you.
It's a little sad to see you go.
This country needs a person like you.
- Right? - Of course.
Can you not go?
He's right. We all looked up to you so much.
I sincerely thank everyone...
for following my orders...
even though I was young and arrogant.
Here.
Ms. Han, you did great.
It was an honor to work with you!
- Me too! - Me too!
Thank you so much.
You did great.
You spilled some. Hold on.
Here you go.
Sang Ah?
In Tae, do you remember me?
Are your memories back?
Yes.
Hyeon Su...
Hyeon Su.
Mom, it was Mr. Dong Baek.
Mr. Dong Baek?
Don't be too relieved. I still need to keep an eye on you.
I can't say you're out of the woods just yet.
Especially with your sister and all.
Just inform me of my test results.
All right.
I don't know why, but your unstable test results...
have all gone back to being in the normal range.
No matter how pleasing it is to hear,
we can't blindly believe it unless we know the reason.
I think I know why.
Gaining back the memories I blocked out 20 years ago...
has brought me stability.
I guess you can say I've been blocking my own abilities.
Tell me more about it.
I need to know everything about you to...
I can't.
You of all people know how I can't explain in words...
about everything that happened to me.
Chairwoman Hwang and former assemblyman Bang...
who stood trial for murder, murder-for-hire, and bribery...
were sentenced to 20 years and 18 years respectively...
in their second trial.
That is two years more than what they received...
during the first trial.
The prosecution also announced investigating...
high-ranking officials linked with Hwang in the political...
and economical circle as well as the press.
Those who have been harming our society...
with their illicit power...
and connections within these high-ranking officials...
will face the ruling of the law once again.
The public has never been this eager to ask for justice to be served.
I'm Kang Ji Eun for OBC News.
Get out!
Why does the company even pay you?
Go out there and find a story of your own...
or make one, darn it!
Get moving!
Mom...
Mom.
Inmate 1605, Hwang Pil Seon.
Your son took his life last night.
Hwang Pil Seon.
You're even worse than your own mother.
You will die a brutal death.
You will face the most pitiful death.
(Attorney Han Sun Mi)
Plants and flowers keep coming in to congratulate you.
Congratulations on opening your office.
(Congratulations)
I hope you don't regret this.
Civil rights attorneys don't earn much.
I won't be able to offer a big salary,
so choose wisely.
I will always choose to work with you.
- Hello. - It's been a while.
- Hi. - Good to see you.
Superintendent Han...
I mean, Attorney Han, congratulations.
It's good to see you.
I'm glad you're back on your feet.
I may not have superpowers, but I'm as fit as the Hulk.
Hulk, my foot.
You almost died like a mere mortal.
(Clean Toilet Paper)
(Toilet Paper)
This is why I said toilet paper was a bad idea!
- Did you? - Yes!
Congratulations!
- Congratulations. - Gosh.
It's good to see you all.
- Congratulations. - How are you doing?
- Congratulations. - Congratulations, ma'am.
- Congratulations. - This Chinese place seems nice.
Why don't we take a photo?
I'll get us all in the frame.
- Sure. - Sounds good.
A photo? Seriously?
Ms. Han, you stand in the middle.
- Come on. - Gather around.
- A little more to the right. - Good.
Say, "Kimchi."
- Kimchi. - Kimchi.
How pretty.
- What are you doing? - What's taking so long?
Are you done?
- Did you take it? - How about another one?
Together.
- Let's take a look. - How fascinating.
Nice.
- What's that? - What on earth?
Why did you only zoom in on Ms. Kang?
- Look at you. - What?
You should file a report against him.
- Unbelievable. - Do you like her?
Is there something going on between you two?
- No... - We could try and make that happen.
- Unbelievable. - Let me see.
Look!
Isn't it fascinating?
You look good even though you're in the back.
I've been reflecting on myself.
- I didn't ask. - That wasn't an answer either.
So what have you done wrong this time?
It's more about how I've been living all this time.
Sounds like you did something terrible.
Who's the victim?
Tell me so I can protect his or her civil rights.
All this time, I thought...
I only had the ability to scan people's memories.
But that's true.
I don't think it was just their memories though.
What they were thinking...
and what they were feeling.
Their time in general.
I have been getting to know everything about them.
I guess I only viewed my ability as a tool...
which is why I read memories of so many random people.
That's why I'm reflecting on myself.
That is the most beautiful side of you that I've ever seen.
I'm stunned.
You're right. I stun myself too.
So? You won't use it anymore?
Of course, I'll use it. I'll use it well.
I'll put in my feelings too and use it well.
Detective Dong Baek.
Thanks for everything.
I look forward to working with you more,
Superintendent Han Sun Mi.
The National Assembly passed a telepathy law today...
supported by a national petition signed by over 8 million people.
The Seoul Metropolitan Police Agency stated that they will create...
a telepathic investigation team to handle violent crimes...
and will bring in Detective Dong Baek early on...
to lead the way in protecting the people.
The special law on telepathy passing appears to be an indication...
that the safety and public welfare will be strengthened.
With OBC News, this is Kang Ji Eun.
I'm here.
A hiker found her and called it in.
We confirmed that she died two days ago.
We need to wait for the autopsy,
but the stab wound was the likely cause of death.
Did we identify her yet?
Shin Mi Young. Age 43. She's a housewife.
Where's that punk Baek?
- Who knows? - He thinks...
he's the police commissioner or something.
- Why isn't he at the scene? - Poof.
The fame got to his head.
Stop it before I kick you.
Who is that?
He's Shin Mi Young's husband.
He returned today from a business trip abroad.
Escort him down.
Yes, sir.
Mi Young.
Sir, I'll escort you down.
It's too hard to investigate if you...
Detective Oh.
I don't know what to say that may help console you.
We'll catch the killer...
I only cared about my job.
I can't believe this happened right when I was gone.
Give it a break, will you?
Are you mad?
Iryu-dong. Sungok Hotel, room 802.
- What? - What else? The killer's there.
You have to hurry. The flight takes off at 2:20pm...
taking this man...
and Kim Yoon Mi,
his mistress, who conspired with him...
and killed his poor wife.
Do you have proof?
The telepathic detective.
Your reads have no weight as evidence!
That's why the cops...
Sorry, but I lose my temper when I see scum bags! Come here!
Hey! Get over here!
He deserves a beating.
I can kiss an early retirement goodbye, right?
- I think so. - Why you little...
Hold him.
- Hey. - Get him.
Let go.
- No. - Get over here!
(Thank you for watching "Memorist")