(School Field Trip Report)
(Yeonhui Botanical Garden)
(Wildflowers of Korea)
- How come you're home early?
- The field trip ended early.
Wildflowers?
Yes.
It looks interesting, doesn't it?
It's all white.
It feels like it's going to turn
into a fairy at night.
(Ghost plant)
It's like a fairy.
Its name was...
"Sujeongcho," Ghost plant.
Do you know it?
My friend's name was Soo Jung.
Why aren't you asking me...
about the smaller room anymore?
You said it was filled
with materials...
of the stigmata serial murder.
Is there anything else?
My friend.
Do you want to talk about it?
I think so.
I'm ready.
Soo Jung was...
(Last Episode)
- Goodbye.
- Bye.
To Detective Cha Young Jin.
I found a way to expiate my sins.
I'm leaving to find...
the evidence of the sins
of my father and Sang Ho.
Whether it be a mirage,
I have no choice.
Eun Ho and Ms. Cha,
thank you.
May the Lord bless you.
Give me that.
Did Sun Ah put you up to this?
Sang Ho, it's for your own good.
So that you can betray me?
Are you trying to abandon me
just like Doo Seok?
Are you?
- Do you remember Kero?
- What?
The black dog that the manager
of our orphanage had.
He used to always bite people
when his leash was loose.
But the kids...
locked me up in a warehouse
with Kero.
My body and mind both froze in fear.
When Kero was about to bite my neck,
you came in...
and reached your arm to his mouth.
I don't think that's an answer
to my question.
My mind that froze that day
still hasn't thawed.
Sang Ho.
I can't...
do anything
when I'm not by your side.
Wait here.
It's okay. It's not too late yet.
- You came.
- Did you stir Doo Seok's mind?
I saw that his mind was swaying,
so I incited him.
I wanted to see which way he leans.
Do you think I can't see
what your mind is doing?
I'm curious.
What does my mind look like
to your eyes?
I know you're worried
about what I might do...
when I'm not around.
What you said to me
when you saved my life.
I've never heard better words
than those until now.
Do you want me to tell you again?
Lim Hee Jung's case doesn't have
any statute of limitations.
I don't think
Sang Won killed Hee Jung.
Let her speak.
Sang Won, help me.
Sang Won!
If you save my life,
you and Sang Ho will...
Stop.
You are still...
- giving me orders.
- No.
If you help me,
I'll do anything...
you tell me...
When greed conceives,
it gives birth to sin.
When the sin comes of age,
it gives birth to death.
Ki Ho,
you still have no idea.
That boy has to be safe
from you forever.
- What?
- If then,
you'll also be safe forever.
The choice has become too easy
thanks to you.
- Were you doing something?
- No.
Oh, boy.
- Why are you staring at me?
- Because I like it.
I like that you're
one of my students.
And I like
that you're Ji Won's older brother.
Hey, Eun Ho.
I don't know about you,
but I just like...
being involved with you...
whether it be as your teacher
or your family.
I'm fine.
I just want to live as usual.
Is it because Ji Won said
she doesn't want a brother?
No one has to suffer
if we remain strangers.
But you know what?
If you were to...
live as you did in the past,
what about the good things
that would have happened to her?
Won't they be gone?
You were going to take
good care of her.
If that disappears,
I think it'll be a shame.
You just have to suffer
a little longer.
But...
you'll be able to experience
more precious and happy things,
don't you think?
Yes.
Eun Ho, your mother dies
if you press that.
What are you doing?
I'm going to kill you both
and end it if you annoy me.
Got it?
Hee Dong, say hello to Eun Ho
and Sun Woo.
Eun Ho, now you remember everything,
don't you?
- Just leave him alone.
- Again!
Why do you and even Ki Ho...
try to protect him
as if he's something?
Sun Woo,
then what would you give up...
to save Eun Ho?
I'll go. Take me instead.
Take you?
Sun Woo.
Hey, you're worthless to me!
Why on earth do you need him?
You forgot?
I'm the one who saved him.
So he's mine. Don't you get it?
Eun Ho, stop wasting my time
and just come.
It's okay.
- Hurry up.
- Eun Ho.
Don't worry.
It's all right.
How annoying.
Eun Ho, follow me.
- Hee Dong, get closer...
- Stop!
I'll come with you.
Let me help you.
Hee Dong.
Stop!
Get off.
You should've turned a blind eye...
to this just like others.
Please stop it.
Fine. I'll stop.
You're good at drawing.
So you saw everything in the study.
Is that why you jumped off?
Get up.
You scared me.
Sang Ho, stop.
You'd better not do anything
to put a spoke in my wheel.
Or your mom will be...
killed slowly by Hee Dong.
Can you promise me?
Yes.
Then, never lay a hand on my mom.
Don't worry.
Your mom is totally worthless to me.
Get changed.
It's your first time leaving
the hospital.
- Yes, Mr. Lee.
- Sang Ho...
took Eun Ho with him.
Please save Eun Ho.
(Eun Ho)
(Soo Jung)
Cha Young Jin?
Isn't it you?
It is.
The day that reminds us
of the old day came.
How amazing.
Put Eun Ho on the phone.
What makes you think he's alive?
Because I said Soo Jung would
be the last victim?
You didn't kill him.
Are you trying to feel me out?
Or is that what you believe?
If I were you,
I wouldn't have finished this
that soon.
Incredible.
You're really good.
Right. Eun Ho is alive.
Now we should meet.
I'll invite you to my place.
I don't need any gift,
but I recommend you come alone.
My place is quite messy now.
I'll open all the doors for you.
But you won't be able to open
the last one so easily.
- Where should I go?
- You can't go anywhere.
You shouldn't have come this far.
We all are over because of you.
Where are Eun Ho and Sang Ho?
You must have some difficulty
understanding what others say.
I'll kill you with my hand.
I have no time.
Just tell me where they are.
- Open it.
- Then remove this first.
No?
Then pluck my eyeball out.
I guess Ms. Cha is really mad.
Even if she's terrible at shooting,
Hee Dong is too big to miss, right?
Eun Ho.
Young Jin is no different from me.
She kills if she has a reason.
This is my favorite tie.
You can put handcuffs
on me and Doo Seok only.
What? Now you want to shoot me?
Sun Ah!
You can't call 911.
Save her.
Save her no matter what.
It's the rooftop.
Please.
You're late this time.
Last time, you barged in
even before you were invited.
Are you hurt?
- Drop your knife.
- No, your gun first.
Which one will be faster,
my knife or your gun?
- Let Eun Ho go.
- I don't know.
I doubt we can have a sound talk
without him.
Now, drop your gun.
What are you doing
when the kid is watching?
We know our situations,
so let's trust each other.
Shouldn't you show him
the virtue of concession, Ms. Cha?
Drop it.
One more round.
Drop your knife.
You can't last forever
with that empty gun!
You're never disappointing.
You know I have no intention
of killing Eun Ho.
The moment he jumped off here,
I fell for this guy.
Put your hands off him.
We're only loving him
in our own way.
Let him go. This talk is about us.
Really? He already knows everything
about Choi Soo Jung's case.
You shouldn't have told
such a horrible story to a kid.
That's ruining his soul.
So from now on,
let's talk alone without him.
No, it's late.
He's gotten strong already.
He's much stronger than you think.
He's something.
In my study,
he noticed who I was, but walked
out of there nonchalantly.
Then he jumped off here to run away.
You know
what's even more impressive?
He let the rope go
in order not to get caught.
This kid is unbelievable.
So don't worry,
and let him hear our talk.
Where were we?
I was telling Eun Ho
about Hee Jung's last moment.
If we change the topic here, he'll
be so curious about what comes next.
Besides, the story gets exciting
from now on.
Because Young Jin appears.
Now we need to choose whom to bless.
It should be...
the friend of Soo Jung
whom you killed.
That woman...
will be a witness
to testify the resurrection.
Her name is Cha Young Jin.
She's still looking for you.
It was also her...
who talked on the phone
with me 19 years ago.
And she lied...
that the stigmata...
will happen again.
How surprising.
She's still looking for me.
Good.
She should be the witness.
Father, I have more to tell you.
My sin is too big...
to ask you for forgiveness.
Please save me from my pain...
and complete the resurrection.
Do you mean it?
Yes.
Like Francis of Assisi...
who received the stigmata
from the angel with six wings,
give me...
the holy mark.
I'll be born again like those
whom you blessed.
I'll lead them at the front...
and show everyone in the world...
what it means to have the grace
of being chosen by you!
The last blessing is mine.
Father, please...
- give me the blessing of stigmata.
- No.
The miracle of the resurrection...
must start from my hands...
and be completed through my body.
Father.
(Senior Inspector Cha Young Jin)
We haven't found Ki Ho yet.
We must leave her like that
until we do.
It's okay.
We've found Ki Ho.
(Emergency Center)
Hey.
What's the name of the kid?
Ko Eun Ho?
Ko Eun Ho...
Follow him.
If the kid has the thing,
Ki Ho will show up himself.
That's when I heard your name
for the first time.
I thought you'd be kind.
I mean, you saved a stranger
down on the street...
and even followed him
to the hospital.
But you...
lived in a house downstairs
from Young Jin's.
I thought it was
an amusing coincidence up to there.
But you two are friends.
I think...
I was meant to kill Soo Jung...
instead of Young Jin.
Eun Ho.
If Young Jin died instead
and you met Soo Jung,
what kind of a kid would you be now?
One thing is certain.
You wouldn't have
gone through something like this.
So blame Young Jin...
for this horrible situation.
Did you...
blame Sang Won?
- What?
- Is that why you woke up...
his madness from its sleep...
and nailed a gimlet on his hand
which saved you?
Don't underestimate his belief.
He believed no one could resurrect
unless the mark was given by him.
Would he have left his hand to me?
I mean, I have no right.
Are you saying he did it himself?
This is why we need a witness.
An honest witness.
Are you saying he did it himself?
This is why we need a witness.
An honest witness.
(Senior Inspector Cha Young Jin)
(Send a message at a reserved time.)
(New Message)
(41 Chueui-ro, Misung-gu, Incheon)
(Senior Inspector Cha Young Jin)
Father, let's begin.
When you whipped me,
you always said:
"Be grateful to receive
the sacred pain."
"And you will be a believer..."
"who doesn't get swayed
by any temptation."
- It's still not late to stop.
- How grateful.
Let me finish this pain.
Father.
Hang in there a little more.
Just a little more.
Young Jin,
you're never disappointing.
Father.
Young Jin is here.
Is it already time?
No, she came by herself
without our guidance.
She is indeed appropriate
to become...
the witness of my resurrection.
"She is indeed..."
"appropriate to become
the witness of my resurrection."
That's all. Now it's your turn.
I've told you already.
So you struggled to save him,
but you lost his hand?
Come on now. You let his hand go.
- You say it like you saw it.
- You said so yourself.
You said that you'll find me
even if it'd take...
your whole life...
- and kill me.
- What did it look like to you?
Did it seem like I lost his hand
or let it go?
What are you talking about?
You were watching it all from
the machine room on the rooftop.
The DNA found on the recorder
from Eun Ho's ward...
and the one found
from the machine room matched.
And it'll probably match the one
from the teacup you used.
Why would you do a DNA test?
You just need to talk to Ki Ho
and get the camcorder.
Soo Jung's case and Hee Jung
and Sang Won's case are separate.
I already told Eun Ho.
Sang Won killed Hee Jung.
Sang Won could have been...
saved by Ms. Cha here,
don't you think?
Sang Won cried someone's name
before he fell.
That was you, wasn't it?
Father, I'll be watching.
Please show me
the miracle of resurrection.
I'll see you soon.
You're invited here as a witness.
Witness the miracle
of my resurrection...
and testify it to the world.
- Let go.
- Please.
You'll also fall down then.
Please!
I'm going to find you
no matter how long it takes.
- Let go.
- Stop...
Let go, Young Jin.
So make sure you stay alive
until then.
You should stay alive until we meet.
Stop speaking!
My lamb
that's been lost in the world.
My apostle and my child!
I give you...
the blessing of faith
with my resurrection!
Stop nagging. I'm a grown-up now.
I can take care of myself, Sang Won.
(Elevator Machine Room)
Amazing.
I like you.
It was wise of me
to kill Soo Jung instead of you.
Wise?
What kind of life
have you lived, Sang Ho?
Well,
I'm not sure.
When my mother...
abandoned me, she locked the door
from the outside.
As I was waiting to die...
Sang Won came in. But you know what?
My mother who abandoned me used to
beat me while crying.
But Sang Won smiled as he beat me
when he saved my life.
Is that answer good enough?
It was your choice
to become a monster.
It must have put you at ease
to make others like you...
because you needed to believe
that you're not the only one.
Maybe.
Are you okay?
Can I release him?
Where are my mother and Mr. Lee?
They're fine.
Ms. Cha, let's just go.
I'm sorry, Eun Ho.
I need to know how Soo Jung died.
I'm really sorry.
I said that I hoped
you wouldn't know...
when something bad happens to me
because you're this kind of person.
You're all grown up now.
It will be much tougher from now on
compared to the time you've lived.
Would that be all right?
Even so...
No, now I must know if it is so.
Why was it Soo Jung, not me?
Are you saying thank you?
Why?
Why did you choose her over me?
Why do you want to know?
- I just don't understand.
- So that I won't forget.
She was next to me,
and I took it for granted.
It gave me strength
just to realize...
the fact
that she'll always be by my side.
That's what she meant to me,
and she died instead of me.
I want to know how she died.
I want to remember her
and feel sad for her.
Because that's all I can do now.
See, that never happens in my world.
- Tell me.
- No.
I won't tell you so that you'll...
remember me every day
for your entire life.
Did you say it was a wise choice
to let me live?
Do you really think so?
She died the next day the picture of
me and her disappeared in my room.
Keep going.
You must have waited for me...
at my house on the day
the picture went missing.
You changed your mind for some
reason and only took the picture.
That was on the evening
of July 31, 2000.
And you killed her the next evening.
The murder was on August 1, 2000
at midnight.
What did it feel like when you heard
the statute of limitations expired?
If you killed me as you planned,
the statute of limitations might
have expired.
But you chose to kill Soo Jung
the next day,
and it's still in effect.
Do you still think
it was a wise choice?
I had to endure
every day of my life.
If I caught you after
the statute of limitations expired,
my only option would be to kill you.
But fortunately,
I was given another choice.
Why did I switch to Soo Jung?
Because she had friends
other than you,
but she was your only friend.
What?
I thought about which will make
someone suffer longer,
and it was you.
That's why I decided
to let you live.
What would you have done without me?
My life would be
a lot quieter than now.
I'm hanging up.
Is that what you told her?
Of course.
It'd be too harsh to die
without knowing the reason.
- The third call.
- That was from me.
I really didn't want to
tell you this story.
This is what I told her
before I called.
"I'll let you go
if your friend picks up."
I could see hope sparkle in her eyes
as I said that.
Hope that she might be able to live.
But you never answered the phone.
If I answered,
were you really going to let her go?
No way.
She knows my face and my name.
Because she had hope
that she might be able to make it,
her pain and despair must have
gotten bigger.
I promise you, I'm going to...
"Kill you."
"I'll find you even if it'd take
my whole life."
"So make sure you stay alive
until then."
Come to think of it, maybe...
I've been waiting for this moment
from that point on.
Now it's time to execute.
- We need to end this, right?
- I'm not...
the old Cha Young Jin anymore.
Or are you?
Her last words she left you are
recorded here.
Yes, it still works.
Let me listen to it.
Will you be okay?
I'll find out after I listen to it.
Can I talk to my family?
Mom...
and Dad, thank you.
I'm sorry.
Please don't be so sad.
Young Jin.
Like you said,
I'm angry and frustrated...
that this will be the last moment
of my life.
So...
I decided to think...
about happy and fun memories only.
You're also part of them.
No!
I'll kill you...
as you wish!
Let's make it straight.
That's what you want.
Revenge for Soo Jung's death...
and the reward
for this meaningless life.
What's stopping you?
Say you want me to save you.
Just get it over with it.
Say: "Save me."
"Please save me."
"Please."
"Don't kill me."
This is the last word Soo Jung said.
As she said that,
her small heart that was palpitating
like a bird caught in hands...
stopped.
Fine.
I'll let you go...
to hell.
Let's go home.
Don't be scared.
I'm here to save you.
You're chosen by me.
Sang Ho.
Come closer and watch.
How grateful.
- It's not too late.
- Let me finish this pain.
If it'd been you,
would my life have changed?
Sang Ho.
On suspicions of abducting
and assaulting a minor,
and...
murdering Choi Soo Jung,
you're under arrest.
You have the right to remain silent
and have an attorney.
You have the right
not to incriminate yourself.
Where's Eun Ho?
He's fine.
Don't worry. Just rest.
You'll regret
making the wrong choice...
every time you wake up
in the morning.
What about his secretary?
She's out of immediate danger.
We arrested Hee Dong too.
- What is she talking about?
- Hee Dong must've made it in time.
I let him go so that he could
save your secretary.
Both of them aren't dead?
No one died.
- Are you okay?
- Yes.
- Are you all right?
- I am.
I will never be late again.
You were never late.
It's just I never waited for you.
I will...
try to wait for you now.
I'm sorry
I let you go through all this.
As long as I have
a superhero neighbor,
it's unavoidable.
- What?
- You're my hero.
- It's cringy.
- I'm glad...
you're smiling again.
Eun Ho and I are both fine.
- How are you feeling?
- It hurts so bad.
It's the most painful time
in my life.
I thought you were only bluffing...
when you said you'd rather hurt
yourself if someone has to get hurt.
But you really meant it.
I never knew it'd hurt this much.
- I hope you get better soon.
- Where are you going?
- Home.
- What about Eun Ho?
- He's home.
- Ms. Cha.
Thank you.
(April)
Hi, you're early.
Eun Ho, is it fun?
- Yes.
- Enjoy.
- Let me borrow it later.
- Sure.
The foundation will be separated
from the church.
- That's good.
- We can't set up a college either.
It was my father-in-law's wish.
That place is yours. I'm his son,
but it slipped even through my ears.
So why cherish it so much?
Because I'm your family too.
I'll run the foundation clean
and hand it over to you.
What are you saying?
I'll make it mine
when I get the intention to do so.
Suit yourself.
But I wonder
if that will ever happen.
These days,
I think being a teacher suits me
perfectly.
What are you doing?
Go back to your seats.
All right,
it's time for the assembly.
Oh, gosh.
Shall we begin without him?
- No.
- We shouldn't do that.
- Dong Myung is one of us too.
- Fine. We'll wait.
Is everyone here now?
- Yes.
- Let's begin.
- Okay.
- Who's in charge of cleaning?
- Me.
- Is it you?
- Yes, right.
- Aren't you feeling guilty?
- I forgot.
I said I forgot.
- I'm telling you.
- Come on.
No, really.
(Eun Ho)
- Hey.
- Were you asleep?
- Yes.
- Why do you sleep all the time?
Maybe you're sick.
I grew to sleep more.
Move a little.
- From tomorrow on.
- Come pick me up.
I want to eat something delicious.
(Shinsung Middle School)
- Let's go.
- Why are you running?
Dong Myung. Min Sung.
- Hello.
I'm here to eat with Eun Ho.
- Do you want to join us?
- Okay.
You're going to cram school, right?
- Eat before you go.
- Okay.
- We're joining you.
- I wanted to see you all anyway.
Let's go.
(Passionate Snack Food)
- Enjoy.
- Thank you.
- Thank you for the food.
Order more if it's not enough.
Save some money. You've been
loafing around for months.
And you wanted me
to buy you delicious food?
Do you not talk to each other
at school?
We talk when we need to.
- What about lunch?
- We don't eat together.
I think my friends are
a bit eccentric.
- And you are.
- A grown-up kid.
I heard you talk to Mr. Hwang
on the phone almost every day.
- Now you call me a grownup kid?
- Who told you that?
Me.
We were working on the farm,
but he was talking on the phone
without working, so I asked.
- Hello, Mr. Hwang.
- This fish cake looks really good.
Have you had dinner?
Why don't you come here then?
The kids are waiting.
- No.
He says he'll come right over.
Have you ever had lobster before?
Have you not?
- How do you eat it?
- I haven't either.
I'm not going to cram school today.
- Who was it?
- My mom's lawyer.
- Eat up.
- Okay.
Looking great.
- Hello.
- You're here.
Hi.
All right, sit down.
Did you eat a lot?
Min Sung ate it all up.
No, Eun Ho did.
- That means it wasn't enough.
- I guess so.
- Should I make an order?
- The lobster one is so good.
Really?
Tae Hyung.
How did you know I was here?
Did Ms. Cha tell you?
I asked her tenaciously.
Seriously. No one can be trusted.
I came in case you'd do that.
What do you mean?
I was worried
you wouldn't trust anyone...
because of people like me
and Sang Ho.
At that time, I didn't trust you.
I suspected you
before hearing you out.
And I'm really sorry.
It's too late to take your apology.
The moment I hurt you,
I became...
someone who deserved suspicion.
Then you should apologize to me too.
I'll just accept it.
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry too.
I heard you have to go up
to the rooftop today.
- Let's go. I'll help you out.
- No.
- It's okay.
- I'm not doing this for free.
Treat me to jajangmyeon after this.
Should I untie this?
Yes. Wait, I'll do it.
Baek Sang Ho,
Oh Doo Seok, and Ko Hee Dong.
These are their written statements.
Please confirm.
These people were...
like devils.
I feel like it hasn't ended yet.
It's true they were horrible
like devils.
But we arrested them.
They're humans.
You must want us
to guarantee your safety.
But that's our basic duty.
Now we know what happened...
to you, Young Sik.
Though we can't be responsible
for your life,
we'll still be able to help.
(Written Affidavit)
These two were waiting for me
at my place.
(1st to 9th victims)
(Outline of Millennium Hotel Case)
- Good work.
- Ms. Hong, make other kids do it...
instead of doing this yourself
every time.
Everyone in our team is busy.
Besides,
there are no kids in my team.
I was just being considerate to you.
Think before you talk.
Just do the thinking
and save the talking.
Are you done with this already?
Our team is a second
before dying of fatigue.
- What is it?
- Mr. Han requested...
materials about Sang Won's trace...
from the 1st to 7th
stigmata murder cases.
We can't rely
only on Sang Ho's statement.
Yesterday, the prosecution grilled
us to hand over the cases...
that passed
the statute of limitations.
Then what? Are they
going to investigate on their own?
- I have no objection.
- Same here.
I want to do it.
It's not that I don't want to do it.
There you go again.
We know even if you don't say it.
Ja Young.
You're almost like one of them now.
She's better than these guys.
Right, treat us to a meal today.
- Little Cha Young Jin.
- Little Han Geun Man!
- You're at it again!
- Let's get to work.
Wait. It slipped away.
- Goodness.
- Again.
- Bring it to me.
- Goodness.
Come on.
Hey, do it properly.
- Hurry.
- Do it like this.
- Look here.
- It's the same anyway.
- The lack of military experience.
- I know.
- You look pretty.
- You think it's dirty?
- Thank you.
- Goodbye.
(Hongje Park Mansion)
All the statements match.
- I see.
- None of them blamed...
one another or made excuses.
You could've reported this
on the phone.
We wanted to tell you this
in person.
- What is it?
- All of us are...
waiting for you.
There you go. Throw it.
He looks so happy.
Why, are you upset?
I'm thinking
Eun Ho was lonelier than I thought.
The way I see it,
Eun Ho's affection for Ji Won is...
far from his loneliness.
Right.
Are you going to Sang Ho's trial?
Excuse me.
- Hello?
- When are you coming?
We need to go now. Why?
- Is there anything you can't eat?
- No.
I'll cook at my pleasure then.
Come and have dinner.
Who was it that you look so serious?
- Eun Ho's mom.
- What did she say?
She wants me to come
and have dinner.
I guess
she'll show off her cooking skills.
Eun Ho, Ji Won. Let's go.
Let's go.
Where are you going?
Let's hang out together again later.
I'm not so fun, aren't I?
I still like you.
I like you too, Ji Won.
Let's go.
What's that cheesy look
on your face?
Hey, Nephew! My nephew.
Let's go. Let's hold hands too.
Let's hold hands!
Thank you for the meal.
I didn't know what you'd like,
so I got many different things.
Thank you for the meal.
How is it?
Welcome.
(Cha Young Jin)
(Seoul High Court)
Both of you look like
you had a hard time.
It's something I've been waiting
for all my life.
Every single cell in my body feels
tense.
She couldn't keep her eyes off
of Baek Sang Ho during the trial.
For 20 years,
I've thought of every face and voice
of random people.
If I make eye contact
with someone...
while walking along the street,
I'd think that person might be him.
My heart would race.
In the end,
I was envious of families...
who found their culprits.
Not because of vengeance,
but because...
now I can put everything down.
Many people feel the same way.
I don't know what to say to you...
because I gave up mid-way.
What are you talking about?
I know how you took the fall
for Young Jin.
Thank you so much.
I wouldn't have managed without you.
Thank you for saying that.
Why didn't you come to the trial?
Because I might regret it.
I might think...
that I should've left him to die.
You made a good choice.
He'd be like us.
He'd eat and sleep like us.
But after seeing his face,
it looked like...
his world was full of hell.
After all,
I'm back in that room.
Shall we take a walk?
Sure.
I heard you didn't ask
to be reinstated again.
No.
You said you'd resign
once you resolve the reason...
of becoming a police officer.
Is that still valid?
Do you still stand by...
what you said to me back then?
What did I say?
We shouldn't focus on miseries.
We should seek the hope
that we still have.
That's our duty.
Right, I did say that.
Thank you.
Congratulations in advance
for your reinstatement.
Thank you.
(Shinsung Middle School)
You should go ahead.
- Will it take long?
- I'll go with him.
Are you going
to skip your class again?
I'm going to go there after I eat.
It's tight.
Eun Ho, we'll start before you.
Hurry up.
I came too late, didn't I?
I'm sorry.
How do you feel?
I'm good.
- What about you?
- I'm good too.
It's like I never got hurt.
I'm glad.
You were a blessing to me,
but I was your misfortune, right?
Saving you...
and doing you a favor,
I hope you don't think of it
as a gift from God.
That...
was my choice.
I...
broke many kids' hearts in the past.
I roughly heard about your story.
You used to be a heartbroken kid
too.
When I was young,
I'd get anxious every night.
Whether my mom was in a good mood
or bad. I was always nervous.
Then Ms. Cha moved
into the house above us.
And those nights disappeared.
Although she wasn't
at home every night.
I should have been
that kind of grown-up.
It's too late for me to become one,
right?
Aren't you going to be a grown-up
until the day you die?
I guess I am.
It was good to see you.
Don't make your friends wait
too long.
All right.
Goodbye.
Hello.
Hello. Here you go.
Thank you.
(Sender, Jang  Ho)
("The Life Before Us")
(Cha Young Jin)
Ms. Cha.
- Yes?
- When will you come?
I haven't even arrived yet.
- Drive safely.
- All right.
I'll hang up now.
Eun Ho.
Yes?
I'll be there on time.
All right.
I feel like having
deep-fried grasshoppers.
Have you tried those before?
- I tried it with Ji Won.
- Really?
I'm not that close with her.
- Shall I introduce you to her?
- Well, I'm a little shy.
Ji Won's good at studying Korean.
- Really?
- She's learning English too.
- I get good grades. Don't you too?
- I do.
Do you want to go see
that new movie?
("In a Voice Resembling Mine")