Heaven and earth will pass away,
but my words will never pass away.
No one knows about that day or hour,
not even the Son, but only...
(Episode 15)
That book.
That book is wrong.
Bring me my book.
Not that crappy copy,
bring my real book.
The contents are the same.
No, then this wouldn't have
happened!
Bring me my book now.
If you're not deceiving me...
Then what?
Are you saying...
I was the fool?
It has to be either you or me.
You know where it is, and...
I would never deceive you!
I deceive no one!
My father also...
didn't lie to me.
So...
bring me the real book from Sang Ho.
Were you memorizing the same things
with Hee Jung?
Have you ever checked with her?
My father did not lie to me.
He would never...
Not even the Son, but only...
the Father knows.
Holy wound and blessed pain.
Please allow me to give
my testimony at tomorrow's service.
Did you...
experience something
in the meantime?
Seven times...
for the last two years.
Pastor Seo's deep faith in
the miracle of resurrection was...
indeed a special experience.
So special that I want to share with
the believers of New Life Church...
No, with everyone in this world.
Stop beating around the bush,
and say it clearly.
The stigmata serial murder.
Holy wound and blessed pain.
It's what Pastor Seo said
every time...
he pierced
through the hands of the victims.
It's also what I always heard
after I got the cane in the past.
I will stop your son.
Instead,
the present you were planning
to give to your daughter,
- give it to me.
- No way.
Do you mean the land
for the house of prayer to be built?
We should at least
give and take that much...
to establish trust between us.
It's not enough.
You should risk your life...
for me to trust you. Am I wrong?
I'm doing it tomorrow.
I'll take care of it.
Stop worrying and just wait.
I'll give you the land
as we promised.
You should hold on to it well
until I get it back.
No one knows about that day or hour,
not even the angels in heaven,
nor the Son...
But only...
the Father knows.
Don't you worry.
From now on, we're
in a symbiotic relationship.
I'm going to hide it in the way...
that only I can find it.
Sang Ho had two private meetings
with Pastor Kwon.
And after that,
the land where we planned
to build the house of prayer...
went to Sang Ho.
It was a land with a great view
of the ocean.
Hee Jung loved it.
Drink this.
Pastor Kwon must have had a weakness
seized upon Sang Ho.
For instance,
one of his children was
a serial killer...
that made a huge stir.
Sang Ho must have gotten the land
for keeping it a secret.
I didn't know.
I didn't know about their deal
at the time.
This is what the pastor told me.
That he and Sang Ho are...
in a symbiotic relationship.
He also said in that deal...
that he'll hide it
where only he knows.
Then he made that special gospel.
He said that that book is...
a map to reveal Sang Ho's sins.
Do you know when the private
meetings were at least roughly?
Roughly?
On July 11th, 2000.
The second one was on August 2nd.
(7th murder, July 9th, 2000)
(8th murder, August 1st, 2000)
What happened
to Sang Won after that?
Pastor Kwon had a small building
he was planning to give me.
He suddenly gave it to Hee Jung,
and let Sang Won live
on the top floor.
- For 20 years?
- Yes.
So he was imprisoned.
And you and Hee Jung were
monitoring him.
Am I correct?
We should go now.
Do you trust me?
I can still reach out for someone
I don't trust.
Hee Jung must have threatened
Sang Ho...
that she'll find the book
and reveal his sins.
Here.
Let's talk while drinking tea.
Sure.
Look at that.
He was so healthy
like he was going to live forever.
Why don't you two...
get your hearts checked
for any problems.
Thanks.
I'll have it tested as you said.
- Good.
- Sang Ho.
We should finish our deal now.
"We"?
The evidence of your sins
that you promised to give back...
when the statute of limitations
expired.
Sadly, Sang Won's sins disappeared.
But your sins gained immortality.
Are you saying you'll pay me?
Instead, I should get my hotel back
which was supposed to be mine.
I'll only take the market price
for the land.
No, I want the interest too.
You still have One Life Foundation
when you lose the hotel.
Deacon Jang, you don't know...
where my sins are, right?
I also know about the map that...
Deacon Jang!
You should see
how Sang Won is doing.
Right. I forgot.
She asked for the hotel?
That's huge.
What would Sang Ho have thought
when he was blackmailed?
Wasn't Sang Won the one
who killed Hee Jung?
Right.
She was murdered brutally...
by the serial killer
who stayed in hiding for 20 years.
Then I got involved.
Because of Sang Won,
Hee Jung's death was...
considered another stigmata murder.
All the other possibilities were
ruled out in the beginning.
There are a lot of blind spots
in that area.
Yes, if someone decided to,
one could come and go
without being seen.
Jang Ki Ho.
If I knew you'd be trouble,
should I have kept Hee Jung alive?
I was waiting for death
without a name...
in that locked room.
You came in like an angel,
saved my life,
and granted me your name.
You have always been the owner
of my soul since then.
But then,
I let the seeds of distrust
of you and let them...
encroach on my soul.
My pupil who used to be loyal.
- Father.
- My won who used to be faithful.
I want to rip out my heart...
and go back.
What do you want me to do?
Punish corrupted Hee Jung...
for suppressing
the grace of salvation.
And...
complete the number eight
of salvation...
to show the whole world
the miracle of resurrection.
I cannot complete the miracle...
with the death
of corrupted Hee Jung.
Then Father,
let me punish her...
to make up for your humiliation.
I give you permission.
Pastor Seo.
You should open the windows
for some fresh air.
But he was pierced
for our transgressions,
he was crushed for our iniquities.
The punishment that brought us
peace was upon him.
And with his stripes, we are healed.
You've always looked at me like that
since we first met.
So even if you haven't
threatened me,
yes.
You would end up like this
by me someday.
The way you look at me is...
very similar to that of the one
who abandoned me.
Don't get me wrong. I'm just talking
about the way you look at me.
My mom was quite a beauty
unlike you.
You know, I take a lot after her.
You're dying like the women
who were killed by Father.
One of them lost her life
in less than half an hour.
He stabbed too deep.
But it'll take a while for you...
because I didn't want to end it
too soon.
How do you like it?
The map that has the location
where my secret has been hidden.
Ki Ho went to find it, right?
It's time to open your mouth.
Oh, right.
There's no use of screaming.
You know that, right?
Where is it?
If I die,
it'll be revealed
to the whole world.
You said the same thing
when you started threatening me.
But you know what?
Father told me everything.
Kwon Jae Chun, the old geezer,
never trusted you guys...
and didn't show it to you at all.
He said none of you guys know
where it is.
Ki Ho,
no.
My faithful brother must have...
laid his hands upon the map by now.
What do you think will happen
if I die?
The world will know about your sins.
Then, you'll be put behind bars
for good.
Just like little Sang Ho...
who couldn't get outside on his own.
What?
So that means...
you're not the only one
who can read the map.
What are you thinking?
Kwon Jae Chun's
dead son and daughter.
And his only alive son, Ki Ho.
He might show up...
because he might've learned
that I have the book.
When will you think about us?
I won't. You're already mine.
As long as you trust me
and remain unwavering,
we're safe.
How can we trust you
when you're so swayed?
Time is running out.
And now that I'm a grown-up,
I can take care of it by myself.
Did you look into it?
Until two years ago,
the Suncheon branch...
of New Life Church had been located
at the site.
They disbanded the branch
when they sold the land.
Can you check if Pastor Kwon went
there before it was torn down?
- Sure.
- Thanks.
Young Jin.
- Yes?
- You know...
we fumble around most of the time
until we solve cases.
- What is it you want to say?
- This is just what we do.
- Just work.
- You're right.
It's just work. It clears my head.
Thank you.
Can I hit the road now?
Where are we headed for?
I'll get off the wrong track now,
and start working properly
back there.
- Anything weird?
- Yes.
We found a clear footprint
above the buried body.
It's the product of a premium
hand-made brand with only one store.
The size is 270 mm.
- Get the customer list.
- Okay.
So it's not the same as the one
we found in the container.
- No.
- It's suspicious.
It's fishy.
- I'll make a call. Excuse me.
- Sure.
- Yes, Ms. Cha.
- How is everything there?
Nothing special. Did you find it?
No. I'll explain when I get there.
What about Eun Ho?
He's walking pretty well
holding onto the wall.
I want to talk to her.
He wants to talk to you.
- Are you all right?
- Yes.
You sound tired.
Of course.
I stayed up all night long.
But you're driving now.
- Get some rest first.
- I can deal with it.
Is that guy with you?
You don't need to worry.
Go back and continue working.
- Is it Eun Ho?
- Yes.
I've wanted to know
what kind of person you are.
I found it in Eun Ho's ward.
It was attached under the bed.
I feel uncomfortable.
Eun Ho and I have been friends
for seven years.
You're 20 years older than him.
Do you think that's right?
To be frank,
you only keep in touch with him
to feel superior to me.
I'm a good adult.
What kind of mother is that?
Don't you say that to yourself?
Am I wrong? Why?
Why do you think...
Stop.
Let go of me.
I was very curious...
about what you said to Eun Ho's mom
outside the ward...
because her attitude changed
totally afterward.
You can say
whatever you want to me...
because you're no one to me.
But watch your mouth
in front of your son.
You're his mother.
No matter how kind and friendly
someone is,
that person can never replace you.
That's what parents are
to their kids.
But Eun Ho had his mom
by his side.
How could you take care of him
for seven years?
You just heard it.
Eun Ho and I are friends.
He talked to me and worried about me
first.
I just did
what I was supposed to do,
but he called me a hero.
I was lonely,
but I was fine with it.
But I realized this
after Eun Ho got injured.
That I haven't been lonely.
Eun Ho, can you come here
by yourself?
I'll try.
- It's tough, isn't it?
- A little.
Still, I'm happy.
I wish I could run.
We should play soccer
after you recover.
What about Felony Crime Section One
versus Class 2-2?
- Sounds good.
- Before that,
let's eat breakfast first.
I'm hungry.
What are you doing here?
Didn't you go to school?
It's Saturday.
- Right. Did you have breakfast?
- No.
Tell me whatever you want.
It's on me today.
I met Eun Ho's mother on our way,
and she gave us this gimbap.
What about her?
She said she'd have
some hangover soup.
- Is your mom a good cook?
- No.
That was flat.
Eun Ho is good at cooking.
Because my mom is too busy to cook.
I have to do it.
Let's have a pork belly party
at the rooftop of my house later.
The room isn't spacious,
but it has a great view.
Are you in?
- What about you, Min Sung?
- I will if I can.
If I can make it,
I'll bring beef or lobster.
You're annoying, but I hope
you can make it for sure.
- Let's eat and go back to work.
- Okay.
Do you work on weekends too?
We work 24 hours
until we arrest the culprit.
Isn't it cool?
See?
Yes, sir.
Yoo Pan Sool was found buried
at the place with the container.
I'll send other guards,
so return to the office right away.
Yes, sir.
- What was it about?
- They're sending other guards.
We have to go back to the office.
All right, let's eat.
Here you go. While we're at it,
let's fill enough of ourselves.
Baek Sang Ho's voice is
recorded here too.
There isn't a world
where no one gets hurt.
That is why...
I've chosen to be on the side
where I wouldn't get hurt.
Will you also have a chance
to choose a side?
Eun Ho, make sure you wake up.
Then I will...
I couldn't hear his voice from here.
Maybe he whispered.
Give it to me.
(Superintendent Han Geun Man)
- Yes, sir.
- Are you with Ki Ho?
- Yes.
- Come straight to the office.
Yoo Pan Sool was found dead
this morning.
- Are you listening to me?
- Where?
Buried at a place with the container
with his neck broken.
Okay.
Let's go.
- I was right.
- Thank you for your hard work.
Don't mention it. It's our duty.
You're the one
who's going through a lot.
It was so hard to open
the door of this room at first.
It felt like
opening the gate of hell.
But now I'm excited
before opening it.
I wonder who's here...
and what they will
talk about with Eun Ho.
So...
I'm a little worried about
when he leaves the hospital.
We might go back to the past.
So what if you do?
You understand each other now.
Contact us when you start working.
I'll go get my hair done there.
People never come after saying that.
- Make sure you come.
- Okay.
I'll visit your shop for sure.
- Thank you so much.
- I'll get going then.
Take care.
- Bye.
I drove last time.
- Hold on.
- What?
Sir, we might be a little late.
We got the tail.
- Good day.
- It's the same motorbike.
He wanted the painting to be done
by the end of the day.
- Do you know his name and number?
- No.
- He paid in cash too.
- Take a look at this.
Right, that's him.
(Namdong-gu Tow Pound)
- No dash cam is installed.
- No GPS device either.
It's 1,000 dollars each.
He carried 6,000 dollars in cash.
Where did he get
all this money from?
Hello?
Okay, we'll go there now.
Jang Ki Ho is arriving soon.
Working properly was arresting me?
Yoo Pan Sool was found dead.
You're the important testifier
of his death case.
Why isn't he getting off?
This was found under Eun Ho's bed.
Okay, I'll request
for identification.
Request them
to compare the DNA with the one...
found at the crime scene
of Lim Hee Jung's murder case.
Okay.
It's not Jang Ki Ho.
Right.
He was with Ms. Cha
at the riverside nearby...
around the time
Yoo Pan Sool was murdered.
Stay away from Sang Ho
for the time being.
Don't leave the place
provided by us.
There's no need.
Just tell him
that I couldn't solve the map.
He wouldn't believe it.
You don't believe me either.
Right?
You think I took you
to the wrong place on purpose.
I suspected you at first.
Now,
I don't know.
You're frustrated
to have found out...
that your world was not real.
Could it be an act to deceive me?
My father always gave roles...
to Sang Won and Hee Jung.
I was always the exception.
They said I was one of them,
but I never got to be part of them.
I was just an outsider.
Live the rest of your life...
as a protagonist.
All right then.
Use me as bait to get Sang Ho.
I refuse.
You don't trust me.
You'll be in danger.
I don't care!
Then...
it will be in vain
that Eun Ho saved your life.
- Did you find the book?
- Not yet.
Why do you think
he left the book with me...
when it was
as important as his life?
I wish I didn't take it.
If then,
I wouldn't have
had to go through this.
Do you regret saving his life?
He hesitated a little.
I don't.
Then he said he didn't.
I would've saved him
even if I'd known he was a bad man.
I got the list of buyers.
I sorted them out
in alphabetical order.
Wait.
- There we go.
- Is it Oh Doo Seok?
Yes. "Oh Doo Seok, 270."
The sole of his shoe is the same
as the mark found at the site.
It's strange
how things are going so smoothly.
He isn't an amateur,
so why did he leave a trace?
- Welcome.
- We're back.
We're back.
- Aren't you going to report?
- You found it.
We found the man
who snatched Eun Ho's backpack.
I'm guessing it's a familiar name
this time again.
It's Baek Sang Ho's secretary,
Oh Doo Seok.
We got his name too.
- Yes.
- The footprint and the snatcher...
both indicate Oh Doo Seok.
- What about our colleagues?
- They're waiting for your order.
(Cha Young Jin)
Team One, protect Ki Ho
and reinforce the investigation.
Team Two, you're going
to the hotel with me.
- All right, move.
- Okay.
(Oh Doo Seok)
Follow me.
This place has high security.
The police will come at night.
- I see.
- Put this on.
In case of emergency,
press this button...
to let us know where you are
and come for you.
Here. Open your mouth.
Good.
It's more accurate
when it's dried properly.
I have a question.
What happens if you can't tell
whose DNA it is?
Simply put,
we've been given false hope.
- Hello.
- You remember me, right?
Of course.
We're getting this place
completely remodeled.
It's a bit messy.
You started the construction
quite urgently.
It was planned a long time ago.
I saw a picture of your friend...
and a red phone.
I saw them in the study
on the tenth floor of the hotel.
- Is the tenth floor part of it?
- Of course.
We're changing everything...
so that we won't even remember
the traces of the past.
It'll be all new.
By the way, what brings you here?
I'm here to see Mr. Oh Doo Seok.
But his phone is off.
Is he in the hotel,
or is he with Chairman Baek?
Is this because of Ko Eun Ho's fall?
Will your answer change
according to my reason?
No.
Actually, I'm pretty anxious
about Manager Oh.
He disappeared two days ago.
And before that,
he asked me to get him
a huge amount of money.
- So did you give him the money?
- No, not yet.
He's probably waiting for my call.
He told me his new number...
and asked me to give him a call.
Give me the number.
I think I can only cooperate
if you tell me what it's about.
I remember you cooperated...
so willingly until now...
to the point where we thought
we should have come to you first.
Skip all these meaningless
gestures,
and give me the number.
- Locate him now.
- Yes, ma'am.
I hope you will cooperate...
with us to the end
and not be moved with compassion.
Don't you worry about that.
I'm trying to separate from him.
Wait.
Mr. Han.
- I'll drive.
- Pardon?
You guys stayed up all night.
Get some sleep on the way.
Give me the key.
(Sang Ho)
- Hello?
- How did it go?
I couldn't find anything
in Young Jin's house.
But I found some of the residences
of the ginseng diggers in that town.
I'm on my way there.
Don't be sad thinking
that I always put you up...
to the hardest jobs.
You know that you'll be getting
the biggest reward, right?
You saved me when I was dying.
- I've already been rewarded.
- Be careful not to be seen.
(Calling)
- How long do I have to wait?
- It'll get there soon.
Hang up.
Wait here.
- What?
- You're our command center.
Right. Don't get hurt.
- That's an order.
- Sure.
- Yes, sir.
There's no sign of him leaving.
How long will it have been
since he escaped?
It hasn't been long.
Why would he have left through here
if it weren't for us?
He must have seen us
through that window.
He's still around here.
Ms. Yoon and Mr. Lee, go that way.
- Yes, ma'am.
These are live rounds now.
Ms. Cha.
It's over, Doo Seok.
Over? Since the moment
my kidney was...
replaced by someone else's,
I got an extra life.
Ending it this way isn't so bad.
Oh Doo Seok,
I hereby place you under arrest...
for murdering Yoo Pan Sool
and attacking Ko Eun Ho.
You have the right to remain silent.
You have the right to stop
answering at any time.
Sang Ho.
- What do we do with Doo Seok?
- I'm not sure.
- What should we do?
- Of course, we have to save him.
Wrong.
What should I do?
- You should listen to what he says.
- Wrong.
Are you going to abandon him?
He abandoned us, okay?
Hee Dong.
What should I do here?
- Abandon him?
- Correct.
Geez.
Doo Seok still remains silent,
right?
Ms. Yoon looks fine, but you should
go home and take some rest.
I'm fine.
We're not fine.
Now I'm scared of you two.
We'll have a meeting.
Go home if you can't take part
properly.
Just go when you can.
- I'll stay.
- Me too.
Let's begin.
How come no one here listens to me?
He seems to have decided
to take all the blames.
Why are we not getting
the search warrant?
Would there be anything left there?
The Millennium Hotel is going
through an all-out renovation.
They must've got rid
of the cell phone and photos.
How did it go?
We found the fingerprints...
of Ki Ho and Tae Hyung
from the recorder Ki Ho gave us.
We also found two different DNAs
except that of Ki Ho.
One of them matches.
The one from the place
where Hee Jung died?
No, from the site
where Sang Won fell.
- From the rooftop?
- And...
from the evidence
of the first stigmata murder.
(From Ha Ru to my sister)
(The sample 1 and 2 are confirmed
to be identical.)
(Seo Sang Won)
See you tomorrow.
- Bye.
- See you.
(Detective Cha Young Jin)
Why isn't she calling me?
Does she really have no idea
how worried I am?
(Detective Hwang In Beom)
I'm sorry I called you
at this late hour.
I just remembered...
that you said we should drink
together some other time.
Are you free tonight?
She hasn't called me yet either.
Did she say she'd call you?
Not really. We don't usually say
that to each other.
She said she'd call me.
Of course, I know...
she's working on an important case.
Still,
I just think she could care...
about someone who worries
about her and waits for her.
I just asked her boss,
and nothing dangerous happened
today.
You really don't need to worry.
- Let's make a toast.
- Okay. I'll no longer worry.
(Cha Young Jin)
Pick it up.
Hello?
I'm drinking in a pub.
What happened?
I'll send you the address.
Drop by on your way.
Okay.
If you have a visitor,
I'll go home first.
No. Wait until she comes.
(564-2 Hyeonjong-dong,
Mapo-gu, Seoul)
(Detective Cha Young Jin)
- Yes, Ms. Cha.
- I failed to find it.
I think Kwon Jae Chun gave
the wrong information to Ki Ho...
Are you all right?
I am.
I wish I could meet you in person,
but I guess it's too late, right?
If you have time now,
come to the address I send you.
Okay. I'll be there soon.
I'm sorry. I've got to leave first.
Just wait a bit longer.
But...
Excuse me.
(564-2 Hyeonjong-dong,
Mapo-gu, Seoul)
Did you just talk to Ms. Cha?
She said she'd come to meet me,
and I'm letting you join us.
Thank you.
Here.
The DNA from the recorder...
matches Sang Won's DNA
from the rooftop...
and evidence from the first victim.
So your intuition about him having
an accomplice was right.
- Good job.
- This is just the start.
I'm proud of you.
Thanks to you,
I have a chance to start.
I could give up mid-way.
I could get out of it
because you'd see the end of this...
without me.
So let's stop thanking and blaming.
- All right.
- Goodness.
We've been talking among ourselves.
It's fine. It was good to listen to.
This case would've wounded you two
deeply.
The more you know about each other,
the more you'd feel the pain
and comfort each other.
It was good to see and hear those.
Also, I felt envious.
Young Jin, let me tell you
one last time...
about what I thank you for.
I have a lot of people around me
now.
Dong Myung, Han Sol,
Min Sung, and Mr. Lee.
Mr. Lee. Let's be drinking buddies
from now on.
We can let Young Jin join us
from time to time.
Shall we?
Then I'll join you next time.
Why? Do you need to go back
to the office?
Yes.
See you again.
Sure.
Don't you feel stuffy in here?
- No.
- I guess...
you didn't complain about staying
at a container either.
On the afternoon
when Hee Jung was killed,
you met Eun Ho
and gave him the book.
Then at the end of the day,
you met Yoo Pan Sool...
and entrusted yourself to him.
We're going to record that process.
By the way,
what happened to Oh Doo Seok?
Of course, we caught him.
Don't you know Ms. Cha?
But they got hurt. Gosh.
- Did she get hurt?
- No.
People in our team got hurt,
not Ms. Cha.
She paid him back by four times.
Doo Seok won't say anything, right?
Well, he's trying to take the fall
for it.
Hey.
All right. Let's start.
An ordinary one is fine.
- Goodbye.
- Bye.
Thank you.
Come in.
- Let's talk.
- Sure.
Come on in.
I thought you wanted to talk.
I don't know where to start.
I'm going to tell Sun Kyung
about Eun Ho.
Why?
Because you'd feel better if you do?
Do you have to be that mean?
You know that I had no idea.
I didn't act as if I didn't know.
If you didn't know,
could you be understood?
I'm talking about me.
The business carried out
by the foundation,
is it related to the church?
You don't need to know.
You've seen me since I was a baby.
When I first saw you,
you were almost all grown up.
Why are you talking
about the obvious?
I know how much you care
and worry about me.
You treat me
like your younger brother.
In extreme cases,
like your son.
But Hee Seob,
I'm an adult now.
It doesn't matter how hard you try
to protect me.
There is no way for you to stop me
from getting hurt.
I want to know everything now.
I want to get hurt completely.
And after that,
in the way I believe is right,
I want to get better.
Come in.
What are you doing?
You should get ready for church.
Right. I should.
Sun Woo,
let's go together.
You know he won't go.
No.
- I'll go too.
- What?
Really?
Yes.
What's the occasion?
Let's go. Come out.
Hurry and get ready.
- This is Jang Ki Ho.
- Hello.
Are you at the church now?
Yes, I'm at the headquarter
of New Life Church.
It's Sunday, you know.
There's something
I'd like to tell the world.
Will you come and hear it?
Sang Ho will hear the news
and show up.
That'd be great.
Come so we can have
a cup of tea afterward.
There's a nice set of teacups
in the Pastors' Office.
Uncle, let's go.
(Detective Cha Young Jin)
Hello, pastor.
My hotel is under construction,
so I don't think
I can join the service today...
Deacon Jang Ki Ho is there?
Then I must be there.
Let this message of life
given by the Lord...
become our daily life...
and give us strength.
Let us be full...
of comfort and peace.
Through today's graceful message,
let us overcome...
the problems ahead of us.
(Pastor Kwon Jae Chun)
(Closed)
Now it's time for confession.
I have been born again.
As you know,
Pastor Kwon Jae Chun founded
our New Life Church.
He died
of an unexpected heart attack.
Recently, my heart also stopped...
on the street
where there was no one.
When I was guided
by the Lord's hands,
I saw the sight of my father,
Pastor Kwon Jae Chun.
For the first time in my life,
I shouted out his name all I wanted.
If I followed him then,
I might've met the brothers
who were going to follow me soon.
My non-beating heart was in peace.
But...
it was suddenly grabbed
by two warm hands.
Then I heard a young voice...
telling me desperately...
to open my eyes...
and to breathe again.
At that moment,
my heart started beating again.
My body...
was back...
with intolerable pain.
After returning
from the gate of death,
the first thing I saw was
the face of a boy.
Covered with sweat and tears,
his face seemed relieved
with pure joy.
That was the first sight
of this world...
after coming back to life.
Kindness and sacrifice
without any cost.
The delighted face of the boy.
Then I realized
the true meaning of resurrection.
It's meaningless
to be born again physically.
Only when you're born spiritually,
your groundless pain in life...
can be changed to joy.
Living is from your instinct.
But living a humane life...
is from your nature.
And it'll be your joy.
There isn't any reason to it.
I was away from the church,
and finally for the first time,
I was able to sense
the scent of joy...
from someone else.
Now for the rest of my life,
I plan to experience the joy myself.
I hope you welcome...
your spiritual resurrection
and its joy...
like a miracle, a gift,
or a daily life.
- Amen.
Amen.
Hey.
What took you so long to show up?
The temporary pastor in charge is...
with the One Life Foundation.
Yoon Hee Seob is in a tough spot.
Anyway,
I'm glad you showed up.
Will you leave us alone?
Look, let's talk outside.
I have nothing to talk about
with you.
I'm sorry.
We raised the kid in the wrong way.
Well, I'll let you two talk then.
Do you want a cup of coffee?
Right, you like sweet coffee.
Your personality has changed.
I guess your sense of fear wasn't
brought back along with your life.
Hey!
Change your preference,
not your personality.
Oh, right.
It was this cup, right?
Here.
I know your preference.
It's your preference...
to decorate a worthless thing
with a flashy and expensive wrapper.
Or is it your nature?
I guess you're mistaken...
that I can't do anything
because there are a lot of people.
Sang Ho.
I'm not scared of you.
Why?
What you desperately want...
is only in my head.
I just need to get rid of the book.
Don't you think so?
You might know
if you have found the numbers.
There are 21 numbers, right?
5, 3, 4, 2, 0, 2
7, 2, 1, 3, 1, 2, 4, 4,
0, 5, 3, 1, 2, 1, 2.
Right?
But you can't find where your sin is
hidden with these numbers.
What is it that you want?
- The hotel?
- Ko Eun Ho.
- What?
- Eun Ho's safety.
Don't mess with him from now on.
There's no statute of limitations
to my father's deal.
Like your sin, I mean.
So that boy has to be safe
from you forever.
If then,
you'll also be safe forever.
What do you mean,
the statute of limitations?
Lim Hee Jung's case doesn't have
any statute of limitations.
While you were with Cha Young Jin,
what did you two talk about?
I don't know.
Sang Ho.
I don't think
Sang Won killed Hee Jung.
Ki Ho.
You don't know anything about him.
Okay?
Pastor Seo Sang Won...
loved me so much.
What he could do for me.
Don't worry. I won't tell anyone.
Stay away from each other.
Why would you show him this?
Get out.
Is Ki Ho under your protection?
Yes.
He has the book, and he's
the only one who can solve the map.
Mr. Baek.
- Please leave.
- Fine.
("New Life Gospel")
Is this fun?
Can we end it with this?
No.
We can start it.
Although it's invisible,
it's clearly part of him.
Starting from that,
I'm going to reveal everything
about him.
(Nobody Knows)
I'm not...
the old Cha Young Jin anymore.