(2012 Special Promotion Ceremony)
With a sense of duty,
contributed greatly
to the arrest of criminals.
We hereby order her to be promoted
up by one rank.
Presented by the chief
of Seoul Metropolitan Police Agency.
I'll call the next candidate.
Assistant Inspector Kim So Eun.
You're here.
- What is it?
- A present. Open it.
This person, with sense of duty,
(Senior Inspector Cha Young Jin)
We hereby order her to be promoted
as an inspector.
Presented by the chief
of Seoul Metropolitan Police Agency.
(Senior Inspector Cha Young Jin)
I have found the prime suspect...
of the eighth stigmata murder case's
accomplice or copycat.
It's the owner
of the Millennium Hotel.
Baek Sang Ho.
(Episode 14)
(Seven hours earlier)
Act like your usual self,
so they don't suspect anything.
You know who our opponent is, right?
Baek Sang Ho.
I'm going to catch that madman.
And let's go back home together.
Eun Ho.
This is as valuable as my life
which you saved today.
Hold on to it
until I come back for it.
And I'll make sure
to return this favor.
It won't take long.
It took too long.
Don't worry about Eun Ho.
You should go.
I'll stay by his side
until his mother comes.
Then I'll grab the book
and go to you.
You were surprised, weren't you?
I was surprised too.
My niece...
has an older brother related
by blood.
And he's a student in my class.
I couldn't accept it in my head.
Then I remembered the picture
Dong Myung's brother drew.
Ms. Cha.
Come and have a look at this.
It was in Dong Myung's notebook.
He drew Dong Myung's mother too.
Everyone is holding hands.
Even if you're not blood-related,
don't you think
you're connected like this?
I kept thinking about
what you said back then.
Even if we're not blood-related,
maybe we're all connected that way.
I know many complicated things
are headed our way,
but I have another dot connected
to me.
So I'm going to bear with it.
You're looking at me
like I'm a good child.
Yes, Mr. Lee.
You're a good person.
I hope the disciplinary hearing
goes well.
I'm going to make it go well.
If we give the book to Jang Ki Ho,
we can catch Baek Sang Ho, right?
(Jang Ki Ho)
- Yes.
- Ms. Cha.
Haven't you found it yet?
We found it.
Then can I trust you this time?
"No one knows about that day
or hour,"
"not even the messengers in heaven,
nor the Son, but only the Father."
Usually in "New Life Gospel,"
it's not disciples. It's angels.
When will you be here?
I'd get there when it gets dark.
Hello...
Shall I go with you?
No.
Eun Ho's alone in there
for too long.
Right. I'm going to go in first.
(Police Disciplinary Hearing)
I'll tell you the results
of the disciplinary hearing.
Senior Inspector Cha Young Jin.
We hereby deduct one month
of your salary.
Superintendent Hwang In Beom.
We hereby dismiss you
from your post.
You should leave first.
I'm going to go in
and say goodbye to them.
- I'll call you.
- Be careful.
Call me if you need
to come here again.
- I will.
- Right.
You're here.
I'll get going now.
See you.
("New Life Gospel")
By the way,
why are you looking...
for Deacon Jang?
What?
Will you excuse me?
This is an important call.
(Kim Tae Hyung)
Yes, tell me.
He came out less than ten minutes
after arriving at school.
Was he empty-handed?
He didn't have a bag
when he went in,
but he had a bag when he came out.
I'll call you later.
Drive safely.
Ms. Cha Young Jin came to school.
She talked to him in front
of Eun Ho's locker.
Then they both left.
- Were they both empty-handed?
- Yes.
Chairman Baek?
Oh, right. I apologize.
You still haven't told me
why you are looking for Deacon Jang.
Something important
became urgent too.
We'd have
to end our conversation here.
The eighth stigmata murder case's
accomplice or copycat.
It's the owner
of the Millennium Hotel.
Baek Sang Ho.
Sang Ho's study is
on the tenth floor of the hotel.
I got information
that someone found...
a picture of me and Choi Soo Jung,
the eighth victim,
and the red cellphone that we
presumed was taken by the murderer.
Was the source
an insider of the hotel?
No, the source was...
I can't reveal
the identity of the source.
Is the source credible?
My decision is...
- Yes, the source is credible.
- Ms. Cha.
- Yes.
- The hearing just ended.
And you'll take the case
of someone you know again...
right after the hearing?
I don't care if this will be
my last case.
Again!
"This is my last one, I don't care,
I can leave."
What does that make us
if you keep saying those?
You're what this organization needs,
and you're okay with leaving.
Then what about us...
who are unnecessary here
but still keep our places?
What about us?
Mr. Han, we're not that bad.
Shut it!
I need someone like you
so that I can last.
Do you understand?
- So what would you have us do?
- From now on,
I'll be in charge of this case
externally.
But you will all...
follow her directions.
- Any objection?
- No, sir.
Young Jin, continue.
Yes.
Thank you, everyone.
You don't have to say that.
We'll still follow your orders
no matter what.
Just tell us what to do.
Baek Sang Ho
is connected to everyone.
Seo Sang Won, Lim Hee Jung,
Jang Ki Ho, and Ko Eun Ho.
He was saved by Seo Sang Won.
There's a debt
between him and Hee Jung.
And he's looking for the gospel
that Jang Ki Ho gave to Eun Ho.
Eun Ho got sucked into that mess
while doing a favor for Jang Ki Ho.
Then what about Choi Dae Hoon,
Kevin Jung, and Lee Young Sik?
They must have been his decoys
to distract us from them.
Jang Ki Ho said that the proof
to catch Baek Sang Ho's in the book.
Is that reliable?
Why didn't he do anything
if something like that existed?
They even kept quiet...
about the murders between brothers.
Brothers?
What do you mean, Ms. Cha?
Are you saying Seo Sang Won
and Jang Ki Ho are brothers?
I think it's time for me to speak.
I got a call from the NFS
this morning.
Seo Sang Won and Lim Hee Jung's
DNA match on the paternal side.
Hold on. And you're saying...
Jang Ki Ho is also their sibling?
Yes, I heard it from himself.
It's getting more dramatic
and burdensome.
Before we secure
conclusive evidence,
we should be careful so that
the suspect won't be aware of this.
Team One,
you'll go to the hospital...
- and protect Eun Ho.
- Yes, ma'am.
Team Two, talk to Yoo Pan Sool
and get any information...
on Seo Sang Won
and Baek Sang Ho in the past.
By the way, who's Yoo Pan Sool?
The old man that caught us
following him.
Didn't you even know the name
of the person you were following?
I'm embarrassed for you.
- Ms. Hong...
- As usual,
I'll support you
with whatever I can.
I should do something too.
I'll call up my sources to see
if there's anything in the hotel.
Ms. Cha, won't it be dangerous
to meet Ki Ho by yourself?
He has a very sharp sense.
If there's someone else,
he won't give me the answer.
Now you will all push ahead
without hesitating.
Hello. No, please don't get up.
That's all right.
Where's Mr. Lee?
I'm afraid he already left work.
So we've missed each other.
I was supposed to...
get a book back.
Is it blue, by any chance?
Yes, it is. Have you seen it?
I saw him leave with it.
Did he now?
I should give him a call.
- Hello!
Those kids.
(Lee Sun Woo)
(Baek Sang Ho)
(One missed call from Baek Sang Ho)
(Kim Tae Hyung)
Hello?
Chairman Baek is going to call you
again. Pick it up this time.
Are you with him right now?
I'm hanging up.
Tae Hyung...
(Lee Sun Woo)
Yes.
I knew Tae Hyung was your weakness.
What are you doing with a kid?
What are you doing
without your students?
- What do you mean?
- Come to school this instant.
I'll give you 30 minutes.
Or I'm going in for
the closing meeting of your class.
What are you trying to do?
I have no idea what
I'm going to tell your students.
Should I tell them
about Min Sung's chauffeur?
Or should I...
tell them about how Eun Ho
didn't report the 30,000 dollars?
Or should I...
tell them about you and Tae Hyung?
They can learn something
from whichever story I tell them.
Don't mess with kids.
I used to be a kid too.
Your 30 minutes begin now.
Get set.
Go.
What's wrong with this?
(Senior Inspector Cha Young Jin)
- How did it go?
- Ms. Cha,
I think some parts were written
using a special type of ink.
It's not showing up in the picture.
And it's not showing up on the copy.
Then we have no choice but
to compare them page by page.
- I'll come and get it now.
- No, I'll do it.
If there's a secret in this gospel,
I think I should be the one
to do it, not you.
("New Life Gospel")
(Jacob, the son of Zebedee.)
(I will...)
Did Baek Sang Ho tell you
to do this?
Did he tell you to bring this?
- Yes.
- Do you even know what it is?
It's a book that has
the foundation's corruption hidden.
Tae Hyung.
Help me.
I need to return to school
in 30 minutes.
But...
I need to hand this
to Ms. Cha Young Jin now.
Are you asking me to help you
investigate our foundation?
Do you think I'm working
at One Life Foundation...
because I neither see
nor know anything?
I know
they're making profits illegally,
but I've seen them save
the lives of many kids.
Between Baek Sang Ho
and Lee Sun Woo,
whom do you think I'll trust?
I'm not telling you to trust me.
I'm asking you this
because I trust you.
You're lying.
Where should I go?
Hi, Eun Ho.
I told you visitors aren't allowed
except for his guardian and friends.
I met him in the hallway earlier,
and he looked healthy.
I wanted to say hi.
Eun Ho.
Do you remember this man?
No.
- I'm sorry.
- It's okay.
Let's talk outside.
Good job.
The person involved in the case
entered the minor victim's room...
when his guardian wasn't present.
- How should I interpret this?
- I didn't have any intention.
I just did it on a whim.
The kid is anxious at all times
because his memory isn't back.
Will you be careful?
I apologize.
Wait a second.
Eun Ho doesn't know...
your face anyway, does he?
Oh, I didn't have that in mind.
I've been watching him
since he received the award.
My heart moved faster than my mind.
It's all right now.
Okay.
You're here.
I dropped by on my way.
It's the same direction.
I see. I'll stay outside.
I have something to tell you.
I was going to do it
after I come back,
but I don't think
I can keep it until then.
The night before your accident,
you came to see me.
I'm sorry I let you go
just like that.
I knew you were acting unusual.
I knew it,
but I still sent you off.
It's not that I didn't know.
I acted like I didn't.
I'm sorry, Eun Ho.
Ko Eun Ho.
I'm leaving your side now...
to protect you.
It's not to catch the culprit who
killed Soo Jung but to protect you.
And...
to protect myself.
There's someone...
who took responsibility
for my wrongdoing.
It's not just you,
but I'm also being protected.
You protected me...
just like I did.
For the past seven years...
It's making me cringe.
When you were little,
you called me a hero
which was quite embarrassing.
I'm not a kid anymore.
You're still a kid.
You're only 15.
Do you want
to become an adult quickly?
No.
I want to take my time.
It's not so bad right now.
What's the market price
shown on the graph?
- It's 1 dollar and 50 cents.
- Then...
Five, four,
three,
two,
one.
Baek Sang Ho!
Wait.
Why don't we talk in your car?
Get in.
Goodness, nice bag.
What brand is it?
Sun Woo.
This.
Whose is this?
Why do you ask?
I have a book I need to get back
from Pastor Kwon Jae Chun.
I think this is it.
Where did you get this?
Eun Ho's classmates took it
from his locker and hid it.
Really?
("New Life Gospel")
That means it's mine.
I'll get going.
Oh, right.
Have you read it?
I've never read mine either.
I see.
You were an exception.
We needed to memorize this...
to be provided with warm food,
clothes, and a place to sleep.
We got whipped if we got
even a single word wrong.
I didn't know.
You just have to keep
living like that.
Not knowing anything,
and sometimes,
pretending not to know.
Mr. Lee.
- What's with the empty desks?
- You're late.
- I know.
- Come on.
I'm sorry.
What's wrong, Mr. Lee?
Did something happen to Eun Ho?
Eun Ho is fine.
Then what's wrong?
It's just that...
I came so late,
but you waited for me.
I'm grateful for it.
Mr. Lee.
Mr. Lee, this is so corny.
Okay.
Mr. Lee wanted me
to hand this to you.
He took the original book
back to school.
Thank you so much.
It must not have been easy for you.
Because I trust you, Ms. Cha.
I've watched you
as I was nursing Eun Ho.
He wasn't related or anything,
but you were so affectionate
and devoted to him.
I was fascinated and envious of him.
What I mean is,
this is not doing
Lee Sun Woo a favor.
It's helping Cha Young Jin.
Eun Ho and I...
have known each other
for seven years.
Bye.
Why don't you give Mr. Lee
another chance?
I hit him in front of other kids.
I'm not in a position
to give him a chance.
You were still a kid back then.
Make up with him
before you grow any older.
Yes. Did you get it?
I did.
- Are you okay?
- They took it away from me.
Be careful of Baek Sang Ho. And tell
the same thing to Tae Hyung.
- You should be careful too.
- Okay. I'll call you later.
Hello?
Okay. I'll be waiting.
I don't know him.
Not this guy either.
Am I supposed to recognize them?
No. If you do, that means
we're on the wrong track.
Have you seen this guy?
Yes.
- When?
- On the day before I fell,
I was on my way to meet Han Sol,
he turned up out of nowhere
and snatched my backpack.
Then, why didn't you call
the police? Do you remember?
Is it because of the money
you'd been hiding?
That's partly right.
But I thought it could've been
Min Sung's driver...
because the answer sheet...
for the exam that Min Sung gave me
was saved on my phone.
Do you think you can continue?
- Yes.
- Let's do it later.
We should check the security footage
of the motorbike first.
Sure.
- It must be very hard.
- It's nothing compared to Eun Ho.
There's nothing I can do for him
as his mom,
and that's what breaks my heart.
By the way, can you give me
the number of Min Sung's mom?
- That would be...
- Then, call her for me...
and tell her
that I want to meet her.
Tell her to come to my house then.
I'm not for sale.
Pardon?
Don't look me over from head to toe
as if you're appraising my value.
I'm sorry, but we should meet
again later.
I am afraid you might take
everything I say...
emotionally.
So you don't get it at all.
- Sorry?
- I'm a human.
A human with emotions.
My son had to go through
such a horrible thing...
because of your son. Of course,
it hurts and infuriates me.
- Leave the living room.
- Come have a seat.
Why did you show the answers
to Eun Ho?
I wanted to make up with him.
Then, why did you
have your driver...
scare Eun Ho in such a place?
- Enough.
- How can I possibly forgive you?
- Please don't.
- What?
Eun Ho got injured and Uncle died...
because of me.
I would never forgive me
if I were you.
So, are you not going to apologize
to me?
Can I?
I don't know what to do either.
But that's the only thing
you can do.
- Get home safely.
- Okay.
I'll come visit you in prison.
How lucky we are.
We, moms, are messed up,
but our kids are kind.
Good afternoon, sir.
Mr. Han.
Are you really Eun Ho?
You're a big boy now.
I wouldn't be able to recognize you
if I run into you somewhere else.
But I would.
I can't believe I haven't seen you
for such a long time.
We should see more often
with Dong Myung and Min Sung.
- How do you know them?
- Well,
Min Sung got in trouble at school,
and Dong Myung was there too.
- I was in charge of it.
- I want to know what happened.
If Min Sung had kept his mouth shut
to the end,
Dong Myung would've taken
all the blame.
But he confessed that
he hurt himself later.
- Hello.
- Hey. Nice to see you again.
Me too.
- What's wrong with him?
- What do you mean?
He looks serious.
Dong Myung, call Min Sung.
Do you want me to call him?
I don't have his number.
You went to work together.
How come you don't have his number?
His mom came to school
and created a scene today,
so he must be in an awful mood.
Make a call...
and tell him to come if he wants to.
Han Sol's surgery went well.
Please come in.
Did you guys make up already?
It was nothing after all.
What did you expect?
When he was with me,
he hit his forehead...
Never mind.
Will all of you three be studying
in the same classroom...
after Eun Ho is discharged?
That'd be exciting.
The case Eun Ho and Dong Myung
are involved in is dropped.
What's important is not to repeat
the same mistake.
Okay?
And someone else will be in charge
of you guys from now on.
- Why?
- I got fired.
Even I'm trying to put up with it
not to get kicked out.
Should we work part-time together?
I plan to give a helping hand
to my friend's farm.
You can work only during weekends.
- You'll be paid handsomely.
It's a job offered
by a former police officer.
It can't be so bad.
("New Life Gospel")
Shall we begin?
Let's see.
- This is it, right?
- It's "oh."
- Write it down.
- "Oh."
- Which page is it?
- It's on page 105.
- Focus, Hee Dong.
- Yes.
"I'm walking down the road."
It's the end.
- Did you find it?
- Yes.
Give me that.
- They're numbers.
- They are.
Twenty.
- Twenty-one numbers.
- It's 21 numbers.
What are these?
What could they be?
Sun Ah, come here.
Hey, it's your turn.
This is exactly...
why I sent you
to a prestigious university.
- The numbers are meaningless.
- What?
It's useless
unless we know what they mean.
- What about this?
- What?
How they use numbers
to locate something.
There are numbers
like this and this.
I think he means
the latitude and longitude.
- The latitude and longitude.
- You need 17 numbers for that.
Won't the rest of the four numbers
be the passcode?
Even if you're right,
we don't know the pattern to come up
with the latitude and longitude.
There will be
a ton of possibilities.
You're right.
So we need Jang Ki Ho after all.
Find Ki Ho.
What is this reaction?
I'm not asking you to find
a dead person.
- Cha Young Jin hid him.
- She doesn't have the gospel.
What do you think Ki Ho will do
if he finds out we have the gospel?
The moment you imply the incident...
No.
That would never happen.
I guarantee you...
- that Pastor Kwon never told him.
- Sang Ho.
Let's get rid of the gospel.
No one will be able to find it
without the gospel.
You're right.
And neither can I.
The gospel is in my hands.
All we need is Ki Ho.
If only we have Ki Ho...
Why am I doing this?
Why?
Because there's a threat
that will knock me down?
No, it's not.
Can't you see?
That is...
a piece of my soul...
that made me who I am now.
- Where's my book?
- In my backpack.
Give me the bag.
I'm fine. Let's get up there.
Doo Seok.
Do you have anything to tell me?
Sang Ho, the situation isn't
looking too good.
Eun Ho woke up,
and he'll regain his memory soon.
I wish we'd stop making this
riskier than it is.
Do you? And Hee Dong?
What? Me?
I think...
We're here thanks to Sang Ho, right?
I'm doing it if you want me to.
- Manager Oh.
- Yes?
Didn't you get the notice
telling you to come...
- to the SCS tomorrow?
- Me? Why?
What do you think?
It's about Eun Ho's fall.
It'll be all right.
Just answer as you practiced.
The problem is Doo Seok.
When Eun Ho regains his memory,
the detectives will find out
that you two took down Dae Hoon...
- in the abandoned building.
- Did Eun Ho see one of us...
hanging Dae Hoon?
As long as you trust me
and don't falter,
we'll be safe.
- How are we going to catch Ki Ho?
- Doo Seok.
Go to Cha Young Jin's old house.
Do you seriously think
she would have made it that obvious?
Her grandfather was
a ginseng digger.
Don't you think he would have had
a hideout in the mountain, Sun Ah?
There could be a clue
about the hideout in her house.
Go.
Okay.
Thank you.
Now show me the book.
What is this?
It's a transcript of
the book you gave to Eun Ho.
Where is my book right now?
- The contents are the same.
- Where is my book right now?
Don't tell me Sang Ho has it.
Did you need the book itself,
not the contents?
That's not it.
That means only you can find
the answer, doesn't it?
Is the transcript correct?
Yes.
Yoo Pan Sool's phone is turned off.
Please tell him to give me a call
when you see him.
Come to think of it,
I haven't seen him for a few days.
Your colleague was absent
for more than a day.
Didn't you try to reach him?
He probably sold his land
and went somewhere nice.
Pardon me? What do you mean?
He'd been so happy lately
saying that he got a chance...
to sell his land for a good price.
Why don't you check it at his home?
Anyway, please give us a call
when you see him.
(Assistant Inspector Kim Byung Hee)
(Kim Byung Hee)
You can ask me now.
Have you seen Yoo Pan Sool
in his house these few days?
Now that I think about it,
it was a bit quiet.
Every time he brushed his teeth,
he used to gag
like he was vomiting his organs.
But I didn't hear him do that
lately.
I saw that there weren't
any parking spaces.
Where does he park his truck?
Turn right at the end of this alley
and walk down the main road.
Then you'll see his shop.
He parks on the road in front of it.
- Thank you.
- Sure.
Wait.
(Tow notice)
It was towed the day
after we were caught tailing him.
His phone is off,
he's not even going to church
he used to go every day,
he's not at home,
his truck was towed,
and his shop is closed.
Where on earth is he?
Should we go to his land?
He could be in the container
where Jang Ki Ho used to hide.
He wouldn't be there.
He doesn't have his truck.
So you're saying you won't go?
When did I say I won't?
I only said that he won't be there.
- I think he will.
- Do you?
Why don't the loser buy beef?
- It's a deal.
Don't you...
dare buy me a burger
and say that it's beef again.
Did you hear me?
(In the midst of glory...)
Mr. Yoo Pan Sool, are you in there?
It's the police.
Are you in there, Mr. Yoo Pan Sool?
I want prime beef.
I wonder who tried to buy this land
at such a good price.
He's out again.
We better check
on Yoon Hee Seob too.
If we lose trace of him here,
doesn't it mean he's missing?
He has neither family nor friends.
I guess you're right.
Hello, Ms. Hong. Did you get
the last location of his phone?
It's Highway 48.
- I'll send you the address.
- Okay, thank you.
- Where is it?
- Let me see.
It's nearby.
Where are you going?
What are you going to do with that?
- We need to find him.
- Is this because of beef?
We would've known where he is
if we hadn't gotten caught tailing.
Let's go.
What's with that face?
This work doesn't suit you, does it?
I guarantee you'll work in this team
until the day you retire.
Do you want to jinx it or what?
- How about we do that together?
- No, thanks.
I already settled down
in Felony Crime Team.
Let's please not meet here, old man.
Angels are changed to messengers.
Is it number four this time?
It wouldn't be hard if this was
only about finding numbers.
Even if people read this book
and find the numbers,
it wouldn't be of use to them.
To them,
it's just numbers
listed in disorder.
Ms. Cha.
A total of 21 words are different
from the original copy.
But they have one thing in common.
Within those words,
there are numbers.
Unless Jang Ki Ho has
another way to solve this.
But if he especially wanted
that book.
That means, the answer must start...
from those 21 words
whatever the case is.
(From the Genesis until now...)
- There are 21 of them.
- Right.
These numbers represent
that the world is full of sin.
Is this how you see the world?
To me,
twenty-one is
Eun Ho's favorite number.
Why does he like that number?
When he was little, he counted
the teeth of a bottle cap...
and said it was 21.
He counted the teeth every time
he saw a bottle cap since then.
Then he figured out...
that every bottle cap has 21 teeth.
That's why...
he likes that number.
It doesn't need a special reason
to like something.
Once this is over,
let me meet Eun Ho.
Is it because he saved your life?
Do I need any other reason?
If we leave now, we might arrive
at the break of dawn.
Let's go.
There may be something else
other than what will bring...
Baek Sang Ho down.
Whatever it is, it will all be mine.
Promise me.
I can't do that.
I'll let you have it
if you can prove it belongs to you.
Right,
I wouldn't have trusted you...
if you had accepted my demand.
Let's go.
Go to the two o'clock direction
in the next crossroad.
Jin Soo, come here.
Why? Did you find something?
Hey, no! Move.
Check this out.
The color is different here.
Bring me the shovel.
- Two o'clock from here.
- Do we still have a long way to go?
We're almost there.
(Hee Dong)
- Yes.
- Where are you?
I'm in front of Cha Young Jin's
old house in Gangwon-do.
Already?
What about the car?
I parked it nearby and walked here.
You're going through so much.
Did you take the medicine?
Yes, I need to go in now.
Let's hang up.
(Sun Ah)
- Did you arrive?
- Yes.
When can I leave?
I'll have things ready
as soon as possible.
Call me with a burner phone
from next time.
- I apologize.
I'll hold you responsible later.
Jang Ki Ho is the suspect?
Turn right a little while later
and you'll see a New Life Church.
Those numbers indicate more than
the church, right?
I can show you the way,
but I can't tell you how.
It's Pastor Kwon's gift given
only to us.
You should turn right soon.
"I tell you the truth,"
"this generation will certainly not
pass away until all these things..."
"have happened."
"Heaven and earth will pass away,"
"but my words will never pass away."
"No one knows
about that day or hour,"
"not even the angels in heaven..."
(Not even the messengers
in heaven...)
"Not even the messengers
in heaven..."
"nor the Son,"
"but only the Father."
("New Life Gospel")
There isn't any church here.
No.
- Are you sure about this place?
- It can't be.
Tell me.
- Is this the right place?
- No.
This can't be.
This can't be it.
(Nobody Knows)
Yoo Pan Sool was found dead.
You're an important testifier
of Yoo Pan Sool's murder case.
They wouldn't believe you.
Stay away from Baek Sang Ho
for the time being.
Don't leave the place provided
by us.
Jang Ki Ho.
He might show up on his own...
because he knows I have the book.
We're renovating the whole building,
so it's a little chaotic.
This place has nice security.
The police will be with you
later at night.
Mr. Jang Ki Ho is here?
The owner of my soul was Father.
I want to go back.
You two, go that way.
- Okay.
You must've found 21 numbers.
Five, three, four, two...
Don't worry. I won't tell anyone.
Stay away from each other.
Why did you show this to him?
I have been born again.