What?
Pack up and move back home.
But Dad...
You both said it's over.
So don't make excuses
about the house price...
and come back home.
I never thought of moving back in
after the divorce though.
I didn't ask for your opinion.
Just move back in.
We let you do what you want...
because we thought
you had your life under control,
but all you did was look down on us.
Would you have done such a thing
if you respected us?
You have one day.
Pack up your things
and move back home. Got it?
Should I call her?
My gosh, what happened?
Did you find your mother?
Yes, she came back home
around dinner time.
Is she all right?
Where on earth was she?
I don't know.
She probably got some fresh air.
Right.
Couldn't you have at least texted me
when you found out?
You know how worried I was.
What on earth do you need those for?
It's to pack up my things.
I'm moving back home.
Dad told me to.
I don't have a choice.
You know how scary my dad can be
when he's angry.
Let me get your books for you.
You can pack your clothes.
Do you have everything?
Think if you've left
anything behind.
I checked and I have everything.
We'll sort out the furniture
when we sell the house.
Sure thing.
I thought about us while packing up.
We had rough moments
over the three and a half years,
but there were
a lot of good times too.
Gyu Jin,
it must've been tough
living with me.
The same goes for you too.
I nagged about everything
and my mom wasn't the easiest.
Are we trying too hard
to part on a good note?
I mean what I said.
I was sorry.
And thank you.
Sure. We'll go back to
being good colleagues now.
You know I'm an outcast
at the hospital.
I'm counting on you to tell me
where they switched meetings to.
Or I guess I could ask
my former brother-in-law.
He's clumsier than he seems.
You're better off
trusting me with it.
Confide in me with
your love life if you need to.
I'll hear about it at work anyway,
so don't make it awkward
by trying to hide it.
Even after all this,
I'll still be the woman
who knows you the best.
I might come to you day and night.
Are you sure you can handle it?
As if.
I'll get going.
Sure.
I knew it.
It's why I told her to check.
I guess I'm back.
I'm home!
Mom?
Madam Jang, you're awake.
How are you feeling, Mom?
She seems okay to me.
- She seems better, right?
- Yes.
Let's be quick on our feet
and help her out today.
- Sure.
- Of course.
My gosh, Na Hee.
- Na Hee?
What are you doing here this early?
Can you look shocked
while helping me with my luggage?
Of course.
Dad, Mom, Na Hee is home!
You're home.
Hi, Dad.
Mom,
I'm home.
What...
Go ahead and unpack first.
He's right.
What's going on?
Just hear me out, honey.
Are you kidding me?
How could you do this
without asking me?
Honey, please.
I still can't look
at her right now.
I'm still angry at her.
It's why I told her to move back in.
So that you can vent.
You're angry with her, right?
So target your anger at her
whenever you feel like it...
until your anger subsides.
Just saying whatever you want
doesn't make it reasonable.
What nonsense are you spewing?
Gosh, my head.
Do you have a headache?
Hold on a second.
(Aspirin)
Here you go, honey.
Take this.
Forget it. Is this a joke to you?
But you said you have a headache.
Whatever then.
I have a headache too now,
so I'll take it.
Give me that.
Gosh, my head.
I had no idea you'd be back,
so the room is a mess.
You can take the bed.
I know you can't sleep
on hard surfaces.
It's fine. I'm not a monster
who takes whatever she wants.
How can you say that
when we're family?
It's fine. You take the bed.
I can't sleep just about anywhere.
Are you sure about that?
Yes, of course. No problem!
Thanks. I'll take the bed then.
My books will soon be delivered.
Is there any space for them?
Sure. You can take up
all the shelves.
All I need is
this section right here.
Shouldn't you have more books...
since you're studying
to go back to college?
What? Oh, right.
Well, I haven't been able
to get very far yet.
I'll buy more soon
as well as a workbook.
Isn't it better to study
for the university's English test...
rather than a nationwide
proficiency test?
The college you're applying to
asks essay questions for math.
You'll need to study statistics,
so where are you on that?
Right, I should get on that.
Kids, get down here!
You heard that, right?
We're being summoned.
This early in the morning?
Since you're all here,
you should say hello.
At the far end is Na Hee,
my second daughter.
These two
are Joon Seon's colleagues.
- I'm Oh Jeong Bong.
- I'm Lee Jong Soo.
I'm Park Hyo Sin,
the part-time delivery guy.
I know. I hope we get along.
I see that we're
quite a big family now.
How many are there exactly?
2, 4, 6, 8, 9.
Mom makes 10 in total.
What? Really? 10 people? No way.
We're all living under
the same roof now,
so get along.
Some may know this and some may not,
but we clean the entire house
every weekend.
Like always,
you're responsible
for your own living spaces.
The men will clean the bathrooms,
the women will clean the kitchen,
and those living up top
will clean the living room.
Dad, I have a question.
Why are we in charge
of cleaning the living room?
She's the one who spends
most of her time here.
She's here nearly 24-7.
How is it fair for four guys to
only clean that tiny room upstairs?
The fact that the four of us
live in that tiny space...
should be a mitigating factor.
Have you not heard of
weighing the pros and cons?
Shut it, you two.
Ga Hee can clean up
some of the space then, okay?
Wise as always, Dad. Salute!
I'll help out
cleaning the living room.
It's all right.
I'll take care of it.
You can stick to our room.
I'm sorry, Dad,
but I need to sleep in late...
to recharge my energy on weekends.
Could I pay a fine instead?
A fine?
We can order Chinese food with that.
Right. Make it a steep fine...
so that we can order
some fancy dishes.
That's enough.
Don't you dare get cheeky with me.
There will be no exceptions
as long as you live here.
It's our rule to clean on weekends,
so stick to it. All right?
- Right.
- Sure.
Over there. Yes, get that area too.
Over here, Ga Hee?
That's right.
We need to finish up here
and clean the porch as well.
I see you're not very agile.
You've got to be kidding me.
Are you still ordering him around?
I'm cleaning too.
Hold on.
Can you shake this out
if you have some extra energy?
My arms aren't strong enough.
Sure.
I knew it.
Gosh, look at those
shoulders and biceps.
Have you been working out?
You seem strong enough to me,
so do it yourself.
What was that all about?
He's a total jerk,
but a charming one.
I'll do that, Na Hee. You can rest.
It's fine.
I'd rather not get kicked out.
Where else do we clean? The kitchen?
Yes.
- Jong Soo.
- Yes.
Can you help out over here?
Don't slack off over there.
Put some force into the scrubbing.
Just so you know,
nagging is a trigger for me.
I'm just sick and tired of this,
you know.
Dad shouldn't make us pay rent...
if he's putting us
to work like this.
What's up, Mom?
We're almost done cleaning here.
Bring the radishes from storage
to the living room.
We're making kkakdugi.
Right now?
Can't we take a short break first?
I'll get them.
I just have to bring them
all out from storage, right?
Aren't I good at chopping these?
This is why the men
should be in the kitchen.
We'd appreciate it more
if you did it quietly.
I'm already pulling my weight.
Look at Na Hee for instance.
They're all uneven.
Mom, aren't I better at this
than Na Hee?
"Joon Seon spoke
but his mom didn't respond."
Mom, how about an apron?
I'll get one for you.
No, let me.
It's fine. I don't need one.
My back is killing me.
Na Hee, come on.
Let's hit the sauna.
The sauna?
Don't say that
like it's news to you.
We always used to go there
on Sundays.
And besides,
we each get a dollar discount
for a group of five or more.
I forgot about all that.
Anyway, count me out.
Don't be ridiculous. Let's go.
I haven't been to
a public sauna in ages.
Stop fighting with me on this.
Let's go.
What will you do
all alone at home anyway?
It'll be refreshing
to scrub your back.
But I don't want to!
Are you seriously
talking back to your sister?
Get up already. Up!
- Get up!
- What the...
Goodness, how refreshing.
Tell me about it.
They should be out by now.
Oh, there they are.
Ladies, this is a surprise.
You're never out here on time.
I didn't want to hear you nag,
so I left without drying my hair.
Anyway, you have no idea
how filthy Da Hee was.
I had to scrub her back forever.
I can't even feel my arms.
What are you talking about?
That's not true.
The drain was clogged up
after I scrubbed your back.
- Are you crazy?
- That's enough.
Did you get to relax your muscles
in the warm water?
Let's just go. I'm hungry.
Okay. Let's go.
Come with me, Madam Jang.
Get off me. That's annoying.
You're being so prickly.
Let's go.
Hey, don't mind her.
Weren't you prepared for this?
That's true.
Mom needs some time.
Just consider it your punishment
and bear with it.
Joon Seon and I went through
the same thing.
It's just that Mom seems
distressed to see me.
Of course she's distressed.
But I think Dad told you
to move in for a good reason.
So you should keep facing her.
That's the only option you have.
I'm not sure
if it would work for Mom though.
Just hang in there.
Why is she so skinny?
It looks like
she hasn't eaten anything.
Is she trying to show me
how hard it has been or what?
This is perfect.
This is where it belongs.
But I had to keep it
stuffed away in storage.
I love it.
This is very nice.
I should set up
the game console too.
Where is that thing?
She forgot to take this too.
She is such a handful.
I should bring this to her.
She wears it often.
Who...
- Gosh.
- Come and take this.
- Gosh, Mom.
- Hey.
What are you doing here?
You didn't even call.
Do I have to call ahead to visit?
You live alone now anyway.
I thought Jae Seok was
being inquisitive.
That's right.
I told him to spy on you. So what?
If she didn't move out,
I would've taken you to my place.
Why would you live with her
when you are divorced?
We just did it
since we couldn't sell the house...
That's enough.
I don't want to hear it.
I got you new bedsheets...
and a few cushions.
Go ahead and change them.
Why bother?
What I have here are new.
They are what she chose.
We will change them all.
Even the curtains.
What?
What is this?
- Isn't this her shirt?
- Yes, it is.
She moved out in a hurry,
so she forgot to bring it.
So? Will you fold it nicely
and bring it to her or something?
Of course. I don't need it here.
And she wears it often.
Gosh, Mom.
You're divorced.
You don't have to
bring her a shirt she forgot.
I'm not happy with you two
working at the same hospital.
Can't she find a new job?
She says she's competent.
Come on out and eat.
Joon Seon.
Come downstairs with the guys.
Okay.
Mom, what's with the feast?
Did you cook all these?
Who else would it be then?
Stop being silly and have a seat.
Enjoy your food. You probably
haven't eaten well for a while.
All right. Let's have a seat.
- Okay.
- Thank you for the food.
Mom, you should sit
and eat with us too.
Na Hee, come here.
All right. Let's eat.
- Thank you for the food.
- Thank you.
My mom's doenjang jjigae
is the best.
Do you guys know that
this can't be bought for money?
You know, right?
Of course.
Ms. Jang, your doenjang jjigae
is truly impressive.
He's right.
It's so good
that I feel like crying.
Right. It's really good.
You don't have to try so hard.
Just enjoy your meal.
- Okay.
- Yes, ma'am.
It's Na Hee's favorite,
seasoned eggplant. Ga Hee.
Try this.
Here. Eat a lot.
Is she the only one eating here?
I made it for everyone to share.
Gosh, I've been through
a lot lately because of Na Hee.
Hey, Seo Young.
What are you doing, Dad?
Me? I'm just lying down
after having a big dinner.
Did you eat dinner?
Not yet. I'm eating soon.
Dad. I have big news.
Guess what it is.
What is it?
I just got the test results
from the academy.
And my grades went up by 20 points.
Isn't that great?
What? Really?
How could you do that?
It makes me worried though.
You're so pretty.
Now that you're even smart,
what if your friends hate you?
Don't worry about it. I'm like you,
so I have a great personality too.
Dad, since I got good grades,
can you do me a favor?
Of course.
I can do you 10 favors. What is it?
I can't tell you right now.
I'll get back to you soon.
You have to do me a favor.
Promise me.
So if you're in your room,
is the cute guy there too?
You know, the guy who works
at Grandpa's store.
Yes. He's here. Why?
Can I talk to him?
It's been a few days,
so I'm afraid he might forget me.
Then it would be hard for me...
Gosh, he's jealous again.
You're so cute, Dad.
Seo Young, dinner.
Okay.
- Mom.
- Yes?
Ta-da.
What's that?
- Is it for the recent test?
- Yes.
It improved a lot.
See? You can do this.
Come here. I'm so proud of you.
Yes, Mom, I know I'm amazing.
You didn't forget your promise,
did you?
You said that you'd grant my wish
if I made it into the top 10.
Of course I'll keep my promise.
What is it?
- Do you want a new phone?
- No.
Let's eat out together as a family.
With Dad. Like other families.
I checked your schedules.
Tomorrow is Seo Jin's
Kindergarten interview, right?
I guess we can eat after that.
You're not going to go back
on your word, are you?
- Are you sleeping already?
- What?
No.
I was going to turn off
the light for you.
I can study with the desk lamp on.
It's okay. I'm fine.
All right. Thank you, Na Hee.
Was this bed always so big?
Done. Jong Soo, let's move on.
Okay.
Next.
I'm sorry, guys.
The mood at home has been
so serious lately,
so we can't do our morning workouts
or chat comfortably in the house.
It's fine, Joon Seon.
I prefer to exercise outdoors.
Me too. It's nice and cool.
Really? That's a relief, then.
But why won't anyone hire us?
Should I hand out
more business cards next week?
- Hey, Hyun Gyung.
- Can you talk?
Yes, of course. Go ahead.
You haven't forgotten Seo Jin's
interview this afternoon, right?
It's at 4 p.m. You can't be late.
I may be scatterbrained,
but I wouldn't forget that.
Don't worry. Trust me.
Shall I meet you at
the address you texted?
Will it take about an hour?
Yes. The interview
will be over in an hour.
Free up a few hours after as well.
Why? Is there something else?
No. Let's have dinner together.
Seo Young wants to eat out
as a family.
- It's her wish.
- We'll really...
- Joon Seon!
- Are you all right?
Why? Do you have plans afterwards?
Are you not free?
No, no.
Of course I'm free. I'm free.
I'll see you later. Bye.
Oh, yes. Oh, yes.
My gosh.
Your jaw might touch the floor.
Did you not sleep?
Does Na Hee snore?
No. It's worse than that.
You don't want to know.
You're leaving already?
Before breakfast?
Yes. I think I should leave
with time to spare.
Dad, I'm leaving for work.
Okay, take care.
Mom. I'm going out.
See you, Ga Hee.
Have a nice day.
Cheer up, sister. Good luck.
What a terrible sight.
She's like me three years ago.
Ga Hee. Could we have some water?
Exercising made us thirsty.
Of course.
Do you want me to serve you?
- No, no. Move it.
- I'll get it.
Where's Joon Seon?
Didn't he go out with you?
He's not in his right mind.
He's eating out with his family
after Seo Jin's interview.
Oh, really? He must be so pleased.
It's been a while
since he ate with them.
Hey, which is better, this or this?
- White.
- Black.
Neither of you are of any help.
Ga Hee, which one?
They both look terrible.
White went out of fashion,
and black will
make you look even scarier.
Still, white should be better.
It's a nice interview look.
Okay, then white it is.
What's the occasion that Hyun Gyung
suggested you eat together?
Is she giving you a green light?
It's not like that.
Seo Young begged.
It's just one meal.
It means nothing.
It doesn't mean anything.
Nothing at all.
Hang on.
Director Jo.
It has been a long time.
How have you been doing?
I need your help
with an urgent shoot.
A shoot? Of course I'll do it.
When is it?
Today?
Today is not a good day.
He was in an accident?
That's too bad.
No, it's just that I have some
personal affairs to take care of.
No, don't do that.
What time is the shoot?
I see.
Then we should be done before 3 p.m.
Then I'll do it. Thank you.
Director Jo, we'll definitely
be done before 3 p.m., right?
Mom?
Come over with Jae Seok later.
Let's have dinner together.
No, thanks. I'm fine.
I'm not fine.
If a divorced man loses weight,
people think you're upset.
It looks bad.
I'm not like that.
I cook well for myself.
Mom, I'm in an elevator.
I might get cut off. Bye.
You need to know
I lose weight because of you.
Good morning.
Don't go too far.
We never greeted each other
like that even as classmates.
Did we not?
You sure have a good memory.
Is it nice to be back home?
I'm trying hard to get used to it.
We all helped clean the house
on the weekend,
and even pickled radishes together.
You did that?
Instead of sleeping in? No way.
I couldn't believe it
even as I did it.
What about you?
Do you like having
the huge space all to yourself?
You bet I do.
It's great to watch soccer
when I want to.
Gosh. I'm sure it is.
It is.
I'm sure it is.
It made no sense.
How are you?
- Good morning.
- You're here.
Don't act like that.
You make us feel worse.
Yes. We'll go back to
being good colleagues.
Treat us as usual
without tiptoeing around us.
Or we really can't
work together anymore.
- Okay, then.
- Okay.
By the way,
the morning meeting was canceled.
The director decided to take
a leave of absence.
- Really?
- Is he very sick?
It's his high BP and diabetes.
He went on a sabbatical.
You should give him a call.
I should do that.
Did we cause him too much stress?
Goodbye, then.
See you.
He did lose control a bit.
He wouldn't stop drinking.
That is true, but...
Gosh, I feel so bad.
I'll call him.
Hey, Gyu Jin.
Na Hee, I mean... Dr. Song.
Did you hear? Our director...
- We heard.
- He took time off.
His blood pressure and diabetes...
We heard that too.
- I'll go ahead. See you.
- Bye.
What's going on?
You two get on better
now that everyone knows.
Is this the Hollywood way?
Be quiet and get ready for work.
Who will be the new director?
Did you hear anything?
I'm sure Director Jang
figured something out.
They could be from Sejin Hospital
since they're our partners.
That's where Director Jang was from.
Let's practice.
Block and kick.
Two is easier.
You're ready.
When will we shoot this darn scene?
Director Jo, hang on.
Why... Why is there a delay?
You said we'd be done by 3 p.m.
I can't stop the lead actor
from leaving to shoot a commercial.
I'm dying here trying to sort out
the locations we booked.
- But still...
- I'm so sorry.
- I'm...
- Can we do 6 p.m. instead?
The shoot got delayed.
That punk just walked off
before I was done talking.
Do that again and I will crush you.
I don't care. I did what I could.
He can shoot without me.
Where is Young Chul's stunt double?
- Let's shoot. Get over here!
- I'm here!
This is crazy. What should I do?
I'm coming!
Song Seo Jin's parents.
We're ready for you.
Ma'am.
Is Seo Jin's dad not here yet?
Not yet.
I'm sorry.
Because of the program we run,
we must see both parents.
I should apologize.
My husband isn't usually late.
I guess something suddenly came up.
I'm sorry.
Hyun Gyung! Hyun Gyung!
My goodness.
Hello, Ma'am.
I am Song Seo Jin's father.
- What?
- I ran over.
I'm sweating so much.
Please take good care of my Seo Jin.
Sure...
Hyun Gyung, I'm sorry. Hyun Gyung.
They said we would be done by 2 p.m.
I thought I'd have time to
shower and change,
so I took the job.
The jerks in this industry
really never keep their word.
They never keep promises.
I was so angry with
the scumbags that I...
5 times. I reminded you 5 times.
"It's important. Don't be late.
You cannot be late."
What did you say each time?
You said, "Don't worry, trust me."
I'm sorry.
I trusted you.
This time was about you as a dad,
not a husband.
I didn't think you'd
let me down with this too.
But you really never change.
I'm sick of it.
I'm very sorry.
I'm in the wrong.
I don't even dare make an excuse.
Apologize to Seo Young, not me.
I don't think
I can sit across from you and eat.
Dinner is off.
(Episode 28)
Gosh, does that mean I'm it?
I told you not to
give the ball to the nerd.
Darn it.
You...
What? Why?
- Here you go.
- Thank you.
- I'm back.
- There you are.
You have to go
right back out though.
One is for the shoe shop and...
The other is for Hyoseong Apartment
Building A, right?
I'll get going.
He's not just handsome
but good at his job too.
What would we have done without him?
Is Ok Boon still depressed?
I guess. She stays in bed all day.
We have a big group
coming in tomorrow.
Would we be able to handle it?
We'll manage, I guess.
You should grab some lunch instead
of working on an empty stomach.
It's not just me though.
What about you?
I don't have much of an appetite.
Grab a bite to eat
before the dinner rush comes in.
Sure thing.
I'll get you something
on my way back.
Gosh, I'm aching all over.
Why must I suffer like this
whenever my nieces and nephew...
cause trouble?
Bye!
- Bye, kids.
- Bye.
- Get home safely.
See you!
We're out of eggs and spinach.
I should get some groceries.
What, already?
This is because you're
too generous with the ingredients.
Customers won't come back
if it seems like...
we're ripping them off.
I rolled all the kimbap,
so just slice and serve them.
- Sure.
- I'll get going.
Can I get some kimbap?
Yes, of course.
Have a seat, Ms. Jang.
It's good to see you.
Welcome.
What's with that expression?
You're saying you're glad to see me,
but you all look annoyed.
Of course not. Please have a seat.
Enjoy your kimbap then.
It seems like the merchants
come around here often.
Who's your most frequent customer
these days?
The owner dried fish store
or Mr. Yang from the butcher shop?
These days,
it has to be Mr. Yang, right?
Right. He's here almost every day.
Is that so?
It's you, isn't it?
You're the one flirting with him.
Is it you then?
Does Mr. Yang come here to see you?
Does he?
- Please enjoy.
I dare you to come, Yang Chi Su.
I'll block your view
so you don't see either of them.
I don't know why,
but she keeps getting on my nerves.
Cho Yeon, my goodness.
- Are you heading somewhere?
- Yes, I'm off to buy groceries.
Is that so?
That's great. I was on my way
to buy groceries too.
- We can go together.
- Didn't you want some kimbap?
No, I was just walking by.
Anyway, please lead the way.
You didn't have
to carry this for me.
It must be heavy
with all the radishes.
Don't sweat it.
I have nothing but strength anyway.
If you're grateful,
you can buy me sundaeguk sometime.
Why not?
I'd like to thank you
for all the free meat anyway.
Really? Then I'll have two bowls.
Goodness.
It's heavy, isn't it? Here. Let me.
It's not heavy at all.
I was just working out...
both of my arms, you see.
I like to sneak in
short workouts here and there.
- Gosh.
- Forget it. Let me carry that.
No, it's fine.
I don't want you to hurt yourself.
My gosh. Cho Yeon, wait for me!
Wait up.
I see he's not coming by today.
He won't be able to get any ideas
with me sitting here.
Get cheeky all you want.
Nothing you do will get by me.
Today is my lucky day!
Wait, it's from Mom.
Seo Young, dinner is off.
Come straight home.
Seo Young!
Hi, Dad.
My gosh.
I offered to buy you steak,
but this is what you choose?
I have money, you know.
I know.
I just wanted to eat tteokbokki.
I've been craving this all day.
Is that so? Then eat up.
Have some more after that.
I will.
Seo Young,
I'm sorry.
I know how much
you looked forward to this dinner,
but I blew it.
It's fine, Dad.
You've already apologized enough.
It gets old at some point.
Is that so?
Seo Young, have you ever hated me?
No. Why do you ask?
It's true that
I'm not like other dads.
I don't have an ordinary job
and I don't get along with your mom.
It's why I can't be
in your life more.
I don't mind it.
Since you live apart,
I get pocket money from both of you.
Also, I have a place to hide
when Mom starts nagging me.
I can choose to be wherever I want.
The other kids don't know
how fun that can be.
I know you're lying.
You want us to be
like a normal family...
and wish for me to work
at an office like other dads.
I know you've thought of that.
That's not true at all.
You're a CEO...
while the others are employees.
You're way better.
I'd rather die
as the daughter of a CEO.
Besides, your business
will take off soon, right?
I'll have to ride it out.
Ride it out?
Yes, I'll hang on
until you finally make it.
Hold on.
I want a corn dog.
Can I order one?
Of course.
Anything for a CEO's daughter!
Have 10 if you want.
Can we get 10 corn dogs?
- Sure thing.
- 10 corn dogs?
Nice!
Gosh, it's good.
Hi.
It's "buy 1, get 1 free".
What grade are you in?
Fourth?
Fifth.
Fifth?
You're small for a fifth-grader.
How are things at school? Is it fun?
Yes, it is.
Is that so?
Let's get together often
at this place.
They have "buy 1, get 1 free" deals
quite often.
Sure thing.
You're home.
It's late. Do you want dinner?
I grabbed some with Dad.
Don't get mad at me, okay?
I wanted to keep our promise,
- but your dad...
- I know.
Dad told me everything.
I know it's his fault.
But Mom,
what is it that you always tell me?
I don't have to be the best
as long as I try my best.
You said that's enough.
Dad may not be the best
but he's trying.
He's trying very hard.
It's clear to me,
so why isn't it to you?
Seo Young...
They're corn dogs.
Dad bought it for you and Seo Jin.
Thank you for the meal.
What's wrong? Are you done already?
Yes, I just don't have
much of an appetite today.
Take your time with your meals.
What's up with him today?
Food is what he lives for,
so why on earth
doesn't he have an appetite?
Did something happen?
- Well...
- You see...
He was excited
about a family dinner,
but I guess it didn't happen.
He was late.
He was late for an appointment?
Who? Joon Seon?
Yes, he was asked to fill in
for another stuntman.
The director promised
to finish on time at first.
What a pathetic idiot.
It'll be faster to wish for
a flower to grow in the desert...
than expect anything from him.
Mom, let me do that.
I have some time today.
Until when will you be like this?
What do you mean?
Don't play dumb with me.
I mean with Na Hee.
Until when will you ignore her?
You're the one who told me
to vent my anger.
I'm just baffled, you know.
You were cooking and everything,
so I thought
you were feeling better.
The eggplants and the other
side dishes were all her favorite.
Don't be absurd.
I'd be crazy to cook all that...
for a daughter
who stabbed me in the back.
Okay, fine.
There's no need to get riled up.
Whatever you say.
Are you coming to work?
Why not take at least
another day off?
Forget about it.
It's not like I can rest forever.
We have a big order coming in today.
I can't just leave you and Ok Ja
to handle it all.
Are you sure though?
The people at the market
are still gossiping about this.
I'll have to face them
sooner or later.
I can't hide at home
because of them.
I really need you to do this for me.
My sister is on her way here and...
Really?
She's already coming back to work?
Really? What about her daughter?
Is she really divorced?
See what I mean?
Just keep quiet for crying out loud!
This is why I took the time
to speak to you.
I know that you're not fond
of my sister...
and that you want to know
what's going on.
But she just made it back
from the devil's mouth,
so please don't say
anything to her today.
Don't even mention
the letter D of divorce.
Please. I'm begging you.
What do you mean
we're not fond of your sister?
Exactly. We're not that tactless.
We'd never ask about it to her face.
But it's how you've always been.
Well,
I guess we've been that way, but...
Don't worry though.
We'll keep our mouths shut.
Please do, okay?
Topics like divorces or annulments
are strictly prohibited...
and words like the end, over,
done, or split...
should never be mentioned.
You are not to say anything negative
that can provoke her.
We hear you, goodness.
So tell me.
What do I do if the words come
flying out of my mouth as usual?
Let's each promise to
clamp our lips shut like this.
- Like this?
- Yes.
How's that?
Yes, I'd appreciate at least that.
Ok Boon!
Do well, okay?
I'm trusting you guys.
- Hello, Mr. Song.
- Hi.
Let me.
I'll take that.
Ok Boon, it's been so long.
I was close to forgetting your face.
Have you all been well?
Of course!
Maybe it's because
you got a good rest,
but you look better than ever.
I thought you'd look gaunt
from all the heartache...
Since you weren't around,
we weren't able
to go to our dance classes properly.
The dance instructor asked
why you haven't been around...
and if there was trouble at home...
Forget about it
and be yourselves, okay?
I'm fine.
Really?
Are you sure you're okay?
Yes, I'm good.
Your kids never turn out
the way you want them to.
I'm done expecting
anything from them.
My gosh. Ms. Jang, you're back!
You have no idea
how worried I've been.
- Me too.
- It's good to have you back.
Right. Thank you.
The market is never the same
without you, you know.
It felt empty without you around.
Your skin looks better than it did
before you took some time off.
My goodness.
Not enough money...
can buy you the skin
that some people are born with.
Do you take care of it at home?
Do you apply a homemade face mask?
No, of course not.
Her skin is so milky clean
even without face masks.
I'm so jealous!
- Love you, Ms. Jang.
- Ms. Jang!
- Beautiful Ms. Jang.
- Love you, Ms. Jang.
Love you, Ok Boon!
- Beautiful Ms. Jang.
- Love you, Ms. Jang.
Things have been so uncomfortable
because of Mom.
Until when will she give
Na Hee the cold shoulder?
It's been hard, you know.
Tell me about it.
Na Hee must be embarrassed.
Mom won't even respond to her.
I know.
This must be killing her pride.
Still, she's been trying hard
to make up for what she did wrong.
Should we help them make amends?
How?
We'll keep pushing them together.
A meal and a movie...
might get them
to start talking again.
Mom is not being this way
because she really hates Na Hee.
I'm not sure.
Shouldn't we give them
a little more time?
What they need is good timing,
not time itself.
Trust me, okay?
A surprise?
I doubt Mom would like that.
Of course, it has been
uncomfortable for me too.
So you want us to
ambush her at the shop?
I mean sure, I can pay for the meal.
All right then.
It will be around six
if I get off work on time.
Okay. I'll see you later.
Hey.
Aren't you coming?
- Where?
- To the meeting room.
The HR team called us in.
Did you not check the group message?
A group message?
Is there a group chatroom?
Gi Yeong is in charge of it.
Did he forget to invite you?
So you should've
been nicer to the guys.
Do you want me to invite you?
No, it's okay.
So is it in the meeting room?
I'm going to kill Gi Yeong.
Gosh, what should I do with her?
All right? We should go.
Hello.
What?
You two are coming in together.
How awkward it is.
Don't you think so?
Why did the HR team call us in
so suddenly?
I'm not sure, but Ji Yeon says...
there will be
an interim hospital director.
An interim director? Already?
You can't say that.
It's not a position
that can be left vacant for long.
Who could it be?
I hope it's someone who speaks
the same language as us.
Hey, you...
You all are here.
As you know, the hospital director
is on sick leave for now.
So we've found an interim director
to take charge of our hospital.
Please come on in.
What?
Hello.
I'm Lee Jeong Rok who will act
as the interim hospital director.
Fortunately, I see a few
familiar faces.
What happened?
It just happened this way.
Director Jang asked me
quite earnestly.
And he's friends with my boss.
I'm just like a dispatched soldier.
I'm honored to work with you.
Everyone is excited
to work with a young director.
Gyu Jin,
I will appreciate your help.
The junior doctors here
seem to like you a lot.
Yes, of course.
Hello.
Gosh, this is unbelievable.
I know he's an interim director,
but he's so young.
Director Jang cares for him a lot.
Director Jang has had his eye on him
since he was in school.
By the way, the new director seems
exceptionally close with Na Hee.
I felt that way during
that joint surgical case too.
Are they close friends?
I don't know. How would I know that?
Hang on.
(Mother)
Let's go.
Wait.
Hello?
Yes. He's right next to me.
Okay. Have a nice day. Bye.
What? Who was that?
Mom. She told me
to bring you home after work.
- We'll have dinner.
- She's so tenacious.
Hey, why did you say yes to that?
If I don't bring you with me,
she won't let me sleep at night.
I live with her, you know.
I don't know.
Just tell her that you missed me.
Tell her that I was already gone
when you came by my office.
If you don't come,
she'll bring the food to your place.
That's what Mom said.
Na Hee.
What took you so long?
We were waiting forever.
The bus came late.
You should've waited in a cafe.
Forget it.
I have no money to spend on coffee.
It looks like we'll be having
a girls' night, thanks to you.
Thank you. It's so touching.
Don't be sarcastic.
I'm in no mood for your jokes now.
Sorry.
Let's just go to Mom.
Let's go, Na Hee.
Here. Can you carry them all?
Yes. These will fit perfectly.
I'll be right back.
Okay. Drive safe.
- Don't drive too fast.
- Okay.
- Gosh.
- What's wrong? Is it your back?
Do you want me to massage it?
It's okay. Don't make a fuss.
I thought we wouldn't be able
to deliver it on time,
but we barely made it
thanks to Ok Boon, right?
Sure. That was so close.
We definitely need her in the store
at all times.
See? Things are totally different
when she is here and when she isn't.
The place is full of energy.
Goodness, that's enough. I get it.
You've been chattering all day.
Your lips must hurt.
I know. I just can't stop talking...
when you're around.
All right then. Let's clean up.
You take care of the kitchen.
I will clean the stand.
You don't have to clean.
You should go home and rest.
Only me?
It's okay.
Let's finish and go home together.
This is your first day back.
You didn't even have time to eat.
You might come down with something.
Just go home.
We will take care of the rest.
Gosh, Young Dal.
You sound so caring.
I worked all day too.
I just don't want her
to resent me later.
Just go home
before I change my mind.
Okay. I'm going home then.
I can't believe
I'm leaving work early.
I guess it's worth falling ill
every now and then.
Gosh.
Are you coming from the market?
Yes.
I guess you're doing well enough
to work at your store.
I'm too upset to work,
so I'm not opening the cafe.
Well... This isn't
your first time though.
I guess your family is
quite used to this.
What?
What did you just say?
Am I wrong?
Because of your daughter,
the whole country now knows
my son is divorced.
What are you going to do?
It's not like
he got divorced by himself.
How is that Na Hee's fault?
Then is it because of Gyu Jin?
It's obviously because of
your daughter's nasty temper.
My gosh.
How did you raise them to have three
of your children get divorced...
and the last one an annulment?
I guess I should make an association
for victims of the Song Family.
It'll be called VSF.
Are you done talking?
No, I'm not done yet.
Gyu Jin was born under a lucky star.
But he got involved
with some unlucky family.
I should stop.
I can't blame someone else.
It's my fault for not stopping him
from marrying her.
Hey, do you think
I didn't oppose the marriage?
I disapproved of their marriage
at first because of you.
Because her future mother-in-law
has such a horrible personality.
What? What's wrong
about my personality?
Do you really not know that?
You are so moody and haughty.
Who would want her daughter
to have a mother-in-law like you?
And what? Some unlucky family?
What about you?
Are you so lucky that you lost
your husband at such a young age?
Is that it?
My goodness.
Gosh, how could you
say such a thing?
Look who's talking.
You're the one who started it first,
you wench.
Hey!
Are you crazy? How dare you hit me?
Do you think I can't hit you too?
Hey!
Oh my gosh!
- Hey, let go.
- You!
Do you think
I can't do the same thing?
You wench.
Let go of my hair.
Get off me!
You wench!
- Get off me!
- Let go!
My gosh. Isn't that Mom?
It's her.
- Mom.
- Mom!
Mom!
Mom.
Mom, have you lost your mind?
- What are you doing, Mom?
- Mom, let go.
What's going on?
- My gosh.
- Let go.
- Calm down, Mom.
- Mom.
Get off me. Let go of me!
- Hey!
- Calm down.
What?
I'll kill you.
I'll kill you first.
Gosh, Mom.
- That wench.
- It hurts so much.
That wench. That darn nasty wench.
Does she think my children aren't
just as precious as hers?
Does she think
only her son is hurting?
How could she say such a thing?
What did she say to make you
get into a fight like that?
She said her precious son's life
is ruined...
because he got involved
with an unlucky family like us.
That all my children got divorced
because I raised them wrong.
That crazy lady.
You should've told me sooner.
Then I wouldn't have stopped you.
There are things that you can say
and things you cannot.
Seriously...
Darn it.
Should I go right after her?
And start a new fight with her?
- That...
- Ga Hee, not you too.
Sit down, Ga Hee.
Mom isn't entirely blameless.
She should've held back.
Why grab someone else by the hair
in the main street?
What?
I'm so annoyed.
That viper.
How could she hit me where it hurts?
I feel...
so, so upset.
Mom, stop. Will you stop crying?
From what I saw, you started it.
What? Was I wrong?
Divorce is a tradition for them!
It's true that they ruined us!
Am I wrong?
Mom, please!
Will you please stop it?
What?
Why do you always
only think from your side?
Don't you care
even a little about others?
Don't you have any idea how much
what you said hurts them?
Just seeing her face
made me so angry.
I couldn't contain my fury.
It's not that you can't.
You don't hold back.
You don't even try to!
Mom, I didn't get divorced alone.
Both of us got divorced.
Na Hee is as distressed as I am,
and her mom is as furious
as you are.
Why do you only think of
how upset you are?
Why are you so selfish?
How dare you talk like that?
Do you think I'm doing it for me?
I say what I do for your sake!
No, no!
That fight earlier.
And dragging me home
for dinner against my will.
It's all for you...
because you want
everything done your way!
What?
That's how you always are.
You do whatever you want,
and get upset and annoyed
when the result isn't satisfactory.
Do you know how distressed
that made Na Hee?
Why wouldn't she be
when your own sons can't take it?
Do you think you have
no responsibility for our divorce?
No, you do!
You're very responsible!
How could you...
Jae Seok.
What is your brother saying?
Mom, that goes for Jae Seok too.
Why do you think
he trained in Turkey?
He couldn't take your obsessiveness
and wanted to get away.
That's why he went so far away!
Is that true?
Is it true, you jerk?
Get out. Get out of here.
- Get out of this house.
- Mom.
If you want to lecture me
and say the right thing, get out.
- Mom, Mom.
- Get out!
Whose fault is it that
I got into a fight in the market?
I shed tears and got mocked?
Mom, will you please
not get so worked up?
- Yes, Mom.
- Mom, don't.
That isn't what she meant.
She was just upset too.
Let go!
Yes. You're all on her side,
aren't you?
You're all united for once
because you're sisters.
Yes, I get it now.
It's because you all put
a stake through my heart as well!
Mom. What has gotten into you?
Why are you suddenly
taking it out on us?
Mom, we just...
Forget it!
I don't need any of you!
I'm home.
What is it? What's wrong?
What's the matter, Mom?
What is it?
Mom, it's not like that.
What is it, then?
What is it, you jerk?
Okay, Mom, so...
Rather than wanting to
get away from you,
I wanted to get some experience.
Say something.
She got the wrong idea.
How... How could you do this to me?
How could you both betray me?
After your dad died,
to think of
what I did to raise you...
How could you?
Mom, why would you say that?
- Why...
- I don't need you.
- I don't need sons.
- Mom.
I don't need you. Get out.
Get out. I'm done with you.
- Wait, Mom.
- I don't care.
All four of you!
The two of you.
Get out!
(Once Again)
What is this mess?
I bet I'm the only forty-year-old...
to get kicked out of the house
by his mom.
Do you know how hard it is
to get the crumbs out?
- Clean up right now.
- You're so tiresome.
Let me help you.
What? You?
Mr. Yoon.
Ms. Song.
Director. Just give me a chance.
I'll even put my life on the line.
- Excuse me.
- Sure.
Yes, Chief. What?
I understand.
Gyu Jin, you know about my hunch.
That's more flirting
than being friendly colleagues.
At least one of them has feelings
for the other.