Mom.
Song Na Hee. You...
What is with the state
of this entrance?
Shoes are flying everywhere!
Gosh, what a mess.
How many times have I told you...
that a tidy entrance
brings luck to the home?
- Unbelievable.
- Mother, let me.
Gyu Jin, it's all right. I'll do it.
Oh, please.
Of course it should be me.
You sure know how
to clean up, don't you?
Anyway,
I thought you said you were too busy
to pick up the food I made,
so how come you're both here?
My schedule got moved around.
My meeting got pushed back too.
If I had known that,
I would've made you come by.
Here.
It's young radish kimchi.
Scoop up a decent amount
every time you enjoy it.
The cucumber kimchi
has been sliced and ready to eat.
- Here you go.
- You really didn't have to.
My goodness!
Why is the fridge empty?
Do you even cook at home?
We're busy all the time,
so we eat outside.
You should at least
cook breakfast though.
Gosh, the boiled chicken
is still here.
Why didn't you peel the meat off
and make porridge at least?
It makes a perfect breakfast.
Mother, let me put this
in the fridge first.
Goodness. Thank you so much.
Na Hee, come on.
Offer her something to drink.
Right.
Don't skip breakfast, okay?
It's bad for your stomach.
You know that your brother
opened a stunt company, right?
According to him,
a major investor came forward.
That's amazing!
A major investor?
Are you sure it isn't illegal?
Please tell me
he vet the investor at least.
You and your suspicions again.
Give your brother some credit.
She's just like
her father sometimes.
It's times like this
when I'm grateful for the fact...
that she was able to marry
someone like you.
Why would you put it like that, Mom?
Mother!
Let me drive you home.
That's not necessary at all.
The bus ride isn't that long.
It makes me uncomfortable too.
Go inside and get some rest.
I'm not tired at all.
Of course you are.
I can see the bags under your eyes.
Eat the kimchi I made
and don't skip breakfast.
And let me know once you eat it all.
I'll drop everything
and make some more.
Thank you. I'll enjoy it for sure.
Right.
Anyway, head back inside.
You should wash up
and get some sleep.
There's no need to see me off.
I'll run if I have to.
Now, go back inside.
Gosh, please don't run.
Goodnight, Mother!
Hurry back inside.
I'll see you around.
Goodnight.
I told you going after her
was a waste of time.
You know how stubborn she is.
Hold on.
My mom could come back at any time,
so let's not put this up.
You've memorized it all,
right?
How long must we keep this up?
Until when must we
keep our divorce a secret...
and deceive our parents?
Our divorce has been finalized,
and I can't go along
with this anymore.
I can't look at your mom
without feeling guilty.
Then what?
You want to come clean?
They'll find out someday anyway.
Did you see the look
on my mom's face today?
She hasn't been at ease like this
for a long time.
She's just getting over
the shock of Da Hee's annulment,
so how can we throw
this bomb at her?
"Mom, I'm sorry,"
"but our marriage
has been way over."
"We didn't tell you
to save you from losing it."
Like that?
My mom might want to commit suicide.
I won't drag this on for too long.
Let's tell our parents
once we sell this house...
and we each find a place to stay.
How long must we keep this up?
Until when must we
keep our divorce a secret...
and deceive our parents?
Our divorce has been finalized,
and I can't go along
with this anymore.
(Yongju Traditional Market)
Coming through!
Gosh.
My gosh.
Here are the additional chickens
you ordered.
- Hi.
- It's good to see you.
Right.
I can't believe you needed
an additional order so soon.
Business must be good.
It's picnic season,
so we should make the most of it.
Don't overexert yourself though.
Earning money is never bad,
but you might ruin your health.
Imagine dying on a pile of money.
Unbelievable.
Must I hear such a meaningless worry
so early in the morning?
You just never stop talking.
If you ever get tossed in the sea,
you'll die from gossiping
with the fish.
Gosh, I feel so bad for them.
Is that your way of greeting me?
You can never go about your day
without picking on me, can you?
Then don't come here...
or keep your mouth shut
when you do.
Stop it!
Mr. Yang, how about a cup of coffee?
Sounds good. Make that two packets.
My gosh.
Just stick to one, will you?
Why would you drink two at a time?
What's it to you?
By the way, the kimbap store
is opening up today.
Shouldn't we help them
make their first sale?
Did you not get a scolding
from the owner?
I don't mind getting a scolding.
Whatever food they give you,
you will eat it deliciously.
Also, we can go over there together
and have them sign the papers...
for the merchant association.
- Right now?
- Why sit on it, right?
I'd love to see the owner
who's as pretty as a rose.
Come on. Ok Boon,
I'll take a rain-check
on the coffee.
Carry on with the prepping.
This won't take long.
Did he just call her a rose?
And here I thought
she looked like a mortar.
What on earth is this?
Unbelievable.
Now this is what I call
new and innovative.
Honestly, I can't wait
to meet this woman.
My gosh.
Hey.
What a pain in my neck.
- My gosh, hello.
- Hi!
Which one of you is the rose...
May I ask which one of you
is the owner?
How may I help you?
I'm the owner.
You're the owner?
Chi Su, move.
Oh, it's you again.
We haven't even
opened yet, you know.
I'm a busy man myself.
This is an application for joining
the merchant association.
You'll be able to join
if the majority agrees.
Here.
The merchant association?
We're here on behalf
of the merchant association,
so we'll take 10 rolls of kimbap.
10 rolls of kimbap to go?
10 rolls of kimbap to go!
Must one join
the merchant association though?
It's best if you do.
For 30 dollars a year,
the association will support
any events,
the use of parking lots,
and group purchase of groceries...
Got it.
I guess I should sign up then.
Just a second.
Would you like to taste one
while you're waiting?
Why would I ever decline?
Thanks in advance.
The piece at the end.
How is it?
The flavors are unique for a kimbap.
If I can, I'll cut the order
down to five rolls.
(Unnie's Kimbap)
It's really hard
to make bland kimbap.
How can it taste this bad
with all the proper ingredients?
That sure is another type of talent.
Born in 1969?
Then she's 2 years younger
than Young Suk.
What are you muttering over there?
Is something wrong?
No, I was just reminded
of my late sister, that's all.
Your sister?
Why did you bring her up?
She just popped into my head,
that's all.
Gosh, she has terrible handwriting.
What do we do with these
rolls of kimbap?
I shouldn't throw these away, right?
You bought them, so finish them off.
This I can be certain of.
That President Song?
I already feel bad
for his wife and kids.
What a grumpy old man.
He still came by
to make our first sale though.
It wasn't him. It was his friend.
Cho Yeon, you lowered your age by
two years on the form, didn't you?
I saw it.
Must you do that
when it's just a couple of years?
You'll get arrested again.
Shut it, you cows.
You'll know when you reach my age.
Those few years are darn precious.
Besides, who would believe
that I was born in 1967?
People think I'm still
in my early 40s.
Says who? My gosh.
His breathing sounds a lot better...
and his oxygen saturation is higher.
Are you keeping up with
your nebulizer therapy?
Yes, I'm not coughing anymore.
I'm sorry to tell you this,
but you can't go home yet though.
And even when you do,
you can't solely rely on
Ventolin either.
- When you start gasping...
- I know.
I should drop my shoulders,
let my arms droop,
and breathe through my nose slowly.
You're a clever one, aren't you?
If you have the time, can you
treat my patients in my place?
Get some rest then.
I'll decide if he can go home
in a few days.
Just know that I'll be
checking his lungs tomorrow.
Right.
He's a clever little boy.
I'm grateful
he doesn't take after me.
Excuse me, Doctor?
Yes?
You're Gyu Jin's wife, right?
I heard from the nurse.
I see.
We used to go to the same church...
although I couldn't make it
to your wedding.
Church?
Yes.
You and Gyu Jin make a great couple.
You're stunning too.
Gosh, thank you. I'll see you, then.
Shouldn't there be more customers?
Restaurants normally do well
on the day of the opening.
Tell me about it.
There's nothing to be heard here...
except for the sound of flies.
Just be patient, girls.
News hasn't traveled
about our diner yet...
and there's a timing for everything.
We'll seize the moment
when it comes,
so stop thinking like
this is our last day.
Guys, the timing has come. Start.
What?
Hey, is this that new kimbap place?
I'm craving for some.
Should we go in?
What if the kimbap isn't good?
Let's get
the sweet and sour chicken instead.
You think? Okay, let's go.
My goodness.
Hello, you handsome young men.
- Do you go to the nearby school?
- Yes.
We just opened today,
so sodas are for free.
Why don't you come in?
My gosh, is it hot out here?
You're sweating.
Let me turn on the fan for you.
- Come in.
- Come on.
Here are your fans.
So, how do they taste?
- Good.
- Here are your free sodas.
- Thank you.
Enjoy.
You guys must not get
good grades at school though.
Why else would your backpacks
be that empty?
Who on earth carries
books around in their backpacks?
Books are only needed
as a pillow at school.
- Aren't I right?
- That's right.
They're so pretty.
They're beautiful.
I wonder which one would be best.
We used to go to the same church...
although I couldn't make it
to your wedding.
It's her, right?
Look at how cute you were
in high school.
You look the same,
but just in a more adorable way.
Wasn't my nose sharper though?
It makes you want to
bite down on it.
Wait.
Who's she?
You seem shy in a way.
What?
Well, she's just my first love.
We just went to the same church,
that's all.
Anyway, let's sleep.
What did you just say?
Your first love?
She's your first love?
- Your first love?
- Wait.
No, I mean...
That acquaintance of yours.
Si Hoo's mother, I mean.
What about her?
She's your first love, right?
The one from church.
First love, my foot.
I'll take that as a yes.
I remembered her face
from the photo I once saw.
Gosh, unbelievable.
I hate her good memory sometimes.
Si Hoo's breathing is a lot better.
He might be going home
in a few days.
Anyway,
How do you feel to meet
your first love again?
You must be thrilled.
Don't be silly.
She has a seven-year-old son.
It was a long time ago.
Can't you feel thrilled
to see a married woman?
Why are you overreacting like that?
I guess you were really into her.
Gosh, you're even blushing now.
I do have a healthy complexion
for no reason.
I'm just healthy.
What's wrong about that?
Why does he seem so flustered?
He really must've been thrilled.
Na Hee.
We have about 20 minutes left
for the lunch break.
Would you have some tea with me?
Let me see.
The one you found online is...
It's right here.
It's close to a subway station
and a park.
The deposit is 100,000 dollars
and a monthly rent of 1,200 dollars.
What? 100,000 dollars?
It doesn't have to be close
to a subway station.
- Do you want something else?
- Yes, please.
What about this one?
It's a little far from the station,
but the air is really good.
The deposit is 60,000 dollars
and the rent is 800 dollars.
The air doesn't have to be so good.
We all have healthy
bronchial tubes.
What about this then?
It's 50,000 and 700.
I don't know.
What price are you looking for?
(Thread factory)
This is it.
This is good enough
for 30,000 deposit and 500 rent.
It's a semi-basement.
What do you think?
Do you want to go inside?
Yes, we do.
This is nice, Joon Seon.
And it's well-located.
- Take a look.
- Okay.
It's spacious.
Joon Seon,
this is bigger than I thought.
It's big enough for training.
I think so.
It's bigger than it looks.
But what about the light?
Can we turn the light on?
Of course. The light...
It's not on, but it's okay.
We can fix it.
You know my nickname is MacGyver.
- I can fix it.
- You think?
What about ventilation?
Joon Seon, we can just open
the windows for ventilation.
Why is it stuck?
Hey, you're a stuntman.
Can't you even open a window?
You little...
It's okay, Joon Seon. I can fix it.
I will fix the windows
and the lights.
Are you sure?
Can you really fix them all?
Of course. Don't worry.
I'll fix everything. Trust me.
Are you sure this is okay
for our office?
Yes. I like it.
I really love it.
We're going to have our own place.
I'm okay with any place
as long as it has a ceiling.
We can at least take
shelter from the rain.
Should I really sign the lease?
Are you sure?
- Yes, Joon Seon.
- Sure.
All right. Let's sign it then.
Now we have our own office.
How do you find
working at the hospital?
You seem to be adapting
to it quite well.
As you can see,
the only problem is
that I'm too popular.
All the women in the hospital
are asking me out.
They just won't leave me alone.
But you're having
a coffee break with me.
I took my time out for you.
Well... Na Hee.
About your younger sister.
Would you say she holds grudges
for a long time?
I don't know.
She's quite mellow most of the time.
But once she gets upset,
she becomes quite stubborn.
Why? Does she have
a problem with your mom?
No. They actually
get along well together.
Your sister handles
my mom's temperament quite well.
By the way, are you all right?
Are things over with Gyu Jin?
It's a little uncomfortable,
but we have to wait
until our house is sold.
I hope Gyu Jin will leave
the hospital soon.
He had an interview
at Hanseo University.
He said he didn't
go to the interview.
What? What do you mean?
I don't know the details.
He just said he didn't go.
So Sang Hoon took the job.
You know the guy
from Saebit Hospital.
He went to the same college as you.
Yes?
Gosh, I'm startled.
Did you not go to the interview
at Hanseo University?
No.
Why not?
I couldn't go
because of the situation here,
but at least you should have gone.
We can't keep working
at the same hospital like this.
Well... The thing is...
I don't know many people
at that hospital.
And I'll have to work
a longer shift there.
Is that why you didn't go?
That's it?
Yes.
This is crazy.
You know it's a great opportunity.
You're a man.
Don't you have any ambition?
Will you work here forever...
hanging out with the director
and junior doctors?
No, it's not like that.
You're always like this.
You're a coward...
who just avoids problems
without facing them.
What?
Hey, whose fault was it that...
Forget it. Let's not do this.
Why? If you have something to say,
just spit it out.
I just can't understand you.
Are you okay with working
in the same hospital as me?
Of course, I'm not.
You always barge in
and pick a fight with me like this.
Do you think I have
nothing else to do?
I'm doing this
because you make me upset.
That's it. I told you to stop.
Hey.
This is why we broke up.
You always see things
the way you want.
You just misunderstand others
and come to your own conclusion.
I always miss the chance to explain.
What's that supposed to mean?
I don't know. It's just...
Get out.
I have to work. Get out.
We're so not right for each other.
No, we're not.
We're not right for each other.
The door is open.
Gosh, I feel so uncomfortable.
I shouldn't have acted up like that.
Welcome...
You're here.
I was thirsty on my way home.
Can I have
a strawberry banana juice?
Okay. Take any seat you like.
Ms. Song, I should pay first.
I always keep my private
and public life separate.
One strawberry banana juice.
That will be 4.6 dollars.
Ms. Song.
Yes? Go ahead.
Why are you being like this?
You seem distant.
Just be comfortable around me.
I'm sorry for what I did.
Here's your card.
Please wait a moment.
Ms. Song, please don't be like this.
I didn't mean to tease you.
All right. To be honest,
I tried to tease you a little.
But that's because
I found you very friendly.
I didn't do it to mean anything bad.
It was just an expression...
Here's your juice. Please enjoy.
Stop acting so cold
and listen to me.
Ms. Song.
You're back, Ms. Choi.
I've been seeing you here
quite often.
I know. It just happened that way.
Where have you been?
I got a massage.
Ms. Hong is having a charity bazaar
at her gallery tomorrow.
I haven't seen them
for a long time,
so I don't want to look bad.
Ms. Hong?
They are like
Choi Yun Jeong 1, 2, 3, and 4.
She met this group at the VIP lounge
of a department store.
It's as if there are four of my mom.
Doesn't it sound scary?
Ms. Choi, we need to order
disposable goods.
Our supplier has a new product,
so they suggested
we try a box for free.
Really? Let's do that.
Okay. We don't even
need cup sleeves with it.
It sounds convenient.
Son, follow me.
All right.
This is my new business card.
My business card. Take one.
CEO Song Joon Seon
of Good Action.
The card is quite stiff.
It looks fancy.
I bet you spent
quite a bit of money on this.
Yes. I spent quite a sum on this.
You know a business card...
is like the face of a company.
You can get three boxes...
for five dollars at the printers
near the market.
Why would you waste money
on things like that?
There you go again.
Will you stop picking on him?
This is his first business card.
He can't get a cheap one.
Gosh.
This is good.
A good business card will...
bring you good business.
So do you like your office?
Sure, of course.
I just found a perfect place.
It's just amazing.
The building is new,
and it has a spacious room.
Really? I'm so happy for you.
It's easily accessible
and the building is well-designed.
It's well ventilated
with the windows open.
I can't even tell
if I'm in a building or not.
I owe it all
to my honorable investor.
Auntie. Have another slice.
Okay, Joon Seon. Thanks.
Can you please calm down
and not get carried away?
Do everything with caution, okay?
Yes, don't worry, Dad.
So when is the opening ceremony?
I plan to order millet cakes
to celebrate.
The opening ceremony?
I was hoping to skip that.
Why? It's your first company.
You should hold a ritual.
With a whole pig head.
Why do you believe superstitions
when you're so young?
I won't entrust
the future of my company...
to a pig head and red rice cakes.
What are you talking about?
You locked the door after
I went to a funeral so I couldn't...
come in until you threw salt on me.
I had to wait
until I got a whole bowl over me.
Don't you remember?
You're right.
Anyway, there's too much to do.
Later. Maybe later.
Skip it if you want.
I'm glad I won't have to
spend the cash.
I should stop eating.
I'm meeting
my old attendant friends tomorrow.
If I eat any more,
I'll puff up tomorrow.
Should I peel more fruit or not?
Don't peel any more.
Most of the fruit's nutrients
are in the peel. Eat the peel.
Oh, my gosh. Honestly.
Isn't that dirty?
Eat the peel. Go on.
Okay.
Seo Jin, that must be Mom. Let's go.
- Here.
- Thanks.
I made young radish kimchi
for Na Hee and packed some for you.
With a few other side dishes.
Thank you, Mother.
My fridge is bare,
so I can't even refuse.
Mom, you should've packed
some anchovies.
Seo Jin loves them.
I did already, you fool.
I'm sure you heard, didn't you?
That he started a business.
He rented an office today,
and he says it's nice and spacious
and in a new building.
Is it? That's great.
I went to a fortune-teller once...
who said that
Joon Seon is a late bloomer.
I used to feel so frustrated
and almost sick when I saw him,
but now I guess things are
beginning to work out.
Even my appetite came back.
Why would you say that?
She'll feel uncomfortable.
I suggested he host
an opening ceremony,
but he keeps on refusing.
He wants to save the money
and invest it in the business.
He has finally grown up.
Mom, go back inside.
Okay, I was just saying.
Anyway, drive home safely.
Put the kimchi
in the fridge right away.
- Okay?
- Yes, Mother.
Seo Jin, Grandma has to go. Goodbye.
- Bye.
- Go.
- Okay, okay.
It's cold.
Here you go.
I put aside the first one for you.
It looks nice. I like the name too.
Why won't you have
an opening ceremony?
Mother wants to invite
the market people to brag.
That's a good thing too.
Giving your parents
something to brag about.
Yes, but I'm busy.
It's early days
and there's a lot to do.
I should show Seo Young this.
She'll be so pleased
that her dad is a CEO.
What about you?
What?
I mean... No, never mind.
Seo Jin must be sleepy.
Let's get her home.
- Okay.
- Let's go, Seo Jin.
Take care, Seo Jin. Bye.
Drive safely!
Bye!
Goodbye.
You moron. Why couldn't you ask?
Why couldn't you say,
"Aren't you pleased?"
You're such a loser.
You're even less than
young radish kimchi.
What is wrong with you?
(Good Action Company,
CEO Song Joon Seon)
My gosh.
You'll wear down the business card.
Are you that pleased?
Of course, I'm pleased.
Our precious eldest son
started a company.
Silly me. I forgot I put barley tea
on the stove to boil.
I was that pleased.
(Good Action Company)
He's a CEO?
That's just his ego talking.
Yes, it's nice.
It's great that I don't have to
deal with drunkards anymore.
Dad, how did the evening service go?
Yes, the market is nice too.
The merchant association president
seems to be fussy,
but he's not a bad person.
Yes. I'll visit with
some kimbap soon.
Sleep well, Dad.
(Pure Soju)
Gosh, that's sweet.
Even if I walk with my eyes closed
Even if I walk with my eyes open
All that I see
Is a shabby form
The face that I miss
Young Suk.
Young Suk!
Young Suk! Young Suk!
Young Suk.
How strange.
Sales were through the roof
a few days ago.
Why did it suddenly drop?
I don't see our regulars
from the billiard hall...
who used to come by
almost every day.
- I know. Isn't that strange?
- Yes.
What's up today?
- Fire! Fire!
- My goodness.
- There's a fire.
- What?
Come here.
You startled me. What is it now?
I don't care if you're startled.
What's really startling
is happening over there.
What happened?
My gosh.
What is going on?
Are they lined up for kimbap?
I think so. What's happening?
Chi Su, is it true that
their kimbap is terrible?
Maybe it's just not for you.
No, no.
Their kimbap isn't
a matter of preference.
Oh, the basketball kid is back.
Did you bring your friends today?
Come on in.
I'll give you all free drinks again.
- Go on inside.
- Thank you.
Oh, my gosh! You guys are back!
Hang in there
while I get you a table.
It's fine. You can take your time.
We're not busy at all.
Don't you run about
and break that pretty heel.
I'm here as well.
What is going on here?
My goodness.
We have no customers because...
they're eating kimbap made by
these people from who knows where?
Dear guests!
The owner of Unnie's Kimbap...
decided to treat you all to...
her special lemon soda!
Thank you.
Here you go.
- Thank you.
Here's a refreshing
beverage for you.
My gosh, red suits you perfectly.
You look amazing!
Is that so?
I've always been known
for looking good in red.
Anyway, can we get
two more rolls of kimbap?
Cho Yeon,
two more rolls of kimbap, please!
Over here.
- We'll take another roll.
- Us too.
Boss, four more rolls of kimbap.
Okay, four more rolls of kimbap!
Sorry you had to wait this long.
Please come on in.
It won't be long now, guys.
What did I tell you?
I said this didn't seem right.
What on earth are they doing anyway?
Tell me about it.
I've run my business here
for 10 years now,
and this is definitely a first.
No wonder I haven't been able
to sell enough today.
That's where all our customers went.
There must be something going on.
Gyu Jin.
Gyu Jin?
Gyu Jin!
What? Just say it.
I can't be bothered to answer.
Let's say you teased someone
but you didn't mean any harm.
However, that person
is now super angry.
You apologized but
that person won't even accept it.
What would you do?
Who did you annoy this time?
You're never nice,
but this is your worst quality.
You go too far with your jokes.
You're never decent either,
and this is your worst quality.
Sometimes, your words really hurt.
- What a freak.
Why do I even bother talking to you?
Bo Young!
Hi, Gyu Jin.
Where are you coming from?
Home? These must be blankets.
- Let me take that.
- It's all right.
Who's she?
We used to go to the same church.
Her kid is a patient here.
This is my younger brother.
He's a dentist here.
Oh, I see. Hello.
I didn't know
your brother was a doctor too.
Your mother must be proud.
It's a pleasure to meet you.
And your name?
It's Yoo Bo Young.
I knew it. "My Bo Young."
Sorry?
He kept saying that
back when I was in high school.
"My Bo Young, my Bo Young."
He probably said it
in his sleep too.
I heard it so much that
it's as if you were my first love...
Gosh, Na Hee.
Where are you coming back from?
I was running an errand.
- Hello, Dr. Song.
- Hi.
I brought some blankets from home,
but they were too heavy.
You know how generous Gyu Jin is.
Right. He sure is
polite and generous.
This elevator is awfully slow,
isn't it?
The hospital was built a while ago.
10 years, right?
No, five.
Five? I guess it's not really time
for an upgrade yet.
Gosh, it's slow.
You, only you
Are my first love
You are my last love
And now
Forever
- Bye, Dr. Song.
- Bye.
Come on. I'll take it from here.
It's okay. I'll take it to his room.
But it's really okay.
Gosh.
It's as if you're not over her.
Hello?
This is Nambu Police Station.
There's something
we didn't ask for you to sign.
I'm afraid you'll have
to come down here sometime.
I see. How about in two hours?
Please don't apologize, ma'am.
Of course, it can slip your mind.
I'm fine waiting,
so take your time
and call me when you get home.
Right.
An hour?
Sure thing. All right.
How many times
has she done this already?
This is what I call
a repeat offender.
What can I do for an hour then?
(Good Action Company,
CEO Song Joon Seon)
Good Action Company?
I really hope he makes it this time.
"We choose this day,
April 18, 2020,"
"to ask that you grant us safety
and help us thrive."
"We deeply pray..."
"that none of us
suffer any injuries..."
"while training or working on set."
Gosh, that's hot!
- Boss, move.
- Out of the way!
Boss, save yourself.
Don't be such a drama queen.
I don't want any of that
in this sacred place.
Please help us thrive.
How much did you put
in the envelope?
Five.
Five?
Yes, five.
But I only put in three.
You guys can make a wish too now.
Sure.
I want to be caught in the rain.
A rain of money.
Why can't you stick to
something more realistic?
You can't become a billionaire
doing stunts.
Why not? It could happen...
if we work on every movie
and TV drama set in Korea.
Just thinking about it
puts a smile on my face.
Wait.
I felt something drop.
Could this be a good sign?
What do you mean
something is dropping?
Guys, water is leaking
from the ceiling!
- Get a bucket.
- A bucket?
But we don't have one.
Then get me a rag.
A rag?
Guys, it's pouring in here!
Water is leaking from the ceiling.
Hey, get over here.
- Joon Seon...
- Get up there.
Block the cracks.
What on earth...
- My gosh.
- Darn it.
Just forget about it.
Here. Let me wipe off the water.
At least get me a dry one.
Darn it.
What's this? Who left it here?
"Look at how handsome you are."
"Why don't you come in
for some kimbap?"
Unbelievable.
Just hearing their voices...
made me crave kimbap too.
Exactly. Aren't they mesmerizing?
Where do you think
they came from though?
It seems like they have
a fishy past.
Yes, I can smell the stink.
There's something going on here.
Did you see what they were wearing?
That's not what you wear
when selling kimbap.
Unbelievable.
Tell me about it.
Isn't it uncomfortable
to work in tight clothes?
Exactly.
Maybe I should also wear
short skirts starting tomorrow.
I'll fry the chicken
while swaying my hips.
How do I look, Ok Boon?
Shut it.
This isn't the time for jokes.
We didn't sell half the chicken
we normally sell today.
It's not just you.
Many stores lost customers today
because of them.
Exactly.
It's terrible for
the market's image too.
Can you believe their style?
Tell me about it!
Must you speak behind
their backs like that?
It's not like...
the kimbap place is selling alcohol.
What kind of a customer...
would be against some added service?
- What?
- Are you kidding me?
My gosh. Don't bite my head off.
Fine, I get it.
I was only just saying.
Gosh.
Why butt in
just to have your head bitten off?
The ladies seem like
they're ready for action though.
Blood will be shed
in Yongju Market soon.
All this because of
one weird kimbap place.
- Young Dal.
- Yes?
Would those tough ladies win...
or would the kimbap ladies
knock them out?
That's something to bet on.
My money is on the kimbap ladies.
But the market ladies
have the advantage in numbers.
Look. They are a force
to be reckoned with.
1, 2...
She's still stunning
even after all these years.
Exactly. You look even better.
Actually, it's because
my skin is paler now.
I don't go out much these days.
Unbelievable.
Meanwhile, you have a tan.
Were you out on a flight?
Yes, Koh Samui.
It's my third flight this month...
and I'm sick and tired of it.
I'd love the chance to go there
and get a tan, you know.
I'll look sexy.
Did you invite her?
No, I just told her that
we were meeting Ga Hee.
It's been a while, Ga Hee.
Have you been well?
We're not close enough to ask
how well the other's been doing,
but I've been good.
You seemed to have aged though.
He must not be
that good to you these days.
Working First Class
has been exhausting.
Sometimes I regret
getting that promotion.
But you won't know that
since you quit before getting one.
I don't and I don't care.
Let's eat, okay?
My gosh, Ga Hee.
It seems like
you put on some weight.
I can only imagine
how easy life is for you.
You receive child support
while lounging around at home...
and you were given alimony.
I'm jealous of you at times.
What's the point in having a man...
when half his salary is given
to his ex-wife and child?
Exactly.
I never understood why you went
after a married man with a child.
You should be careful too.
Once a cheater, always a cheater,
you know?
Don't you worry.
I'll make sure to stand guard.
I'm not blind like someone I know.
It's not because one is blind.
What will happen will always happen.
Classes for kids
aren't cheap these days, right?
This restaurant
is on the pricey side,
so I guess lunch should be on me.
Actually, it'll be on me.
As you know,
I receive child support.
If I need more,
I'll call Yoon Mi's boyfriend...
and ask him to send some.
He never complains
when I ask for money.
Here you go. No installments.
Ga Hee, isn't this a bit too much?
- Ga Hee, thanks for the meal.
- Gosh, this is nothing.
Honey, you're here!
I told him to pick me up
so that we can go shopping.
So they were...
the friends you were meeting.
I guess you didn't know.
Look at her
still playing you like a fiddle.
Excuse me then.
I knew! It just slipped my mind.
That wench.
She deliberately called him here
to flaunt.
I'm not at all jealous, you know.
He's not even that great.
I can't believe
he actually came to pick her up.
What a loser.
You loser!
Is that Seung Hyun's car?
Hey!
Stop right there!
Valet service?
Coming.
What on earth... There's a dent.
Are you kidding me?
What's the point in paying you...
if you can't stop this
from happening?
I'm sorry, sir.
We'll pay for the damages.
Unbelievable!
What a joke.
- Our apologies, sir.
- The door needs to be replaced.
I can't believe it.
Ji Hun, I'm home!
- Hi, Mom.
- Hi, Auntie.
Are you guys eating pizza?
Did Grandma order it for you?
No, I bought it for everyone.
You? That's out of the blue.
I thought you were...
saving up to buy celebrity goods.
You ask Ji Hun
to buy snacks all the time.
Auntie, you're talking
about the old me.
- It's completely different now.
- How so?
My dad is a CEO now.
I should be more generous
to fulfill my role...
as a CEO's daughter.
I'll get a raise
in my allowance soon,
and we could be riding around
in a fancy foreign car.
Well, I'd love
for that to happen too.
Don't you trust my dad, Auntie?
What? I do.
Of course, I do.
Go ahead and have a slice.
If needed, I'll order another one.
It's all right. I'm full anyway.
Maybe I had too much
because I feel bloated.
You guys go ahead and enjoy it all.
Do you have indigestion?
Should I get you some medicine?
No, that's not what I meant.
Anyway, eat up.
I'll go and get changed.
Cheese.
Ji Hun, how about
we get some ice cream too?
All right then. Eat up.
(Witness)
- Here. Are we good then?
- Yes, ma'am.
I apologize for making you
come down here again.
It's all right.
Will the dad
get an added sentence...
if he's proven to be
a repeat offender?
That's right. You know your law.
I guess this isn't your first rodeo.
I've gone through this a few times.
It should never happen,
but it happens frequently.
So you've been through this before?
No wonder.
I get why your husband
seemed worried that day.
Sorry? My husband?
He came by as soon as you left.
Didn't he tell you?
He was shocked out of his mind.
It's as if the blood had been
drawn from his face.
(Ttobongee Chicken)
I scheduled an appointment
with my dermatologist...
for Botox shots this month,
but I guess I should cancel.
Why? I thought you got
a good deal on them.
How can I ask for my monthly salary
when business is so slow?
That'd be wrong.
Don't be like that, Ok Ja.
Business can be slow at times...
but then go back to normal
the next day.
Have you forgotten...
how we almost went under
when avian influenza circulated?
When a new diner opens,
business fluctuates.
The new diner
will lose its novelty...
and our sales
will be back to normal again.
But that doesn't seem to be the case
this time.
The store just has an odd concept.
It's why I've been telling you
to start making deliveries.
Talking about it is a waste of time.
You know he'll never hire extra help
just for the sake of deliveries.
The prices of flour
and pepper powder keep rising.
There are so many expenses.
Can you find someone for me?
I should spend money when I have to.
Are you sure?
What is going on?
Are we really doing deliveries?
We can just give it a try.
If something doesn't go right,
we can stop it then.
Good for you.
You know how things are these days.
Everyone seems to order food
on those delivery apps.
People have even
a bottle of water delivered.
There's nothing you can get
from delaying the decision.
You should change yourself
to adapt to the changing world.
Only then you can survive.
I wonder why you always
hang out here...
and not in your own shop
when you know so well.
Don't worry about me.
My brother is taking
good care of my shop.
Regulars only go there
to see the shop owner.
I'm the president,
not just the owner.
Do you not know that?
I'm the president.
- No, Young Dal is the president...
- Excuse me.
Have you seen my husband?
We have to unload the products now,
but I can't find him.
I have to carry 20 boxes
of anchovies all by myself.
Where on earth did he go?
Did you check the billiard hall?
Your husband is a regular there.
I already did.
And I went
to the noodle restaurant...
No way. My gosh.
- Cheers.
- You guys are really nice.
- Yes, we are.
I'm new here,
so I'm unfamiliar with the town.
And that president
of the merchant association...
keeps nagging me.
I found this place unwelcoming,
so I was worried about my business.
But you guys can be my regulars.
What do you think?
Sure.
All right then.
I'll show you my special talent.
Here. I can fold my ears. Look.
That's amazing. Look at her ear.
How does she do that?
Hey, you idiot.
What are you doing here?
- My gosh.
- Follow me.
What's happening?
- Come here.
- What...
What's wrong with her?
Let go of it.
You're pulling out my hair.
Do you want me to go bald?
Shut it. Who cares if you go bald?
Just follow me.
Let go of my hair.
Gosh, ma'am.
I guess there's a misunderstanding.
Please calm down.
Misunderstanding, my foot.
Just stay out of this.
Gosh, you can't leave like this.
- Let's go inside and talk.
- Let go of him.
You'd just do anything for money.
How vulgar you are.
What kind of people are you?
- Let's go.
- I just went there to eat kimbap.
- Don't be ridiculous.
- Don't do this.
Vulgar? What did she say?
What a nasty wench.
Should I go in there
and talk to her?
I'll just skip it today. I'm tired.
I always love
how you've decorated your place.
By the way, what's that painting?
I don't know the artist.
It's a painting by a new artist.
I like simple paintings
like that these days.
I like the uniform effects
of light and shade.
And yet, it's not so conventional.
- I see.
- I agree.
- That's very nice.
- I love it too.
By the way,
when is your second son coming?
Gosh, those ladies never change.
I feel drained
just at the sight of them.
Ms. Song,
I'll stay here for a while.
Only until the guests leave.
Gosh, you're now treating me
like I'm invisible.
You hold grudges for too long.
I said I'm sorry.
Will you please accept my apology?
Ms. Song.
Can't you see me? Hey...
You see me, right? Ms. Song.
Okay. You're unbelievable.
I have to admit it.
Okay. I give up.
Ms. Song, I'm really sorry.
Song Da Hee.
Okay. I really give up.
Take care and have a good life.
Where did I put it?
Ms. Song,
I'm not here, okay? Please.
Ms. Song, you should close up now.
Okay. Let me finish cleaning first.
Do you need anything?
Yes. I can't find my wine anywhere.
I guess I left it here.
It has a white label on it.
Can you check the fridge?
Okay. Please wait.
Move over.
I told you to move over.
Who are you talking to?
Gosh.
Jae Seok, what are you doing there?
Mom.
Mom. I was a little thirsty.
There's water in here.
There's no water.
Hey, my friends were
waiting for you.
Come on.
Mom, I'm a little tired today.
Ms. Choi, is this it?
Yes. This is it.
What are you doing?
Let's go. My friends are waiting.
Mom, I just can't deal with...
Just go say hello. Let's go.
Let's go, son.
Bye.
Eat slowly.
And have some water.
Here.
Is it good?
Yes. It's a lot better than
hospital food.
We have some fruit too.
Hey, you're eating dinner.
Yes.
My son wanted to eat
my fried tofu rice balls.
Si Hoo, say hello.
This doctor is my friend.
Hello.
Hello, Si Hoo.
You're so handsome
since you take after your mom.
Are you still working?
Yes. I have some work to do.
Go ahead and eat.
Gyu Jin.
I went a bit overboard
and made a lot of rice balls.
If you didn't have dinner,
do you want to join us?
Really?
I was just wondering
what to have for dinner.
Let's eat together. Have a seat.
Can I join you?
I want to sit next to you, Si Hoo.
Here.
Gosh, this is amazing.
I love fried tofu rice balls.
Let me try it.
It's so delicious.
Did you make this yourself?
Are you sure you didn't buy it?
No. I make good kimbap
and fried tofu rice balls.
This is really good.
- Mom.
- What, Si Hoo?
I need to go to the restroom.
I'll take you to the restroom.
We'll be back...
No. I can go by myself.
I was careless earlier. I'm sorry.
All right.
I should be cool and go talk to him.
What are you doing here alone?
Hello.
Are you waiting for your mom?
No. I'm just sitting here.
Really? Why?
So Mom can be with the doctor.
The doctor? Who?
My mom's friend.
She likes him.
She keeps smiling.
Apparently, your mom
and the doctor used to be close.
That's what I heard.
By the way, Si Hoo,
where's your dad?
I don't think I've met him before.
I don't have a dad.
I don't even know his face.
I haven't met him before.
Do you remember?
There was a bakery near the church.
You bought me
a lot of cream buns there.
I remember that. I did.
To be honest with you,
I don't like cream buns.
One day,
I just said that I liked it.
And I had to eat it
until I got sick and tired of it.
Really? You should've told me.
How could I tell you that?
I mean you bought them for me.
You're so silly, Gyu Jin.
Then why are you
telling me all this now?
You should've taken it
to your grave.
To embarrass you.
Gosh, you're so mean.
That's perfect timing, Gyu Jin.
Excuse me.
Hello, sir.
With Dr. Song?
Right now?
That jerk.
Instead of watching the store,
he sat there...
laughing with those nasty women.
The moment I saw that,
I felt lasers come out of my eyes
like I was an evil dinosaur.
Wait. Don't evil dinosaurs
spew flames from their mouths?
They do. From their mouths.
Whether it's eyes or mouth,
that's not the point!
Let's all calm down, shall we?
What are you saying we should do?
You said we can't let this happen.
What do you want to do?
Give them a warning.
Once and for all.
A warning? What kind of warning?
It's not like our market
is a huge bar.
They're stealing our customers...
and laughing while
they're barely clothed.
That's a huge minus to
our image as a whole.
We should act as one...
and tell them
not to do business like that!
As one? As in, we all go over there?
If you don't want me to,
Ok Boon can lead a few of us.
What? Me?
Why me? I can't do that.
Those women scare me.
Still, you're married to
the merchant association president.
Who can take action
at a time like this if you won't?
We don't have the authority.
But I don't think that...
Yes. Just do it, Ok Boon.
- What?
- We three will back you up.
Let's give them a notice...
and go back to business as usual.
I need my chemical peels.
Let's go.
Let's put them in their place.
- Yes, let's.
- Let's all go.
My gosh.
- Appear on TV?
Yes.
You know the show "Doctors",
don't you?
It's the number one hit show
on cable TV.
The producer is
my society president's nephew,
and the president
had recommended you two...
join the panel as regulars.
It's spring and they're planning
to switch things around.
Isn't that great?
I don't know. It's a bit...
I'm not interested.
TV isn't my thing.
Please refuse for me.
What?
I already gave the okay.
I thought you'd jump at the chance.
Every doctor wants to
be on that show.
It's a regular spot.
Not only can you
promote our hospital,
but it'll be a huge plus
for your careers.
Yes, I know that, but still.
If it has to be from our hospital,
ask Dr. Jo and Dr. Park...
My society president
recommended you.
You two, not Dr. Jo and Dr. Park.
I'm sorry, director.
I have nothing more to say.
Dr. Song.
You can't leave
during the conversation!
Do something, will you?
You should back me up
even if she won't.
The timing is not that great.
I apologize.
Do it instead of apologizing.
Must you be like this?
- Put the ingredients in the fridge.
- Okay.
We're closed for... My goodness.
My gosh.
Aren't you the chicken lady?
What brings you all here?
Okay, so, the thing is...
We're here to give you a warning.
(Once Again)
I was nasty in my time.
I'll show them what it means
to belittle someone.
Don't back down. 90 percent
of a fight is your energy.
It's game over
the moment you feel intimidated.
I think we're at a dead end.
We have to go through this one day.
Mom. How about
you take a day off work...
and go on a date with me?
I felt so excited just now.
Just the thought makes me so happy.
You must tell her.
You must tell her, Na Hee.
This is great.
Mom. The thing is...