Put the ingredients in the fridge.
Okay.
We're closed for...
My goodness.
My gosh.
Aren't you the chicken lady?
What brings you all here?
Okay, so, the thing is...
We're here to give you a warning.
A warning?
(Episode 15)
I don't think I quite follow.
I've been...
watching you for a few days
after you opened your diner and...
Yes, I'm listening.
Well...
The way you operate
your diner isn't...
It doesn't fit the market tradition.
It's tasteless to be exact.
What do you mean by "tasteless"?
Let's start with the sign out front.
The drawing on it
is a bit hard to understand.
The sign out front?
It was for my previous business,
and it's practically brand new.
It'll be a waste of money
to throw it away,
so I thought I'd make
good use of it.
Hold on.
Are you saying
you're going to keep using that?
What else can we do?
New signs cost extra money...
and we spent every last penny
we had for buying this place.
We're broke.
It's not like you ladies
will pay for a new one.
Also, please refrain...
from soliciting people out
on the street to come inside.
We don't know what sort of
business you previously ran,
but we don't do that here.
Why not?
How can you run a business without
asking customers to come inside?
We live in an era of self-promotion.
Only accepting customers
who walk in willingly...
- is too old-fashioned.
- Exactly.
It's nice that
you're taking initiative, but...
- But then we're good, right?
- Right.
So what else?
Your clothes and hair!
That's what I hate the most.
Who shows skin like this
in a small diner?
One might think you're a call girl.
Tell me about it.
Who cares what you think?
Are you saying we're not allowed
to wear what we want?
Must those who run
a business at a market...
wear baggy pants of all colors
and have extra curly hair?
It's like a uniform, if you ask me.
Fashion is all about
being satisfied with yourself.
It's not like
we're carrying around daggers,
so I'd appreciate some level
of respect for our individuality.
While we're at it,
let me explain my makeup.
Growing up in the woods
gave me so many freckles.
I would've given anything
to be born with...
fair skin like yours,
but all I can do is conceal it now.
I'm sure the sister understands.
- What?
- So,
did that answer your questions?
I tried my best, you know.
You're probably exhausted,
so go ahead and get some rest.
Gosh, look at the bags
under your eyes.
You must be exhausted.
Then get home safely.
- Girls, let's call it a day.
- Sure.
- Mop the floor.
- Got it.
- Mop the floor!
- What on earth?
Mop, mop.
My goodness.
My gosh.
Let's go.
Can you believe it?
Gosh, look at the time.
I should close up.
See you tomorrow.
I need to clean up too.
Bye, Ok Boon.
What now?
You dragged me here
and look what happened.
What will they think of me now?
I'll never lead the pack again,
so don't you make me.
What on earth
are you blaming me for?
What has that woman been eating?
Never have I seen a woman...
that boisterous
and shameless before.
No, sir.
Saying that won't persuade us.
We're not going on TV.
We won't change our minds.
Gosh, what's this smell?
The stew must be burning.
Sir, I'll call you back.
I'm terribly sorry!
No, sir. That's not it.
It's not because
you did anything wrong.
No, it's just that we're...
That's not it.
Wait, what's that smell?
I mean sound?
I think I'm hearing something.
Someone must be at the door.
I'll call you back.
I'm terribly sorry.
I thought my ears
were going to melt.
He's been calling us back and forth
for hours now.
Why won't he give up already?
Tell me about it.
The man sure can whine.
It doesn't seem like
he'll give up easily. Now what?
What else can we do?
It's not like we can
actually go on TV.
That's not what I meant.
Why don't we...
just tell the director our status?
Are you serious?
Have you forgotten
that he's close to your mother?
This isn't at all like
keeping your brother's secret.
Who do you think
the director is closer to?
Us or your mother?
The show is next week,
so let's hold him off until then.
I'm sure they'll look
for a substitute shortly.
I can't believe the stress.
The stew has completely boiled down.
How am I supposed to eat this?
But I saw you eat earlier today.
You want more?
Well, Si Hoo didn't like
the hospital food,
so she packed some food for him.
She packed too much
and asked me to finish it off.
But I was interrupted
by the director's call.
One might think of you
as the husband.
Don't be ridiculous.
Don't let Si Hoo's father hear that.
Si Hoo's father?
You see,
she's always been the type
to be generous to those around her.
When she was in the choir,
she used to pack...
- sandwiches for everyone...
- Who cares?
Yes, exactly.
I don't even know
why I'm explaining myself to you.
So I'll officially start
my promotions today.
With running a business,
half of it is getting started,
and the other half is promotions.
I'll send out
my business cards today and...
Look at you,
talking like a true businessman now.
I'm amazed.
Da Hee, I'm grateful and all,
but I'd rather you call me a CEO
than a businessman.
Shouldn't you put on a suit to
make yourself look more presentable?
Something casual
would probably be better.
Wearing a suit
makes me look like a thug.
My gosh. Who said that?
Which scumbag said that to you?
Hyun Gyung.
That's what you listen to?
Hyun Gyung is someone
he always listens to.
It's why he divorced her so easily
when she asked.
Do you want my help
promoting your company?
I can get people's attention.
Save it, old lady,
and look after the kids.
Old lady?
Are you kidding me?
No one calls me old on the streets.
Son, do I look old to you?
No, you're beautiful.
Right? I am, right?
My son sure has good taste,
unlike someone I know.
This is why brainwashing
can be dangerous.
Gosh, I almost forgot. Mom,
did you leave this and a plant
outside my office?
No, I don't even know where it is.
Well, the address
is on the business card so...
Was it either of you then?
- No.
- It wasn't me either.
If I had stopped by,
I would've announced myself.
You're right. Then who...
No way. That's impossible.
I must be crazy to think that.
What are you mumbling on your own?
Stop yapping and eat up.
Your mother and I
have a meeting to get to.
Eat up.
(Monthly credit card bill:
4,732 dollars)
Over 4,000 dollars?
No way. When did I spend that much?
That's right. The restaurant!
You crazy cow. How stupid are you?
Your pride doesn't pay
your credit card bill.
I need to pay my monthly rent soon,
so what am I going to do?
Right, then.
I'm sure you all know about
our regular disinfection tomorrow.
Also,
I'd like to talk to you about adding
a new member to the association.
It's Unnie's Kimbap in Block A.
- What?
Unnie's Kimbap?
You want us to approve
of them joining?
I'm against it.
Me too.
Why should we let her join
when she doesn't care...
about following the rules
of our market?
Does she think
she can walk all over us?
Exactly!
There's no need
to be so petty, you know.
They're part of the family now,
so if it's not a problem...
We're only being this way
because they are a problem.
Do you even know what she said?
We're to respect
their individuality...
since fashion
is about self-satisfaction.
She can work alone
since she values her individuality.
Why bother joining
our association anyway?
Lower your voice.
There's no need to take the lead.
Guys, come on.
It's not like I particularly want
to be generous toward them.
But it's hard to run a business...
without joining the association.
How about we let them join first...
and try to have them
meet us halfway?
He's right. It's not nice...
to ostracize people anyway.
It could start a rumor...
about the merchants here
being territorial.
So let's take
a peaceful approach and...
Keep the peace yourself,
why don't you?
If we must do this,
then get them to promise something.
If they agree...
to follow our rules and cooperate,
we could think about
letting them join.
That's right.
They should make a promise.
Yes, they should.
What? On one condition?
Just forget about it.
We'd rather not get involved
with an association...
that strong-arms people.
We're not joining.
What's going on, Cho Yeon?
In order to join the association,
we need to comply
with the ladies' rules.
They won't let us join if we don't.
What a dirty move.
Who gave them the right
to push us around?
This is ridiculous.
I guess they found out
that I used to run a bar.
That's why they are
looking down on us.
The monk said...
no human is above a human,
and no human is below a human.
Who's calling who vulgar?
Forget it, Cho Yeon.
Just ignore them.
Right. Just forget about them.
Gosh, I just want to fight them.
If they keep being like this,
I'll just have it out with them.
What did she say?
Did she say she wouldn't accept it?
She said she doesn't need it.
She just hung up on me.
My gosh. She's unbelievable.
My goodness.
She just hung up on you?
I knew she was something,
but she's stronger than I thought.
She wants to run a business here...
without joining
the merchant association?
I guess she doesn't know anything.
She's so stubborn.
Anyway, she's really something.
Even if we threaten her,
she will never cave in.
What are you talking about?
We didn't threaten her.
We're giving her a chance.
Why are you yelling at me?
You were practically
shaking with fear in front of her.
Gosh, when did I do that?
It's not that I was scared.
She was just being so ignorant.
It's not that I was afraid of her.
I just have no time for her.
- You're here.
- Hello.
Good morning.
- Good morning, everyone.
I can't get caught.
- Excuse me.
- Hello.
Hang on. Let me in.
Hello.
Director Jang, come on in.
I guess you're quick
because you're young.
Thank you.
- Gyu Jin.
- Dr. Yoon.
Hello, Director Jang. Good morning.
Hi.
Hello, Na Hee. You're early.
Hey. Good morning.
Did you turn off your phone?
- What phone?
- I mean your cell phone.
If not,
the director will call you all day.
What are you guys doing?
Do you have eye trouble?
Turn off your phone
and have lunch outside.
That whiny director is
quite persistent.
We never know when he'd barge in.
That whiny director is so stubborn.
Have a nice day.
- I have to go.
- Gosh, what was that?
How could you do that?
What's so hard
about doing me a favor?
I wasn't going to do this.
(Director Jang Choong Soo)
Take a look at this.
We've been in deficit
since last year.
Do you know why?
Dr. Yoon.
You advised me to make aggressive
investments for high-quality care,
so we increased the number
of hospital rooms.
Dr. Song.
We changed to more
expensive medicines...
because you said so.
What?
I will get back as much as I invest?
What nonsense.
Do you think I'm getting it back?
You can't do this to me.
So the president called her.
Do you know what she said?
She said, "I don't need
the merchant association."
"I know how to get things done."
"I will show you
disregard and disrespect."
She practically wants a fight.
My goodness.
Did she really say that?
Of course, she did.
That's what I heard.
I don't make things up.
Has she lost her mind or what?
I don't care what she's up to.
I used to be quite notorious
in Wangsimni back in the days.
- Just bring it on.
- I know.
Hello there.
- You're early today.
- Hello.
Look at your clothes.
Those are huge flowers.
You look great.
- Have a nice day.
Have a nice day.
They are smiling.
They just made fun of us, right?
- Yes.
- Sure.
I can't believe this.
Darn it.
Did you just see their faces?
They look brutal.
I was so intimidated.
They are quite scary
when they're together.
Don't be intimidated.
A fight is all about spirit.
Once you lose your nerve,
the fight is over.
We should treat them with a smile
at a time like this. You know?
Okay. I get it.
Fine. We're experts in smiling.
By the way, those petty things are
just getting on my nerves.
The woman with the tiny eyes.
She keeps acting up.
She's so annoying.
Hello. I'm from Good Action Company.
We can hit, get hit,
or rise from the dead.
We can do just about anything.
Please call us. Thank you.
Producer Choi, do you remember me?
I was the stand-in for Lee Seo Jin.
I heard you're starting
a historical drama.
My guys look
like prisoners of war...
even without makeup.
If you hire two people,
we can send you an extra.
Buy 2, get 1 free.
Isn't it a good deal?
Please call us.
Good Action Company. Thank you.
Hello, sir.
Why are you carrying a heavy box?
You might hurt your back.
- Hello.
- You know who I am.
It's Good Action Company.
Gosh. I was so afraid
the toilet would be clogged again.
What are you doing?
Are you a larva? Just get up.
I'm so cold.
I have aches and pains
all over my body.
Really? I feel the same way.
I feel itchy all over.
Come on and scratch my back.
Is it because the room is moldy?
Did you see the ceiling?
When I lived alone,
I saw the map of Korea
on the ceiling.
But this is my first time to see
the map of the world.
If it's that bad up there,
it means the walls and floors
are all rotten.
Can't we just go back to a sauna?
At least the floor is warm there.
No, we can't.
Did you not see
Joon Seon feeling so happy?
And what about the money?
What are you doing?
- You're here.
- Hello.
Hey, did you sleep well?
How was it?
Did you get some good sleep?
- It was like paradise.
- It's so comfortable.
Really?
I guess this place suits you well.
That's nice.
Let's eat before we practice.
Put these away.
I'll go cook noodles.
Okay.
(Sort out your recyclables.)
Stop.
(Please separate your garbage.)
How are you?
How I'm doing is not your business.
You're not supposed to dump
your garbage here.
I heard this is where merchants
take out the garbage.
It's for the members
of the merchant association.
You're not a member.
Then where should we throw out
our garbage?
- Come again.
- Thank you.
You left your food.
I'll pack it for you.
- No.
- It's okay.
- I'm full.
Come again. Study hard.
People in this neighborhood
have small appetites.
Hey.
Are you loafing around
and avoiding doing the dishes?
No.
I had to go all the way
outside the market...
to dump the garbage.
The disposal site over here is for
members of the merchant association.
So we're not supposed
to use the place.
- What?
- Cho Yeon.
The merchant association wouldn't
let us cash in gift cards.
It's only for the members.
- What should we do with these?
- Hang on.
We get a lot of gift cards.
What do we do?
Gosh, this is unbelievable.
Give me that. This is ridiculous.
Take this.
I told you.
That's not within my authority.
Then who's in charge?
It's fine that we can't use
the disposal site.
We can walk all the way
for exercise.
But we're running the business
in the market.
It's just unfair that we can't
cash in the gift cards.
It's like you don't want us
to run a business in the market.
I understand. I really do.
But it's the association that issues
and manages the gift cards.
There's nothing I can do.
Gosh, this is ridiculous.
Gosh, it's so hot.
Now that you're here,
let me tell you something.
Why don't you just give in
and join the association?
You can't run a business in a market
without winning over the women.
You should look further ahead.
It's so touching.
You're just playing the hypocrite.
Holding out like that wouldn't work.
We're having
the regular disinfection today.
If you keep being like this,
you can't be part of it.
- Are you okay with that?
- Are you threatening me now?
I'm not threatening you.
If you give way a little,
I can arbitrate between you two.
The women in the market
aren't that bad.
They just lost their temper,
but they don't hold grudges.
- So if you...
- Apparently, in the colonial era,
the Japanese exchanged
awards of honor amongst themselves.
- What did you say?
- The bottom line is...
that I can't cash
these gift cards in.
Fine. I get it.
My goodness.
What woman is as stubborn as
a whale's tendon?
My gosh.
I wondered why she didn't visit.
Did you butt heads again?
We didn't butt heads.
I don't care anymore.
I did what I could.
I give up.
The more I see that woman,
she reminds me of you.
Her facial features
and that stubbornness.
One would even think
you're siblings.
Hey. How does she look like me?
How so? How does she look like me?
- The way you act!
- What?
- Move.
- Darn you.
- What?
- What else?
Don't you think we need to talk?
I thought about it all day.
We have two options.
- We appear on TV.
- That's nonsense.
Or we tell the hospital director
the truth...
and explain why we can't do it.
We can't do that.
Once he knows, it's a matter of time
before your mother does.
Then my mom will hear right away.
The director can't keep a secret.
Then what do you want to do?
Can you think of a reason
other than that we're divorced?
The director called me
14 times today.
He won't give up.
Should I quit my job?
Are you serious?
I have even less reason to do that.
I just said it out of frustration.
I'm not prepared myself.
But...
I think we're at a dead end.
This might just be
our chance to come clean.
I know it's harder for you
to tell than me.
Yes. The shock would be immense
for your mother.
But still,
we have to go through this
once someday.
Think about it carefully.
I will too.
Thank you.
(Yongju Traditional Market)
(Unnie's Kimbap)
- Wait.
- Skip this store.
What? It'll be of no use
if you disinfect...
all the stores but one.
I don't care. Skip this store.
Move onto the next one.
Skip this one.
Hurry up.
Cho Yeon. They really passed us by.
They're really skipping our store.
They said they would.
Would they change their mind?
Forget them and come help.
Will this be enough?
It's extra potent.
Are you supposed to stick this here?
Cho Yeon, how about...
you just give in
and join the association?
The disposal site is way too far,
and customers complain that
we don't take gift cards.
Yes, Cho Yeon.
They say that crawling is winning.
"Losing is winning."
You can't crawl and win.
It's the same thing.
We're already at war.
We took out our swords.
We must either cut a radish...
or cut down the highhanded
association people.
We'll do something.
It's just so inconvenient.
Yes. Fighting might only hurt us.
You sound like
someone from the past.
Hey. If everyone were like you,
we'd have never ousted the Japanese.
(Unnie's Kimbap)
Wait and see.
I will fight to the end...
and uphold our style.
Do you think I'll fail?
No. If anyone can do it, you can.
Why are you watching TV today?
You won't study?
Not today. I'm taking a day off.
Me too.
You take every day off.
Is that allowed?
Won't Auntie scold you?
Ji Hun. I don't have to
study anymore.
My dad's a CEO now. Right, Auntie?
I have a lot on my mind today.
Let's watch TV in peace.
What's bothering you?
Talk to me. I'm a great listener
for my friends.
Are you?
Do you have cash?
Yes. 18 dollars.
Keep quiet and watch TV.
Grandma and Grandpa are late today.
I really need to see Grandpa.
- My gosh.
- Finally.
Did you all have dinner?
Oh, look, Seo Young is here too.
Grandma, Grandpa,
did you have a good day?
What?
Grandpa. May I request
an audience with you?
I have something urgent to tell you.
Sure, come on in.
I'm not sure if you heard,
but I scored pretty well
in the last exam.
Oh, did you?
What was your average score?
My average score
isn't the point, Grandpa.
The point is how much
I improved from last time, isn't it?
Since I'm doing better,
I plan to raise...
my average score by five points
in the next exam.
Oh, great. That's good to hear.
But I need something to motivate me.
I'm now a CEO's daughter,
and I could do with more funding
to keep up the appearance.
- You want an allowance?
- Yes. You're the best.
If you pay me a little in advance,
I'll use that as motivation...
to not inconvenience you or Dad.
Fine. I do hope
you stick to your word.
I like that.
- Here.
- My gosh.
Grandpa, can't you be
a little more generous?
A little more, please?
Fine, here you go.
Thank you.
I'd have appreciated two of these,
but I'll study hard!
That kid.
She didn't get her smarts
from her dad.
Who does she take after?
She's so cute.
You got money?
From Grandpa. I do this sometimes.
He's generous
if you take him on alone.
You should give it a go.
Oh, it's Mom. What perfect timing.
Smiley. Wake up.
Yes?
Father. Are you free for a chat?
I have something urgent to tell you.
Come in if it's not about money.
I'll let you rest.
I wonder who she takes after.
Did you have fun today?
Let's go home.
Seo Young, I said I'd scold you
if you missed class once more.
Just wait until we're home.
Yes, Mother, do as you wish.
You're just leaving?
- Dad!
- My dear girl!
Why are you so late?
I waited for you.
Dad was a bit busy.
Hi, Seo Jin.
What did you do?
Did you have business meetings
or something?
Well, something like that.
CEO Song, good for you!
Good for you too!
Seo Young, get in the car.
I'm tired.
Okay.
I have to go. Make lots of money.
I will.
There's an interview for
Seo Jin's kindergarten next month.
It was hard to find an opening
at a special needs center.
They want to see both parents.
Okay. Tell me when you have a date.
Hyun Gyung.
Did you leave a potted plant...
and business card case
outside my office?
No. Why would I go there?
See you.
Yes. You'd never visit.
Then who was it?
It must be nice for you.
You stay the same and never age.
Do you know what day it is tomorrow?
It's the 35th anniversary
of the day we met.
I can't forget the look on your face
when you fell in love with me.
- I'm home, Mom.
- Welcome home.
Let's eat. I'm hungry.
I already ate. You haven't?
Can't you just pretend
I'm not around...
and eat when you're hungry
and sleep when you're sleepy?
How can I pretend
you're not around when you are?
Okay, fine. I apologize. I'm sorry.
Come home early tomorrow.
I don't want to eat alone, okay?
Okay, I'll do as you wish, Mother.
He's so cold-hearted.
He's even worse than Gyu Jin.
I know it's harder for you
to tell than me.
Yes. The shock would be immense
for your mother.
But still,
we have to go through this
once someday.
Think about it carefully.
Na Hee, hi. This is out of the blue.
- Is something up?
- Of course not.
You probably have to go
to work today, right?
Of course.
What else should I do
when frying chicken is my job?
How about you tell Dad
you're taking the day off...
and go on a date with me?
Today? Just the two of us?
Yes, just the two of us.
My heart just skipped a beat,
you know.
I'm excited just to think about it.
Okay, fine. I'll get that day off
if it's the last thing I do.
Sure. Hold on. I'll call you back.
- Honey!
- Yes?
- Honey, hold on.
- What is it?
Let me take the day off today.
It's Na Hee's day off too...
and she asked me out today.
Na Hee? That's not like her at all.
Who cares
if this is like her or not?
My husband never takes me anywhere,
so it'd be nice
to go on a date with her.
I'm taking the day off, okay?
Wait. What should I wear?
My dress is at the cleaners.
What else do I have?
Look at her all excited.
What's so good about going out
when all you do is spend money?
Anyway, don't they know
what time it is?
Loafers, wake up!
Where did it go?
This is definitely where I parked.
(From Na Hee)
I took the car to see my mom.
(Unnie's Kimbap)
It's as if the disinfectant...
washed away all my troubles too.
Tell me about it.
I haven't seen Ok Boon
all day today.
Did she go somewhere?
She took the day off...
to go on a date
with her second daughter.
- The doctor, right?
- Yes.
She's as cold as dry ice,
but I guess she's warm
toward her mother.
(Unnie's Kimbap)
This coffee sure is delicious.
Sharing cups of coffee like this
among the people...
is the beauty of working together
in the market, right?
Yes, of course!
It's sweeter than usual too.
Did someone add in honey?
Who does she think she is
glaring at us like that?
How dare she.
Why doesn't she join
the association then?
Look at all this dust.
Gosh, the dust.
Let me dust this off.
Unbelievable.
They're not just annoying
but childish too.
What's wrong?
Did the ladies pick on you again?
Ga Yeon, can you make some coffee?
Make it strong
with three instant coffee packets.
Instant coffee?
But you don't like it
because it's too sweet.
I'm craving something sweet,
that's all.
I want it served cold too.
Sure thing.
What's this?
What's going on?
My gosh.
Girls, stop being so silly.
What's so scary
about one little cockroach?
Are pretty ones
always this dramatic?
Unbelievable.
There's nothing scary about bugs.
Bugs...
It's good.
Young Dal, are you still on board
for deliveries?
Yes, is there someone
that I can hire?
My brother hired
a new delivery guy...
for his galbi restaurant
and I snagged him away.
He's good on the motorcycle...
and has made deliveries before.
That's great then.
When can he start?
Tomorrow if you like.
My brother already approved.
I'm sorry, Young Dal.
Our coffee break got extended.
I bet you talked smack
about the kimbap place.
I can't understand how women
bond over a common enemy...
when they're normally
at each other's throats.
That's absurd.
We've always been
good friends and colleagues.
Well, you've done enough.
You should now
persuade the ladies...
into allowing the kimbap place
to join the association.
They can't run their business...
without joining it.
Why should we?
They should be the ones
begging to join us.
They just don't seem
like the type...
to back down from a fight,
that's all.
My gosh. I'll do it!
- Do what?
- I'll accept the terms...
and heed your warning.
Please...
It was terrifying.
My gosh.
(Episode 16)
I tried doing something
fancy to my hair,
but I don't think I did a good job.
Maybe I should've
stopped by the salon.
You're beautiful, Ms. Jang.
So what's gotten into you today?
Did something happen at work?
Like what exactly?
I just wanted to get
something nice to eat with you...
and talk about a few things.
Gyu Jin will be uncomfortable
without his car today though.
I'm sure he took a cab.
He'll be fine for a day.
That's not true for someone
who drives every day.
This is why
you should've bought a car too.
No way. It won't be good
for my already bad temper.
You say that like
there's a problem with you.
I hate when people
don't follow the rules...
and I step on the brakes
when I get too angry...
He didn't even signal,
that son of a gun.
I get it now.
Let's only have Gyu Jin drive.
What?
Wasn't that hilarious?
Gosh this is so pretty.
- Look at the seagull.
- Where?
This is amazing.
- It is.
- How nice.
I haven't been to the beach
in a while.
I'll walk over there.
Sure. Mom, watch your step, okay?
Na Hee!
Gosh, it's good.
After all that fuss,
this is where you wanted to come?
This acorn jelly place?
I didn't know a better restaurant.
The story is the same
for when I dated your father.
All we did was eat buns
at a local bakery.
This is the one special place
we came to on a date.
We were on our way back...
from telling my parents
that we were getting married.
Have you ever regretted...
your life with Dad?
Of course I have.
More than a hundred times.
Still, the man grew on me.
And thanks to marrying your father,
I was able to give birth...
to such a sweet
and devoted daughter.
Gosh, Mom.
I haven't done much for you.
This is more than enough!
I feel like I'm on cloud nine,
you know.
Then enjoy the dish.
I'll take you out more often.
Actually,
once a year would
be more than enough.
It'll definitely
give me some air to breathe.
So, Mom...
Hold on a second.
Doesn't Gyu Jin love acorn jelly?
He gobbled it down
the last time I made it for him.
I guess...
Wait a second.
- Ma'am.
- Yes?
Can we get a bowl
of acorn jelly salad to go?
Mom, there's no need for that.
Take it home for Gyu Jin.
He seemed gaunt the other day...
which has been horrible
for his handsome face.
Is it because you don't
cook for him often?
I was embarrassed, you know.
He eats fine, Mom.
He only seems gaunt
because work has been stressful.
I'm just saying that
you should be more attentive.
Gosh, Gyu Jin would love this.
He enjoys everything he eats,
doesn't he?
I remember how he enjoyed
this acorn jelly too.
Have some as well.
Please have a seat, everyone.
So the ladies want three things.
One, change your sign out front.
Two, no attracting customers.
Three, appropriate attire.
Will you accept those conditions?
Right.
I'll change my sign out front
as soon as possible...
and refrain from attracting
customers on the street.
But the clothes and makeup...
Okay, fine.
I can change what I wear.
But I can't give up my hairstyle.
Just like you...
pray underneath the talisman...
for a successful
day of sale every day,
we go to the salon every morning...
to get ourselves ready
for what's to come that day.
Our hairstyle is our talisman
and our symbol.
This I can't give up.
Okay, sure. Your clothes
were the real issue anyway.
I didn't really care
about your hair either.
Okay, then.
So we've come to an agreement.
Do you now approve...
of Unnie's Kimbap joining
the merchant association?
What you say here is final.
- Sure thing.
- I'm good.
Then go ahead and shake hands...
to show that you've made peace.
What? That is hardly necessary.
You do it instead, Young Dal.
You just never can be generous,
can you?
Okay, fine. Young Dal, go ahead.
Sure thing.
I know we clashed at first,
but let bygones be bygones
and move forward from here.
Welcome to our market.
- Sure. Thanks.
- Good.
- Let's applaud.
- All right.
I doubt the girls have
anything long to wear.
Must we go shopping?
How annoying!
I'm only taking a step back
so I can take two steps forward.
We'll see who gets
the last laugh, ladies.
Ma'am!
- Goodness.
- You're here.
What did you bring today?
Shepherd's purse
and things like that.
The spinach last time was delicious.
Thank you for enjoying it.
Let me drag this for you.
Guys, why weren't you picking up?
Jong Soo, what's wrong?
Are you sick? Talk to me.
I woke up today...
but my body was aching all over
and I couldn't move.
Then you should've
gone to see a doctor.
Where's Jeong Bong?
Jeong Bong...
What's wrong with you?
Joon Seon, it's the mold.
I'm allergic to it, you know.
This place is too damp...
and I can't live here.
Can you scratch my back for me?
Unbelievable.
Come on in.
Are you sure we can stay here?
It'll be uncomfortable
to share the space with us.
Don't sweat it.
When did that ever worry me?
As you can see,
it was cheaper to let it rot...
rather than fix it up for a rental.
The ceiling leaks sometimes
and the toilet gets clogged,
but it'll be better here.
Thanks, Joon Seon.
This place is like a hotel to us.
Thank you so much, Joon Seon!
Keep your voice down.
Guys, listen up.
Just so you know,
I'm not exactly the most
welcomed person in the family.
Rather than a son,
they see me as a tenant.
So would they be happy to know
that I've brought in...
two more people?
No, they wouldn't.
- They'd hate it.
- Right?
So you must stay silent
and be almost like ghosts.
- Do you understand?
- I do.
- What did I mean?
- What?
What did he mean?
Could you repeat that?
So in short, you two will now...
be ghosts in this house.
Until I get us a deal
for a new place,
you'll practice being invisible.
- What did I say?
- Be invisible.
That's right. You can probably
tell this by the wallpaper,
but this is an old house,
so the walls are thin.
My mom may not be an issue,
but my dad is someone
you need to watch out for.
He's a dangerous man.
If you get caught,
he'll kick me out too.
He might even kill me.
He sleeps lightly too.
- Do you get me?
- Yes, we get you.
- I'll be careful.
- Good.
- Seriously?
- Sorry, it was my dumbbells.
Gosh.
I thought that
nothing scared the woman,
so hearing her talk about her hair
was a bit of a surprise.
I did feel bad for her in a way.
Don't be ridiculous.
- No one told her to stick it out.
- Exactly.
Anyway, we got what we wanted.
Gosh, that feels great.
Hello, ladies.
- Hi, Ms. Jang.
- Hi, Yun Jeong.
Sorry, Ms. Choi.
You must be here
to shop for groceries.
It's good to see you, Ms. Choi.
It's been a while.
Has business been well?
Yes, of course!
So is Ok Boon at the store?
No, Na Hee took her out on a date.
They're on Ganghwa Island.
A date?
I'm having dinner
with my son this evening too.
My second son
has come back from Turkey.
I see.
Then...
Have a good day then.
Why does she always
greet people like that?
She never bows her head.
She owns a building, remember?
I guess she believes
she's too classy for us.
Fundamentally,
we're all human beings though.
She's always been a jerk.
Even since high school,
she'd glance at others like that.
It's an illness if you ask me.
My gosh.
She never wants
to have a meal with me,
but she goes off on a date
with her mom? Unbelievable.
You're back, Ms. Choi.
Please let me take that.
It's fascinating how two sisters
can be so different.
Why did you buy so much today?
I'm grilling some steak today.
It's a special day,
so I was hoping to
enjoy it with my son...
accompanied by a glass of wine.
That'd be nice.
I wonder when he'll get here though.
Son, when will you
be home this evening?
Mom, I'm going to be
a bit late today.
An implant procedure
has been scheduled.
What?
You promised to have
dinner with me today!
Did I? When?
I guess that's what you said,
but I didn't hear it.
Do you have a death wish?
Come home right after the surgery.
I don't want to eat alone tonight.
What did you say?
I can't hear you. What?
Mom? I'm busy. I have to go.
I'm sorry, Mom. I love you.
Hey. Well...
Jae Seok!
Gosh. That jerk.
Ms. Choi.
I like steak.
Why did you lie to her?
Your afternoon schedule is empty,
so you're just slaking off.
Mom wants to have dinner with me.
I don't want to be alone
with Mom anymore, Gyu Jin.
So?
What are you going to do
with the TV show?
Gosh, I don't know.
I'm still thinking.
Why is everything so tough for you?
What are you thinking about,
Dr. Yoon?
Hi, Bo Young.
You looked so lonely from the back,
so I wondered who it was.
Why? Are you worried
about something?
No, I'm not worried.
I guess you are.
You never could hide your feelings.
What's wrong?
I just have a lot on my mind.
I'm not sure
if I made the right choice.
Life is a series of choices.
And it's not so bad to make
a wrong choice from time to time.
It makes you feel confident
about your next choice.
You think?
Yes. So don't lose sleep over it...
and just go ahead with your choice.
- What?
- You haven't changed at all.
You used to give me a lot of advice.
Gosh, you're quite nosy.
What? How dare you say that?
It doesn't hurt at all.
Don't tease me.
Have some bread.
Okay. This place is so nice.
And the coffee smells great.
The coffee is really good.
Ga Hee is going
to cook dinner, right?
If she can't, she will at least
order some Chinse food.
Sure. She has a son.
She wouldn't let him skip a meal.
Don't worry.
Why worry about their dinner here?
I know. This is my problem.
All right. I don't care
if they skip a meal or not.
I'm on strike today.
I'm so lucky today.
Then do you want to live
with me like this?
You can travel around with me
every weekend...
and eat lots of delicious food.
It's okay. You have your family.
I know that's not easy.
This is good enough for me.
Mom. The thing is...
Gosh.
When Gyu Jin came to my place
the other day, he was thirsty.
So I told him to drink juice
in the fridge.
That day, I got...
some red pepper oil
in a juice bottle from the mill.
He just drank it up.
He kept gasping out
and his eyes turned red.
It was hilarious.
Why do you keep
talking about Gyu Jin?
You've been talking about
nothing but him all day.
That's because he is
my one and only son-in-law.
Gosh.
Are you jealous of him?
You know what?
Sometimes Gyu Jin is very reliable,
and sometimes
he's like a little kid.
Unlike Yun Jeong, he's just lovely.
Oh, right. We should call Gyu Jin.
I wonder if he's doing well
without his car.
It's okay. I'll call him later.
I need to go to the restroom.
You should tell her.
You have to tell her, Na Hee.
Gosh, what should I do?
What a waste. This is terrible.
My goodness.
Mom, what's that? What happened?
I tried to stand up
and get some water,
but I accidentally knocked it away.
Do you think I can pick up
the pieces on the top?
You can't eat this. Just get up.
It might ruin your clothes.
I can't believe this.
It was for Gyu Jin.
Gyu Jin loves acorn jelly.
I'm so stupid.
I should've been careful.
I didn't even check
if it was sealed.
Is it too far to go back there
and buy it again?
My goodness.
What a waste. I feel so terrible.
My gosh.
This is really upsetting.
This was for Gyu Jin.
(Ttobongee Chicken)
This is Mr. Song Young Dal.
And this is Ms. Jang.
Mr. Song's wife is not here today.
You'll meet her tomorrow.
Ms. Jang, will you stop drooling?
Welcome. Nice to meet you.
What's your name?
I'm Park Hyo Sin.
Nice to meet you.
I'm glad you're here.
I hope we get along.
By the way, you're so handsome.
You have a creamy complexion.
We don't even need a light
in the store.
I don't even smell
the hot oil anymore.
Thank you.
You need to know the neighborhood
to deliver chickens.
You might have a hard time
for the time being.
No, I know this neighborhood.
My friend lives around here.
Dad, I brought pepper powder.
The owner wasn't there,
so I waited for a long time.
- You're here.
- Long time no see.
Well...
We will start doing deliveries.
He's the deliveryman.
This is Mr. Song's oldest daughter.
Hello. Nice to meet you.
Did you bring your driver's license
and insurance certificate?
Yes. Here.
Let me see.
It's so good to see you.
This is the working environment
I've always wanted.
Women care so much
about men's looks.
It's not just men
who like beautiful women.
Will you move over? I can't see him.
- My goodness.
- Move over.
Gosh, I'm still upset
about the acorn jelly.
Why could I drop it like that?
This just won't do.
I should come again
with Gyu Jin next time.
I won't be satisfied
until I see him eat the acorn jelly.
I guess the traffic is bad
on weekends.
Right?
Na Hee, why are you being so quiet?
Are you sleepy?
No.
You shouldn't doze off
while driving.
Here. Open your mouth.
Mom. You should wear gloves
when you fry chicken.
Look at your hands.
It's okay. I'm used to it.
Make sure to use ointment.
It might leave a scar.
Okay. I will.
I wish every day was like today.
I'm so happy.
This looks amazing, Ms. Choi.
It's like I'm in a restaurant.
Try it.
It doesn't taste bad either.
With some wine.
This is crazy.
It's so delicious.
It's so tender
than I don't have to chew it.
You're so good at cooking.
That's not true.
I just used good meat.
You should try some. Here.
It's good.
Wait.
That's against the rule.
You can't drink alone.
How old did you say you were?
I'm 28.
What a great age.
If I were born now,
I'd have done everything I wanted.
In my time,
marrying well and having kids...
was a woman's standard of happiness.
It all means nothing.
It doesn't mean nothing.
You raised both sons to be doctors.
What's the point in that?
They think they did it themselves.
I suffered to raise them,
and now they ignore me
to enjoy their own lives.
Today is a rough day for me,
and I feel sentimental.
It's the anniversary of
my first date with my husband.
Oh, dear.
I can't believe I said that.
You should eat and close the cafe.
- Let's eat.
- Yes, ma'am.
The steak is really amazing.
Did I eat too much?
What are you doing?
I was going to pass by,
but I came in to ask.
Ms. Song. How could you
betray me at that moment?
Do you know how long
I suffered because of you?
I don't know and I have to close up.
Why don't you spend time
with your mother instead?
What? You're changing
the topic again?
No. We need to talk this out today.
Must you make me feel
so uncomfortable?
What did I do that's so wrong?
You didn't do anything wrong.
So go and check on your mother.
Why do you keep mentioning my mom?
She's not a baby!
There's a reason for all this,
so just go upstairs.
- Get out of here.
- Wait, Ms. Song.
- Get out already.
- Why are you so strong?
- Wait, wait.
- Get out! My gosh.
Mr. Yoon.
Ms. Song.
Oh, dear. It looks very swollen.
I'm so sorry.
Shouldn't you go to a hospital?
I work at a hospital.
I'll get an x-ray
as soon as I get there,
and ask for an estimate.
I'll get some painkillers
and pain relief patches for now.
No, sit back down.
Forget the pain relief patches.
- Are you really sorry?
- Of course I am.
I feel so bad I want to die.
Then including treatment
and pain relief patches,
- buy me something else.
- Something else?
Okay. What?
- Thank you.
- Goodbye.
How can you want alcohol
instead of pain relief patches?
It's not just alcohol.
It's a reconciliation drink.
I feel bad for what
I did to you, and vice versa.
Let's drink this
and call it even. Okay?
Okay.
I'm a bit cheeky
and on the naughty side,
so I sometimes cross the line.
Even more so with people
who I think I clicked with.
I'm truly sorry.
Don't be. I was small-minded.
I let my inferiority complex
control me.
It's fine.
We both feel bad,
so let's not talk about that again.
- Here. Cheers.
- Cheers.
Let's eat.
Order more food.
I'll eat 64 dollars' worth.
Oh, come on!
Eat up quickly
and comfort your mother.
She said it's a special day for her.
It's the first day
she met your late father.
She was so lonely.
I ate with her in your place.
That's why she said...
She should've just said so.
Moms get upset by the smallest
of things the older they get.
So care a bit more for her
from now on.
She likes flowers,
so you can surprise her
with a bouquet delivered.
I'm glad you were there for her.
I hope you work at her cafe
for a long time.
I will only for a few months
until my transfer exam.
Are you studying to transfer?
Yes.
I'd like to study
what I'd always wanted to.
- Though it's a bit late.
- It's not late.
You can study at any age.
That's cool. You're amazing.
I thought you were timid.
Where did you get the guts?
I don't know. I found them.
I feel a little proud of myself
these days.
Do you study during the day?
It's so hard having to study
after years of not doing it.
I can manage English somehow,
but math...
I was dreadful even in high school.
We share the same parents,
so why am I so dumb?
Na Hee's best subject was math.
Do you know...
who did better in math than she?
Who?
It's me.
Ask me if you're stuck.
I bet I'm better than any tutor
in Daechi-dong.
I'd be grateful for the help.
I'll really take you up on
the offer.
You should. No problem.
- I even speak English.
- Oh, stop it.
How about we have another drink?
Let's get along
from now on, Ms. Song.
Yes, let's do that.
Can you really manage alone?
Shall I help you?
No, I live across the street.
I'll take my time.
It's late. Go on home.
Go on. Go.
Put some ice on it later.
And see a doctor about it tomorrow.
I will. How many times
will you say that?
Go on home. Go.
- Go home. Go.
- Goodbye.
Why is she so late?
(Director Jang)
Darn it.
You're home.
Did you tell your mother?
Did you tell her?
Don't take it. I'll be the director.
He just called me.
Hello, Director Jang.
I'll do it.
We'll go on TV.
Flower delivery.
- Ms. Choi Yun Jeong?
- Yes, that's me.
These are for you.
- Sign here, please.
- Okay.
Who sent it?
It says Mr. Yoon Jae Seok.
My gosh.
It must be from your son.
How many flowers are there?
It's beautiful.
You must be so pleased, Ms. Choi.
Have a nice day.
Thank you.
Why did he send me flowers?
He can be so cheeky.
My dear son.
Thank you so much
for agreeing to be on the show.
Especially Dr. Yoon Gyu Jin
and Dr. Song Na Hee.
I heard a lot about you.
You refused at first.
We had some private issues that...
I must make this clear.
We won't be on for long.
It's just for two months.
Yes. Two months.
I was told about that too.
Don't worry.
Does this mean...
the panel of doctors
is just us four?
No. There's an orthopedics
specialist as well.
- He'll be here soon.
- Orthopedics?
Dr. Lee's here.
Hello.
I must be the last to arrive.
I meant to hurry.
Jeong Rok.
- It's been a while, Gyu Jin.
- Yes.
It's even nicer to see you.
Crazy Song Na Hee.
Hello, Jeong Rok.
(Once Again)
I have another question to ask.
Gosh, Na Hee.
You haven't changed at all.
- My gosh, are you all right?
- Seriously?
You'll make up for this.
What?
Hold on a second.
You're the one who knocked the cup,
so why should she pay for anything?
Guys, come on down. No one's home.
Who are you people?
Ga Hee, you're home.
I was wondering if you let others
borrow your husband too.
Gyu Jin!
I lied to you about something.