Actually, I...
Na Hee!
Darn it. You almost hit a person!
Gyu Jin, are you all right?
Yes, of course.
(Episode 19)
- My foot.
- What? What is it?
My foot. You're...
Darn it. Gosh, I'm sorry.
I don't see anything wrong
on the X-ray.
How can it hurt
when nothing's wrong?
Are you sure?
Well...
Your bones and ligaments are fine,
but your muscles must be in shock.
It'll probably hurt
for a few days or so.
How did you end up tripping though?
You just said that
Na Hee and Gyu Jin are divorced.
What? Well... Did I?
I wonder why I said that.
Mr. Yoon, look into my eyes
and answer me.
It's what you said.
You got stuck living with her...
so that you can keep
your brother's divorce a secret.
Your brother is
my brother-in-law...
and your sister-in-law is my sister.
Right?
What makes you think
I only have one brother?
Just so you know,
our family has a tragic secret...
regarding my siblings...
Okay, fine. I'll tell you.
It's already spilled milk anyway.
You're right. They got a divorce.
Gosh.
I don't even know where to begin.
It's true that they got divorced,
but they're still living together...
because they couldn't
sell the house.
They're keeping it a secret
from the families...
and will tell them
when it's the right time.
This is absolutely insane!
How are they going to explain this?
That's what I thought at first,
but there's nothing in this world
that doesn't make sense.
A lot of things can happen.
Not for my sister!
She's the most shrewd person I know.
She doesn't do anything
that doesn't make sense.
What are you yelling at me for?
I'm not the one who got a divorce.
I just don't get it, that's all.
Why would they keep it a secret?
When did this even happen?
I don't know the exact date,
but it's around the time
I came back to Korea.
So I guess a month and a half ago.
Then it's my fault.
What? What do you mean?
It's my fault.
She couldn't say anything
because of my annulment.
My parents were already in shock,
so she couldn't add to their stress.
The timing just wasn't right.
It's not your fault at all.
Don't be like that.
It's not like you caused
their divorce or anything.
Still...
This is absurd. Na Hee too?
My mom will be in shock.
Why don't we give Gyu Jin
and Na Hee some time?
I think that'll be better.
Ms. Song,
forget everything I told you today.
Just forget it all.
Don't look at me like that.
You're making me nervous.
Gyu Jin will kill me
if he finds out I spilled the beans.
You have no idea how scary he can be
when he's furious.
Got it? Come on...
Okay, fine. I'll try and forget it.
- Forget what?
- Na Hee and Gyu Jin's divorce...
Stop! I told you to forget.
Okay, fine.
Promise me.
Come on.
You are not to tell a single soul.
Got it?
Seal the deal.
Finalize it.
Now copy the contract.
Laminate.
This is as good as
any bullet-proof deal.
You must keep it a secret.
Is Na Hee's show on tomorrow?
At what time?
It's 10:30 a.m. at KBN.
You memorized it so much...
that the answer just
popped right out of you.
Of course she's excited.
All the people in the market
will watch.
Mom, it's been a while
since you enjoyed a proud moment.
Of course.
This is more than just a big deal.
Someone in our family
is on TV for the first time.
That's not true.
I've been on TV too.
It was the back of your head,
so it doesn't count.
Your character died in seconds.
You said you never watched
the show I was on.
I guess you did.
It was only in passing, okay?
Today's training has exhausted me.
I'm calling it a night.
Why are you taking that?
To eat some more?
What? Well, I've been
getting hungry at night.
There must be a few beggars
living in my stomach.
You're not entirely wrong.
They're just not in your stomach.
What do you mean by that?
It's nothing.
I was only talking to myself.
Good night then, Joon Seon.
Night.
Ok Ja, are you all right?
You've been spacing out all evening.
What? What do you mean?
I'm fine, you know.
I'm perfectly fine.
Auntie, what are you doing?
Goodness.
- Here you go.
- Gosh.
Oh, of course.
No wonder it hurt my teeth.
No, this is wrong.
Calm down, my beating heart.
Not that jerk.
This is insane. You're crazy.
You've lost it!
Ok Ja, are you going somewhere?
I need some fresh air
before going home.
Not caring about
my health these days...
must've led to angina.
I'll get going then.
See you tomorrow.
- Sure, good night.
- Goodnight, Auntie.
- My gosh.
- Auntie, are you leaving? Bye!
- I'm home.
- Da Hee, you're home.
- Dinner?
- I grabbed a bite to eat.
- I'll get changed first.
- Sure thing.
Hurry on out for some chicken.
They agreed to be on TV together
after getting a divorce?
Unbelievable.
(Na Hee)
Gyu Jin will kill me if he
finds out I spilled the beans.
You must keep it a secret.
You've got to be kidding me.
Na Hee, what are you going to do?
I wonder if they got
a face massage in advance.
I'm glad your brother takes after me
and my great skin.
I blame my darn big mouth.
What on earth are you doing?
Nothing, Mom.
I'm annoyed with my big mouth.
There's nothing wrong
with your lips.
I, for one,
think they're nice and plump.
Of course my mouth is good looking.
This is more about
how I never think before talking.
What do you mean?
You're better off not knowing.
Why did I have to take after
your big mouth too?
The apple never falls far
from the tree, does it?
Blaming me is a habit of yours now,
isn't it?
You dismiss me as if I'm your peer!
Are you kidding me?
See what I mean?
My big mouth deserved that!
Darn it.
Why? What now?
You did it on purpose, didn't you?
What? How can you even...
Sure. I hired someone to almost
hit you with a motorcycle...
so that I could push you. Happy now?
Is this what I get for saving you?
You call this "saving"?
Things happened so fast
that I couldn't help it.
I would've dodged the motorcycle
just fine, you know.
You always overreact.
Everyone knows that
you're slow in your movements.
You wouldn't have dodged anything.
I was so shocked
that I acted without thinking!
Well, it's because
I have a strong sense of justice...
and I'm chivalrous.
Chivalrous, my foot.
What about you then?
Why didn't you see the bike coming?
It's not like I didn't see it.
You were busy looking
at your phone, weren't you?
Haven't you tripped at work enough
from doing that?
You just never learn.
Is your brain only smart
when it comes to academics?
Stop nagging me already.
You're not my husband, you know.
That's enough.
I say this as your colleague.
Get a hot pack on that.
What's it to you?
Fine. That's your loss anyway.
Why did I have to overreact?
Na Hee!
Who does he think he is?
My bodyguard?
What a joke.
Isn't your room too cramped
for the three of you?
It's not bad.
How long are you
going to let them stay here?
You will eventually get caught.
Once you get caught,
you might have your head cut off.
I'll take care of it myself.
Just mind your own business.
Yesterday...
Da Hee, are you going out already?
You seem tired.
Were you up all night?
I didn't sleep well.
Why not? Is it hard to study?
Don't feel pressured.
I'll make sure to send you abroad
to study if it doesn't go well here.
Where do you want to go? Australia?
That's the type of thing
you always say.
You should've made sure
to take good care of your family.
Must you hit me
where it hurts like that?
Well...
Ga Hee. Joon Seon.
- Yes?
- What? Do you have anything to say?
No. Nothing.
Mom, I'm going out.
Wait, Da Hee.
Make sure to eat breakfast.
I wish you had time to eat here.
And you know Na Hee will be
on TV today, right?
Make sure to watch it
and send her a text message.
See you.
- Bye.
- See you.
- Are you leaving now?
- Work hard.
- Okay.
Did you check the water meter again?
Yes. It's just strange.
The meter seems fine,
but the numbers are
increasing quite fast.
We're not doing anything different.
I don't know what's wrong.
I'm sure there's nothing wrong.
Gosh, you're unbelievable.
Who else checks
the meter every morning?
You're helpless.
No. It's still strange.
Gosh, Dad. Where are you going?
I want to go check if there's a leak
in the rooftop room.
There was a leak the other day,
so I guess that's what it is.
No, Dad.
I'm sure it's fine.
How do you know that?
I've got the feeling.
Gosh, don't be silly.
No, Dad. You can't go up there.
- Move over.
- No. Wait, Dad.
- Why?
- No.
Dad.
It's...
my doing.
What?
Water.
I'm the one who used it a lot.
I'm so into lower-body
bathing these days.
Lower-body bathing?
Yes. I've been
feeling tired these days.
I'm sorry, Dad.
I see. They say jobless people
die from overwork.
You're just like that.
What makes you so tired?
Are you tired from breathing
or eating free meals?
I know.
Am I suffering from spring fever?
Why do I feel so tired?
If you want to keep taking baths,
make sure to reuse the bathwater
for the toilet.
If you don't want to,
go to a sauna with your own money.
- Okay.
- Here.
I'm sorry, Dad. I will be careful.
Gosh, are you doing this on purpose
to make me feel sorry?
No, I'm not.
I can tell you do feel sorry though.
All right. Fine.
You got hurt because of me.
So I will give you a ride.
Forget it.
Better to be
physically uncomfortable...
than feel uneasy.
Whatever. It's your loss.
Maybe I should've pretended
to give in and gotten a ride.
Dr. Song.
- Dr. Song.
- Hello, sir.
My dear Dr. Song.
Why are you alone?
Where's Dr. Yoon?
I guess he went to buy something.
I see.
Your show will be aired today.
I told everyone
in the patient's rooms,
waiting rooms, and staff lounges
to watch it.
You will watch it as well, right?
Yes. If I don't have
any patients to take care of.
What are you talking about?
You have to watch it.
Your body is innocent.
The real doctors argue about
which treatments are the best.
Let us introduce you
to our new panel of doctors.
Here with us are the doctor couple
with great chemistry.
They are Pediatricians Yoon Gyu Jin
and Song Na Hee.
Thank you for joining us today.
- You two are working...
- One Americano, please.
- At the same hospital together.
- Hush. I'm not taking orders now.
Go somewhere else.
You two are like two love birds.
My gosh.
It's an old TV,
but they still look great.
Hyo Sin, are you filming it right?
Yes. I will send the video
to your phones.
It's okay.
I just want to watch them like this.
They say those who make good dough
make good noodles.
It's not like they are just smart.
They are good talkers too.
Why were you dressed like that?
You look much better
in bright colors.
Na Hee was wearing colorful clothes.
Did she not even look after you?
I'm the one who picked it.
That's what I like.
And why would she talk
back to you every single time?
She was on TV
for a longer period of time.
That's just because
she speaks better than me.
That's not true.
It's just that you are modest...
while she's such a show-off.
If she's like that again next week,
I won't let it slide.
Gosh, Mom. Please.
Oh, my.
I'm getting a call from a friend.
I bet she watched the show. Bye.
My goodness.
I guess a TV show is a big deal.
It seems the TV show
is very popular.
There's no one around me
who didn't watch it.
They are all jealous
that I have a daughter...
and son-in-law like you guys.
Na Hee, I enjoyed the show.
You looked pretty.
Your dad didn't say much,
but he seemed happy.
He even gave out
more chicken to the customers.
You know that doesn't happen a lot,
don't you?
Mom, I have to get back to work.
Okay, right.
I'm sorry. Go ahead and work.
Tell Gyu Jin
that I really enjoyed it.
Okay. Bye.
Is she that happy?
Her voice sounds so bright.
Ok Boon, I watched the TV show.
Your daughter is so lovely.
Did you watch it?
Thanks.
I watched it too.
Your son-in-law is so handsome.
He has such big eyes.
Gosh, how did you manage to watch it
when you're so busy?
I guess my daughter
has an eye for men.
Thank you anyway.
You must be happy, Ms. Jang.
Your daughter and son-in-law
are so famous.
Gosh, they are not that famous.
They were just on TV.
It's no big deal.
Thank you anyway.
Here.
Where have you been?
We're busy here.
I'm sorry.
I went to buy some green onions,
but people kept talking to me.
Why did you buy green onions?
We have a lot in storage.
Really?
I had no idea.
You are so tactless.
She just went out
to brag about Na Hee.
That's not true, you brat.
Yes, it is.
You can fool a ghost, but not me.
I'm Jang Ok Ja.
I have the quickest of wits.
- I brought chickens.
- Hey.
You're here.
Ok Boon, I watched the show.
Na Hee is the best.
She sounds so smart.
You're too kind.
Anyone can do that...
in front of the camera.
Why would you say something
you don't even mean?
How many chickens did you bring?
I brought 20 for now.
The weather is getting hot.
It's steaming hot.
My goodness.
Well...
Would you like me to help you?
It must be hard.
Smoothly.
The other way.
Go ahead and feel Chi Su's touch.
Ok Ja.
Are you asleep?
Are you sleeping?
You should go home
if you want to sleep.
You're ruining my eyes.
Do you think you're in your 20s?
That's just ugly.
You should try carrying around
heavy heaps of meat.
I'd strip down to my shorts
in this weather.
My gosh,
what on earth are you saying?
I should get going before
I get another earful from you.
- See you later, Young Dal.
- Okay.
See you, Ok Boon!
Why not have a cold cereal smoothie?
Why do you keep chasing him off?
Do you enjoy doing that?
Yes, I just love it.
So what? What's wrong?
That's not what I wanted.
I wish he'd stay longer.
Darn it.
Hi, Seon Ja. What's the occasion?
My gosh, you saw the show?
Yes, yes, that's my second daughter
and my son-in-law.
Don't congratulate me.
It's nothing at all.
Oh, yes, yes.
(Pediatric Dentistry)
Oh, Dr. Song.
- I enjoyed the show.
- Right.
You're awesome.
Right.
Dr. Song, I saw you on TV.
Me too.
Can I get an autograph later?
- Me too.
- Sure. Thank you.
All this after just one show?
What a nuisance.
My gosh.
You scared me! Darn you.
What were you doing in here?
Can't you tell? I was resting.
My department is full of patients...
and everywhere I go,
people make a fuss about the show.
I needed some time alone.
I feel the same.
This won't go on, will it?
I don't know.
I didn't know people watch
so much TV.
We could end up
conning the whole country.
Wow, you sound afraid.
Are you feeling weak?
Don't pretend to be brave.
You're just as scared.
- Gosh...
- Goodness gracious.
I said I'd give you a ride.
Your pride does you no good.
Don't pick on me.
I have no strength to fight back.
Ask me for a lift after work.
If you plead nicely,
I might be willing to help.
No thanks.
I might think about it
if you beg me to ride with you.
Why would I do that? Dream on.
Same here.
Why would I ask
for such an uncomfortable ride?
My gosh.
Hey. What are you two
doing in my hideout?
- This was my...
- This was my hideout...
You two, in here?
Oh, that's what you two got up to?
I was just about to leave.
You brothers can rest.
Okay. Get back to work.
Here's your almost-large medium.
- Thank you.
- Bye.
Yes, of course.
Call me when you're next in Seoul.
You've been talking for hours.
Your phone bill will cost
more than the kids' pay.
I've only been taking calls.
Just one appearance on TV...
and people who never used to call me
are calling me.
Hey, Ok Ja.
Do you remember
Ms. Young Hee's daughter Eun Sook?
That brat.
She looked down on me
for selling chicken in a market,
and even she called
to brown-nose me.
This is why one must be successful.
- I'm back.
- Good job.
It's hard work, isn't it? Well done.
It's fine. The customer paid cash.
Okay, good job.
You must be hungry.
I was too preoccupied
to bring lunch today.
You have to go out and eat.
We can't leave the store unattended.
Let's take turns to eat.
You go first.
Me, me. I'll go and eat first.
Okay. You both can...
No, I have to...
I'll go alone. I have to eat.
Hey, Ok Ja... What got into her?
She can't stand hunger.
(Take-out available,
Delivery available)
(Chi Su's Butcher Shop)
My gosh. Oh, dear me.
My goodness.
I must be out of my mind.
Why is he so sexy?
What's this about?
What do you want?
Is it this?
Gosh, it's hot. Why am I so hot?
Who was that?
The village crazy lady?
It costs 30 dollars
to join the association?
We must sell 10 kimbap
to make that much.
It's not like they do anything.
Cho Yeon, don't you think
30 dollars is cheap?
We spend that on coffee in no time.
Eat the end bits,
not the perfectly long ones.
There are some benefits.
They disinfect our stores regularly
and provide parking spaces.
Cho Yeon, look at this.
There's a sports dance class.
That's hilarious.
There's a class?
You're right, there is.
One during the day
and one in the evening. Okay.
Why? Are you interested?
Of course. I paid the fee.
I shall reap the benefits.
Come with me. Make it worthwhile.
No thanks.
There will only be potbellied men
and chatty women.
Yes, Cho Yeon.
Our working environment here...
is just too desolate.
Do you miss the old days that much?
After dealing with all those losers,
do you still miss men? Do you?
I can't stand
even thinking about men.
Welcome.
Can I eat here?
Yes.
(Integrated Care Center)
Good job, you two.
Wasn't it a long day? Good job.
Is Dr. Song still working?
Yes.
I think she'll be late.
She still has patients.
Oh, does she?
My gosh.
Let's see...
He's an attacking midfielder.
Why put him on defense?
Come on, pass, pass. There you go.
Shoot.
When does she finish?
My gosh.
What?
You're in, good.
Help me. It's an emergency.
Why? What's the diagnosis?
I'll see you next time.
The nurse will set an appointment.
Thanks. I enjoyed your show, doctor.
Okay, thank you. Bye.
What time is it?
People are so susceptible to TV.
How come I have double the patients?
What? He left?
He acted as if he'd give me a lift.
As if. I shouldn't have
expected anything from you.
Forget it.
Why won't any taxis take my call?
(Calling for a taxi)
Are you leaving work?
Yes. What are you doing here?
I met the director
and had dinner nearby.
What's wrong with your foot?
I sprained my ankle.
Did you? Get in. I'll take you home.
No, I'll take a taxi.
It's rush hour
and you'll never get one.
Get in. You hurt your ankle.
Come on.
I doubt it was easy
having dinner with the director.
Oh, right.
He hasn't changed at all.
I thought my ears
were going to bleed.
You'll have to endure it
even more now.
You know how he favors you the most.
I know.
I was thinking about
asking him to lend me some money.
Then he wouldn't
want to meet so often.
How smart. I love the idea.
So how did you sprain your ankle?
Did you trip?
No, it's just...
Gyu Jin should've
given you a lift home.
But I guess he had plans.
It's not like
his ankle is hurt, right?
That's nonchalant of you.
I was surprised at first
when I heard you two got married.
You seemed like an odd couple.
How so?
I'm not sure,
but when I first heard about it,
I was like, "What? Those two?"
From what I remember,
you weren't exactly the dating type.
I thought you'd live alone
without getting married.
Do you know what
my first memory is of you?
Remember how I was the TA
in your anatomy class?
Blood was drained from
most of the students' faces...
when they first saw a cadaver.
I offered to buy you
a meal afterward.
Do you remember
what you said you wanted?
I'm not sure.
Tripe!
I was amazed by
the strong stomach you have...
and kept an eye on you
ever since then.
Is that so?
So how is it that you never married?
I'm sure the ladies love you.
I'm not sure.
I never met anyone
who I wanted to marry, I guess.
Set me up sometime
with someone decent.
Someone as funny as you
would be a delight.
But I don't have any friends.
I'm an outcast, you see.
Must you really throw punches...
at yourself like that?
You're hilarious, you know.
You don't have friends
because you're an outcast?
So will Mom and Dad be late today?
Orders have been
piling in at night...
ever since they started
to make deliveries.
Let me get you all some.
This is for you, Ji Hun.
Seo Young, here you go.
And you, Seo Jin. Enjoy.
Thanks, Mom.
Thanks, Auntie.
Is it good, guys?
Yes, it's delicious.
I thought you were
just a pretty face,
but you're gifted
when it comes to bibimbap.
This is absolutely delicious.
Now I'm upset.
You're saying that my looks
aren't as exceptional as my food.
No, of course not.
That's not what I meant.
Whatever. Who cares, anyway?
It's not like
I'm going to marry you.
Seo Young,
just so you know,
those guys are only staying here...
while my office is under renovation.
They could stay at a hotel...
and this isn't due to
a lack of money.
I'm teaching them a lesson
on how to never forget...
about the time
when we weren't well off.
I know.
This is part of their training too.
That's right.
They are here to train.
So don't tell
your grandparents for now.
Sure, I'll keep it a secret.
They'll leave once
the renovation is over.
Of course.
Ji Hun, you too.
- Got it?
- Got it. Don't worry.
Dad, I know what's going on.
Even though you're a CEO,
you're still just as poor.
I'm only pretending to be excited
so that it can...
give you energy.
Joon Seon, I'm sorry,
but is there more to eat?
I'd like just a few spoons more too.
Of course.
How can vegetables be enough?
They need to eat well
to gather their strength.
- I'll give them a call.
- What?
You're saying they need protein.
I'll give them a call.
Sure, of course.
I'll bring home what's left.
Okay, bye.
- Who was that?
- Seo Young.
She asked me to bring home
the leftovers to eat.
I bet it was Joon Seon
and Ga Hee who made her do it.
They never change, do they?
Let me do that, sir.
You should head home.
No, it's okay.
You closed up yesterday too.
You're here to make deliveries,
not clean up.
You should hurry home.
Of course.
Go home and get some rest.
Take this.
Have some for a late-night snack.
Here you go.
Thank you.
- I'll get going then.
- Sure thing.
Ms. Ok Ja, I'll see you tomorrow.
Ok Ja, he's leaving.
Oh. Of course, Sweetie.
See you tomorrow.
Darn, that's hot!
You put it straight
in the microwave?
You're supposed to wrap
a towel around it first.
How stupid are you?
Why do you care?
So where were you just now?
That's none of your business too.
After you huffed and puffed
about giving me a ride,
you went off all by yourself,
you jerk.
"You jerk"?
Sure, call me a jerk. As if I care.
Then why promise me a ride home?
Was it just to annoy me?
Okay, fine. Can we just leave it?
I'm exhausted as it is.
Fine, let's forget about it.
There are enough guys out there
to give me a ride home anyway.
Like who? Who gave you a ride home?
Some guy who thinks I'm funny.
She's just full of herself,
isn't she?
What a narcissist.
It's not good at all.
My gosh.
(Da Hee)
Hi, Da Hee.
Are you calling about the TV show?
Yes, I did, but...
The TV show isn't
what's important though...
So? Hello?
Da Hee?
What on earth was that?
Ms. Song,
I never thought
you'd stab me in the back.
(Episode 20)
Ms. Song, I never thought
you'd stab me in the back.
Well, it's...
What else can I do?
I can't even study properly
because I'm too worried.
Still, this is wrong.
Have you forgotten
the deal we signed?
No wonder I had this weird feeling
when out with my friends.
I definitely have
the gift of foresight.
What can I do?
I'm completely confused.
I am too
and it's all because of you.
Don't pretend to be deeply worried.
Whatever you're feeling,
I feel it 10 times more.
My head is about
to explode as well, you know.
I'm not happy about
my brother's divorce either.
I'm only doing my best
to keep this a secret...
because he's grittier
compared to the last time I saw him.
I'm afraid it could
lead to bloodshed...
All right, fine.
I won't say anything.
I really won't.
I don't know how I can
look at my mother now though.
She's super excited
about Na Hee being on TV.
When she finds out...
Well, it'll be like
a bomb has exploded.
There's no going back.
I know. It'll sure be scary.
And we'll have to suffer
the consequences.
Is there no chance
of them getting back together?
Could they take back the divorce?
They wouldn't have gotten one
if it were that easy.
Besides, it's hard to tell
what goes on in a relationship.
They growl at each other
at the hospital too, you know.
Na Hee truly loved Gyu Jin though...
and Gyu Jin only had eyes
for Na Hee.
That's how I remember them too.
But that's how relationships are.
Futile.
I'm never getting married
ever again.
Na Hee taught me the final lesson.
I agree.
What good does marriage do
when people fall out of love?
Let's just drink our beer.
Sure thing.
(Ttobongee Chicken)
(Father)
Children have
narrow nasal cavities...
which can lead to them...
taking loud breaths
after catching a cold.
We haven't had this many patients
ever since opening day, right?
The doctors are
yet to take patients,
but the waiting list
has over 50 names.
Many have asked about
when we're open at night too.
My goodness.
Now that's what I call publicity.
Could this lead to us
expanding our building?
Gosh, that'd be awesome!
You know,
you should get your hair done again.
The curls are no longer intact.
I know I should,
but my hairdresser
just can't get it right.
Maybe I should switch salons.
The ladies at Unnie's Kimbap always
have nice curls in their hair.
Right?
I saw them from afar and it was
as if they were wearing royal hats.
Here come the King
and the state councilors.
"Your Majesty!"
Good morning.
- You're having your morning coffee.
- Hold on.
Are you brushing the streets today?
That was something
your husband always did.
No, I do it sometimes too.
The place needs to be clean
before we open up.
I don't want customers
speaking ill of us...
especially now
that our daughter is on TV.
Yes, of course.
I thoroughly enjoyed
the show she was on.
Your daughter sure knows
how to make an impression.
I enjoyed it too.
She looked stunning
and so did your son-in-law.
Oh, my. So you two watched it too.
They aired so many reruns
of the show...
that almost everyone watched it.
You have no idea
how many people have called me.
It's exhausting to have a child
that stands out so much.
Parents of celebrities
must have it rough.
I guess it'll be a nuisance
for a while.
She's a regular
on that show, you see.
- I see.
- A regular?
Anyway, that's great news.
Hold on.
This isn't the time to drink
some cheap instant coffee.
We should have Ok Boon buy us
one of those expensive ones.
You're right!
You should buy us some coffee.
Americano would be nice.
Ok Boon, me too.
Is that so? Should I buy you all
a cup of morning coffee then?
Right.
No, he's busy taking care
of his patients.
Well, you know how he has
always been gifted that way.
Not everyone can be on TV, right?
My daughter-in-law?
Well, she is a smart one.
He's just letting her win.
Of course he's just as smart.
I have a customer,
so I should get going.
Sure thing.
What does she mean
Na Hee looks smart?
Looks can be deceiving, you know.
Annoying cow.
Yun Jeong!
Yun Jeong.
Yes, hi.
What brings you by at this hour?
The ladies at the market
wanted me to treat them to coffee...
since the kids were on TV.
I'll take four Americanos.
Sure.
Why does Na Hee keep
cutting Gyu Jin off though?
Did she?
I only saw it
as affectionate banter.
Another one of those banters...
might lead to her
swallowing him whole.
Gyu Jin surprised me, you know.
The camera just
absolutely adored him.
On TV, he looked like that actor.
Yes, Hyun Bin! They look so alike.
The people at the market say
that he's incredibly handsome too.
His good looks?
He takes that after me, I guess.
Yes, of course!
He's so sweet
with his words as well.
You have no idea how proud I was
to be his mother-in-law.
Na Hee looked incredible on TV too.
She seemed so smart as well.
She only looks that way because
Gyu Jin let her take center stage.
What does Na Hee have anyway?
She was a bit too talkative too.
Don't say that. Na Hee seemed
like the smartest one up there.
Ok Boon,
I'm heading out
to the department store later.
Should we ask
the kids out for a meal?
The hospital's nearby.
Could we do that?
They're probably busy.
They still need to eat though.
Don't they get a lunch break?
Shall we then?
I mean, could we?
Of course we can.
Don't you know who we are?
We're the mothers who gave birth...
to the two celebrity doctors.
That alone makes us worthy
of getting a meal out of them.
Right.
Why would you go there
when the kids are at work?
Okay, fine.
Just stick to the meal...
and don't do anything
to bother them too much.
Unbelievable.
One minute,
they're at each other's throat,
and the next minute,
they're best buddies.
Ok Ja, is that how women are?
Those two have always
been like that.
They team up
but then go back to arguing.
You seem discouraged today.
Is something troubling you?
Troubling me?
Young Dal,
have you always wanted
to marry someone like Ok Boon?
What? Where on earth
is this coming from?
They say your dreams and reality
are two different things but...
- I'm back.
- Right.
He's more of my type.
Sorry?
The fact that looking at you
puts a smile on my face...
proves that my eyes
are fully functional,
but why is my heart acting out?
What's going on?
You're not making any sense.
This is all your fault!
This is because you said
he might actually grow on me.
I'm going to hold you
responsible for this!
Yes?
Your morning shift is over.
What a relief.
How many patients
do I have in the afternoon?
You're fully booked today...
and we have a few walk-ins,
so the shift will be long.
Okay.
(Mother)
Yes, Mom. What is it this time?
What? The hospital lobby?
Yes, Mom.
The hospital?
Who? With Mother?
Here. Please enjoy.
I asked Ok Boon to come.
I wanted to eat with you guys.
I see.
I know it's so sudden.
I hope you don't mind, Gyu Jin.
Of course I don't.
We're just happy to see you.
I heard you're getting
a lot of patients after the show.
Jae Seok told me.
It's not that many.
It's just temporary.
You are such a good speaker.
You sound so kind and gentle.
It's quite captivating.
But Na Hee just retorts sharply.
She should sometimes
beat around the bush.
Why? That's what makes
Na Hee attractive.
I don't like people who say
things they don't even mean.
I prefer honest and straightforward
people like Na Hee.
Thank you
for your kind words, Ms. Choi.
My pleasure, Ms. Jang.
- Let's eat.
- Eat.
- Are they from "Doctors"?
- Yes.
- They are the pediatricians.
- The pediatricians.
That's right. "Doctors".
My goodness.
He's my son,
and she's my daughter-in-law.
He's my son-in-law,
and she's my daughter.
- You must be happy.
- I'm a fan.
- He's so handsome.
- Gosh.
Hello.
- They look amazing.
- Gosh.
They say you're handsome.
- Let's eat.
- This show is really something.
Just eat.
Are you that happy?
What? Of course I am.
I feel like
I'm floating on cloud nine.
It's not that big a deal.
I'm serious.
It feels great
to go to the market these days.
I didn't say much,
but ever since Da Hee's annulment,
I've always felt like the women
are gossiping about my kids.
So I even took the long way around.
But I try to pass by
more crowded areas these days.
What? Do you think I'm snobbish?
I just can't help it.
I'm so happy these days.
Really? I'm happy for you then.
What?
Nothing. Let's go.
Hey, why are you walking like that?
Did you get hurt?
No. It's not serious. I'm fine.
You don't seem fine.
You have weak bones.
You would often sprain your ankle
when you were young.
I'll buy some beef leg bones
from Mr. Yang and make bone soup.
You should stop by and pick it up.
It's okay. Don't bother.
It's not okay at all.
Just listen to me.
Make sure to stop by
and take it later. Okay?
Yes. He's out at the moment.
Who is this?
Did you put your house on sale?
- What?
- It's from a realtor.
He wants to see your house.
Gosh. Hang on.
Why did you answer my phone?
I was just... Why...
Did you really put
your house up for sale?
No. What are you talking about?
Hang on.
Yes, hello?
Yes. I think you have
the wrong number.
My number is 3778. Yes.
Okay. You should feel sorry.
He called the wrong number.
He asked if my number was 3779.
I wondered what was going on.
I know. That can't be right.
Hurry.
If you're done eating,
shall we go now?
- Gosh.
- Get home safely.
- Bye.
- Okay. Bye.
I enjoyed the meal.
Na Hee, make sure to
come and pick up the soup.
- Okay.
- Bye.
Please drive safely. Bye.
- Hurry.
- Gosh, don't rush me.
Hello, sir. I'm so sorry.
I had some circumstances.
Yes.
Sure. We can be there now.
In 30 minutes? Tell him 20 minutes.
We can get there in 20 minutes.
Sir.
- Hello.
- You're here early.
Yes. We're on our way. Hello.
I'm sorry.
I couldn't reach you earlier,
so I showed them something else.
And they liked it,
so we're about to sign
a provisional contract.
I'm sorry you came for nothing.
What?
Goodness.
You always carry
the phone with you.
Why did you not bring it today?
If you answered the call,
we wouldn't have missed it.
Why are you blaming me?
I didn't know
the realtor would call me.
Whatever.
It was the first call in a month.
What do we do now?
When are we going to sell the house?
How would I know? I'm upset too.
Stop nagging me.
Are you yelling at me now?
No, you're making me upset.
Do you think you have
the right to say that?
Oh, hello.
- Hi.
- Hello.
Right. We were just out together.
(Yongju Traditional Market
Merchant Association)
I just can't do this.
I can bench press 150kg,
but my body is stiff.
This is just too hard for me.
We're just doing it for exercise.
Don't worry about your moves.
What are you talking about?
I want to do it right.
My goodness.
I'm a bad dancer, so I'm jealous...
of those who are good at this.
They're so cool.
Ok Ja, you're here.
Where's Ok Boon?
She's making beef bone soup,
so she can't come tonight.
Ok Ja, what's up with your lips?
Did you eat gochujang or what?
I didn't eat anything.
My lips are always red.
Gosh, that's not true.
You put something on your lips.
You're wearing perfume too.
This is what I smell usually like.
Do you think I'm crazy?
Why would I wear lipstick
and perfume when I exercise?
It's not like there's someone
I want to impress here.
My point exactly.
I know. That's my point too.
Don't be ridiculous.
Is this the dance sports class?
Yes, it is.
I'm here to learn how to dance.
Gosh, the floor is too small.
How would I make
my moves properly here?
- Stop.
Where are you going?
I want to dance
in front of the mirror.
You're new here today.
Don't you think...
you're being too sassy
to stand at the front?
I know.
We have our system and progress.
We stand according to skill level.
It's like a tournament.
It will take you about three months
to get to the front.
Is that so?
Don't humiliate yourself
and stand at the back, newbie.
- What's going on?
- Was she a dancer?
She's unbelievable.
She's so cool.
It feels great to dance it out
after so long.
Wait. Excuse me.
Excuse me.
Are you the kimbap restaurant owner?
Yes. And you're
the butcher shop owner.
Why are you leaving so early?
Why don't you stay and talk
with the other merchants?
No. I'm not used to this group yet.
Well... Can I call you Cho Yeon?
I saw your name
on the membership card.
Yes, sure.
Names are meant to be called.
Gosh, your moves were so...
You're such a great dancer,
Cho Yeon.
I used to take dance lessons.
As a hobby and to lose weight.
You don't need to lose weight.
This is the secret to my vitality.
Eat this on your way back.
I can easily find red ginseng juice
at a convenience store.
Thank you anyway.
She's so feisty and prickly.
A perfect wild rose.
She almost has a sting.
What are you doing here?
In an alleyway two days ago,
someone jumped a lady for her bag.
I'm too scared to walk alone.
Someone got jumped? For real?
Dad? Will you wait for me outside?
No, someone got jumped nearby.
Don't hang up.
Let's talk while I walk home.
Hey, I'm at the hospital.
I'm going straight home.
You know that three card wallets
got canceled, right?
Yes.
Close up and go home.
Bye.
(Gyu Jin)
Bo Young.
Oh, Gyu Jin.
Why are you here?
Papers for the insurance company.
- Are you leaving now?
- Yes.
I saw you on TV.
You look good on camera.
I thought of texting you but didn't.
Why didn't you?
In case you ignore it
because you're famous.
I wouldn't do that
after just one appearance.
Maybe after 2 or 3 more shows?
Are you going to the workshop?
I'm headed home today.
The helper has to leave at 7 p.m.
Didn't you say you live
in Yongho-dong?
It's on the way. I'll drop you off.
I'm not sure if I should
keep owing you like this.
I'm dropping you off on the way.
You don't owe me for that.
Some people even carpool.
By the way, is Dr. Song okay?
It looked like
she hurt her foot that day.
Yes. She sprained her ankle.
She's slow and doesn't exercise,
so it happens a lot.
Really? It must be so uncomfortable.
What was it you were
going to tell me that day?
What?
You said I shouldn't feel ashamed,
and were about to say
something else.
Oh, was I?
That was...
I don't know. I forgot.
How's your workshop?
Is business good?
So-so.
Not many come to make
real masterpieces.
They just come to relieve stress.
When you really don't want to think,
it helps to keep your hands busy.
I think I might have to visit.
You can, at any time.
For you,
I'll provide much nicer leather.
It's Si Hoo.
- He wants his favorite gummies.
- I see.
Drop me off in front of that store.
Shall I get out too?
I have to get a few things.
My girlfriend wanted this so much.
I couldn't find it
once the season passed.
Exactly.
I can never get it back,
and to think I must sell it...
It's in such great condition.
No scratches at all.
You bet.
I treasured it more than
my own skin.
Here you go. In cash.
You reached rock bottom, Ga Hee.
But then again,
you can't afford designer bags
at the moment.
I'll only have 60 dollars left
after paying off my credit card.
I should buy
Ji Hun's favorite snacks.
So is this what Si Hoo likes?
It looks good. I should get some.
Here, my gift to you.
Share it with Dr. Song.
I'm paying.
No, I'll...
It's to celebrate his discharge.
Gummies are the best when
trying to bribe kids under 10.
He's good.
A true pediatrician.
Gyu Jin?
Wait.
What will you get?
Where's the curry?
Oh, right.
What is this?
Ji Hun, Mom's home.
Na Hee.
You're home. Where were you?
Oh, I was out.
Kids, I bought snacks.
Yay, snacks.
Thank you, Mom.
Why are you at home?
Mom called me 12 times to tell me
to take some beef bone soup.
But she's not at home.
I see.
Hey, your show was awesome.
Didn't you get great reviews?
So-so.
Why didn't Gyu Jin come with you?
What?
Oh, he's at work.
He's working late,
preparing for a seminar.
He said that?
That he'll work late?
Yes. Why?
No... It's nothing.
Seo Young, Seo Jin, Dad's home!
I'm home.
- Let go. Let go of me.
- Ga Hee.
Why drag me out
as soon as I got home?
I want some soup.
Yes, Ga Hee. I'm tired.
Can't we talk tomorrow?
Hey. This is no time to
talk like that.
This is an emergency
sibling meeting.
About what?
You should call Na Hee too.
Why leave her out?
Song Na Hee!
What is wrong with you?
What's this about?
My gosh.
Don't get shocked and just listen.
Song Na Hee that idiot.
She's not smart at all.
My heart breaks for her.
What is this about?
I'm dying over here.
Just spit it out.
Gyu Jin.
Song Na Hee's husband, Yoon Gyu Jin.
The jerk is having an affair.
- What?
I saw them myself.
He was buying groceries
with some woman.
But Na Hee...
believes that he's working late.
That idiot.
That's why book-smart kids
get into trouble.
Their other senses are way too dull.
Is that true? Did you see for sure?
Ga Hee, don't you think
you got the wrong idea?
Or maybe there's an explanation.
Isn't this a jump because he was
at a grocery store with a woman?
Hey. Don't you know how sharp I am?
I may not have a hunched back,
but my hunch is always correct.
To be honest, it's been a while
since I sensed something was off.
When he came over for chicken,
Gyu Jin wasn't his usual self.
That's when it began.
Yoon Gyu Jin.
With that sweet face,
he talked up to Mom,
and he stabbed us in the back.
Exactly.
Cheaters don't go around
with a sign saying they're cheating,
but I never suspected Gyu Jin
of all people would cheat.
No. Whether he really did
stab us in the back...
isn't sure yet.
It is sure.
The woman was shooting hearts
from her eyes.
I know that look!
I wanted to grab them both
on the spot.
I will make him pay.
Joon Seon. Where will you go?
To get Yoon Gyu Jin.
The scumbag
betrayed our sister to cheat!
Yes! Let's go.
Let's go and beat him half-dead.
Let's go.
Ga Hee, Joon Seon.
It's too late to do this.
Last One, you stay here.
Yes. Don't tip off Na Hee
or Mom and Dad.
Na Hee got divorced!
What?
Na Hee and Gyu Jin got divorced.
Not too long ago.
(Once Again)
You're giving me this for free?
I had some leftover parts.
Why does he keep
bringing over free meat?
Why else?
He has fallen for one of us.
- This just isn't right.
- What can we do though?
We have to talk to Na Hee.
You know how Na Hee is.
She could just explode, right?
And it's Dad's birthday tomorrow.
You're right. It's Dad's birthday.
Families and friends,
and everyone in attendance today,
thank you all for coming.
Did you know that our President Song
is gifted on the guitar?