(Cohabitation Contract)
What is this, Gyu Jin?
(Episode 25)
Mother.
I want water.
You're home.
(Cohabitation Contract)
I asked you what this is.
Mother...
This is...
Na Hee.
You tell me.
What's this cohabitation contract,
and why does it mention
the finalization of a divorce?
What is this about?
Mother, it's... You see...
We got divorced, Mom.
What?
What did you just say?
Na Hee.
We're divorced.
We have been for some time.
Wait. Hold on.
What on earth are you talking about?
Why would you get a divorce?
Why would you end your marriage?
Why would you...
Why would you get a divorce?
- Why would you...
- Mom, hold on.
- Why...
- Calm down, Mom.
- Mother, please.
- Why are you divorced?
- Right.
- Get her a bag.
- Mom, are you all right?
- Why?
What's this?
Why would auntie and uncle
be divorced?
This is outrageous.
Tell me about it.
I can't believe people
would start such vicious rumors.
A divorce?
That's insane. Right, Joon Seon?
What? Yes, exactly.
I heard about how nasty
people could be online.
They're the worst, aren't they?
Unbelievable.
Shouldn't we report
these people to the police?
Let's tell Aunt Na Hee.
No, don't. There's no need to.
But still...
(Na Hee)
Na Hee, things are bad...
Ga Hee, Mom just fainted.
We're on our way to the ER.
What?
Why? Why would Mom suddenly faint?
- What?
- Mom fainted.
She fainted?
Na Hee? Mom!
- Mom?
- Mom, are you all right?
- Mom...
- The doctor gave her a sedative...
and she just went to sleep.
She was hyperventilating
and convulsing.
It's why I told you to tell her.
I said it'll only shock her more
if you drag this along.
Why don't you ever listen?
Joon Seon, keep it down.
We're sorry, Joon Seon.
You're just as responsible.
How can you let it get this far?
You know how much
my mother adores you.
What a jerk.
You know, I withdrew this
to pay this month's rent,
but take it first.
Joon Seon, there's no need...
I'll pay you back the rest
as soon as I make the money.
- You borrowed money from him?
- Yes.
How is that important
right now though...
when Mom is in a hospital?
How did she find out?
I doubt she read
the online comments.
Online comments?
I don't think she knows.
("Couple Doctors Yoon and Song
Reel in the Ratings")
(Yoon and Song
are actually divorced.)
What are you going to do?
There are over 1,500 comments.
What should've stayed
within the family...
is now known by the entire nation.
Meanwhile, you also stabbed
Mom and Dad in the back.
So what are you going
to do about this?
Say something? What will you do?
Joon Seon, keep it down.
Dad?
Father.
Dad.
Did either one of you
cheat on the other?
- No.
Was money involved then?
Did one of you
guarantee someone's debt?
- That's not the case.
- No, Father.
Then what?
Why did you get divorced?
You two had a good marriage,
so why did you suddenly
decide to call it quits?
Irreconcilable differences.
What?
I thought it was stupid
when people got divorced...
over irreconcilable differences.
Is that even an excuse?
People are born
to be unique and different.
But...
now I understand
how important it is.
If that is truly
a major reason for divorce,
your mom and I would've
gotten at least hundreds of them.
Compromising and sacrificing...
For how long?
It's been torture,
and I've been lonely and unhappy.
So, for how long must I endure it?
It's unbearable.
We're only torturing ourselves.
I'm sorry...
for disappointing you.
I'm truly sorry.
Father...
("Doctors" Director)
Mr. Yoon,
can I get you another beverage?
I'm good,
so don't mind me and study.
Aren't you going home?
Well, I'm a little exhausted today,
so I'm waiting
until my mom falls asleep.
Why? Am I bothering you?
No, of course not.
Actually, yes.
You're bothering me quite a bit.
I can't focus on these questions.
Gosh, that's harsh.
You're being too brutal now.
I won't let out a squeak,
so go back to your studies.
Goodness.
What? Are you serious?
That won't get you to the answer.
That...
Okay, got it. I'll shut up.
Ga Hee, what is it?
I'm at the cafe.
What? So what happened?
Is Mom okay?
Sure thing. I'll be right there.
What's wrong?
Is something up with your family?
Yes, Mom found out about
Na Hee and Gyu Jin.
She fainted
so they took her to the ER...
and now they're heading home.
I should get going.
Anyway, your mom
will find out soon too.
I hear that someone
wrote about it online.
I'll leave you
to deal with her, okay?
What do you mean
someone wrote about it online?
What the...
Da Hee,
how about we close up early...
What are you doing here?
Where's Da Hee?
Something urgent came up,
so she left.
Something urgent? As in what?
You'll soon find out.
Mom, how's your blood pressure
and heart?
Are they both fine?
Why are you suddenly
asking about my health?
What is this about?
Mom, please sit.
Let's take a few deep breaths.
What's going on?
Just tell me.
You know how impatient I am.
Mom,
Gyu Jin...
got divorced.
Divorced? When? When did it happen?
Mom,
please calm down
and have a sip of this.
Let's be rational.
So when was it?
When exactly
did you sign the papers?
It's been a little over a month.
What? A month?
Why?
For what reason?
Did you cheat on Na Hee or hit her?
No way. She'd never let
anyone do that to her.
Don't tell me that
she's been hitting you.
Mom, that's not it.
It just happened, all right?
I'm sorry.
What did I tell you from the get-go?
I said that you weren't
meant for each other.
Remember her reaction
when I told you...
about the shaman who said Na Hee...
would swallow you whole?
"No one believes in such
superstitions anymore, Mother."
This is what she does
after making me look...
like an old-fashioned hag?
My son is now divorced
because of her!
Mom, it's not just me.
She's a divorcee too,
- so stop...
- Shut it!
Do you really want to take her side
even amidst all this, you moron?
I know you're upset, Mom,
but not as much as Gyu Jin
and my sister-in-law.
Sister-in-law? They're divorced now!
You know what? This is for the best.
You're still young and you have
your whole life ahead of you.
You can meet someone better.
Her family was never
right for you anyway!
Mom, please...
Mom, Gyu Jin's divorce
is still quite fresh.
It's too early to say those things.
Well, I'm that upset!
I blame myself for
not disapproving hard enough.
Unbelievable. Are you kidding me?
Mom, I bet you want to lie down.
Shouldn't you eat something?
How about some porridge
or ground-up rice?
They're practically the same thing.
How are they the same?
Porridge has chunks in them
while ground-up rice doesn't.
Mom! Mom...
My goodness.
Look at how pale you are.
Shouldn't you have stayed
at the hospital?
Are you sure you're okay?
Your mom will be fine,
so leave the room and let her rest.
Sure.
Mom, get some rest.
Goodnight, Mom.
You three, come and have a seat.
When did you find out about it?
You knew about it, right?
When did you find out? Tell me.
I was the first one to know, Dad.
I found it out two weeks ago.
And we heard it last week.
About three days ago to be exact.
Is it four days?
Anyway, it's been less than a week.
We told Na Hee to tell the truth
as soon as possible,
but she asked us
to wait a little more.
Still,
how could you pretend
not to know about it?
Do you still call yourselves
her brother and sisters?
I'm sorry.
We were wrong, Dad.
It's my fault.
I found out about it first,
but I was afraid to tell you.
I'm sorry.
How could you guys do this to me?
How could all four of you...
This is unbelievable.
You guys are just unbelievable.
Dad.
Dad...
This is crazy.
Is Ms. Choi all right?
The worst is over on our end.
What about your family?
They are devastated.
What did Ms. Choi say?
Hello?
Yes, Mr. Yoon.
I was going to text you,
but I just called you instead.
Is Ms. Jang's condition really bad?
I'm afraid so.
She's not saying anything.
What about Ms. Choi?
She's furious, isn't she?
Of course.
She is going on and on furiously.
She's cursing with words
that I can't even dare to repeat.
Come to think of it,
we're like enemies.
How did we end up like this?
I know.
And it's not just about Mom.
I'm worried more about tomorrow.
I mean the hospital.
Oh, the comments.
I can only imagine.
What are Na Hee
and Gyu Jin going to do?
The hospital director is
quite hot-tempered.
There will be a big fuss
at the hospital.
What is this all about?
You should've told me
about it sooner.
Look what you did
to the hospital's reputation.
I'm sorry, sir.
I'm sorry.
I told you to promote our hospital,
but you become the talk of the town.
Some are even calling it
a publicity stunt.
Is that true?
Is that what you intended?
No, it's not like that.
You should've been more patient.
Why couldn't you just get along?
I will take full responsibility
and resign.
I will...
quit my job too.
What?
Then what?
As if we have anyone to replace you?
You can't just quit
without any kind of plan.
How could you be so irresponsible?
Director Jang.
- Director Jang.
- Gosh.
- Loosen your tie.
- Just go away.
Are we done getting yelled at?
Who knows?
There might be someone else.
How is Mother doing?
What about your mom?
She's enraged.
I knew she'd be like that,
but it's just too hard to deal with.
Let's just think
it's the punishment we deserve.
We were expecting this
to begin with.
She's so heartless.
So heartless.
("Couple doctors Song and Yoon
revealed to be divorced")
The comments are so harsh.
This is way too much.
It was bound to happen.
There were even articles
that said they had good chemistry.
People probably feel
like they were fooled.
It's obviously tarnishing
the hospital's image.
Dr. Yoon.
You knew about it, didn't you?
Yes, I did.
I'm an accomplice in this.
I aided and abetted their fraud.
So go ahead and criticize me too.
I will take the heat about that.
Hey, we're not criticizing them.
We're just worried.
I know.
I don't know about Dr. Song,
but I do feel bad for Dr. Yoon.
Honestly, he's probably the one
who put up with Dr. Song.
Isn't it obvious?
It's so obvious.
I can almost see it now.
You know Dr. Song has
an aggressive personality.
I would never marry a woman
as scary as her.
I'd rather kill myself.
She would nitpick
at everything I do. Gosh.
Who said so?
Who said I put up with her?
Are you guys such good judges
of character?
Are you mind-readers or what?
Don't shoot your mouth off
when you don't know anything.
I'm the one who nags at home.
I'm a neat freak. I have mysophobia.
Did you not see that?
Darn.
Don't you dare
say things like that again.
This is a warning.
- Song Na Hee speaking.
- Hello, Dr. Song.
This is An Hyun Joon,
a fellow at Sejin Hospital.
I'm calling to update you
on Yo Han's surgery.
The surgery went well,
so we can start rehabilitation
right away.
Really? I see.
Okay. Thank you.
We'd like to have him transferred.
When is it convenient for you?
(Sejin Hospital)
Na Hee must be upset.
No wonder.
Hey.
You're not here to meet me, are you?
Well, not really.
Is it telepathy or what?
I just wanted to come this way.
I wanted to thank you.
I heard Yo Han's surgery
was successful.
Sure. Of course it was successful.
I took care of it.
I know.
Are you all right?
- Here.
- Thank you.
You're good at surprising people.
To be honest, I was shocked too.
I know.
It's harsher than I thought though.
My name is all over the internet.
What made you decide
to appear on TV?
It must've felt uncomfortable
to be on TV as a couple.
My parents didn't know
about my divorce.
And when the casting offer came,
the hospital director
practically forced us.
If I knew it would cause
so much trouble to the show,
I would've refused the offer.
People would say malicious comments
were a social issue,
but I didn't care about it
all that much.
But now that it's happening to me,
I find it hard to deal with
even when I'm quite bold.
I understand people calling us
a pair of tricksters.
But they even tell us to
quit our jobs and kill ourselves.
I'm not sure
if I did something that bad.
Don't trouble yourself.
They just want
something to gossip about.
Apparently, I'm called
the Icy-Cold Witch online.
It sounds about right.
That's a good nickname.
You know what?
Ice begins to melt as soon as
the temperature rises by one degree.
You seem to get hurt
more easily than you look.
Am I wrong?
I don't know.
I'm not even sure about myself.
I can tell what you're like.
Let's go.
I have afternoon appointments.
Make sure to get the data
from Dr. An on your way back.
We took the biopsy and there wasn't
any sign of metastasis.
Thank you. I'll see you later.
My pleasure.
Bye.
Yes, Mom.
Don't you dare talk to me like that.
I'm the one who should be
giving you a deep sigh.
Why are you calling me?
What do you want?
When will you sell the apartment?
Will you go on living with her?
We notified the real estate agent...
Let me deal with it, Mom.
What can you deal with?
Shall I call an agent I know?
If I offer more commission money...
Mom, I'll deal with it.
I want to sort out
some other issues first.
Why do something that
needs sorting out? Hang up!
Why does she keep...
- Hi, Bo Young.
- Gyu Jin.
Can you talk?
Yes, well... I'm free.
I wasn't sure whether to call or not
but I was worried.
Are you all right?
You were surprised, weren't you?
Things just happened.
I finally understood
what you said last time.
It must've been tough for you.
Even more so now.
Well, it's fine. It'll pass.
Well...
I have to deal with it.
It's my fault.
Okay.
Call me whenever you need me.
Whether it's food or coffee,
I'll buy you anything.
Okay.
Thanks for calling.
Cheer up.
Take care. Bye.
(Closed today for personal reasons!)
The darn brats never let us
have a day of peace.
How could Na Hee do this to us
as well?
We got stabbed in the back
by the person we trusted the most.
Are you going home? Hop on.
You go ahead.
I'll get some groceries.
I don't think Lady Luck
cares much for that family.
She was so excited that her daughter
and son-in-law were on TV,
she even threw a party
and celebrated.
How did that daughter
end up divorced in just two days?
Exactly. You get sick
if you eat too much at a party.
She celebrated way too much.
She was down for a while
after her youngest got an annulment.
She was so haughty
about the TV show.
At this rate, shouldn't she get in
the Guinness Book of World Records?
It's rare for 100 percent
of your kids to be divorced.
"The youngest got an annulment!"
That's what Ok Boon
would've said if she heard.
Sorry.
What was that?
Did he do that on purpose?
What? He couldn't have.
The fishcake needs to cool.
- Cho Yeon!
- My gosh.
Cho Yeon! Cho Yeon, Cho Yeon.
She heard gossip.
Why do you dress
weirder and weirder each day?
What is it?
The second daughter of the president
who runs the fried chicken place.
She came on his birthday...
and signed autographs
and acted over the top.
- Yes.
- What about her?
That daughter
and her husband got divorced.
Over a month ago!
What? For real?
What are you saying?
They went on TV
and said they were married?
Yes, but the president and his wife
found out just now.
His wife lost her mind
and passed out, causing a fuss.
The fried chicken joint
is closed today.
My goodness. How did that happen?
- She adored those two.
- Yes.
Aren't her older son and daughter
divorced and living at home too?
Yes. Everyone in the market
gathered around...
to talk about that family.
Everyone is whispering
and gossiping.
It's no joke.
Too bad.
The president must be really upset.
Stop doing that. How can you focus?
Give it back. My problems
should be kept separate from work.
I have to update that today.
I'll do it. Leave it to me.
I have to notify everyone...
that the recycling truck will be
coming at a different time now.
I'll do that as well. Leave it.
You just chat with me.
How's your wife?
Shouldn't you be at home?
I left because I thought
I'd only be in the way.
She's better off alone.
I guess nothing can comfort her now.
She wouldn't want to hear anything.
It's so devastating.
Even I feel brokenhearted.
How could all four of them
do this to their parents?
I know.
I must've wronged
all four of them in my past life.
Yes. Think of it that way
and let it go.
Don't feel wronged or guilty.
Aren't you going to
the kimbap place today?
I may be head over heels in love,
but how can I leave
a friend in distress?
I'm not that disloyal.
What do you think of me?
Thanks a lot.
I feel so touched I could cry.
Right? Aren't I the best friend?
A man puts loyalty
before love, okay?
Loyalty.
My gosh.
(Unnie's Kimbap)
I wish I could see
Cho Yeon's face just once.
No. No.
My friend is moping
because of his daughter,
and I came here to see my love?
This is wrong.
Yang Chi Su, you're a man
and this is not how you live.
What's wrong with
just seeing her face?
It's not like
I'll get sweet with her...
or do anything untoward.
Why not? Why not?
Don't make excuses.
If you go inside, you're a traitor.
You're a jerk.
Darn it.
Sweep up outside your door!
It's so dirty I can't stand it!
Look at all this!
You have no conscience!
What...
- What?
- What's so dirty?
It's way too clean.
Mom, Joon Seon bought
your favorite cream buns.
Have a bite, will you?
Yes, Mom. Eat a little,
for my sake for going to get these.
You haven't eaten all day.
Mom, this is really upsetting.
She didn't starve
when we got divorced.
Mom, this is discrimination too.
It is.
You say you love
every child the same,
but you ate after our divorces
and can't after Na Hee's?
Now I'm upset.
- You must eat...
- My gosh!
Get out of here. Get out! Out!
Mom.
- Sleep, then.
- We'll leave.
- Auntie.
- Hi, Auntie.
How's your mom?
Did she eat something?
No. She just turned these down.
She can't eat something that dry.
I'll make abalone porridge.
You can have some too.
What is Dad up to?
Is he with Mr. Yang?
No. I think they parted ways.
Then where is he?
Is he alone in the store?
My afternoon appointments
were canceled?
- All of them?
- Yes. There was one left,
but the kid went to stay
with the mom's parents.
The mom just called to reschedule
the appointment for next week.
Okay.
I get it. You can go.
- Yes, doctor.
- Go.
My gosh. This is not fair.
(Father-in-law)
Hello, Father.
Can you...
really not get back together?
Father.
All married couples...
experience a crisis or two.
If you try to be
a bit more understanding...
and get over that,
everything else will come easier.
This I can guarantee
as a man who has lived more years.
Isn't it possible?
Even...
when I'm here...
asking you for another chance?
Father,
since I was a kid,
my mom was a handful.
Actually,
if I'm being honest, I hated her.
Unlike other moms,
she was always emotional...
and got frustrated easily.
But she's my mom, right?
We're related by blood,
no matter how I feel.
It's how I learned
to accept her for who she is.
But I don't think it's the same
for married couples.
When things clash
and we go off track,
it's almost impossible to recover.
We haven't laughed...
with one another for a while now.
We live under the same roof,
but we don't share a single laugh.
No silly jokes
are said between us either.
We only talk when we argue.
I'm truly sorry, Father.
I couldn't keep the promise
I made at the altar.
I'm terribly sorry.
I'll be in touch. Sure thing.
(Episode 26)
Why is she thrilled
about my son being divorced?
They just love seeing
others unhappy, don't they?
Jerks.
Excuse me, Ms. Choi.
I have something to tell you.
Go ahead although I think
I know what you're going to say.
I'm guessing I should look
for another place to work.
You won't be comfortable
seeing me anyway,
and I don't want to walk
on eggshells around you.
Quitting is probably for the best.
Right.
I can't disagree with you, I guess.
Should I work
until the end of the shift...
or stay until you hire someone else?
It's fine. You should get going.
I'll find your replacement myself.
Then let me stay
until the end of business today.
I said it's fine.
I doubt I'll have
any more customers anyway.
Right.
I'm truly sorry about this.
What are you sorry for and why?
It's not like
you did anything wrong.
Still...
I feel horrible, you know.
I feel bad for Na Hee and Gyu Jin...
and I hate that we're ending
our relationship like this too.
I don't know how you felt,
but I loved working here with you.
Ms. Choi, don't drink
too much of the wine today,
and please don't skip your meals
no matter how upset you are.
Thank you for everything.
How can two sisters
be this different?
Half of each sister
would make the perfect woman.
Where do I find a part-timer
as decent as Da Hee?
It'll take her some time
to find my replacement.
Gosh.
Ms. Song!
Mr. Yoon.
So that happened.
You had to quit your job too.
Yes, this happened in the end.
I guess we're not officially
in-laws anymore.
What should I call you
when I meet you on the streets now?
Na Hee's my former sister-in-law,
so are you my "ex in-law" too?
Just call me Da Hee.
Mr. Yoon,
you're older than me, right?
Then will you call me...
by my name as well?
No, I don't think...
I'll be able to do that.
I don't think I'll be able...
to call you by your name either.
Let's not call each other
anything then.
"Hi, it's been a while."
We'll keep it like that.
Sure. We'll leave out the names.
Can you believe the things
these so-called grown-ups are doing?
They fell in love, got married,
and brought us together
to make this one big family.
Just how many people
are affected by this?
Irresponsible jerks.
That's because
one's love for another changes.
I've been there, remember?
My sisters and brother
have all experienced it.
Still,
let's stay in touch, okay?
It's a shame to let
this friendship go to waste.
Keep up your studies...
and work hard on
changing your personality.
Here.
I'm sorry you have to experience
this sour mood again.
Bombs keep going off, don't they?
It's all right.
You and I were a bomb
three years ago too.
Na Hee, are you just getting home?
Your work must've ended late.
It's all right.
Please go back to your meal.
Where's Mom?
Na Hee, you're here.
Your mom looks like death in there.
I gave her some
abalone porridge to eat,
but she wouldn't open her mouth.
Why don't you try
and get her to eat some?
Would she take the food
served by the one who caused this?
Mom,
it's me.
I heard you didn't
eat anything today.
Can you please have
some of the porridge?
Just hate me all you want.
Don't hurt yourself
by skipping meals.
Mom...
You!
How dare you.
How dare you do this to me!
The others might be clueless,
but you know how I feel.
The divorce itself is just as bad,
but how could you
hide it from me like this?
Do you even respect me
as your mother?
Do you look down on us...
because we sell fried chicken
at the market?
Mom, that's ridiculous
and you know it.
How is it ridiculous?
Then why would you do this to me?
I don't want to see your face,
so get out.
I can't be bothered, so leave.
Get out!
I told you to leave.
- Mom?
- Get out!
Mom, don't.
You hardly have the energy.
Just get out of here.
Ok Boon, please calm down.
Just breathe.
Ok Ja,
just get her away from me.
- Tell her to leave.
- Yes, of course.
- Ga Hee, take her.
- Sure.
Na Hee, come on. Let's go outside.
Mom...
Joon Seon, just go.
My gosh.
Ok Boon, just like down, okay?
Don't waste any more of your energy.
Ok Boon, lie down.
I'm home.
What's going on? What happened?
Serves you right
for waltzing in there.
Would Mom want
to even look at you...
after what you did?
You're a sinner, you know.
You wronged her.
I know I wronged her,
- so stop it.
- Stop what?
Who are you to tell me
what I can and can't do?
What gives you the right?
Those who wronged others...
should be too mortified
to say even a word.
Who are you to
stand tall in front of us?
Joon Seon, stop.
- Keep it down.
- Joon Seon,
let's get some fresh air.
Let go of me.
You don't even know
what you did wrong, do you?
You have no idea
have much you've hurt...
this family and our parents.
I know. I know it all too well.
It's killing me too, you know.
If you did know,
you wouldn't be talking back to me!
Joon Seon, please.
What should I do then?
Should I get on my knees
and await her punishment?
Is that what you want me to do?
What about you then?
What makes you such a good son?
You drove a nail in Mom's heart too.
You have no right to yell at me!
Hold on.
Why would you bring that up?
- What do you think you're doing?
- My gosh!
- Dad?
- Dad...
- Goodness.
- Dad, that's not it.
Na Hee, this brat,
went in to see Mom when she...
Shut it!
You've got to be kidding me.
Even the most stupid ones...
would think twice
before raising their voices here.
Unbelievable.
Get out. All of you, leave!
- But Dad...
- I don't want to see any of you.
- Dad, we're sorry.
- Get lost!
Go!
We don't need any one of you,
so get lost!
My gosh.
This is on you
and that temper of yours.
Look what you did to us.
How is this my fault?
It's Na Hee's fault.
Stop it already!
I can't believe
you're still arguing.
All right, fine.
There's no need to yell.
I'm sorry about this.
We keep showing you
the worst side of us.
So what now?
I don't think we can go back inside
any time soon.
How about the rooftop then?
Hold on, 3 are already up there
and there are 4 of us.
That makes seven total.
I guess there's room
for us to all stand around.
Follow me.
We'll take this chance
to do some sibling bonding.
Where are we off to?
Are you ignoring
my suggestion again?
I'll tell Mom and Dad...
Hey, wait for me.
I feel bad for our mother, you know.
She worked her whole life
to raise us well,
but 3 got divorced
and 1 got an annulment.
It's not common for a parent.
Call me the original sinner, guys.
I'm the one who kicked things off.
Don't be like that.
I'm the worst out of us four.
I hit the wound you left behind
which made it hurt even more.
No way.
My annulment was the final straw.
Mom was finally moving on
but I open up old wounds again.
Na Hee only hid her divorce
because of what I did.
Because Mom was still recovering.
Don't be so annoying.
This isn't your fault at all.
My punch was probably
the one that hurt the most.
I stabbed her in the back, didn't I?
I'm glad you know.
Na Hee,
let me give you some sincere advice.
You have too much conviction
in your own decisions.
Your thoughts and choices
could be just as wrong, you know.
When you make big decisions,
seek advice from your siblings...
and those around you.
There's a reason why...
people say things
that you don't want to hear.
Humbly let hurtful advice sink in...
and be open to other opinions.
Don't you agree?
Isn't she the lady doctor
from "Doctors"?
The one that got divorced.
She is.
Even I wouldn't be able
to stay married to her.
A woman who stomps all over men...
- What did you just say?
- Joon Seon!
She wouldn't even
marry a punk like you,
so who are you to
talk smack about my sister?
- Joon Seon, stop.
- Gosh, we're sorry.
We're just in a terrible mood,
you see.
Stop it.
Aren't we entitled to free speech?
Like sister, like brother.
What a family of thugs.
What?
- What did you just say? A thug?
- Ga Hee, please.
Who are you to say that
about my siblings?
I'm the thug in the family,
you know.
Want a taste of this?
Ga Hee, not you too.
Na Hee, please.
Just punch him, Ga Hee.
I'll take care of the rest,
so do as you wish.
Did you hear that?
My sister gave me the go-ahead.
You're dead meat today.
She's notorious
for knocking out people's teeth.
Ga Hee, no.
- What the...
- Ga Hee, please don't.
- Don't do this.
- Get over here.
I dare you to say it again!
Why aren't you sleeping?
Is it still keeping you up?
Ok Boon,
let me get you a glass of water.
Honey.
Right, of course.
I know how you feel.
I don't think
I have it in me this time...
to share words of wisdom
like I normally do.
What can we do though?
It's not like we can do anything
to get them back together.
Honey...
Let's just think of this
as our fate.
I mean, what else can we do?
Honey, why is it always me?
Why only our children?
I had no idea...
that Na Hee of all people
would betray us like this.
This is so unfair.
What did I do to deserve this?
What am I supposed to do now?
Honey, I don't know
if I can keep going.
My gosh.
Honey...
That's it. Let all the tears flow.
Think of this as
the last day you'll cry.
And tomorrow, we'll close up
the store for a day...
and get some fresh air.
I'll buy you crab, your favorite.
That's it.
Let it all out.
Oh, dear.
Dad, you're up early.
We spent a long time...
serving out our punishment
outside last night.
I didn't ask.
Well... In case you're wondering.
Where's Mom? Is she still asleep?
She left home.
What?
Your mom ran away from home.
What? She ran away?
What now? What's wrong?
Mom is gone.
What?
Mom ran away from home.
When Dad woke up, she was gone.
Hey, wait. I'll drive you there.
You can't go there without the car.
Forget it.
It has nothing to do with you now.
I see. So she's not there?
Yes. Her phone is turned off.
Yes.
If you get a call from my mom,
could you please let us know?
Yes. Thank you. Bye.
She's not at the playground.
What about the park
near the community center?
She's not there.
I looked there already.
Gosh, where did she go
without saying anything?
Let's look for her a little more.
Follow me.
(Mapo Seolleongtang)
She's not at Ms. Yeong Sun's either.
And Mom didn't call her.
It's the weekend,
so their store isn't even open yet.
I have no idea where she is.
Hang on, Ga Hee.
Aren't you even worried?
How can you be frying chicken now?
I'm worried sick about her.
We still have to work.
We can't make a habit of randomly
closing a small store like ours.
Don't worry, Ok Ja.
I'm sure she will come back
after getting some air.
It's not her first time
to run away like this.
Back when Da Hee caused trouble,
she came back after half a day.
Things are not the same now.
This is a lot more serious.
Both you and I know
what Na Hee means to her.
Na Hee was her only pride
when people gossiped at the market.
"I still have my Na Hee."
That's how she held out.
She must be devastated now.
Ok Boon, where are you now? Ok Boon.
Young Dal, do you think...
Hey, that's enough.
Stop crying, Ok Ja.
I just have bad feelings about this,
Young Dal.
Why don't you call her again?
Ok Boon is practically
like a mother to me.
I can't live without her.
Ok Boon, where are you now?
Ok Boon.
Gosh, where on earth did she go?
Wasn't that hilarious?
Gosh this is so pretty.
Mom.
Where are you going?
I'll be in my room.
Where's Na Hee?
Is she still on Ganghwa Island?
No. She said she left.
I guess she's on her way home.
This won't do.
I will go to the police...
and report her missing.
I don't feel good about this.
I'm worried.
What are you talking about?
It's been less than a day.
We should wait a little more.
For how long?
What if something happens to her
while we wait?
What will you do then?
I can't wait any longer.
You go ahead
and wait for her calmly.
- Gosh.
- That punk.
Mom?
Mom. Mom!
Mom, where have you been?
I've been worried about you.
Why are you being like this?
Get off me. I can't breathe.
I thought you jumped
into the river or something.
I was on my way to the police
to report your missing.
I don't want you to worry me
like that ever again.
Promise me, okay?
So where have you been?
It's not like you know all places.
I don't know. I don't care.
I'm just glad that you're safe.
Don't be silly.
Why are you whining like that?
- Mom.
- Mom!
Mom, we've been
worried sick about you.
We called all your friends.
Na Hee even went
to Ms. Yeong Sun's restaurant.
Thank you so much
for coming back safe and sound, Mom.
- Mom.
Gosh, get off me. Don't overreact.
You're back.
Yes, I'm back.
Good. Go get some rest then.
You must be tired
from walking around all day.
Mom, did you eat anything?
Do you want some abalone porridge?
Heat up some porridge.
I doubt she ate anything.
- I'll go heat it up.
- Let me help you.
So where did you go today?
I wanted to go with you,
but you left me out.
The beach on Ganghwa Island.
Na Hee took me there before.
You went quite a long way.
I bet you liked it a lot.
It was nice that day.
But now that I think of it,
she took me there because
she wanted to tell me something.
She wanted to tell me the truth.
Are you tired?
Yes, I'm tired. I'll get some sleep.
Go ahead and sleep.
Sleep well.
So where did she go, Dad?
Who did she meet?
You don't have to know everything.
She's back and that's that.
I still want to know.
Is she asleep?
She wants to sleep.
Don't bother her.
Is she sleeping?
I heated up the porridge.
Save it for later.
I'm going to
the merchant association office.
Don't wake her up. Okay?
- Yes.
- See you.
- Bye.
Really? Is she asleep now?
Where has she been?
Okay.
Ga Hee, take good care of her.
All right. Okay. Bye.
Hello, Na Hee.
Hyun Gyung, where are you?
I just finished work.
I had a make-up lesson to do.
I haven't eaten all day.
Will you eat with me?
Go ahead and eat.
You must be hungry.
I'm sorry, Hyun Gyung.
I know you should go home.
I called home already.
Seo Jin is asleep.
Seo Young takes good care of her.
Why aren't you asking anything?
You must've heard the whole thing.
I want to let you eat first.
Does that sound too much like a mom?
You'll get sick if you do that.
Do just one thing. Eat or cry.
Good for you.
Cry first, then eat.
If you eat then cry,
you'll get hungry again.
Bear with it.
You have no other choice.
You made the decision.
It was my decision,
so I can deal with my pain.
But the pain that my decision
caused Mom and Dad...
That's too hard to bear.
Time is...
Time is too slow.
How delicious.
It's full of red bean
from head to tail.
- Mr. Song!
- My goodness.
What were you thinking about...
that you didn't even see me coming?
Were you out somewhere?
Yes, taking care of things
at the office.
What about you?
I took out the trash...
and the fish-shaped bun lady
gave me some leftovers.
- Do you want one?
- No. I don't feel well.
Something must be bothering you.
Goodbye, then.
Go on ahead.
Mr. Song.
Do you have a few dollar bills?
Dollar bills?
How many?
This is the best when you're upset.
Sing a few songs like crazy
and you'll feel better.
It's just a temporary measure,
but it's 4 songs for a dollar,
so let's just sing 4.
I'll be in the booth way over there.
Don't worry about
my overhearing you.
Here you go.
No, I... Ma'am.
- Where is it?
- Over there.
I look around, wondering what to do
But all I see are people
with their backs to me
Let's all go
To the East Sea
Who is throwing rocks
and bruising me?
Who is it?
Who is making my poor heart cry?
- Who is it?
- To the East Sea
Why are you filling your own glass?
It's fine.
I'm used to pouring,
but not to others pouring for me.
How do you feel?
Didn't the shouting
make you feel better?
Well, I guess it worked a bit.
You should eat as well.
If you just drink,
you'll be too sick to work tomorrow.
- Here. Eat this.
- Thanks.
The fish-shaped bun lady said...
she uses the same batter...
and same red beans to make them,
but some cook well and some burn.
She's never completely pleased.
Even buns from
the same batch are like that.
Kids from the same parents
would be like that too.
You never get your way with them.
Don't be too upset.
Everyone is talking about
our family, right?
I can't deny that.
But it's so strange.
Why is it so exciting to talk about
someone else's misfortunes?
It can't be because
we're all bad people, right?
It's because it's not their problem.
I don't have any kids,
so I don't know half of
what you're going through.
But when I'm upset,
I think of the worst outcome.
I could fall down a manhole
and break a leg,
or I could die alone in my room
without anyone knowing,
and my body would rot away.
Why would you think of
such dreadful things?
Compared to those situations,
the rest is nothing.
So what if your kids are divorced?
Pretend they were never married.
Isn't it better than them
dying of something dreadful?
Maybe.
I'm okay, but my wife is half-dead.
You're not okay either.
Don't pretend to be okay.
Your heart will suffer.
Vent it by singing,
or by drinking,
and don't keep it inside.
Then start again tomorrow.
What's more to life?
You sound like
you lived longer than I have.
I tried to lecture
someone older, didn't I?
Sorry.
(Mr. Song Young Dal)
Yes, Dad.
Dad.
You're here.
You drink instant coffee, right?
You can talk, Dad.
Drink before it gets cold.
Just talk.
You called me to say something.
You should...
come home.
What?
Pack up and move back home.
(Once Again)
I'm moving back home.
Dad told me to.
Yoon Gyu Jin.
It must've been tough
living with me.
I was sorry.
And thank you.
Let's eat out as a family.
You won't go back on your word,
will you?
Keep trying to get close to her.
That's all you can do now.
Let go. You're being a nuisance.
Na Hee must feel so embarrassed.
Mom doesn't even answer.
Should we help them make amends?
What's that?
My gosh. Isn't that Mom?