- Mom.
- You idiot.
Mom, talk it out.
Don't resort to violence.
That could become a habit!
- How dare you?
- Mom.
- What?
- You...
You...
- Mom, we're here.
- Mother, we're...
What?
Da Hee. Why are you here?
Na Hee.
Why are you here
and what's with the apron?
Na Hee, I was going to tell you...
Your sister...
is working part-time here
in the evenings.
- Sorry?
- I needed extra help...
and she was looking for a job.
Isn't it nice that
we can help each other?
I get to have a reliable employee...
while your sister
has a safe place to work.
Hold on a second.
So she's my in-law?
Na Hee's real biological sister?
Would she be a fake sister then?
You met her at the wedding.
We should talk.
But...
Da Hee...
Right!
Now I remember.
You will quit this instant.
What?
Quit working at this cafe.
- Why?
- Must you ask?
There are other places to work.
You can keep searching for a job,
so why here of all places?
Don't you see
how uncomfortable this is for me?
I'll make sure
it doesn't get to that.
I know what you're worried about,
but I'm going to work hard
and always stay on her good side.
Na Hee, please.
It's close to home and my academy...
and the hourly rate
is higher than in other places.
Mom already approved.
Mom approved?
So please
just let it slide this once.
I'll do a good job.
You working hard isn't the issue.
I just hate the fact
that you're working here.
Things are already...
Just quit, okay?
I'll pay for your classes
if you need the money,
so focus solely
on your studies instead.
You're really good at
kicking me down.
Don't you understand why I'm
going back to college at this age...
and working a part-time job
to support myself?
It's because I want to succeed
without your help or dad's.
I don't want to be a shameless brat.
So just let me work this job, okay?
Please.
Da Hee, but still...
Can you stop glaring at me?
Your eyes look like
they're going to pop out.
He's right, Mom.
Let your anger subside now...
and stop glaring at him like that.
Getting all worked up will only
elevate your blood pressure.
It's dangerous considering your age.
How sweet of you to think of me.
How considerate!
So why have you been
hiding from me...
after returning to Korea?
You're his big brother,
but instead of telling him off,
you joined him on his lie
and deceived your mom.
Mom, please. This wasn't deception.
You're taking it too far.
He's right. You're overreacting.
I wasn't going
to lie to you forever.
I was going to surprise you
with my presence...
after enjoying some freedom.
Surprise me? My foot!
You jerks.
Is this what I get
for worrying about my sons?
My blood pressure is rising.
Na Hee, you're just as bad.
These two have always been clueless,
but I didn't think
you'd deceive me too.
Shouldn't you of all people
have told me about him?
Mom, why are you
taking it out on her?
Na Hee didn't do anything wrong.
Mother, I apologize
for not telling you.
But I think my sister
should find another job.
It'll be hard for her
to work for an in-law...
and your relationship with my mom...
- will make things uncomfortable.
- It doesn't.
I'm fine. It's not uncomfortable.
Sorry?
Your sister has been doing
a great job...
and she's nice to the customers,
unlike her own sister.
Your mother already approved too,
so there's nothing more
to talk about.
Not telling me about Jae Seok
is one thing,
but why don't you ever
pick up my calls?
Are you busy
every second of the time?
You're not the only doctor
in this family.
Both of my sons are doctors too!
You always boast about...
graduating at the top
of your class,
but Jae Seok
received top grades once.
- Aren't I right?
- You are.
- Right?
- Yes.
I raised my sons as doctors
without any hitches either,
so why do you keep ignoring me?
Are you not going to stop this?
Stop what?
I'm talking about Da Hee.
Things with us
are complicated enough.
I don't get why your mother
insisted on hiring Da Hee anyway.
It doesn't make any sense!
Since when did you try
to understand my mom anyway?
It's nothing new.
I'm not looking for an argument.
We're divorced
but our parents don't know.
Doesn't it bother you?
Whatever.
If you're that bothered,
talk to my mom yourself.
She's someone I can't persuade.
Are you kidding me?
I'm not kidding you,
but what else can I say, right?
You're being childish.
Right, I'm childish...
- and you're selfish.
- What?
Our divorce is our problem, right?
Just like you said,
our families don't know.
You can't tell Da Hee
she can't work there...
just because
it makes you uncomfortable.
That's extremely selfish.
Da Hee did nothing wrong.
Of course, you're considerate
at times like this.
We're never on the same page.
Yes, exactly.
No wonder we got divorced.
Yes, I guess you're right.
Me being uncomfortable is my issue,
so I'll deal with that myself.
But your mom is your issue,
so you should deal with her.
Okay, got it.
What about your mother though?
Don't you think you'll ask me
for any favors with her?
I can deal with my mom just fine.
She just thinks
she's above everyone.
The truth is,
my marriage was voided
on the day of the wedding.
I won't say why
because that's privacy.
But then today, I even lost my job.
Don't you think that
life is just crazy?
What on earth did I say
to my in-law?
How stupid of me.
Why didn't I remember him?
I greeted him at Na Hee's wedding.
Gosh, this is embarrassing!
I blame my useless brain.
Why bother
bringing it around with you?
Why? Why?
She was Na Hee's sister?
No wonder she seemed familiar.
Could I be losing my touch?
I never forget a girl's face.
Anyway, what a fun connection.
I'm entertained.
My gosh!
Mom, at least knock.
Where are your manners?
Manners, my foot.
You're unbelievable.
Who are you to speak about manners?
You imbecile.
What do you want to eat?
We can argue some more later,
but you should
have some dinner first.
It's all right, Mom. I'm not hungry.
I'm good.
As if you are, you jerk.
Take your pick already.
Steak or salmon?
If I had known,
I would've gone grocery shopping.
You brat.
I can't believe you're making me
cook on the fly like this.
Mom, I'm really good.
I had a sandwich earlier,
so I'm not hungry.
Shut it. As if a sandwich
can keep you full.
Anyway, get changed.
I'll whip something up.
I'll now be cooking for
my grown-up son at this age.
What a hard time I'll have.
My goodness. Unbelievable.
I have a bad feeling about this.
Looking good.
Where's the frying pan?
I put it all the way up there
since I never use it.
Jae Seok, can you get over here?
I need your help.
Jae Seok?
Please get that frying pan for me.
All right. So the meat is out...
and now for the balsamic sauce.
I'm glad I had it restocked.
My gosh.
Jae Seok, please open this for me!
My goodness.
Please open this for me.
Thank you.
Jae Seok?
It's nothing.
My gosh.
Jae Seok. Jae Seok,
pass me the paper towel.
Gosh, thanks.
Jae Seok?
Jae Seok!
- No, I hear nothing.
- Jae Seok!
Why didn't you answer me?
I've been calling you.
Yes, Mother. You called?
Can you open the wine bottle for me?
I should've poured the wine
in a decanter sooner.
I'm already regretting
moving back in.
What on earth do I do?
It's like I'm cooking
the meal myself.
He should be home by now.
I wonder how much he drank.
(Not on my side)
The person you called
is unavailable.
Why isn't he answering his phone?
Yes, Mr. Yang.
Are you perhaps with my husband?
You parted ways?
I guess he'll be home soon then.
Sure. Goodnight.
- My gosh. Honey!
- Hello?
My wife!
You'll fall. Be careful.
Why did you drink so much today?
Yes, I drank today. I drank a lot.
Ok Boon!
My gosh.
You saying that shows me...
just how drunk you are.
Ok Boon,
there's no need to be angry.
How scary.
Goodness.
Unbelievable.
How was it?
It went really well.
I don't get why you always insist on
going there yourself.
Let me join you next year.
I may not have met my sister-in-law,
but I should at least say hello.
What if she thinks
that you married...
some selfish woman?
What? No way!
My Young Suk is the sweetest ever,
so she'd never think that way.
It's why she put her trust in me
and went to a dangerous place.
Honey, please.
Ok Boon,
I'm a little sad today.
Life couldn't be sadder.
Why have you aged so much though?
Who did this?
Who made my wife age like this?
Who else could it be but you?
Get out here!
- Who was it?
- Honey, be quiet!
Just wait until I catch you.
Whoever it was, show yourself!
- Honey, keep it down.
- Get out here!
Dad. Why did he drink so much?
He had a few drinks with Mr. Yang.
- Hurry up and take him.
- Of course.
Dad, are you all right?
Loafer 1 and Loafer 2.
I see you're fine.
Son, life is hard, isn't it?
How about I give you an allowance?
Dad, it's okay.
You'll only take it back
tomorrow anyway.
Don't be like that. I'm not kidding.
I promise I won't take it back.
Gosh.
Hold on. How much should I give you?
Here you go.
Wait a second.
There you go.
Wait, 100 dollars each?
Is this for real?
Why? Isn't it enough?
Do you want more?
Hold on a second then.
Here. Take as much as you need!
- Dad, it's all right.
- Take it all.
It's fine.
Honestly, it's fine.
Dad, isn't this a bit too much?
You're closing up the bar?
- Really?
Of course.
I wouldn't joke about this.
- But this is too sudden.
- Are you getting married?
My gosh. I wouldn't mind
you setting me up with someone.
It's just too sudden, that's all.
Are you ill then?
I'm just sick and tired
of running a bar.
Dealing with drunk jerks
is annoying enough.
And the smell of alcohol
is sickening.
Trying to sound cute all the time
is exhausting too.
I'm thinking about
moving on to another business.
Something more ordinary.
What about us then?
You two?
You should go about your own ways.
Don't you worry though.
I'll give you a good reference
if you need one...
and pay up a fat pension...
if you wish to retire
and head back home.
No way.
I'd rather stick with you.
But you don't know
what I'll end up doing.
Just go on your way.
I will pay your money back
once I get the security deposit.
I don't want to.
I'll come with you no matter what.
- So don't even try to send me away.
- Me too.
- What?
- I'm coming with you too.
Wherever you go, I'll be there.
Don't be silly.
There's nothing you can get from me.
That's not true.
You pay us, feed us,
and even care about us.
We get everything from you.
So don't even think
about abandoning us.
I'll follow you
to the ends of the earth.
Gosh, you fools.
Do as you like.
Just remember I gave you
a chance to get away.
Don't blame me later.
So what are you going to do?
Will you open
a supermarket or something?
No, kimbap.
- Kimbap?
- My goodness.
I want to run a kimbap restaurant.
If I run a restaurant,
I will never starve to death.
And you guys said...
I make the best kimbap.
You said it is even better
than a franchise restaurant's.
Oh, right.
Kimbap.
Maybe I should make kimbap
with this corn.
It's corn kimbap.
What should we do?
Don't you think
we should be honest with her?
Her kimbap tastes terrible.
We can't say that to her.
And it's you who said
her kimbap tastes terrible.
You... Gosh, I can't believe this.
Why are things going this way?
Hey, make sure to hold out
to the end this time.
Just worry about yourself.
He's coming.
- That feels good.
- Did you shower already?
Gosh, you're amazing.
Sure. He's even stronger
than a stuntman like me.
- Bring it back.
- What?
Bring what?
The one who brings it first
will get 30 dollars.
- Here, Dad.
- Okay.
Gosh.
Hey, hand it over.
- Here.
- Okay.
What?
Isn't there 100 dollars missing?
Who is it? Hand it over.
- It's not me.
- It's not me either.
Do you want me to search you?
Do you want me to search you
while you do handstands?
Seriously, it's not me.
I swear I didn't take it.
I swear on Seo Jin.
What are you guys doing
early in the morning?
Once you give them money,
it's a done deal.
Just go have breakfast.
Hey, go wake Ji Hun up.
And you should put the soup
on the table.
- Okay.
Hang on. Just wait.
I'm sure 100 dollars is missing.
I'm going to find out.
If you want to eat,
go buy some instant rice.
I made the steamed egg,
but your mom made this kimchi
and stir-fried anchovies.
Don't act like you care.
Forget it.
Kimchi and stir-fried anchovies?
I just blew myself up.
Fine. Take it all.
I can eat only with the egg.
Darn it. What's wrong with this?
Is it broken?
Darn it! What's wrong?
Was she really top of her class
at medical school?
Isn't she a fool?
Mom. I was going to call you.
About Da Hee.
Will you let her work
at my mother-in-law's cafe?
What can I do?
They already agreed on it.
But it's so uncomfortable.
You know what she's like.
Just leave her be.
She won't be working there for long.
By the way, we're buying
new chickens today,
so I'm thinking about
making chicken soup.
You should stop by
with Gyu Jin after work.
I can't. We're busy
preparing for a conference.
Are you? Then I'll bring it
to your house.
You can eat it after work.
Gosh, no. I'll stop by.
Why? You said you're busy.
I should eat anyway.
You don't have to come.
I'll go there.
Will you? That's better for me.
Then why don't you stop by the store
on your way here?
I should boil 10 chickens.
They are quite heavy.
I want to take them home
in your car.
Okay. I'll do that.
I'll see you later then.
Bye.
Why does it have to be now?
I guaranteed him
that I could handle my mom.
Darn it.
What should I tell him?
Gyu Jin, I'm so tired.
I have bags under my eyes already.
Look. Can you see them?
I just can't live like this.
She keeps calling me for no reason.
"Jae Seok".
And then again the next moment,
I feel like I'm hearing things.
Stop overreacting.
It's not like this is anything new.
It's been a long time,
so I just can't get used to it.
Jae Seok, what time do you get off?
It's Mom again.
She keeps messaging me. Look.
"Are you having dinner at home?"
"I have yellow corvina.
Do you want it steamed or grilled?"
This is a nightmare.
What should I do?
Should I just go back to Turkey?
Hey, getting used to Mom
would be easier...
- than living abroad.
- Gyu Jin.
You're just saying that
because it's not your business.
Whose fault do you think this is?
This is all because I was covering
for you and Na Hee.
What should I do then?
Do you want me to come clean...
and move back in with Mom too?
- Can't you do that?
- Do you think that would work?
What should I do then?
Mom is even more tiring now.
Yes?
Are you two having coffee together?
Not really.
I was just grumbling and whining.
I'll join you
and hear you grumble next time.
But right now,
we need to plan a strategy.
A strategy?
What more do you need to plan now?
You're being so talkative.
Did you not hear her?
She wants you to leave.
- Get out.
- Don't be mean.
I'm very sensitive now
because of Mom.
Na Hee, don't call me even if you
have no one to eat with today.
I'll be very cranky all day.
Move over.
Gosh.
All right. What's the matter?
Go ahead and say it.
Well...
Today,
I think I should go home.
Home?
Whose home?
You know what I mean.
My home. Mr. Song Young Dal's house.
Mom told us to come
and eat chicken soup.
If we don't go,
she will come to our place.
So I told her we'd go there.
I see.
You said you could handle things.
She asked us to stop by at the store
and take the chickens.
Make sure to leave on time.
Hey, make note of this.
You have to go to my mom once too.
How shameless.
How could she change her words
just like that?
My gosh.
Goodness.
- What's going on?
- What should we do?
My goodness.
Get off me.
Where did they go?
- My goodness.
- They just ran away.
I can't believe this is happening.
- What?
- I know.
She and I chatted away
on the street just yesterday.
But they just ran away overnight?
What's the matter? What happened?
They ran away with the lodge money.
- My gosh.
- Hey.
What's wrong?
- Wake up.
- Hurry.
- Please hurry.
- Call 911.
Really?
Did they run away
with all the lodge money?
Yes.
The lodge money and borrowed money.
They even borrowed 10,000 dollars
from the shoe store...
promising they'd pay
20 percent of interests.
The shoe store owner
turned deadly pale.
Gosh, it's so scary.
A few days ago, she asked me for
money offering 20 percent interest,
but I turned it down saying
my savings had not matured.
What if I gave her my money?
I'm so lucky.
My goodness.
People are really scary.
How could she do that
with such a nice face?
Everybody who opened a store there
has moved out within a year.
Is it a bad site?
I guess you're right.
Before the dumpling restaurant,
there was a fire
in the rice soup restaurant.
Fire!
And the owner of the dollar store
died of a heart attack.
I guess the place is cursed
or something.
Hey, Ok Ja. There you go again.
Think about it.
Something keeps happening
in that place while others are fine.
Don't say things like that.
Try to think if the dumpling store
owner borrowed money from you.
You might regret it later.
Gosh, I don't have any money
to lend others.
When you come home drunk,
I just pocket 50 or 100 dollars...
I knew it.
It was you.
- What?
- My 100 dollars.
It's you who took the money.
My gosh, what are you talking about?
I didn't take your money.
I'm innocent.
Hang on.
Onions, I must pay for them.
I have to go out. See you later.
Hey, hey! Gosh, that woman...
They say the thief is always
right under your nose.
You're so weird.
You never waste a single cent,
so why do you hand out cash
when you're drunk?
Shall I get you drunk
and make you give me an allowance?
Count the chickens.
Count the small
and large ones separately.
Okay.
The landlady must be so frustrated.
I don't believe this.
I knew something was up when she
missed the rent for three months.
It's not like fraudsters
have a sign on their forehead.
And I'm not a psychic.
Enough of that nonsense.
I want my rent,
so find a tenant soon.
Quickly.
How about you offer to rent it
below the market rate?
You really know how to upset me.
Bite it off. Bite it off.
That's enough. Bite it off!
How dare you?
Can I have some broth?
Hey.
You can't just sip the broth
without taking a noodle.
Don't you...
You ate more than half.
Jong Soo. We may have no money,
but let's keep our pride.
I'm always hungry,
however much I eat.
I couldn't stop myself.
I'll try not to eat any noodles.
Jeong Bong! Jong Soo!
- Joon Seon!
- You're here.
Why are you eating cup noodles?
You should eat some rice.
No, Joon Seon.
We ate earlier. This is a snack.
Right, Jong Soo?
That's right.
Do you want some broth?
Do you get some sleep?
Honestly, Joon Seon.
The room is warm all day long,
and there's unlimited hot water.
It's a hundred times better than
Action Art's dorm.
Don't you worry, Joon Seon.
No? You can't spare anything?
I understand. I just asked.
I'm just fine,
but the guys need a job.
Hey, Sang Gi. Your office...
Darn this stupid...
No, not you.
How much did it cost
to open up your business?
With the rent
and equipment and everything.
40,000 dollars?
That's a lot.
Your office isn't that big.
Where would I get 40,000 dollars?
I just have a plastic bag.
Okay, thanks anyway. Bye.
Hello...
there.
Hello, Ms. Song.
Hello. How are you, Mr. Yoon?
Where's the boss?
She went upstairs to get changed.
Oh, okay.
So, were you
very surprised yesterday?
I was so surprised myself.
No wonder you looked familiar.
At the cart bar and the hotel...
Anyway.
I had no idea it was you.
Pardon? What do you mean?
What cart bar?
You don't remember?
Two days ago at the beer joint.
You drank a whole pitcher,
and at the cart bar with me,
you got drunk and vented at me.
That's not true.
I didn't drink two days ago.
I think you're mistaken.
Don't say that.
However drunk you were,
you must remember me.
I'm the type that shows up
in your dreams once we meet.
Hello? Ms. Song? Hello?
I did all sorts of things
for you that evening.
I imparted wisdom
that I'd accumulated...
and offered heartfelt encouragement.
I even offered monetary support!
That really wasn't me.
Did you confuse me with
someone else?
I have such a common face.
And I'm so terribly shy.
I don't drink alone with a guy
I just happened to meet.
I didn't say it was just us.
I said we drank together.
What?
Whether there were
2 or 3 of us is not important.
Because it wasn't me.
Oh... Right...
Jae Seok. What are you doing here?
Why not go home if you got off work?
Oh, well, that was because
I knew you'd be here.
That's great.
Let's go to the department store.
You need new bed linen
and your desk lamp is too old.
We can have dinner there too.
Well, I'm so tired.
Can we go on the weekend, Mother?
Just come with me now.
Let's shop when the idea came up.
Let's go. Come with me.
Let's go now.
Mom. But I...
Da Hee, clean up and close up.
- See you tomorrow.
- Bye.
- Let's go.
- Mom, wait.
We're leaving now.
You, the cart bar.
Mom, wait.
How can someone be
such a terrible liar?
She practically broadcast that
she's bluffing.
Will you hurry up?
Why is someone so young so slow?
Mom.
Can't we cut it short and go home?
Bed linen is all the same.
No. You start and end
your day in your bed.
You can't buy just anything.
Those small details
determine your quality of life.
Let's hurry. There's no time.
We're only halfway through.
Come along.
I'm a slave, not a son.
Mom.
Welcome, Gyu Jin.
- Mother! Mother.
- Gyu Jin.
I didn't eat all day
just so I could eat your chicken.
Did you really? Good for you.
Today's chickens are so fat.
Have one each and recharge.
Is it because you
deal with kids all day long?
You both look so haggard.
Are the chickens inside?
Let's get them quick. I'm hungry.
- Okay.
- Well...
- Wait, wait.
- What?
Hey there. You know them, don't you?
My son-in-law, the pediatrician.
Oh, hello.
Hello. Na Hee,
it's been a while since I saw you.
The shoe seller is in the hospital.
Shouldn't we visit her?
Hey, Jin Ju,
don't you know my son-in-law?
My daughter and the pediatrician.
- Hello.
- Yes, hi.
The great son-in-law
and clever daughter are here.
He's not that great.
There are so many doctors nowadays.
Still, they say it's nice to have
a doctor and lawyer in the family.
It's a great help when you're sick.
Sure.
Let's go in. Dad's inside.
- Okay. Bye.
- Go on inside.
- Bye.
- See you.
She's such a show-off.
You'd think that she's the doctor.
Let her be. What else
does she have to brag about...
than that daughter and her husband?
But still,
I'm kind of jealous.
Just a bit.
Really? Your brother is home?
That's great.
Your mom must be pleased.
Yes, she's very pleased.
She gets quite lonely.
She does.
She was like that even in school.
She was.
I'd never seen someone so fussy.
Was it when I was eight?
I still remember.
She had her hair
braided into two pigtails,
and a book of poems...
under her arm either for show
or to actually read.
She walked around the neighborhood
like that just to show off.
She was given this nickname...
Oh, dear.
What did I just say?
That she showed off?
My goodness. I take it back.
Gyu Jin, I take it back.
I'll pretend I didn't hear anything.
Please do.
You're so considerate.
You're a good man.
Thank you.
I think a small bone
got stuck in my throat.
You should be very careful
with chicken bones.
They're hard to get out
if they're stuck.
Okay, Dad.
Why isn't Joon Seon home?
He jumps out of bed
for boiled chicken.
He wouldn't miss this feast.
Kid. Does it taste good?
My Seo Jin loves that ice cream too.
I miss Seo Jin and Seo Young.
Don't you miss your dad?
Mom!
Yes? What's wrong?
That's my cue to leave.
Na Hee, wait up!
I packed one more
for you to take home.
You can make porridge
with the leftovers.
It's fine, Mom.
Let me take that.
Thank you so much.
It's still quite hot,
so let me carry it.
Here you go.
Mother, let me carry it instead.
Na Hee.
What's wrong?
Did you and Gyu Jin argue?
- What do you mean?
- You know what I mean.
You were practically
shooting lasers at him.
What was the argument about?
Your temper was the issue, right?
Of course not.
I don't let my temper
flare up for no reason.
I'm very rational, you know.
Right. Of course, you are.
Anyway, be nice to him.
There aren't many guys...
who are this cooperative
when it comes to their in-laws.
Cooperative?
Only those who don't
know Gyu Jin say that.
What?
I'm just saying.
Anyway, I'll get going.
Take care then!
- Are you good?
- Yes.
This is enough
to feed us for three days.
Gosh, thank you so much.
It's nothing.
You must be tired, so get going.
Thank you for enjoying
the meal today.
Cooking food is harder
than eating it.
Thank you so much, Mother.
I'm the one who should be grateful.
Na Hee is not the most diligent
person around the house, right?
Don't I know it.
All she did was study all the time,
so I never got the chance
to teach her anything.
But you understand all that
and make up for what she lacks.
You have no idea
how grateful and sorry I am.
Please don't say that, Mother.
I may not have lucked out
with my kids and husband,
but I did with my son-in-law.
Are you two
filming a movie or something?
Well, who says that we can't?
I'm exhausted, so let's go.
- Right, go ahead.
- Right.
Stop the car.
Just let me drive you home.
We're both going there anyway.
It's better for the environment.
I'd rather not cross the line.
My mom cooked this,
so this is mine, right?
Mother packed it for me.
I doubt it was just for you.
Besides, how is she
your mother-in-law now?
We're not married, remember?
Hey. Just wait!
Must she be this cruel
especially with food?
(Episode 10)
What brings you by at this hour?
I was on my way home...
when the girls suddenly
popped into my head.
Here.
I'll give them these tomorrow.
Wait.
Could I...
see the kids for a second?
I'll briefly see their faces
and get going.
You sleep just like I do, don't you?
My sweet babies.
You both came out
with pretty faces...
to save me money on plastic surgery.
How kind of you.
Dad?
Did I wake you?
Gosh, I'm sorry.
You should go back to sleep.
It must be a dream.
Still, it's nice
to see you in my dream.
That's right. It's a dream.
Go back to sleep now.
I'm sorry, Seo Young.
I'm sorry about everything.
Thank you for letting me
see the kids.
There's no need to thank me.
You're their father.
Right. Yes, I'm their father.
It's late. You should head home.
Hey, Hyun Gyung.
Am I doing all right?
Hearing you say
that I'm doing fine...
will give me a boost of energy.
Get home safely then.
You're doing fine...
and you still have
your whole life ahead of you.
She's right.
I'm still young
and my life has just begun.
You can do it, Joon Seon.
You're their father!
You can do anything.
You crazy jerk, shut it!
Hold on.
Before you excuse yourselves,
I'd like to give you
a short presentation.
What nonsense are you spewing
this early in the morning?
It'll be your eldest son's...
new business plan for the year 2020.
You'll start another business?
Before I begin my briefing,
I'd like to inform you
that this is your chance...
to become investors
of the Good Action Company.
First, let me explain
the stunt industry...
regarding its current status
and future.
The current stunt industry...
Uncle Joon Seon,
I'm sorry but I need
to get ready for school.
Of course. You can't skip school.
Right, off you go.
- Thanks.
- All right.
All right then.
Hold on. Where was I?
The current stunt industry.
Right. Thanks.
The current stunt industry...
is a monopolistic market.
We must channel the energy and...
Enough of that.
What you want is for us to invest
in this crappy idea of yours.
Father, please. Why do you always
have a negative view on things?
Do you know what
makes people a success?
It's the fact...
that they take a step forward...
even though there's only
a one percent chance.
I'd like to have
a positive view on things too,
so please let me be that way.
Yes, exactly.
The bank only offers
a two percent interest these days.
Investing in real estate
gets you only four percent.
Those kinds of investments
won't help you much anyway.
Forget it.
I'm done hearing about this,
so I'll head to my room.
But Dad!
I need to get an early start
to the day as well.
I should get some more sleep.
Sorry, Joon Seon.
I have classes,
so I'll hear you out later on.
But I haven't even started.
Mom, would you like
to hear more of it?
Ga Hee, how about
you hear it in your sleep?
Dad,
I know you don't trust me
and you have every right to.
Still, I'm desperate this time.
Can't you trust me one last time?
Desperation shouldn't motivate you.
- You need a vision.
- And that I have!
You know the stunt coordinator
Jung Doo Hong, right?
- He...
- Forget it.
If you want to run a business,
come work at the chicken place.
Dad,
I told you that I'd never
fry chicken for a living.
You imbecile!
What's wrong about
frying chicken for a living?
What money
do you think I raised you with?
You kids should be
bowing to the chicken I fried.
I know that Dad,
but please give me one more chance.
Just this once.
No way. I'm done.
Leave the room.
I need to change my underwear.
Let me do that for you.
Okay, fine. I'm leaving.
Mom?
Mom...
Just stop it already.
I barely have any money
to put food on the table.
I took 100 dollars
from your dad last night.
- How about I give you that?
- Yes.
Da Hee, hold up.
Actually, you get a pass.
I'm sorry Joon Seon.
When I earn enough money,
I'll make sure
to invest in your company.
Good luck. I'm off!
Will I be around 60
when she earns enough money?
Ga Hee, the most
beautiful lady on the planet.
I'm completely broke, you know.
There's no point in asking me.
Really? Are you sure you're broke?
Don't you have
a few thousand dollars stashed?
I'd like nothing more
than to be the sister...
who can invest in your new project.
Just talking about it
makes me ashamed of myself.
Fine, penniless sister.
The presentation will be in a month.
You know that, right?
- Yes.
- Sure.
Sung Woo, make sure
we're registered to speak.
- Got it.
- Joo Hyuk, come up with...
a mock question sheet by this week.
Next week, I'll start working on
the presentation material...
(Neulpuleun Children's Hospital)
Hi, Joon Seon. This is a surprise.
Where?
Na Hee!
What brings you by?
Seo Jin doesn't have
an appointment today.
I saw walnut buns
and was reminded of you.
Have some while they're hot.
What's wrong? You love these.
- Do I?
- Don't you?
Then you can like them as of today.
Try one. They're delicious.
- How much?
- What? How much is what?
You want money, don't you? How much?
Don't be ridiculous.
I only brought these...
for you to enjoy. Really.
Just tell me already. Would you
rather go home empty-handed?
I need to see patients.
20,000 dollars
or at least 10,000 dollars.
20,000 dollars?
Did you get into trouble again?
No, of course not.
I'm thinking of opening...
my own talent agency
for stunt performers.
Joon Seon, the economy
is bad right now.
It might be wiser to
receive a salary yourself instead.
I know that but it's just
where I'm at right now.
Can't you help me?
I can't believe
you bought walnut buns...
when you're asking me
for 20,000 dollars.
You can be really stingy, you know.
I'm sorry, but I don't
have the money either.
I'll be needing it too, I'm afraid.
I guess I can spare
about 5,000 dollars.
5,000 dollars?
Unbelievable.
It still wouldn't be
a wise investment on my part.
In order to start a business,
one must do proper research
and have a vision.
- But you never...
- I'll take what you can give.
And stop with your nagging.
I'll take the 5,000 dollars.
See you.
And now you're taking
what you bought me.
Na Hee was my last hope...
which means I'm done for.
Isn't there anyone
who has money lying around?
I'd give up everything
for money to fall out of the sky.
- Joon Seon?
- Gyu Jin, hi!
It sure is nice to see you here.
What brings you by though?
Are you here
for Seo Jin's treatment?
Not exactly.
Do you perhaps
have some time to spare?
This field is like any other field.
I'm not as young...
or in great shape as I used to be.
It's embarrassing to work under
a junior stuntman too.
Let me help.
- What?
- You want to start a business.
Still,
I don't have
a lot to spare right now,
and I can only lend you
about 8,000 dollars.
- Would that be okay?
- 8,000 dollars?
That's more than enough!
- Thanks, Gyu Jin.
- Don't mention it.
However, promise me...
that you won't tell Na Hee.
It's from my secret stash.
Are you sure I can take this?
I feel shameful for some reason.
It's fine. I'm investing in you...
because I see the potential.
I'm a big fan of your stunts.
Gyu Jin, thank you so much.
This is a huge help.
I'll wire it to your account
right away.
You can't tell Na Hee, okay?
I won't.
- Promise me.
- I promise you.
Of course, I don't have money.
I send everything I earn
to our parents...
and you come by
whenever I've saved some up.
I can barely put food on the table.
- So get lost.
- What can I do then?
The baby will be born soon,
so I need the money
to find us a decent place to stay.
Whatever. Your life
is yours to manage.
I'm broke too, so sue me.
Is this how it's going to be?
Should I go back to gambling again?
How dare...
- you say that.
- That hurts!
- I'll kill myself.
- Unbelievable.
Here you go.
What's this?
Get your brother a place to stay.
It'll be enough for a deposit.
- Cho Yeon...
- Unbelievable.
No wonder you were
on the phone for so long.
Why didn't you come to me for help?
I can't believe you were
trying to handle it yourself.
Didn't you sign the lease today?
How will you make the payments?
It's fine.
There are other places I can go.
I'll find something cheaper.
If nothing pans out,
I can also head out of the city.
I'm getting sick and tired
of Seoul anyway.
- Cho Yeon...
- Wait, hold that.
I don't do touching moments,
so don't you dare.
Cho Yeon, thanks. I love you.
You know I hate physical contact.
- Let go of me.
- Guys, I love you too!
What on earth?
My cheeks are about to explode.
Guys, let me breathe, okay?
You'll crush my face at this rate.
Ji Hun, that wasn't on purpose.
- Are you sure?
- I think it was.
Tae Jin!
Dad!
Did you have fun today?
- How were your classes?
- I had fun.
That's my boy. Let's get going.
Here you go.
- I'm home.
- Hi.
Auntie is in the bathroom.
Aren't you going to answer me?
You always seem to ignore me
and it's annoying.
Hi, Seo Young.
It went dead again.
Ji Hun, hold on.
Can I borrow your phone?
Mom put a time limit on mine...
- and it shuts off after an hour.
- No way.
Let me borrow it for a while.
I won't snoop around.
No.
Please!
Just for 30 minutes.
- Hey, you're bleeding!
- I said no!
Just stop bothering me.
What was that?
Wow.
What? Was it Ji Hun who just yelled?
I guess he's going through puberty.
I see. It's about time.
He's 11 years and 3 months old.
I know it's true, but...
By the way,
his fingernails were bleeding.
It must sting a lot.
Ji Hun, are you hungry?
Do you want a sandwich?
No. I'm not hungry.
You aren't?
Did you eat a lot for lunch?
What did you have at school?
Today? I had curry and rice.
I ate a lot.
I see.
Was everything okay at school?
Yes. It was fine.
If you want to bring a friend home,
you can do that.
I'll order jajangmyeon
and tangsuyuk for you.
Okay.
I should do homework.
What? Okay.
Tell me if you're hungry, Ji Hun.
Okay. I will.
Wait.
If Joon Seon calls you,
just make things up and play dumb.
Why? Is something wrong with him?
You don't have to know.
Just do as I say.
Did he call you already?
No, he didn't.
Gyu Jin, are you going home already?
Come home with me.
I want to escape Mom's attention
just for one day.
I can't do that.
Na Hee, please help me.
You know that doesn't make sense.
What should I do then?
Gyu Jin, I got five calls today.
And she sent me seven text messages.
What if I'm tortured to death?
Gyu Jin, how will you deal with it?
Na Hee, how will you deal
with that guilt?
- You won't die.
- Life is so tenacious.
It won't happen.
You two are so mean.
You can't do this to me.
If you don't have any ideas,
I'll just tell her about you two.
- You can't do that!
What?
Gosh, look at you two
with your perfect teamwork.
I wonder why you broke up.
Fine.
I get it.
It's happened already.
It's all my fault that I made...
the wrong choice for loyalty.
It really is.
Fine.
You should go.
Go enjoy your golden lives
and live well.
All right. Good luck.
Make sure to flatter Mom.
(Ms. Song)
(Please don't put gum
and toilet paper in the toilet.)
Welcome.
Thank you for your hard work,
Ms. Song.
Hello, Mr. Yoon.
Are you going home now?
Ms. Choi went home early today.
I know she's not here.
I needed to brace myself
before heading home.
- Would you like something to drink?
- It's okay.
Please don't mind me
and continue what you were doing.
Okay.
What?
What? What did I do?
Nothing. It's nothing.
Ms. Song.
Do you really not know me?
Of course, I do. You're my in-law.
My brother-in-law's brother.
And my boss' son.
Oh, is that it?
Do you still not remember
the cart bar?
I said it wasn't me.
Why would you keep saying that?
I see. I'm so sorry then.
But the thing is, I was robbed
by that woman at the cart bar.
What? You were robbed?
Yes. She said she'd pay
for the drinks,
but she just ran away after paying
only part of it while I was away.
So she's a robber.
Well... You can't call her
a robber for that.
That's not true. She's a robber.
She's the one who ordered
the drinks and the food.
And she ate it all.
Then she... My gosh.
Look at this.
She just ran away
after leaving this message.
Look.
Should I go to the police
to catch her?
Maybe I should go to the NFS.
My gosh.
Hang on.
(Please don't put gum
and toilet paper in the toilet.)
I think your handwriting
looks very similar.
Even the squirrel. Right?
Gosh, that's not true.
It looks totally different.
Give me that. Let me compare them.
No, I can't.
I should put these up.
Wait. Give me that. Hang on.
Just give me that.
She just can't hide
that she's flustered.
It makes me want
to tease her even more.
They call this cheap?
A 40,000-dollar deposit
and 2,000-dollar rent?
Gosh. I guess everyone is rich...
except me.
What can I do with 13,000 dollars?
Gosh. Darn it.
No. I'm a man.
I have drawn my sword...
and it cannot be sheathed
until it draws blood.
Right. I'm Song Joon Seon.
I just have to do
with what I've got.
If I don't have money,
I need tenacity.
All right.
I just have to brazen it out.
Be shameless.
Gosh. Give me that, Dad.
You should call me
for things like this.
You might hurt your back.
It's not that heavy.
You might strain your back.
You should think of your age.
You know you're the light
of our family.
Your body isn't all yours.
I said no.
Dad, please.
I've attracted investments
of 13,000 dollars.
With an extra 20,000 dollars,
I can get a semi-basement room.
I'll pay five percent interest.
No, let's make it 7,
What about 7 percent interest?
I'm not going to run
a moneylending business with you.
I'm doing this
because I have no other choice.
I have people who count on me.
Forget it. If you talk more,
you will just waste your time.
All that debt is only going to
get you into trouble.
Don't try to run a business
with someone else's money.
You should try to steadily
build a fortune.
It's not like you're a stranger.
Think of me as a stranger.
My money isn't yours.
Dad.
Gosh.
I can't believe this.
You're his dad. Can't you at least
pretend to listen to him?
What?
He wants to start something
for the first time in a while.
You can at least hear
what his plan is...
We know what he's like.
It's not his first time to ask
for money trying to start something.
He lost money after
guaranteeing a debt for a friend.
And he lost money again
running a business with a friend.
He doesn't seem clever at all.
Why would I give him money again?
I have no money to spare.
I don't even have enough for myself.
But he's your son.
It's not like
he will be unlucky forever.
He's been doing this for 14 years.
It might go well if he starts
his own business.
Gosh, have you not give up yet?
You're truly unbelievable.
What kind of parent would
give up on her own son?
I see. You're so determined
when it comes to money.
You will make a lot of money
and die with it in your arms.
Your grave will be
packed with money.
Are you cursing me to die now?
- It's just a figure of speech.
- My gosh.
Why complain?
Oh, ma'am.
Ma'am, you're out today.
- I'll pull it for you.
- No.
- It's fine.
- It's okay.
You're early today.
- Did you have breakfast?
- Yes, I did.
He has such a weird temper.
Wouldn't it be nice...
if he were half as nice to his kids?
My goodness. He's so mean.
Young Dal is a bit harsh
on the kids.
Especially Joon Seon.
Exactly.
He makes him pay rent
every single month.
He's so nasty.
What about him did you like so much?
- What?
- I kind of remember a lot.
You fell in love with...
Young Dal who worked at
our mill at the time.
You wailed that
you'd die without him.
Dad even shaved your head.
I know.
I fell for his guitar skills...
and totally lost my mind.
Love does make you crazy.
Once you're head over heels,
there's no cure.
What'll happen to
the dumpling place?
I hope they find a new tenant...
or Yun Jeong will take out
her stress on Na Hee.
I know.
When I think of Yun Jeong,
I think it serves her right,
but it does worry me too.
No one who knows what happened...
will want to rent that space.
Ok Boon, can you fry up
a whole chicken right now?
Yes, of course. It won't take long.
By the way, have you heard?
The dumpling store was let out.
My gosh. Someone rented it?
- For real?
- Yes, for real.
I just met the real estate agent.
Someone signed today.
The space got rented out? Really?
Yes, really.
Ok Ja said the dried goods seller
heard from the real estate agent.
Really? Gosh, that's great news.
I was worried it would
stay empty for a long time.
It's a relief.
My in-law must've
rented it out really cheap.
No one on that side
sells pork trotters.
I wish a pork trotter seller
would come in.
Why? To get drunk?
It's not about getting drunk.
It's about filling my belly...
and my empty heart.
I'd like to do all that.
Whatever they sell,
I hope the person is decent.
You're right.
If it's someone like Mr. Oh
who thought he was so great,
they're not welcome.
They just cause trouble...
and make our jobs harder.
I'd hate that.
I am a bit curious.
What person rented that space?
I wonder too.
(Ground Goods)
(Epilogue)
Mom!
(40 years ago)
Where should I put
the empty bottles?
She sent me a letter
Shortly after we parted
Inside was a neatly folded
White handkerchief
Ok Boon.
Bring the rice flour in the basin.
Okay!
It's heavy. I'll...
My gosh!
Oh, dear.
What a waste of good rice flour.
This is terrible.
Oh, no.
Why did you want to see me here?
Are you asking because...
you don't know?
I do know, but still.
"Love Story" is showing
at Daeji Cinema.
Shall we go?
"Love Story"?
I asked you out,
so I'll buy the tickets.
But after the movie,
you can buy me dumplings.
Meat dumplings.
Meat dumplings?
Okay. Let's go.
Ok Boon!
(Once Again)
There's an opening for
a pediatric research lecturer.
That's great.
One of us will get the job.
Fine. Let's really split up.
The women at the market were right.
They're not your average women.
President!
The other merchants
feel uncomfortable.
Is that for Unnie's Kimbap?
Bring it over here. Line them up.
Why did you call...
My mom is on her way.
The Cohabitation Contract
we stuck on the wall.
Taxi! Taxi!
Mother! Mother!