Dr. Lee's here.
Hello.
I must be the last to arrive.
I meant to hurry.
Jeong Rok.
- It's been a while, Gyu Jin.
- Yes.
It's even nicer to see you.
Crazy Song Na Hee.
Hello, Jeong Rok.
I hope it's not a show
that connects...
medical advice
with product promotion.
No product placement either.
I hear you.
I'll make sure the show
is strictly educational.
- You should...
- I have another question.
Does your face
really look bigger on TV?
Gosh, sorry about that.
It was just hilarious, that's all.
Na Hee, you haven't changed at all.
Ready, action!
("QnA with Doctors")
A high-end talk show brought
to you with a panel of doctors.
This is "QnA with Doctors".
Walnuts are packed
with omega-3 and choline...
which helps strengthen
memory function and blood vessels.
It's why we can benefit from
eating nuts at an early age.
However, forcing a child
to eat nuts...
against his or her will...
can add unnecessary stress,
and stress can hurt
their brain health.
They still need
to consume nuts though...
unless there's a cheaper way
to obtain vitamin E, that is.
Once they're old and find it
necessary to eat them, they will.
You should just leave them be.
Instead of forcing your children
to eat nuts,
talk to them,
and compliment them sincerely.
That's a better way
to develop their brain synapses.
There's a study that indicates...
how children with good relationships
with their parents...
do better academically.
Dr. Song, you must've talked
to your parents a lot as a child...
considering how you became a doctor.
My parents were too busy
frying chicken at the market...
to spend any quality time with me.
A pat on the head here and there...
and a pat on the back
from time to time.
That's also a way of conversing.
I didn't mind the smell
of fried chicken coming from them.
They smelled that way because
they were busy living their lives,
and that was all the encouragement
I truly needed.
- Good job today.
- Thank you.
- Thank you for coming.
Did you have to undermine
my opinion like that?
I was only adding my point of view.
But you're not that way
with the other doctors.
Gosh. Good job today.
You were trying to make me
look like a fool, weren't you?
That wasn't the case at all.
You should think deeper
before answering their questions.
You don't want to deceive
viewers with false information.
Deceive viewers?
Don't you know
how knowledgeable I am?
All I'm saying is that...
Why are you rolling your eyes?
Good job today, Gyu Jin.
- You too, Na Hee.
- You did well too.
You guys had great chemistry today.
Na Hee, you especially...
made the show today.
Did you hear that?
Jeong Rok thinks I did well.
If you're not busy,
how about we grab a bite?
I'd love to get
a snack or something.
I'm sorry, but I have to get home.
Really?
Yes, me too.
Gosh, that was refreshing.
Why couldn't Ga Hee let us go first?
Is she worried we'd sell her son
after giving him a bath?
She just never makes
life easy for anyone.
And I wouldn't mind you shutting up.
I nearly went deaf, you know.
Got it.
Gosh, what's taking them so long?
Ji Hun, my son!
- Unbelievable.
- Guys, we're sorry.
We tried to hurry up,
but Ok Ja insisted
on drying her hair longer.
You did too,
so why would you only blame me?
- Let's get going then.
- I can't believe you, Auntie.
- This is heavier now.
- Gosh.
Joon Seon, did you scrub
Ji Hun's back thoroughly?
Don't tell me you just
poured water on him.
I scrubbed him well...
to the point that
his skin almost peeled off.
What about the back of his neck
and his behind?
I told you I did.
Just so you know,
I spent too much time on him...
that I didn't have
enough for myself.
See? I still need a good scrub.
Gosh, that's disgusting.
Good job, my son.
I'm the one who did a good job,
not him.
Fine. Good job, Joon Seon.
Can you hold this for me?
Can't you throw that away?
You've lost most of
the studs on that anyway.
You see,
living with a certain someone
makes you think like him.
Why would you drag me into this?
I never told you
not to buy hairpins.
I never said it was you, so what's
with the guilty confession?
Mom,
I better get going
to my part-time job.
Sure, go ahead.
Call me if you're scared
to walk home alone.
Sure. I won't be late anyway.
Joon Seon, here.
- I'll get going.
- Have a good one.
Have a good time.
Look at our youngest sister
working hard.
- Doesn't it make you proud?
- It sure does.
A person should always work
to make a living...
like I am doing now.
Don't you agree, Ga Hee?
- Those losers.
- Ji Hun, let's go.
Gosh, I'm hungry.
Unbelievable.
I wonder if Na Hee and Gyu Jin
successfully wrapped up the show.
Should I call them?
I'm sure they did well.
You sure did raise
a smart one, didn't you?
- I mean she's even on TV.
- Tell me about it.
I'm more nervous myself.
Yes, Mom.
The show's over and I'm almost home.
Really?
If you're not home yet,
come by with Gyu Jin.
We can order some jjajangmyeon.
We're both a bit tired right now.
Right, of course you are.
All right then.
Go home and get some rest.
That reminds me.
Can you ask Gyu Jin if he'd
like some more scallion kimchi?
Hold on.
Mom wants to know if you'd
like some more scallion kimchi.
Oh, I see. Mom?
He says we have
more than enough right now.
He'll tell you
when he wants some more.
Okay, I got it.
Go home and get some rest then.
Don't skip your meals, okay?
Got it.
Gosh, that was refreshing.
Mom, can we order Chinese?
I'll have a ganjjajang.
I'll have a seafood jjamppong.
Mom, let's order tangsuyuk too.
Sure, order a big plate.
Why would we order in
when we have leftovers?
We still have the doenjang jjigae
from this morning.
I'll buy, so let's order Chinese.
If that's the case,
I'll have a ganjjajang.
Let me take your order then.
Who wants ganjjajang?
Seafood jjamppong?
- Me.
- Got it.
Orders received.
Hello, is this Hong's?
This is President Song Young Dal's.
We'll order 4 ganjjajangs,
2 seafood jjamppongs,
and a big plate of tangsuyuk.
We'd appreciate a fast delivery,
a lot of pickled radishes,
and a free plate of fried dumplings.
Wait, what was that sound?
Didn't it come from above?
A stray cat must've gotten inside.
No, Dad, hold on.
Let me go up there.
It's not like there's
anything to eat up there.
Gosh.
See? I can do a push-up
on my thumbs, right?
You can't.
I just saw you miserably fail.
Also, I saw you
make fists with your hands.
You're wrong.
I was balancing on my thumbs.
- No way.
- You two!
Have you forgotten what I told you?
You're supposed to be like ghosts.
No one can know you're up here.
It's his fault for insisting
that a rookie like him...
can do a push-up on his thumbs.
I wasn't insisting.
Didn't I just prove it to you?
Shut it, you two, and listen up.
My parents eat
home-cooked meals every day,
work consistent hours,
and take dance classes
at the market.
Do you know what that means?
It means that
they're healthier than us.
Everything including their sense
of sight, hearing, and smell...
are quite sensitive,
so keep it down as much as you can
or you'll be back at the sauna.
We're sorry.
We thought you were
still at the sauna.
So, are you two feeling better now?
Yes, we're in better condition.
I'm loving the warm floors...
and the fact that it's not damp.
I'm glad then.
Here you go.
Hold on a second.
Hello, sir.
This is President Song's again.
Our food hasn't been
delivered yet, has it?
Then I'll order two large portions
of jajangmyeon.
Can you deliver it
to the rooftop apartment...
using the outside stairs?
Yes, please keep it a secret.
Don't forget
the free fried dumplings.
- Welcome.
- Hello.
This is pretty. Mom would love it.
- How much is this?
- Six dollars.
- I'll take it.
- Sure.
Do you perhaps have one more
of the same design?
- The person you have reached...
- They just never answer me.
The show must be over by now.
- It's me, Ms. Choi.
- Hi, there.
Goodness. Your hair is wet.
You can catch a cold
if you don't dry this, you know.
My entire family
went to the sauna today.
Your whole family?
Isn't that what families
used to do 50 years ago?
The whole family goes
sometimes on the weekends.
Meanwhile, my mom and aunt...
always go to get rid of
the stench of fried oil.
I see.
This is for you.
What's this?
You grilled me that steak
the other day, remember?
It's nothing expensive though.
I just bought it on the street.
Is it a gift?
Gosh, it's pretty.
Maybe it's because
I have such an elegant look.
It must be because you look lovely.
It's like one
from a department store.
I'm only kidding.
Anyway, thank you so much.
So this is what it's like
to raise a daughter.
Well, I'll take my break now.
Good luck down here.
Sure, go ahead.
Welcome.
Is there a seat with a plug here?
Yes, over there.
So what can I get you?
My mom is the lady
with the long hair!
My mom's hair is so long
that it drags on the ground.
Her hair...
- is over 2m long...
- Excuse me.
- Yes?
- Can I get a glass of cold water?
Well, it's self-served...
- Her hair...
- Sure thing.
For 23 years...
I told you
I have an operation tomorrow.
Well, don't drink so much.
We'll talk again soon.
Is she working part-time
on the weekends too?
Here you go. My gosh!
- Are you all right?
- Seriously?
- Unbelievable.
Move it!
Who serves water like that?
You should've come from the front.
How can I see you
if you come from the side?
I don't have eyes
on the side of my face.
I'm terribly sorry.
I didn't think of that.
So what are you
going to do about this?
Do you know how expensive this is?
Suede should never
be drenched in water.
Are you kidding me?
Whatever. You'll just have
to get me a new one.
What?
This is your mistake, so of course.
It's already losing its color.
Hold on a second.
This looks like a fake to me.
Real suede wouldn't
lose color like this.
Who are you to butt in like this?
Mr. Yoon...
I'm someone who can represent
the owner of this cafe.
From what I saw,
you're the one who
knocked over the cup.
So why must she take responsibility?
That's absurd!
Unbelievable.
You have a bad memory
for someone your age.
Let's check
the security camera then.
If you really did
knock over the cup,
you'll have to pay
for the dry cleaning...
and compensate her
for emotional injury.
It's not like I caused her any harm.
You tried to blame
an innocent person just now.
I heard you yell
and shoot impolite comments.
Look at how pale your skin is.
You must be in shock.
What? That's right.
I can't believe you people.
Whatever. Just forget about it.
We won't see you out.
Have a good day.
I'm sorry, ma'am. Take care.
Ms. Song,
are you too nice or foolishly naive?
- Sorry?
- Why let her bombard you like that?
No wonder she saw you
as a pushover.
I wasn't being a pushover.
You're still being that way
even at this moment.
You know what?
Changing your personality is
more crucial than college for you.
I'm taking it upon myself
to train you. Got it?
All right. Got it.
(MG Community Credit Cooperatives)
Your employee bank accounts
have been opened.
A variety of commission fees
are for free...
and you can withdraw money from them
after hours.
Thank you so much. How nice of you.
Here you go.
Save up your salaries
from here on out.
Don't you go about
spending money...
just because you feel like it.
Got it, Cho Yeon.
I'll try and enjoy the fun
of saving up money too.
It feels amazing to receive
a bank account just for my salary.
Until when must we
wear clothes like this though?
Just look at this.
Are you kidding me
with this elastic waistband?
Tell me about it.
I feel like someone's choking me.
It's too stuffy.
We need to show them
that we're following their orders,
so just hang in there.
We'll wait for a window.
It's not like they can
watch us every day.
Wearing boring clothes
can be so annoying.
Welcome!
Hello.
Goodness.
I wasn't expecting all three of you.
We're not here for a special reason.
Just lunch.
I see you're here
to keep an eye on us.
Don't you worry.
We may not be the obedient type,
but we keep our promises.
It's not to observe you three...
Anyway, we'll have
three rolls of kimbap.
Sure.
Cho Yeon, 3 rolls of kimbap
on table 3.
Okay, 3 rolls of kimbap on table 3.
The cutlery is in the drawer.
Here are your three rolls of kimbap.
Please enjoy.
Your soup will be right out.
The clothes look great on them.
Tell me about it.
They look like ladies now.
Exactly.
It's not like we mean
you used to look cheap of anything.
Guys, just eat.
You're making it worse.
What on earth is this?
Why? Does it taste bad?
Well,
I'm not sure if I should
just call this bland.
Did you even season the ingredients?
Of course I did.
I seasoned all of them this morning.
- Let me try one.
- Maybe...
you left this one out.
It tastes fine to me.
It's seasoned perfectly.
Aren't you just trying to nitpick?
My gosh.
I also sell food for a living,
you know.
I wouldn't joke
when it comes to food.
Is that so?
If you're not satisfied,
I won't take your money then.
My gosh. Really?
No, that's all right.
We're not here for freebies,
so we'll pay.
No, don't.
It just doesn't feel right.
No, I'm going to pay.
I won't feel comfortable otherwise.
I said it's okay.
You don't have to pay.
No, take it. Where's my change?
The food wasn't satisfying,
so it's on the house.
It doesn't change the fact
that we ordered it.
Now, take the money
and give me my change.
It's about Na Hee's sister.
She's nothing like Na Hee.
Na Hee is too straightforward.
But Da Hee is too soft-hearted.
Is it because she was repressed
by Na Hee growing up?
It wasn't easy to shoot a TV show.
There were cameras everywhere,
and the lighting was too hot.
It felt like I was taking
a test in histology.
She's very nice though.
It's just unfair
that nice people like her...
are always struggling.
And Na Hee kept pouncing
on my words the whole time.
The director found it interesting,
so he pushed ahead with it.
And Jeong Rok was giggling
watching it.
I was so upset.
Jeong Rok was a senior
at our school.
You know that, right?
Jeong Rok was like a legend.
All students in our school became
doctors with his test materials.
He recently got trained
at the New York Cancer Center.
He will start working
at Sejin Hospital next week.
It's our affiliated hospital.
Will you keep talking about yourself
without listening to me?
You're doing the same thing.
- Am I?
- Yes, you are.
So what? Did the shoot go well?
Forget it.
I don't want to talk about it again.
Then don't.
I should go take a nap.
This coffee isn't enough.
Keep talking to yourself then.
What a nut.
He's a complete nutcase.
Why are you being like this again?
We're done talking about it.
I don't care if he's single or not.
I just don't want to get married.
I will just raise Si Hoo
by myself like this.
That was the plan when I had him.
If I needed a man,
I would've gotten back together
with him no matter what.
I'm just fine.
Why are you being like this?
What? Why?
I want chocolate milk.
Research says milk products are
not good for kids with asthma.
I don't drink it often.
Why are you drinking
something sweet then?
My mom doesn't drink
things like this to stay fit.
- I don't gain weight easily.
- I don't think so.
You've gained some weight
since I first met you.
What?
Who, me?
Gosh, what are you talking about?
Can I ask you about your dad?
Yes. It's okay.
Since when was your dad not around?
I didn't have one
from the beginning.
My mom says I've never had a dad.
I'm sorry, Si Hoo.
Oh, Dr. Song.
Mom, Dr. Song bought me
chocolate milk.
Thank you.
I was talking on the phone.
I see.
Si Hoo should go get a shot.
We should get going.
Say bye.
Let's go.
I didn't gain weight.
What's funny?
No, nothing.
(Balloon Art Show with Dad)
What are you doing, Si Hoo?
Let's go.
Okay, Mom.
He's so handsome.
He's like a walking mannequin.
I know.
I will marry a man like him
in my next life.
- You're here.
- Yes.
They gave us the wrong address,
so it took longer than expected.
Oh, no.
He must've had a hard time.
What kind of idiot
doesn't even know his address?
I see.
I should've checked it again
when I took the order.
Thank you anyway.
Come on in
and drink something cool.
Go on ahead.
Have something cool in there.
The kimbap was just terrible.
It's unbelievable.
But the owner didn't seem to agree.
She says it tastes just right.
Really?
Is it that bad?
Yes. It does taste bad.
You know Jeong Sik
has a big appetite,
but he could barely finish
half of the kimbap.
My point.
It's rare that we agree
on something.
- Come on in.
- You're here.
- I'm back.
- Hello, Sweetie.
You must be tired.
No. I'm okay.
The delivery is going well.
The sales are on the rise.
Really?
I wonder whose idea it was.
There you go again.
You just demean yourself
by talking too much.
You look quite stoic though.
Look who's talking.
You just never stop talking.
- Men and women aren't the same.
- What's the difference?
They are always like that.
Don't bother.
- Okay.
- I should just drink my coffee.
Asthma isn't easy to care for.
Your husband should have
to help out a lot.
Well...
No wonder.
(Balloon Art Show with Dad)
Watch carefully and follow me.
Tie it carefully.
Well done.
Si Hoo.
Where did he go?
- What is this?
- Si Hoo.
Mom!
Do you like it?
Let me see.
What is this?
Is it a gun?
It's a gun.
What's up?
What?
You'd never come to my office
for no reason.
What is it?
I was just wondering
if you lend your husband.
What do you mean?
You know there's a balloon art class
in the small assembly hall today.
And I just went there.
And Dr. Yoon was in the class
with some kid.
You know him. He's your patient.
Si Hoo or something.
I see.
What? Did you know about it?
Sure. I asked him to do it.
The kid's dad couldn't make it.
I see.
I just thought...
maybe I should tell you
to take good care of your husband.
All right then.
What am I doing now?
He must've been tired.
He was working so hard
sweating all over.
Thank you
for doing this with Si Hoo.
It's no big deal.
Actually,
my husband is abroad.
He will come back soon,
but it's still not easy for Si Hoo.
There are things
he wants to do with his dad.
I understand.
I had no idea.
Yes.
Tell me whenever
something like this comes up.
I can do this much.
No way.
That would be insulting to Dr. Song.
It's okay. This is nothing.
Right?
I put up the closed sign.
I'll get going now.
- You do that.
- Get some rest.
- See you tomorrow.
- Okay.
Goodbye, Sweetie.
You two can go ahead too.
I booked a foot massage.
I'll close up in time for that.
What? Okay, you do that.
I'll drop by
the association's office.
I have to update
the membership fee ledge.
Okay, then. Let's all split up.
We need days like this too.
This is great.
My gosh. My poor shoulder.
Yes, of course.
I mixed three-and-a-half vats
of batter.
No wonder it hurts.
Still, I wish we got more sales,
even if my arm falls off.
I'll make lots of money
and invest in my son's business.
I'll buy Ga Hee a home,
and send my youngest abroad
to study a foreign language.
Ok Boon.
Hey, Yun Jeong. Did you buy flowers?
How lovely. Let me see.
Oh, they smell great too.
You're wearing the pin too.
Da Hee said she got one more
while getting me one.
It suits you so well too.
Of course it does.
The kids.
How do you think the shoot went?
I can't believe they'll be on TV.
Hey.
I'm a bit busy. Bye.
My goodness.
What got her in a bad mood now?
She just has two extremes.
I can't stand her.
I think your biggest problem
is your attitude.
You act like
you're beneath everyone.
You have a submissive attitude
that makes everyone think...
there's nothing wrong with
making excessive demands.
You act submissive.
This is the biggest problem.
Do you get what I mean?
Yes. Submissive attitude.
You don't have to write it down.
Just change how you act.
Okay, how I act.
If we go into detail,
your attitude is expressed by...
the look in your eyes
and the tone of your voice.
First.
The look in your eyes.
You need a strong gaze.
If your gaze wavers
or you act unsure,
the other person is bound to
look down on you.
Now,
glare at me.
Glare. Ms. Song. Harder.
As if you want to crush me.
That's it. Yes, not bad.
More, more. More.
More, more. Well done.
That was great.
Don't forget that tip.
You can stop glaring now.
The second part is
about how you speak.
You must always be firm.
If you don't sound like you mean it,
you will lose every argument.
For example,
say a sit-in customer
wants a paper cup.
How will you react? Let's practice.
- Go on.
- Okay.
Hey, can I have a paper cup?
I'm sorry, sir, but you're not
allowed to use paper cups indoors.
Can I give you a mug now,
then give you a paper cup
when you leave?
Why are you asking
the customer's opinion? Why?
Be firm!
Again. Ready?
Can I have a paper cup?
Sir. I'll give you a mug now,
and a paper cup when you leave.
That's the rule.
Perfect. Now you look like
you mean business.
Sit back down.
This way, no one can
talk back to you.
Mom. You're back.
Why do you keep on
coming here after work?
Come upstairs for dinner.
I'll take that, ma'am.
No. It's not for the cafe.
I'm going upstairs.
You can close up and go home.
Okay.
Won't you hurry up?
I'm coming.
Was it buy one,
get one free or something?
Gosh. Why are you so annoyed, Mom?
Be quiet,
and stop dropping by the cafe.
You look bored.
Why would I be bored?
So many friends beg me
every evening to hang out.
Whatever.
I just can't seem to like
the kids from that family.
My gosh.
Practice what you learned today.
That's homework.
A strong gaze and firm tone.
You puff up like crazy
and you're eating ramyeon at night?
Why do you care?
You should act appropriately.
Officially, you're still my husband.
What are you talking about?
You were in the auditorium
with your first love's son.
Ji Yeon came to tell on you.
Doesn't she have
anything better to do?
Anyone else could
and would think it strange.
It's strange to think it strange.
Why can't I hang out with a kid?
Is that a bad thing to do?
It's not a bad thing,
but you're not Si Hoo's dad.
If his dad's busy,
an uncle can take his place,
or a doctor for that matter.
Why did she have to
gossip about that?
That really ticked me off.
I should give her a call.
Don't overreact.
I'm just saying
you should be careful.
Are you throwing that away?
Don't leave it there.
Put it in the recycle bin.
My gosh.
(Yongju Traditional Market)
(Ttobongee Chicken)
(Episode 18)
Sit down and have some breakfast.
Mom,
can I take mine upstairs on a tray?
There's something about my business
I need to quietly think about.
I'd appreciate double the rice.
Is that so? Okay, got it.
What makes you worthy
of getting a separate tray?
Just sit down and eat.
Yes, Dad.
I'm missing a few things
from the fridge though.
Half of the rice cakes...
given to us
by the rice cake store is gone.
Did you guys eat it?
No, not me.
It wasn't me.
Not me either.
I didn't even know
there was any rice cake.
That's right. It was me.
I've just been hungry
all the time these days.
Mom, the rice cakes
were delicious though.
You know how
I've always loved rice cakes.
Don't be ridiculous.
You hate rice cakes.
You almost died after eating one
when you were young,
and you've hated them ever since.
Yes, you're right.
I forgot about that
and actually ate some.
Starting a business
has been taking a toll on me.
Is that the only thing
you've forgotten?
- What?
Ga Hee, Joon Seon,
you're late with this month's rent.
Both of you.
I didn't forget, Dad.
I was just too busy.
I'll wire it over right away.
Ga Hee, what about you?
What?
Right...
Sure, Dad. I'll get it to you soon.
You have until this week.
After that, I'm charging a late fee.
- Got it.
- Sure.
Mom.
What is it?
Do you have something to say?
Yes, can I borrow some money?
Money? I think I have
about 30 dollars.
Gosh, are you kidding me?
I need money for this month's rent.
Things were tight
and I don't have enough left.
I'll pay you back
with even an interest.
I don't have any either.
With what I had left,
I paid for gas
when I went out with Na Hee...
and also the chili a few days back.
What do I do then?
I barely have enough
for my credit card bill.
Could you please put in
a good word to Dad for me?
What are you doing?
Dad...
Well, you see,
things were
a little tight this month.
How so?
Because you were busy
shopping at the department store?
What did you say
when you first moved back here?
You said you'd rather pay rent to us
than to some stranger.
You're the one who said
you won't miss a payment.
Got it.
You should get to work, Dad.
Gosh.
You're the cruelest, you know.
Why can't you cut her
some slack for once?
Once becomes twice and then
it'll add up to 10 occasions.
Staying here for free
will only ruin her.
This isn't a world
you can slack off in.
Right, of course.
Your love for your daughter
is truly impressive.
Sure thing.
What in the world...
Unbelievable.
No.
I'd rather get
kicked out of the house...
than sell them.
Buying these weren't easy.
Limited editions aren't sold
to just anybody,
so I had to keep going back
for them to recognize me.
No, I can't let it go.
(Monthly credit card bill:
1,320 dollars)
That's right.
I forgot I had another card.
Look at how good the photos are.
They're to die for.
Okay.
I'll first upload them onto...
the second-hand
designer outlet website.
How much should I ask for them?
Normally, I'd ask for more
than its original price.
Since I'm urgent though...
(Second-hand Designer Outlet,
Price: 3,000 dollars)
Ok Ja, you're here.
You're here early today.
That's odd.
What do you mean?
Before I went home yesterday,
I neatly sorted out the chairs.
They're a mess right now though
and a used cup is out here.
You probably didn't
clean up properly.
It's not like
those chairs have feet.
That's not it.
I'm sure of it, you know.
I stacked the chairs properly,
cleaned the surface,
turned off the light,
and then went home.
You know how I remember
even the frivolous details.
No theft was committed, okay?
Not that there's anything to take.
Good morning, everyone. Morning.
What brings you to work so early?
Don't you get here around noon?
I was bored, that's all.
I'll sort out the storefront first.
Sure thing.
How diligent of him.
I doubt many young people his age
find their own work to do...
like our Hyo Sin does.
It's uncanny how he's my type
from head to toe.
Didn't you say your dream guy
was Park Bo Gum?
It's as if every man is your type.
Actually, that's not true.
Someone like Yang Chi Su
is definitely not my type.
Don't be like that.
Hate can easily turn into love.
Young Dal, I'd rather
you throw profanities my way.
How could you say
such an evil thing?
How is that a curse?
Mr. Yang is a decent man, you know.
Unlike someone I know,
he's affectionate...
and spends money when he needs to.
Didn't it say it was going to rain?
I guess I brought my umbrella
for nothing.
- Jeong Bong.
- Yes?
Focus!
How can you hold your ground
when someone comes at you...
if you let a sandbag push you back?
Plant your feet on the ground...
and absorb the force.
- Got it.
- Again.
Sure thing.
What's wrong with you two?
Are you still not feeling well?
We're not exactly
back to full strength.
Joon Seon,
I thought we were fine,
but we've been lacking strength
in our legs.
I guess you're not ready
to go back to training.
Taking too much time off
will be worse though.
Still, your health comes first.
You won't be able to train anyway
if you hurt yourselves.
Let's get a bowl of seolleongtang
and go home...
to review the movie we filmed.
That sounds better.
- Seolleongtang?
- It's okay.
We don't deserve
something as fancy.
Seolleongtang-flavored cup noodles
will do.
Don't be ridiculous.
I may not be much of a boss,
but I can still
buy you seolleongtang.
You can have two bowls each today.
- Let's go.
- Two bowls?
It's all right.
One bowl is fine enough.
Yes, I'm on my way.
Of course, it's the real deal.
You'll know once you see it.
Sure. I'll see you soon. Got it.
Suspicious cow.
I didn't know I'd be parting ways
with you so soon.
I hope your new owner cherishes you.
Hold on.
It's you, right?
Don't you remember me?
I'm Mr. Song's eldest daughter.
I see that we haven't
introduced ourselves yet.
I'm Song Ga Hee,
a divorcee of three years.
I see.
What I said is at least worth
a name out of you.
Don't you have one?
It's Park Hyo Sin.
Park Hyo Sin?
Like the singer?
How old are you?
No, wait. Let me guess.
Mid-20s?
No, late-20s!
Yes.
I knew it.
Is it your first time
making food deliveries?
You don't seem comfortable
on the bike.
That's right.
Am I annoying you?
Should I stop talking?
I still have
more deliveries to make.
Deliver them yourself
and I'll be glad to talk.
That's not the case, right?
Prickly jerk.
Young but prickly.
You get a pass
because you're handsome!
She's calling again?
Yes, what's up?
I'm still on my way...
How can I lower the price
another 100 dollars?
You can buy that one instead then.
Whatever. I'm not selling!
She's an outright thief.
Selling this bag is already
breaking my heart enough.
Darn it.
Guys, come downstairs.
No one's home.
- No one's home?
- Really?
Everyone must be out.
Anyway, it's better to watch a movie
on a bigger screen, right?
Look. There I am.
- Where?
- It's over.
There I am. That's me.
- The guy in red?
- No, the one next to him.
It's over.
Hey, I told you.
You have to stall
as long as you can.
At least your acquaintances
should recognize you.
Watch.
When you fall down,
you shouldn't look like this.
Turn your head toward the camera
a little like this.
If you turn it too much,
the director won't like it.
Just turn it a little
at a 35-degree angle.
Do you know what I mean?
It's better to show your face
for two seconds...
than the back of your head
for 10 seconds.
At a 35-degree angle.
It's better to show your face
for two seconds...
than the back of your head
for 10 seconds.
You guys should be shrewder.
You still have a long way to go.
Jeong Bong, go to the fridge
and get me some coke.
I'm thirsty after the lecture.
Okay.
Who are you?
Ga Hee, you're home.
Did you do something wrong?
Why are you stammering?
Who are they?
I see. I must admit
that you're a man of loyalty.
But you should think
of your current situation.
You're practically a freeloader now.
If Dad finds it out,
he won't let it slide.
If things go wrong,
I might end up getting involved.
I know, but I have no choice.
The mold is just killing them.
Gosh, you're so helpless.
I will get them a new place
as soon as I make money.
Just wait until then.
Did you not see their faces?
They look so pathetic.
So if you keep it to yourself...
No. This just isn't right.
I can't keep it a secret.
Hey, Ga Hee.
Why are you being so rash?
Gosh, what are you doing?
All right. Fine.
So how much do you want?
- What?
- We're pros. Let's not do this.
This is all about money.
How much do you want?
Now that you know it,
we don't need to waste time.
- I want 300 dollars.
- Do you have a death wish?
I'm behind on my credit card
bills this month.
I need more money to pay for it,
but I don't want to be
so harsh on you.
It's just for living expenses.
Gosh, this is like daylight robbery.
100 dollars.
- 250.
- 150.
- 200.
300.
Okay. Make it 200.
Can I pay in installments?
Gosh, how much do you have?
I'll go easy on you.
Don't get all upset about it.
We're on a ship
that's about to be wrecked.
I need a life vest.
Consider it danger pay.
Just think that
you got a good companion.
You're so wicked.
- Joon Seon.
- You mean wench.
Oh, yes!
It's been a while.
Are we going to be kicked out?
You must've been quite surprised.
It's okay.
If things don't go well,
we can go back to a sauna.
Jong Soo.
About Joon Seon's sister.
Yes.
Isn't she beautiful?
She's like a goddess.
Really? I don't like tall women.
And her eyes are too big
that they look a little scary.
Right. She's a goddess
with big eyes.
Joon Seon, did it go well?
Yes. Kind of.
I'm glad. Then can we stay here?
Yes.
Your sister is so generous.
Gosh.
If you say that again,
I swear I will kill you.
Okay?
You just stopped your hiccups.
You got rid of it.
Joon Seon, come on down
and have some fruit.
You guys should come too.
I didn't get to say hello earlier.
Let's get along.
Come downstairs.
Na Hee.
Hyun Gyung. Hello, Seo Jin.
Are you going somewhere?
Yes. I'm going out for lunch.
What?
There's your uncle.
Why aren't you eating together?
Our schedules don't match.
I don't have to eat with him.
I should get going then.
Enjoy your lunch.
Have fun at therapy, Seo Jin.
Na Hee.
Call me if you need
someone to talk to.
I can give good counseling
about married life.
Let's go.
(Yongju Traditional Market)
(Unnie's Kimbap)
The rain is pouring down.
I know.
The rain reminds me of the old days.
My first love liked
getting caught in the rain.
Which one? The guy who ran away
with your money?
Gosh, he was nice at heart.
He was just in a tough situation.
Look at you getting angry again.
A naive girl like you always
ends up with a bad guy.
He had a good heart though.
Right. They say to condemn the sin,
but not the sinner.
Isn't that from the Bible?
You're Buddhist.
It doesn't matter whether it's from
the Bible or Buddhist scriptures.
We just need to heed
all good sayings.
The coffee tastes so good.
Cho Yeon, how many rolls of kimbap
did we sell today?
About 25 or so.
The guy from the hardware store
bought 10 to go.
He's been here quite a lot lately.
He might be a frequent customer.
It's nice to have a regular.
Since we're running a diner
in a traditional market,
we should have more regulars.
You should take good care of them.
Okay.
Don't worry about it.
I flattered the hardware store owner
saying he looks about 40.
Well done.
The spring rain is pouring
like it's monsoon season.
I like the sound of rain though.
Spring rain
Spring rain that makes me cry
- That's nice.
- You sound amazing.
Always
Where are you going?
It's raining out there.
Ma'am, I knew you'd be doing this.
You should've brought an umbrella.
Did you not see the news?
I had no time.
- Here.
- Gosh.
If it rains a lot,
just go home early.
It's a loss if you get sick.
I should get going then. Bye.
Gosh, thank you.
Do you want some cucumbers?
No, it's okay.
Cucumbers are expensive these days.
You should sell them.
Bye.
My gosh.
What do I do with them?
I guess she brought
an umbrella today.
She always forgets to bring one.
I hope she won't catch a cold.
My gosh.
Why are you back?
Didn't you go to take
the vegetable lady an umbrella?
She has one already.
What's up with her?
She always forgets to bring it.
She would rather bring more carrots
instead of an umbrella.
So she always gets caught
in the rain.
I know.
Where's Hyo Sin?
Is he out for delivery?
Yes. We are getting a lot of
delivery orders because of the rain.
He's quite nimble and taciturn.
I'm glad that we started delivery.
It's good enough to offset his pay.
It's good that our sales are rising,
but it's a serious problem
that people are growing lazy.
They should do some legwork.
All they do is
just move some fingers.
Then they would pay money
and join a gym to lose weight.
Why would they spend
double the money?
Walking around is good exercise.
It's just how the world changes.
Stop worrying about someone
else's money and fry chickens.
We're running out already.
Where's Ok Ja?
I don't know.
She was feeling sleepy,
so she went out for vitamin drinks,
but she hasn't come back.
She's just busy
meddling in everything.
That's because she's healthy.
If she was healthier,
she would never come back.
She always chatters away
without getting married.
I just hope she gets a crush
on someone and marries him.
Gosh. She's waited
for such a long time.
She can't just marry anyone.
Actually, she is
quite picky about men.
I know.
I mean she can't afford to be picky.
Why would she care about looks?
It's just useless.
And she doesn't like older guys
because they look old.
She's so immature and childish.
Gosh, she's unbelievable.
My ears are burning.
Is someone talking about me?
Why is it so itchy?
It's Ok Ja. Ok Ja!
You saved me.
If not for you,
I'd be completely drenched.
That would look bad.
Where are you headed?
- What?
- Where are you headed?
I'm going to the supermarket.
Then drop me off at my store.
I'll buy you coffee later.
Okay. Why not?
Thank you so very much.
Let's go!
Do you feel cold?
Then drink some hot water
at my store.
No. I'm okay.
I'm fine.
Jeong Bong.
You should go to a pharmacy.
Why won't your hiccups stop?
No. I'm okay.
Let's get along.
Okay.
(Hiccup)
Welcome...
Welcome.
One iced americano.
You're paying by card.
You said "for one day".
Here's your iced americano.
You don't eat for 16 hours.
16 hours, 8 hours.
You divide the day
into 16 hours and 8 hours.
- Give me some cold water.
- Pardon?
Oh, okay.
For 20 hours...
First. The look in your eyes.
The second part is
about how you speak.
You must always be firm.
A firm tone.
Excuse me?
What?
As that sign says,
you must get your own water.
I'd be grateful
if you got it yourself.
What?
That's our rule.
And also,
you could inconvenience
other customers.
Please use earphones.
Okay.
I had to get my own water?
You should've said so.
Thank you.
Hey. I'm outside my place.
Tripe? What's the occasion?
You got a bonus?
Then I must come and eat.
I'll be right there.
- Mr. Yoon!
- My gosh.
- You startled me.
- Congratulate me.
How did you know I was here?
I was watching from inside.
- Mr. Yoon. I did it.
- Do what?
That customer, the suede bag woman.
She came back.
And she asked me to bring her water.
So I glared at her and firmly said,
"Get your own water."
She went and got the water
and she didn't complain either!
You did great.
See? It works if you try.
Mr. Yoon, are you off work?
To thank you, I'll buy you a drink.
Okay. We must celebrate. Let's go.
- Here you go.
- Thank you.
- Goodbye.
Gyu Jin.
Bo Young.
Are you leaving work?
I almost missed you.
I was going to call.
I'm meeting someone.
Oh, is he getting discharged?
I had no idea.
I thought it would be
a few more days,
but Dr. Song said she thinks
he can go home today.
He got better much quicker here
than at the other hospital.
Your wife's a great doctor.
Yes.
- Where's Si Hoo?
- With the nurses.
They finally became friends
and now they must part.
It's a good thing.
The shorter you stay here,
the better.
I guess so.
Still, it's a bit upsetting.
We met after a long time.
We can always meet up again.
Let's meet elsewhere next time.
With people from the church.
Okay, let's do that.
- Gyu Jin?
- What?
I want to thank you.
I'll call.
Okay.
Say bye to Si Hoo for me.
I will.
Wait, Gyu Jin.
Ms. Song.
Cheers.
On a day like this,
we must drink outside.
Yes. The weather is just amazing.
It's strange.
I thought that
if I talked to a customer like that,
I'd feel uncomfortable,
but I felt so good.
It's oddly cathartic.
Now I'm worried.
What if this catches on
and you become outspoken and snarky?
Like Na Hee?
Yes. Like Na Hee.
Well, I like Na Hee,
but you should be yourself.
It's boring if you're like her.
You can change just a bit.
Just say what you must.
Anyway, thank you so much.
It'll be a great help in life.
You're welcome.
Cheers.
I get this impression
whenever we meet,
but you have a great personality.
I'm envious.
I turned out this way
despite having the mom that I have,
so I guess I am a great guy.
Why? I like Ms. Choi.
She's very sensitive.
Sensitive?
That's a good way of putting it.
She's too moody.
She's really nice when she's happy,
but if something upsets her
even a little bit,
she throws punches.
You're right.
She was in a bad mood all day today.
Yesterday, she was happy,
and she talked a lot,
and even suggested we share a cake.
See?
That's why...
I fled to Turkey.
She smothers you with love,
and then with anger.
Gyu Jin is sweeter than me,
so he goes along with it.
It's too much for me.
It's because she's too lonely.
Be a little nicer to her.
I want to, but it's hard.
I keep wanting to run away.
If you don't get along,
you can just live apart.
I read somewhere that even parents
and kids have a compatibility count.
If that count is low,
it's much better to live apart.
I want to live apart.
She dragged me home.
It's all because I helped keep
Gyu Jin and Na Hee's divorce secret.
What?
What did you say?
Gyu Jin and Na Hee did what?
Oh, I don't know.
What did I just say?
I'm so tired that I spoke nonsense.
Gyu Jin and Na Hee are divorced?
I...
lied to you.
The truth is,
Si Hoo has no dad.
I had him alone.
I never found that shameful,
but I just couldn't tell you.
I don't know why.
You became a doctor...
and have a beautiful wife.
I felt so shabby.
Maybe that's why.
To be honest, even right now,
I feel embarrassed.
This is unbelievable.
Are they in a romance movie?
For what reason?
You really shouldn't be.
It's not like...
my life is any better.
Actually, I...
Na Hee!
Jae Hyung, are you all right?
(Epilogue)
Does anyone have a handkerchief?
He's bleeding too much.
We should take him to the infirmary.
Here. Let me.
I'll take that.
Are you all right?
I need dressing...
Well...
Doesn't anyone have a bandage?
Could someone
please call an ambulance?
Seong Gyun,
is Gyu Jin perhaps inside?
He said he'd meet me here.
No, he's not.
Maybe you should call him.
Right.
Bo Young, practice will begin soon.
You should come inside.
Sure.
You did well, Na Hee.
You were quite calm yourself.
It wasn't as impressive
as your fast-thinking.
Are you okay though?
The skirt looks expensive.
It's cheap.
If it weren't, I would've ripped
your shirt instead.
Since I sacrificed my skirt,
you should buy me a meal.
I'm hungry, you know.
(Once Again)
This is absolutely insane!
How are they going to explain this?
I'm dead
if they find out I told you.
My brother is super scary
when he's angry.
The real doctors argue about...
which treatments are the best.
Let us introduce you
to our new panel of doctors.
That's right.
They're on "Doctors".
He's my son
and she's my daughter-in-law.
- Goodness.
- How nice.
No, this can't be true.
Calm down, my beating heart.
Is this the dance sports class?
I'm here to take lessons too.