Ga Hee, Joon Seon.
It's too late to do this.
Last One, you stay here.
Yes. Don't tip off Na Hee
or Mom and Dad.
Na Hee got divorced!
What?
Na Hee and Gyu Jin got divorced.
Not too long ago.
What...
They did what?
Did you just say they got divorced?
What nonsense are you spewing?
Why would they get divorced?
Maybe you got it wrong.
Are you sure they got divorced?
Yes, and it's been a while too.
I think it was around the time
I got my annulment.
No way.
You've got to be kidding me.
Are you saying that those two
have been putting on a show then?
Unbelievable.
Those cheeky rats.
Meanwhile, Mom has been
cooking food for them...
and sending over side dishes.
They been accepting her generosity
even though they're divorced?
Those jerks.
Joon Seon, please don't.
Calm down for a second.
How can I right now? Move!
Joon Seon, don't.
I shouldn't be telling a soul,
but I only did
because you two were about to...
make a huge mistake.
So please keep it down.
She's right.
We shouldn't get
all worked up like this.
Let's calm down.
What am I supposed to do then?
Keep it down!
What were they thinking?
How can they keep
their divorce a secret?
Mom had a hard time
processing my annulment.
It's probably why they didn't think
it was the right time.
Na Hee acts like she cares
about dearly about Mom,
but she has a funny way
of showing it.
I get why she couldn't tell Mom,
but what about us?
She should've at least told us.
I'm her brother, you know.
I may have a lame life,
but I'm the oldest in the family!
Joon Seon, lower your voice.
Mom will hear you.
Na Hee, that brat.
And why did she agree
to be on a TV show?
She has no idea
how scary this world can be.
I can't take it anymore.
Those jerks...
Joon Seon, please!
Gosh.
Enough with that temper of yours.
You've got to be kidding me.
Let's keep it to ourselves
until Na Hee tells us, okay?
I'm sure she won't
drag this out for too long.
Da Hee's right.
I'm sure Na Hee has a plan.
Let's see how things go for now.
Fine. No, no can do.
Those brats...
- Joon Seon!
- Joon Seon, please.
- Get off me.
- Joon Seon...
- No...
- All right, fine.
I won't go, so let go of me.
- Let's head inside then.
- Hands off.
I'll get going, Mom.
They're all packed
in small portions,
so freeze them
as soon as you get home.
Let them defrost before having it...
and serve it boiling.
- Got it?
- I got it.
You've already told me that anyway.
Are you leaving already?
Are you leaving?
I'm exhausted, so I'd like to rest.
If only Gyu Jin was here
to drive you home.
Will he get off work late?
He's the on-call doctor tonight,
so he'll be staying at the hospital.
On-call, my foot.
Joon Seon, you seem
to be in a sour mood.
Are you upset about something?
He's just stressed out from
getting his business off the ground.
You should get going.
- Off you go.
- I'll get going then.
Let me catch a cab for you.
You'll see her out? Bye, Na Hee!
- That little brat...
- Joon Seon, stop it.
- Stop!
- Joon Seon, stop.
We told you to stay put.
You're like a ticking time bomb.
All right, I'll stay calm.
Why did she have to pack so much?
Mom...
You should eat with me.
Mom packed heap portions
of beef bone soup.
I'll heat it up, so have a seat.
What's gotten into you?
You said I shouldn't eat
anything from your mom.
They go to waste.
Besides, she didn't pack them
just for me anyway.
The stir-fried chili
and pickled cucumber are for you.
They're your favorite.
It's good.
Of course.
My mom made it, didn't she?
Clear your soup too.
I want nothing but an empty bowl.
Standing all day
while boiling the beef bone soup...
took a toll on my back.
I bet you feel great...
that you were able to feed
Na Hee and Gyu Jin though.
Of course I'm happy.
Just so you know,
I'm done wishing for anything big.
All I want is for Na Hee
to keep living a good life...
and have the others
do things that satisfy them.
That's enough, right?
That is one big decision.
If only you had
thought so in the past.
Honey, you know that it's
your birthday in two days, right?
Why's that important?
A birthday is what everyone has.
Still, I'm inviting
the merchants from the market...
to celebrate it,
so don't be against the party.
As the president,
you should have these parties,
not only attend those for others.
Don't be ridiculous.
All I need to eat
is a bowl of seaweed soup.
I know what you're really after.
You want a reason...
to invite the merchants
from the associations...
so that you can boast about
Na Hee and Gyu Jin.
And I know what's exactly
on that mind of yours too.
Every year on your birthday,
you become depressed...
and forbid us from
mentioning parties.
That's all because
of your sister, right?
You've mourned her enough.
Enjoy your good days
and let others...
congratulate you now.
I'm now going to do
everything I want...
and celebrate your birthday.
Your father's birthday
is tomorrow, right?
What was that, Mom?
I'm inviting the merchants
to his birthday dinner,
so be there as well.
Really? Did Dad agree to that?
- That's odd.
- Tell me about it.
He used to yell at you...
for making special dishes
on his birthday.
That takes me back
to what happened last year.
Dad almost bit my head off
for buying him a strawberry cake.
He said that I spend money
on useless things...
and only those privileged
should eat 50-dollar cakes.
Well, I managed
to persuade him this time.
So help me out in the afternoon.
- Got it.
- Sure.
- I should get there early.
- Hold on.
My gosh, Gyu Jin!
Mother, it's me.
I enjoyed the beef bone soup
you sent over yesterday.
The side dishes
were delicious as well.
Did you already have some?
The chilies had
a grassy smell to them though.
Really? Well, I enjoyed them a lot.
Thank you so much, Mother.
It's fine.
Always let me know if you want more.
Of course.
You know it's your father-in-law's
birthday tomorrow, right?
We're having a feast at the market,
so swing by.
Right, of course.
You have a show today, right?
Good luck with that.
So much for your weekend.
I'll see you tomorrow then.
Take care.
What did he say?
Will Gyu Jin be there?
Of course he will.
Did he actually say
that he'd be there?
Yes, of course.
Why wouldn't he be
at your dad's birthday party?
It's his birthday.
Those jerks are unbelievable.
What's with that response?
It's nothing, Mom.
Gyu Jin keeps acting
like he's busy, that's all.
I'm glad that he'll be there though.
He's not faking his busy hours.
He's been working late often
as well.
Did you see his gaunt face?
Na Hee must not be
serving him proper food.
Why is that Na Hee's job?
Should she be feeding him too?
Also, stop being
so sweet on Gyu Jin all the time.
He's not your son, you know.
I, Song Joon Seon, am your son!
Why on earth did these drop?
What's gotten him in
a sour mood this morning?
Has his business
not been doing well?
Tell me about it.
Ga Hee will keep quiet,
but I'm worried about Joon Seon.
Should I come clean
with Gyu Jin's brother?
(Mr. Yoon)
I can't.
Mr. Yoon, I'm sorry...
I'm too nervous
to sit through class.
Ok Ja, are you waiting for someone?
What? No, of course not.
I was wondering
when Ok Boon would be here.
She went to buy groceries,
so she'll be a while.
Why do people even
celebrate birthdays?
Ok Ja, cut it out.
She'll get here when she's done.
Is it because you're hungry?
Yes, I skipped my breakfast today.
We can't eat until
Ok Boon gets here, right?
Honey, can you take this from me?
Gosh, it's heavy.
- It's too heavy.
- What on earth did you buy?
Goodness, that's heavy.
What is this?
What on earth?
Did you seriously buy
a box of these expensive abalones?
Do you have any idea
how much this costs?
Don't ask for you might
have a heart attack.
A feast needs
one special dish to be complete.
I'm baking them with butter.
The ladies absolutely love those.
Buttered abalones?
The money you must've spent...
Can you stop worrying
about the money...
for at least once a year?
You're unbelievable.
Ok Ja, what on earth
are you wearing?
Where's your apron?
Are you going somewhere nice today?
No, I just felt like
wearing this today.
There's only...
a limited amount of time
to wear spring clothes.
It'll be uncomfortable, you know.
At least wear an apron.
Let's eat first
and then get everything rolling.
Sure thing.
Ok Ja was starving
and she has been waiting for you.
Really?
He hasn't been around much
these days.
Before, he'd always stop by
when it was time to eat.
Who? You mean Chi Su?
I don't know.
He's been awfully busy lately.
He hasn't been around because
you keep voicing your hatred.
There's only so much
someone can take.
Are you really
giving this to us for free?
Of course.
I always hand out leftovers
to my neighbors.
I'm not one to make a fuss
over chump change.
This doesn't seem
like leftovers to me.
It weighs at least a kilogram.
Yes, that's not a small portion.
And it's beef! My gosh.
I have an abundance of beef,
you know.
Anyway, this is premium sirloin,
so make sure to grill them.
There's just enough fat in that,
so it's perfect for grilling
and it won't make you gain weight.
My gosh. I'm truly grateful.
I was wrong to think that
I didn't have any decent neighbors.
This isn't about
just being a giving person.
Only those with good hearts
are this generous.
You're too kind.
While we're on the subject,
you should know that
I own more than one store.
I have another one nearby.
Korean barbecue is offered there
and my brother runs it.
And the one in Suwon
is run by my sister.
However, they're all in my name.
My gosh. You're a meat tycoon.
You're quite a successful man.
Let me know anytime
if you need more meat.
I'll bring it over right away.
I love meat, you know.
No way!
Mr. Yang, just a second.
I can't receive this
without giving anything in return.
Have a seat
and I'll get you a roll of kimbap.
Why not?
It's not like I wanted
anything in return...
Please have a seat.
Goodness.
- Good job today.
- Thank you.
- Good job.
- That was great.
- Good job, everyone.
- Good job.
Good job today.
You both did great too.
I guess I was less nervous today.
Me too.
But that wasn't the case
for a certain someone.
Me?
I was extremely nervous, you know.
If I weren't, I would've
ripped you apart on stage.
Guys, save the quarrel
for when you get home...
and join me for lunch today.
Don't tell me
you'll decline today as well.
Enjoy. We'll order more
if it's not enough.
It's hard to divide the shrimps
since there are only four.
You're buying today,
so you can take one extra.
Sure. Thanks for that.
I won't decline.
All right.
So how has life as an outcast
been treating you?
Well, it's not the first time
I've been ostracized.
Come to think of it,
I was like that in middle school
and high school too.
I never had many friends.
Judging by your personality,
it's not a surprise.
It's all right.
This world needs
people like you anyway.
Our show would've been boring
without you.
So keep it up
and don't change anything.
Also, don't mind the hate comments.
What? Hate comments?
("Doctors" passes
8 percent in ratings!)
That lady is so annoying.
You'd get sick
living with a woman like that.
The lady doctor is scary.
I feel bad for the husband.
Doctor Song Na Hee
thinks this is her own talk show.
Are you kidding me?
Who are they to say
that I make them sick?
It's not like I'm doing anything
to harm them.
Unbelievable.
Why would you voluntarily read that?
They'll only hurt your mentality.
You should've told me
about their harsh reactions though.
Why? Are you going to press charges?
I will if there's a need to.
This is a social issue, you know.
Anonymity doesn't give you the right
to talk smack about people.
They're killing me with their words.
You're not entirely wrong,
but your words are
just as harsh as theirs...
on and off TV.
It's why you should've
watched your words.
You didn't hold back as always...
which resulted in hurtful comments.
Even I would've chimed in.
Did you?
No.
You did, didn't you?
Of course not.
Why would I write hate comments?
I'm a civilized person, you know.
This accusation is absurd.
- Let me see.
- What are you doing?
Don't you look at my phone.
I'm going to see
if you wrote any comments.
I didn't! I only pressed
the like button next to a few.
Are you satisfied?
What? You pressed the like button?
Are you kidding me?
Darn it.
Hey!
No. This is wrong.
I'm sorry.
- That hurts.
- Why did you suddenly stop?
That's because Joon Seon said no.
Were we doing things wrong?
Keep training, okay?
I'm heading out.
Where are you headed?
See you later then.
- Jong Soo.
- Yes?
Let's try that again. Take that!
That hurts!
It wasn't on purpose, you know.
It hurts, doesn't it?
You did it on purpose.
- Of course I didn't.
- Get back here.
Do you like the pizza I bought?
It's good, isn't it?
Yes, it's delicious.
Skipping lessons was worth it.
Thanks, Auntie.
Did you come into
some money recently?
Yes.
But this is probably
the last time...
I'll be comfortably
buying you pizza.
Call it the calm before the storm
because that's how I feel.
Dad?
Hi, girls.
Uncle Joon Seon, have some pizza.
Mom ordered it.
I'm good, Ji Hun.
You guys can finish it off.
Ga Hee.
Why? What's up?
This is just wrong.
How can we pretend
to not know anything?
Does that make sense to you?
I'm upset about it too,
but what can we do?
We'll go to Na Hee and...
And do what?
Talk some sense into her.
We'll talk to Gyu Jin too.
Don't. Persuading them won't help.
Was that the case
for you and Hyun Gyung?
That wasn't the case
for me and Ji Hun's father.
Then we'll tell the truth.
Isn't that what we
should at least do?
How are you going to handle
Mom and Dad later on?
I can barely make it through the day
and this anxiety is killing me.
Of course I'm worried
about what's to come.
I'm reminded of
what happened three years ago.
I'm most curious
about Na Hee's thoughts.
I want to know
why she's putting on a show.
I've been wondering about that too.
She's not the type
to do anything irrational.
Right? So let's meet up
with Na Hee and ask.
Shall we?
Okay, let's go to her.
We're her older siblings, right?
We can ask that much.
Let's go. Move. Okay.
Let's go.
- Da Hee.
Where are you two going?
- What?
- What's the matter?
Where are you going?
What are you doing here
at this time of the day?
- What about training?
- Well... I was just...
We have to go see Na Hee.
We can't just sit on our hands.
We are her sister and brother.
No, you can't.
I promised the person who told me
that I'd keep it to myself.
I don't think this is an issue
that we can solve.
And you know what Na Hee is like.
If she finds out that you know,
she might just drop a bomb
right away.
Tomorrow is Dad's birthday.
Do you really have to do this now?
Oh, right. It's Dad's birthday.
This isn't right.
We can't drop a bomb
on Dad's birthday.
Hey, you just keep
changing your words.
I thought you had a point earlier,
but what Da Hee says
sounds about right now.
I know. Joon Seon,
we can do this later.
Just wait until
Dad's birthday is over.
Mom is busy ordering rice cake
and preparing food.
This isn't the right time.
Am I supposed to see them pretending
not to know anything tomorrow?
I can do some acting.
I should tell myself.
I don't know anything.
I know nothing.
- I don't know.
- Right.
Joon Seon,
you need to relax a little.
You don't know anything, okay?
Forget it!
My goodness.
Ms. Choi, I'm back.
You're here.
Look. Isn't this beautiful?
It's lilac.
Oh, it's lilac.
It is pretty. And it smells good.
Do you know what lilac means?
First love.
Beautiful memories of youth.
Isn't it just perfect
for the flower?
Youth that's sad but beautiful.
And first love.
Come to think of it,
you are just like this lilac.
You're young and beautiful.
You are a lot more
beautiful than I am.
You are dignified and elegant.
I can tell that you don't mean it.
That's not true. I really mean it.
Is it because you like flowers?
You are just like a flower.
I'm just like a withered flower.
Oh, right.
Tomorrow is your father's birthday.
I heard there will be a party.
You should take tomorrow off.
I will take care of the shop.
Are you serious?
Can I really do that?
Sure.
And this is your paycheck.
I put in some extra for this month.
Gosh, I thought
I'd get it next week.
Thank you so much.
Actually, I didn't have enough money
to buy my dad a birthday gift.
Now I can buy something expensive.
I'll be upstairs then.
Okay.
Ms. Song, hi.
Hello. You're home early.
Yes. Mom isn't here.
Ms. Song, when you get off work,
how about we grab a beer?
On the steps?
No. I have a lot to study today.
That's too bad.
All right then.
Study hard!
I'm sorry that I didn't
keep the secret, Mr. Yoon.
You can blame me for that later.
I'm so sorry.
Other kids are so devoted
to their parents.
She was so happy to buy
her father something expensive.
Is it because she's a daughter?
She's so sweet.
Hello, Mom.
I'm home.
Jae Seok.
Do you know when my birthday is?
Mom, are you kidding me?
It's August.
Wrong.
Is it July?
Wrong again.
It wasn't summer. I know that.
October?
November?
You punk.
Do you even know my name?
- Go away!
- My gosh.
You fool.
Why am I a fool?
- I love you.
- Hey!
Why don't you come...
and have dinner here tomorrow?
It's my husband's birthday,
so I will prepare some food.
You always told me
to throw a birthday party.
So is it Mr. Song's BP?
BP? What's that?
A birthday party. It's a BP.
Right. It's a birthday party.
So please come and have dinner.
Are your daughter and son-in-law
from the TV show coming too?
I want to take a picture with them.
Of course.
It's not like they are celebrities.
Now that they are on TV,
we can call them celebrities.
My daughter told me
that they are quite popular.
Gosh, she didn't really mean it.
Hello, Ms. Kang.
Please come and have dinner
with us tomorrow night.
It's my husband's birthday.
Oh, it's his birthday.
I'll be glad to be here.
I'll bring the girls too.
Okay.
Hello, everyone. You all are early.
- Hello.
- Hi.
Is she here yet?
Oh, there she is.
Hello, Cho Yeon.
Hello. Oh, right.
You left this at our store
Gosh, I totally forgot.
I looked all over for it.
Thank you, Cho Yeon.
No problem.
I really enjoyed the meat
you gave me.
It melted in my mouth.
- It was so soft.
- Soft.
- Hey.
- What?
Did you have lunch
at her kimbap restaurant?
Well... I just dropped in on my way.
And what about the meat?
She means she liked the meat
she bought the other day.
Go ahead and warm up.
And stop staring at me like that.
7 and 8.
1, cha-cha. 2, cha-cha.
3, cha-cha. 4, cha-cha.
2, cha-cha. 3, cha-cha.
- 1, cha-cha. 2, cha-cha.
- My goodness.
I'm sorry.
I got my steps twisted.
My gosh.
It's okay.
You didn't do it on purpose.
(Birthday, Grandpa)
(Hello, Grandpa. This is Seo Young.)
(Happy birthday to you.)
(Hello, Grandpa. This is Ji Hun.)
You've got a lot of nerve,
Joon Seon.
What if Mom and Dad come home early?
We have to eat dinner anyway.
We will go upstairs soon.
If you haven't had dinner,
you are welcome to join us.
We had pizza earlier.
And I don't want to eat
from the same pot with you.
- Darn it.
- My goodness.
You startled me.
You nearly gave me a heart attack!
What?
It's just a joke.
I'm fine.
Why are you being like this?
We should pretend
not to know anything.
How are we supposed to see Na Hee
and Gyu Jin's faces tomorrow?
I don't think
I can keep it a secret.
It's hard for me too.
I'm not good at hiding things.
But we have no choice.
We should do some acting
and play innocent.
What about Na Hee? Why?
It's nothing. It's grown-up stuff.
Just finish your letters.
I'm so curious.
Can I just hear what it is
and pretend I didn't?
Just finish your letter.
Anyway, we have to try our best.
Whatever.
Hey, did you eat it all already?
Gosh, you jerks.
Stop.
Give me that.
Jeong Bong, bring some rice.
I'll eat it with rice.
Gosh, you're humming.
Are you that excited?
Yes, I am.
You are the president
of the merchant association.
We should've done this sooner.
It's your birthday party.
It's not about my birthday.
You are just excited
to brag about Na Hee and Gyu Jin.
That's why you can't stop smiling.
I've lived with you
for over 30 years.
Gosh, it's not like that.
I don't care.
Don't brag.
People might get jealous.
I don't brag.
I'm just proud of my children.
See? You just told the truth.
My goodness.
Gosh, wait. Oh, no.
What's wrong?
Did you forget something?
I was charging my phone
and left it in the store.
What was I thinking?
I'll be right back.
Okay.
It's dark in the alley.
Watch your step.
Okay.
Who's there? Who are you?
Mr. Song.
What...
Why...
You've been sleeping here
since you started working here?
Yes. I apologize, sir.
Forget about that.
How can you
not have a place to stay?
There are studio apartments
and saunas everywhere.
It looks you've been
doing this for a while.
Where's your home?
Don't you have a family?
Oh, dear.
I know you're displeased.
If you want me gone, I'll leave.
You must leave.
You can't stay here forever.
Clean up and pack your things.
Come in.
The building is old,
so it'll be cold and drafty.
But wouldn't it be much better than
sleeping on stools in a cold store?
Yes. Thank you, sir.
Watch the steps.
There's already a tenant,
but the room is big enough
for two grown men.
He's a fool, but he's not evil,
so don't worry.
Mr. Song.
I can't stay for free.
You can deduct my pay...
Be quiet. If you disrupt my business
because you lack sleep,
that's my loss.
That's why I'm doing this.
Don't say a word and work hard.
Now follow me.
- We haven't started yet.
- We have started.
Come in.
My goodness.
Who are you?
We're...
Guys, I stole some mandarins.
Are you in your right mind or not?
How can you let them stay
when you barely support yourself?
Is this your house?
It's not. I know very well it's not.
Dad.
They quit with me
when I left the stunt team.
They had nowhere to stay
and I couldn't ignore their plight.
Don't you start!
This is insane.
I told you to stop saying,
"I couldn't ignore their plight."
Because you can't ignore anything,
you lost your home and got divorced!
Does loyalty feed you?
Does it pay
for your kids' education?
Didn't I tell you to
fend for yourself?
You idiot.
I'm sorry.
Thank you for everything, Joon Seon.
I won't forget what you did for us.
I didn't do anything,
so forget about it.
Call when you find
a sauna or inn to stay at.
Yes, Joon Seon.
We were a nuisance to the end.
I apologize.
You weren't a nuisance.
I should apologize to you.
I brought you into this place
where you could barely breathe.
You couldn't even
go to the toilet at night.
You should train to do stunts
and I only fed you vegetables.
I wanted to feed you meat
on my father's birthday,
and you couldn't even eat that.
It's okay, Joon Seon.
You thought of us
and that's good enough.
What a joke.
Are you three shooting a movie?
Ga Hee.
Thank you for everything you did.
Ma'am. Your side dishes.
They were delicious.
I had no idea that you ate any.
Yes, but thank you anyway.
Before we leave,
we'd like to bow to you.
Take our bow.
You don't need to bow.
It's fine. Just go on your ways.
Mom, just accept their bow.
Accept our bow, ma'am.
We want to thank you.
I'll bow with them.
What on earth is this bow...
Go back up and unpack.
- Pardon?
- It's just for a while.
Once you save up by doing stunts,
you move out!
- Dad.
- Thank you, sir!
Thank you so much, sir!
We did it! We found a way out!
Song Joon Seon!
Starting this month,
you pay 1.5 times in expenses, okay?
Dad, that's not right.
1.5 times is too much.
Dad, forget that hike
and I'll be good to you.
Gosh, no!
Dad, I'll pay the 0.5 extra.
- Let's work hard, okay?
- Yes.
- Work hard.
- My gosh.
Do you have something to say?
Yes. How old are you?
Why do you ask?
Just to get our age difference.
How about a girlfriend?
Do you have one? You must.
Yes. I do.
How old is she? Is she a student?
Is she okay with you
delivering food?
I don't mind.
No wonder
I couldn't find you anywhere.
What are you doing up here?
Don't mind me, Auntie.
I'm hitting on a guy.
My goodness.
You're hitting on someone?
You know what I'm talking about.
I like this guy.
We met, haven't we?
I'm sorry. She's brazen for her age.
She loses her mind
when she sees handsome guys.
That's you, Auntie.
I value style over looks.
They're the same thing.
Shouldn't you go home?
A teenager must sleep to grow.
And you must sleep early
to prevent wrinkles from forming.
Shall I tell your mom
you skipped class to come here?
That's not fair!
Don't be silly, Auntie.
Threaten me and I'll tell Grandpa
that you have your shopping...
delivered to my place.
How dare you talk back to your aunt?
I'm sorry,
but could you please leave?
I'd like to change.
We should get out
if you're to change. Right.
Let's go.
See you again.
I'll come by the store tomorrow.
Goodbye.
You can change now.
Come in and unpack.
What should I do about that fool?
How can he run a business
when he's so soft?
Why are you smiling?
He takes after you. Don't blame him.
Who? How does he take after me?
Being soft.
Not being able to say no.
That's all you.
Who brought Hyo Sin here?
You're the only one who doesn't see
Joon Seon is like you.
Should I bring them more bedding?
Let them fend for themselves.
(Episode 22)
Here comes the soup!
Is this how it'll be from now on?
Will we have to gather around
to eat breakfast?
Don't be ridiculous.
They're part of the family now,
so we should at least
have breakfast together.
It's Mr. Song's birthday,
so I cooked seaweed soup with beef.
I hope you enjoy it. Now, eat up.
Honey, you should eat the most.
Happy birthday, Mr. Song.
Always be healthy, sir.
Happy birthday, Dad.
Happy birthday.
Happy birthday, Grandpa.
Happy birthday, Mr. Song.
Having a bigger family
sure has its perks.
Thanks, everyone. Now, eat up.
- Sure. Thank you.
- Let's eat.
Will the party take place
at the merchant association lounge?
Yes, and the food
should be delivered in advance.
Ga Hee, lend me a hand.
Joon Seon, go to the fish market
and buy some raw fish.
Halibut and rockfish would do.
- Okay.
- Got it, Mom.
I'll get there as soon
as my class ends.
Ms. Choi let me have the day off...
so that I can attend Dad's party.
Gosh, how grateful.
These days,
she's been the best in-law ever.
In-law, my foot.
It's nice to finally
celebrate Dad's birthday.
Tell me about it.
Honey, finish off your meal today,
and don't leave a drop
of that seaweed soup.
Must you nag me on my birthday?
Okay, fine. I'll eat it all.
Ms. Jang.
The marinated crabs are to die for.
They're awesome.
You must like marinated crabs.
Let me get some more for you.
- No, that's all right.
- Thank you!
I mean, we're good.
It's okay.
There are a lot, so eat up.
What else should I bring out?
Gatkimchi and soy braised beans.
- Hold on a second.
- But there's a lot left here.
It's fine.
Mom is too generous
for her own good.
Are you heading up there again?
Yes.
Don't be late though.
The birthday boy shouldn't
be late to his own party.
I won't. I'll just say hello.
Pick up your phone
and don't put it in silent mode.
Got it.
That reminds me.
I was going to call Na Hee.
Hi, Mom.
You know about your dad's
birthday party today, right?
Be there on time with Gyu Jin.
Mom, what if we just
went by the house after it's over?
Must we say hello
to all your guests?
Of course.
It's your duty as our children.
Besides, the ladies at the market...
have been dying
to take photos with you.
You're practically
celebrities to them.
That's ridiculous.
Anyway, I got it.
We'll head there after our shift.
Na Hee.
What time are we expected
at your father's birthday party?
Sometime around dinner, I guess.
We'll take my car.
Call me when your shift ends.
Right.
That's odd.
He never offers
to go to these things before I ask.
So...
I was too flustered yesterday
to say anything to you.
We should at least exchange names.
Fate brought us together, right?
Anyway, I'm Oh Jeong Bong.
And I'm Lee Jong Soo.
It's good to meet you.
I'm Park Hyo Sin.
I hope we get along well.
Can I ask how old you are?
I'm 28.
28?
Since I'm 30,
I'll stop addressing you formally.
Jong Soo is a year older than you,
so be super polite.
Sure thing.
You probably figured it out by now,
but we've been learning
stunts from Joon Seon.
We'll soon be like Bruce Lee
from "Shaolin Temple".
It was Jet Li who starred
in "Shaolin Temple".
Hey. Seriously?
Jet Li starred in "Fist Of Fury".
We've been stuntmen for 10 years,
you know.
Jeong Bong is a smart man.
He graduated from a decent school.
Don't you dare.
Bruce Lee was the one
in "Fist Of Fury".
When that movie was released,
Jet Li was only a kid.
Everyone who loves martial arts
knows this by heart.
No, that can't be.
Jong Soo, look it up.
Sure thing.
What...
Jet Li was the one
who starred in "Shaolin Temple".
Is that so? Let me see.
I wonder why I got that mixed up.
Look up "Fist Of Fury" too.
Was Bruce Lee in that one?
In what year was that released?
In 1973.
Okay, I got that mixed up too.
I admit that I was confused.
Let's start working out now.
(Song Young Suk,
Born March 19, 1967)
Young Suk,
it's my birthday today.
I came by to hear you
wish me a happy birthday.
You should be the one
who comes to me, you know.
I can't believe you'd make me...
come all the way up here
on my birthday.
Young Suk?
Young Suk!
Ma'am, have you seen my sister?
I haven't.
I saw Young Suk.
Did you? Where is she?
Over there.
Get some gum. I have gum.
What are you doing here?
Who told you to do this?
I've been looking
everywhere for you.
Who told you to do this?
I asked if I could just for today.
I begged...
Why? For what reason?
It's your birthday.
It's your birthday today.
You wanted to buy this for me?
Because I love sweet red bean buns?
Thanks, Young Suk.
I promise to earn a lot of money
so that we can stuff ourselves...
with sweet red bean buns...
on my birthday and yours.
Promise.
Here I am aging year after year
when I never got...
to keep that promise.
I should've bought it for you
in any way I could back then.
I can't believe I was never able to.
It's already been eight years
since I joined this temple.
All this time though,
you haven't been able...
to let her go
from deep inside your heart.
Well, it's easier said than done.
I can't shake it off since I'm
the one who led her to her death.
Just so you know,
it's my birthday today,
but I haven't been able
to celebrate it.
I felt terrible for only being
the one that keeps on aging.
Still, my family has been upset
because of it though.
Please go ahead.
The tea has been brewed perfectly.
Everyone we encounter
in this world...
is like the tea leaf in your teacup.
It always drifts back toward you.
Those who you're bound to meet
will show up in your life somehow.
I sometimes just swallow
the tea leaf, you know.
I let it be if it gets caught...
in my throat.
I'm finding it hard
to remember her face now.
If she had been alive,
she would've become
a beautiful lady.
Two rolls of beef kimbap, right?
- Please enjoy.
- Thank you.
We'll order another
roll of tuna kimbap.
Cho Yeon, one roll of tuna kimbap.
Okay, one extra roll of tuna kimbap!
Gosh, you guys are on a roll today.
Mr. Yang, you're here again.
A few chunks of meat
didn't sell today.
It's a rump steak.
Instead of grilling it,
make a dish of raw beef.
You'll love it.
I love raw beef, you know.
I'm not sure if I should
be taking this though.
By the way, will you be at
President Song's birthday party?
I thought I'd swing by for a meal.
His wife is an exceptional cook,
so don't miss it.
I'll see you two there as well.
See you later.
- Bye.
- See you later.
Girls, look at what he brought us.
How much do you think this is worth?
Isn't it odd though?
Why does he keep
bringing us free meat?
Why else?
He's fallen for one of us.
I thought you knew men better.
I wonder which one of us though.
You? Me?
Why are you leaving me out?
I melted the hearts
of a number of men back in the day.
That's a lie, right?
It can't be you.
Mr. Yang has standards, right?
It hurts my pride to say this,
but I guess I'm not a match
to you when it comes to age.
You must be happy
to have him bring you...
free meat like this.
So who could it be?
Did Joon Seon go
to catch the fish himself?
He should be back
from the fish market by now.
Why not help us with the food?
I'm exhausted, you know.
He'll be back when he's done,
so stop complaining
and taste this for me.
Should I add more soy sauce?
That's a job I'm the best at.
Here you go.
What do you think?
- It's amazing.
- Really?
It's perfect.
Me too, Mom.
You too?
Here you go.
My gosh!
Can I take some of this to Ms. Choi?
She let me have the day off.
Why not?
Ok Ja, can you pack
some of the japchae and jeon...
for Yun Jeong?
What? What did you ask me to do?
Unbelievable.
The japchae and jeon!
Get a grip on yourself.
You've been spacing out
a lot these days.
When did I space out?
You're making that up.
Auntie, your makeup
seems darker these days.
Is it perhaps
because you're seeing someone?
Dating?
At least accuse me of that
after setting me up with someone.
I'm too busy finding someone
for myself, you know.
Isn't there anyone decent
who works at the market?
Auntie, what about Mr. Yang?
Isn't he sexy in a way?
Tell me about it.
So you realized it too.
Are you insane?
Don't dare link me with that man.
It's upsetting, you know.
She and Mr. Yang won't work.
They're polar opposites.
Really?
I think he's a decent guy though.
- He's manly.
- Yes.
- Funny.
- Of course.
And sexy for a man his age.
He sees the world in a simple way
which makes him cute.
Exactly.
That's why he's been
driving me insane.
If you're that interested in him,
maybe you should date him.
Should I?
I would've jumped at the chance
had he not been Dad's friend.
Unbelievable.
Are you insane?
You just don't know
what's appropriate.
I was only joking. Gosh, that hurts.
Unbelievable.
Auntie, Mom doesn't approve.
I guess he's all yours.
I'd love to call him mine.
Here you go.
It's raw halibut and rockfish.
You love raw fish.
Enjoy it with the kids.
I even got some freebies
on the side.
Take them with you.
How could you hand us these
when it's for your dad's birthday?
I bought extra for you guys.
Just take it, will you?
You had to cancel your class
since I couldn't take Seo Jin today.
A day won't hurt me.
Besides, I'm grateful
for your parents...
babysitting her every other day.
Anyway, just take this.
Please.
Come on.
Anyway, enjoy,
and leave some for Seo Young.
She loves raw fish,
so she'll smell it in the air.
All right. Thanks for this.
At the market,
I was reminded of the time we dated.
We bought a plate of raw halibut...
and enjoyed it by the Han River.
Our hearts were full
of all kinds of emotions...
even though we barely had
anything going for us.
Get going now.
You don't want to be late.
I hope your dad's party goes well.
Right.
You were brave back then...
to fall for someone
who had nothing to offer.
Look, it's my daughter!
Dad, you're an idiot.
You should've pushed it more.
You should eat the raw fish
instead of this.
I'll have that too.
I can eat a lot, you know.
- Dad.
- Yes?
How did you and Mom meet?
Your mom?
On the job.
Did she do stunts too?
As if.
You know how she's awful
at physical activities.
It was something else.
Mom loved you back then, right?
Why else would she have married you?
Did she?
I guess she did.
Then Mom is the traitor.
How can one's love change?
I'm grateful for you
being on my side,
but your mom did change...
and I caused it.
That makes me the bad guy.
As if you know anything
about love anyway.
You little pinhead.
My goodness.
You didn't have to bring me this.
I could've easily bought some
at the department store.
Store-bought food
is nothing like homemade meals.
Please have some
while they're still warm.
All right. Then I'll enjoy this.
Tell your mother that I'm grateful.
Sure thing.
I'm home, Mom.
Hey.
Hi, Ms. Song.
I'll get going then.
My mom needs my help.
Sure thing.
I had flowers delivered to wish
your father a happy birthday.
Gosh, thank you.
- I'll get going then.
- Sure.
Ms. Song...
Look at all this food.
Ok Boon has always been generous.
Maybe I should've given her a cake.
I have a whole cake in the fridge.
Let me run along and give it to her.
Ms. Song.
Ms. Song!
Here you go.
Mom said you should have it.
It's for the birthday party.
She shouldn't have.
Tell her I'm grateful then. Bye.
Ms. Song.
Why does it feel
like you're avoiding me?
Did I do something wrong?
No, of course not.
Then was it you
who did something wrong?
I'm only joking, you know.
I really need to get going,
so I'll see you some other time.
Bye, then.
But...
Something is definitely up.
Why else could she be like that?
And here I thought we were friends,
but maybe not.
Say that this is from you.
It's a dress shirt.
I'll give him some money
in an envelope.
Sure.
The ladies at the market
can be a bit too much,
but please try and get along.
Got it.
Why are you so pliant today?
This isn't like you.
Let's say that
your mom's chilies worked.
Besides, it's your expression
that needs to soften up.
Anyone could tell that
we're a divorced couple.
Guys, get over here.
You recognize them, right?
Here's my daughter
and this is my son-in-law.
- Hello.
- He looks familiar.
Right.
- He's on TV.
- That's right.
Anyway, guys, get over here.
You recognize them, right?
My daughter and son-in-law
are on that show "Doctors".
Hello.
This is my first time seeing them.
The celebrities
look even better in person.
Celebrities?
- Gosh, thank you.
- You're both so pretty.
Thank you, ma'am.
Let's head over there next.
Where?
Over here.
Here.
You recognize them, right?
This is my daughter
and son-in-law from "Doctors".
I've been enjoying the show,
you know.
Can I get a photo later on
so that I can brag about it?
Me too. I want one too.
Yes, of course.
Look at those pretentious jerks.
See the show they're putting on?
They're following Mom around
and saying hi.
Gyu Jin is the worst.
Tell me about it.
I'm disgusted
now that I know the truth.
Joon Seon,
please look the other way.
You're only making it obvious
by glaring at him.
I just can't help it.
Look how excited Mom is now.
How can I not lose my temper?
May I have your attention?
Today is the birthday...
of President Song Young Dal
of the merchant association.
I'd like to thank all the merchants,
family, and relatives...
for taking the time
to be here today.
Please allow me
to introduce myself first.
I'm Young Dal's best friend,
Yang Chi Su.
All right.
I guess everyone is
mostly done eating.
At a party like this, we definitely
need singing and dancing.
To celebrate
President Song's birthday,
the nightingales of
Yongju Traditional Market are here.
Here are DT Sisters.
They are the owners of dried fish
and twisted doughnut stores.
Let's go.
(Start)
Life is all about now
Amor fati
There you are. Come sing with us.
He's standing up.
Gosh, I shouldn't do this.
You're so good.
Yes!
Amor fati
You're amazing.
He must be really happy.
His children and son-in-law are here
to celebrate his birthday.
He's a little stubborn,
but he is a lucky man.
I know. The president has
a lot of good people around him.
I think so.
And his wife is so beautiful.
Now that we finished eating,
we should get going.
Why? It's getting fun.
Let's just sing one song.
This is what we are good at.
Let's just go. I'm tired.
Do you know
how many kimbap I made today?
Wait.
Please give them a big hand.
That was amazing.
They are the nightingales
of Yongju Traditional Market.
Now it's time for Mr. Song
to sing in return.
- Mr. Song, please come forward.
- Gosh, no.
I can't sing.
- Why not? Just go ahead and sing.
- My gosh.
Don't be shy.
- Just come on up.
- Mr. Song Young Dal!
- Hang on.
There's something Mr. Song needs.
Please wait.
All right.
Here you are.
What?
I haven't played it for a long time.
I can't do this.
You don't have to be good.
Just show us what you can do.
Please give him a big hand.
My gosh.
- Song Young Dal!
Walking with my eyes closed
Walking with my eyes open
All I can see is
a shabby-looking woman
A face that I want to see
(Yongju Traditional Market
Merchant Association)
Let's go.
Why are you so depressed
after having a good dinner?
I know.
You don't seem to want to have fun.
I was waiting for my turn to sing
my favorite song.
I don't know.
I'm not jealous
of rich or pretty people.
But I'm really envious of people
with a happy family.
Cho Yeon.
We are your family.
You're making me upset.
She's right.
And you have the monk too.
You are right. I have a big family.
Yes, you do. You're so lucky.
You have two pretty sisters.
That's true. You can't buy
pretty sisters like us with money.
I don't think so.
Walking with my eyes closed
This is nice.
- Walking with my eyes open
You're good.
- All I can see is
- A shabby-looking woman
- A face that I want to see
- Waves on the streets
Gyu Jin, have some melon.
Honey, eat some melon.
Okay. Let me just change my clothes.
Mother, I will have just one piece.
I'm so full now.
Okay. You've had a long day.
You must be tired from
taking pictures with the ladies.
It's you who dragged him around
to brag.
I didn't brag.
I just introduced him to people.
Why did you introduce
only Na Hee and Gyu Jin then?
Aren't Joon Seon, Ga Hee, and Da Hee
your kids too?
Aunt Ok Ja, I understand Mom.
Me too.
They say they understand.
The kids want to eat later.
Just leave them be.
Do you want me to peel one
so you can bring it to them?
Okay. That would work.
All right.
Oh, right.
Ok Ja, you should cut this.
I made sikhye for Gyu Jin,
but I guess it's a little bland.
Why don't you go taste it?
Okay. Let's go.
Joon Seon,
I heard you caused trouble again.
What?
It's not like you're a parasite.
Why would you hide your juniors
in the rooftop house?
Hey. I don't think you can say that.
What?
What are you talking about?
Why can't I say that?
- Gosh, Joon Seon.
- Joon Seon.
What's wrong?
Do you have something to tell me?
Do I have something to tell you?
She just asked
if I have something to tell her.
You've been acting strange all day.
You gave me the cold shoulder
and glowered at me.
What's the matter?
Song Na Hee, we need to talk.
- Gosh, Joon Seon. Wait.
- Joon Seon.
- Hey, Na Hee.
- Na Hee.
- Joon Seon.
- Why?
I can't believe this.
Gosh, Joon Seon.
Hey, where are you guys going?
Can I come too?
What was that?
Are they leaving me out?
My gosh.
Gosh.
What is it? Tell me.
Joon Seon, please.
What's going on?
You've been trying
to pick a fight with me.
What's the matter?
Gosh, it seems really serious.
It's like a calm before the storm.
I know.
Joon Seon looks really upset.
What is going on?
Is something happening out there?
- My goodness.
- You startled me.
What is it?
- Why did you call me out...
- I hear you got a divorce.
Gosh.
How did you know?
Does that even matter?
Who cares how we found out?
Joon Seon, keep your voice down.
Mom would hear you.
Joon Seon, please.
Calm yourself down.
What are you thinking?
Why are you putting on this show?
I understand a married couple
can get divorced.
If you two are not compatible,
you can break up.
But you should've told us first.
Are you an orphan?
Do you not have a family?
I just couldn't tell you.
Mom was really devastated.
So you just got a divorce
and pretended nothing happened?
- Do you think that makes sense?
- Gosh, Joon Seon.
Can't you lower your voice?
Mom just pulled herself together.
I'll wait a bit longer...
and tell Mom and Dad
when the right time comes.
So please keep it
to yourself until then.
How can I pretend not to know
when I actually do?
This is deception.
You're ignoring us...
and fooling Mom and Dad
who care so much about you.
Is that what smart people do?
What did Na Hee do to fool me?
Mom.
Oh my goodness.
Cut. I said cut.
Seo Jun, are you all right?
You hurt your little finger.
- What do we do?
- Hurry.
He hurt his little finger.
Bring the first-aid kit.
- Disinfect the wound.
- Are you all right?
- Gosh.
- Hey.
- Clean it first.
- It looks bad.
Don't you see he's hurt too?
He was hurt even worse.
He's spilling blood.
- No, I'm fine.
- Oh, right.
Do we have another kit?
Who are you?
Me? I play a minor role.
Oh, a minor role.
I love you.
- What?
No, no. I mean, thank you.
Thank you.
(Once Again)
How do you feel about Gyu Jin?
Look carefully into your heart.
Is it really because of
those reasons,
or are you not yet ready to
leave Gyu Jin?
My mom used to be very sick
with lung disease.
Oh, and I remember one more thing.
A song.
My older brother sang for me.
That show is quite fun.
Wait. Those two...
Wow, so it's true that
TV programs are all staged.
Do you know them?