What did Na Hee do to fool me?
Mom.
Oh my goodness.
What hasn't Na Hee told me?
You see...
Mom, what's this?
Is this sikhye?
It must be for Joon Seon's friends.
Let me.
Stop changing the subject.
What hasn't Na Hee told me?
Tell me right now.
What is it?
What's going on
and why is everyone so serious?
Mom,
truth be told...
Your birthday!
What?
Na Hee suggested that
we throw you a surprise party.
We had a feast for Dad today,
so it'd be wrong
to not do anything for you.
It was supposed to be a secret,
but you kind of ruined it.
Right?
That's right. A surprise party.
Unbelievable.
And here I thought
something serious had happened.
But there's no need
for a birthday party.
I'm good with a family dinner.
Tell me about it.
Still, you ruined the surprise.
Anyway, guys.
That's the end of that, okay?
Let's scatter, people.
Joon Seon, you take these inside.
We should head back down.
My feet are getting cold.
- Come on.
- I'd like some sikhye too.
Come on.
You've got to be kidding me.
It was exhausting, wasn't it?
I hope you can understand though.
Your mother-in-law
just wanted to brag, that's all.
It's all right, Father.
I had a blast too.
What were you doing up there
with your daughters?
Were you having
a meeting without me?
They were in a way.
Gyu Jin, how's the sikhye?
It's delicious, Mother.
It's perfect.
Na Hee, have a seat.
I'll get you some sikhye.
Mom, we'll get going now.
Hand me my purse.
What? Right now?
You're leaving?
But you just sat down.
I forgot that I had a meeting
early in the morning...
and I'm exhausted.
- Come on. Let's go.
- Okay, sure.
We'll get going then.
Happy birthday, Father.
Thank you for everything, Mother.
We'll get going then.
You don't have to see us out.
Okay, sure. Get going then.
Don't skip your meals, okay?
- Thank you for coming today.
- Don't mention it.
What's with those two though?
Did they argue?
I doubt it.
They seemed fine earlier.
Of course they're exhausted.
You invited them just to
brag about them to people.
I couldn't look Gyu Jin
in the face after that.
It's not like I did anything.
Na Hee, wait.
What was that?
Did something happen?
Can you just get the car?
You wanted me to play nice
to thank her for the beef bone soup.
What's got you
all twisted this time?
Did you get into it
with your siblings up there?
The three of them know
that we got divorced.
What?
Joon Seon, Ga Hee, and Da Hee
know that we're divorced.
No wonder.
Joon Seon was glaring at me
all evening.
They won't spill the beans
any time soon.
I told them to give me some time
and that I'd tell our parents.
How on earth did they find out?
This is why I said Da Hee shouldn't
work at your mother's cafe.
Her cafe?
What does that
have to do with anything?
Are you an idiot?
Apart from you and me,
only one other person
knows about the divorce.
Jae Seok, you colossal jerk.
You're dead to me.
(Brother)
That's what I'm talking about. Nice!
Guys, aren't I on a roll today?
I bowl at maximum power!
You sure are on a roll today.
Well, you're up next.
The person you called
is unavailable.
Why isn't he picking up?
Gyu Jin will
beat him to death tomorrow.
Should I leave a text?
How can I tell him this via text?
(Neulpuleun Children's Hospital)
My sister-in-law
was born to be on TV.
She gets better with every episode.
You're right.
Dr. Song sure is bright and smart.
Meanwhile, I haven't heard
a word from my brother.
Maybe the staff
chose to edit out his comments.
There's Dr. Yoon.
You can ask him in person.
Hey, Dr. Yoon!
What happened, Gyu Jin?
Did you fail to make a comment
or did the staff edit you out?
Gyu Jin, what's with that face?
Why are you taking off your watch?
Get over here.
Today's your last day on earth.
- What?
- Get over here!
Gosh.
What's this about?
Get over here.
Get over here, you jerk!
Gyu Jin, use your words,
not violence.
You're scaring me.
We'll talk
after you get your beating.
I'd like to know
what I'm getting beat up for.
It was you, wasn't it?
You told Da Hee about
our marital status, didn't you?
Gyu Jin, please calm down.
Just wait.
- Get over here.
- Hold on.
Get over here!
Gyu Jin, please!
Help me!
He just had to go
for the vital points, didn't he?
I can't believe he'd take advantage
of his medical training like this.
No wonder Na Hee's sister
has been avoiding me.
And here I thought
she was a decent person.
"To get revenge or retaliate..."
(Mr. Yoon)
My gosh. What do I do?
He must've found out. Oh, no.
That's right.
Sky-blue suits you much better.
Look how handsome you are,
my sweet son.
Our children adapt and grow
at their own pace,
so there's no need to worry.
Yes, just like Dr. Yoon said,
it's natural for growing children
to suffer from minor illnesses.
Look at how smart they both sound.
They're not even nervous
in front of the camera.
My life is complete
thanks to you two.
My sweet babies. Goodness.
I definitely chose
the wrong profession.
Seeing couples
that were once in love...
come in to get divorced
makes me give up on marriage.
I can only imagine.
I've been enjoying that show lately.
The doctors on that show
are hilarious.
A husband and wife are on it
and the wife keeps smashing him.
- Really?
- Yes.
Wait, those two?
So it's true that
TV programs are all staged.
Why? Do you know them?
What do you know?
This is deception.
You're ignoring us...
and fooling Mom and Dad
who care so much about you.
Dr. Song, the doctor taking over
Yo Han's case is here.
Sure. I'll see him right now.
Jeong Rok?
I put together his status report...
just in case
there are any complications.
It's a thorough report.
I expected no less.
Don't worry though.
I got this covered.
Sure.
Na Hee, I was actually
on my way to you.
We'll talk later.
Can we get this over with right now?
I'd like to get scolded
and put this behind me.
We'll talk later, brother-in-law.
Brother-in-law?
You must be Gyu Jin's brother.
Sorry?
He's a dentist here and he graduated
from Sejin University.
I'm sure you know Lee Jeong Rok.
Mr. Lee!
I heard a lot about you.
This is an honor.
Dentistry students know me too?
Of course, Mr. Lee.
So many are working
as doctors these days...
thanks to your sacred notes.
You saved the lives of many.
Well, so I heard.
You don't seem
a lot like Gyu Jin though.
I took after our father
while he took after our mother.
As you can see,
my genetics are better...
I'll see you around then.
It was nice meeting you.
Sure thing.
He's an odd one too, isn't he?
His personality doesn't seem
like Gyu Jin's either.
Jeong Rok? My gosh.
What brings you by?
I'm here to take over the care
for Na Hee's osteosarcoma patient.
Whoever it was got lucky then.
Just a second.
Na Hee, are you free right now?
Maybe later.
The transition isn't over yet.
I still need to get him
the other materials.
Would you like to meet Yo Han first?
Why not? I'll see you around then.
Sure thing.
I was hoping to set up a plan,
but I guess I'm the only one
who thinks of this as an emergency.
Aren't they being
too friendly though?
Darn it.
Joon Seon,
your noodles will turn to mush.
Isn't the dish good enough?
This is why you should've
ordered from the usual place.
Jajangmyeon is pretty much the same,
so why would you bother him...
by ordering one
that's 50 cents more expensive?
You told me to order from here
because they served chunkier meat.
Guys, cut it out.
I'll eat mine, so stop arguing.
(Hyun Gyung)
Hi, Hyun Gyung.
Where are you? At the office?
Could we meet?
Yes, of course. Where are you?
I hope I didn't
make you wait too long.
I didn't.
You didn't have to run over here.
I wasn't running.
I only walked at a fast pace.
Here.
- What's this?
- A dress shirt for your dad.
I didn't know if I should buy this,
but it seemed rude to ignore
his birthday after knowing about it.
Please tell him that
I wish him a happy birthday.
This wasn't necessary, you know.
Gosh, it's expensive too.
It's way better than what I got him.
You shouldn't have spent so much...
especially when
you don't spend any on yourself.
That's not enough
to show my gratitude though.
You know how I owe
your parents a lot.
I'll get going then.
Head back inside.
Hyun Gyung, wait.
How about we get some lunch?
I haven't eaten yet.
I haven't had jajangmyeon
in a while.
Gosh, it looks good.
This place is famous for
its old-fashioned jajangmyeon.
Really?
It's a work of art.
The kimchi is delicious too.
That's what I call skill.
Ma'am, what kind of fish sauce
did you make the kimchi with?
We buy our kimchi from China.
No wonder I could taste
the flavors of China.
They know how to make
good kimchi these days too.
So tell me. What's going on?
What do you mean?
There's something on your mind.
It's why you asked me to lunch.
As always, I can never fool you.
It's about Na Hee.
What about her?
That brat got divorced.
It happened over a month ago.
Unbelievable, right?
That's 4 out of 4 now.
It should be in
the Guinness World Records.
What about your parents?
Are they all right?
They don't know yet.
It's been eating me up inside.
Without knowing anything,
Mom looks after them
as if they're royalty.
My gosh.
I was so upset
that I yelled at Na Hee.
And it's still weighing on my mind.
What does she say?
Is it really over?
Did she say there's no turning back?
I don't know.
You know what she's like.
She always leaves people speechless.
What about Gyu Jin?
Did you talk to him?
If Mother and Father don't know,
you should probably talk to him.
I know your meddling can't
make them change their mind,
but you're
her older brother after all.
I know.
I'm her older brother, right?
What are you doing here
at this hour?
- What about training?
- I need to talk to you.
This is Hyun Gyung's gift for Dad.
What is it?
Oh, it's a dress shirt.
It's pretty.
She's got a good sense of fashion.
That's not important. About Na Hee.
Now that they know we know,
we should have a serious talk.
I think so.
I've been feeling uncomfortable.
And I wonder how Na Hee feels.
Let's do this, Ga Hee.
You should talk to Na Hee.
- And I'll meet Gyu Jin.
- And?
We have a heart-to-heart talk
and try to convince them.
All men and women in the world
are all the same.
They have to give it a second
thought before it's too late.
I don't know if it will work,
but we have to give it one last try.
Ga Hee, we have a grave mission
to carry out.
You and I have to keep
our family happy.
Can you do that?
Okay.
Let's do this.
Got it.
Gosh, again?
I'm not sure I can take this.
Gosh, it's no big deal.
You don't have to feel pressured.
Like I said before,
this is like a drop in the ocean.
Please feel free to eat it.
Still, this is just...
Just take it, Cho Yeon.
I believe Mr. Yang is doing this
for a good reason.
She's right. There's no such thing
as a free lunch.
What's good for the goose
is good for the gander.
It's just mutually beneficial.
That's how things work.
Don't you think so, Mr. Yang?
Well... I guess you're right.
If you still feel bad,
you can give me some kimbap.
I don't think we can't call it even
with some kimbap.
Please wait a moment then.
I can wait all day.
Take your time.
Ju Ri, get him some soda.
- Okay.
- Let me do it.
- Please have a seat here.
- Okay.
Here.
Mr. Yang.
Please have some soda.
Okay.
Let me take care of this.
- I'll do this.
- No, I will.
Look. He's looking at me.
- The phone is turned off.
- He didn't come to the meeting.
And I just can't reach him.
Where is he?
Is he indulged in gambling
or something?
See you, Mr. Yang.
Bye.
- Please come again.
- Of course I will.
I'll come again. See you.
Bye.
Hey.
Hey!
Stop drooling.
You seem to like
their kimbap very much.
My gosh.
Thank you.
Mr. Yang, why do you keep buying
their kimbap when it's not good?
I'm so sick of it.
You punk. I bought it for you.
Did you sharpen the knives?
If you haven't,
go ahead and sharpen them right now.
I was going to.
Why? What did I do?
Hey, I know what's going on.
Just come clean.
It's clean. Happy now?
Why is it so hot today?
It's a scorcher.
Hey, you have a fever, right?
It's spring fever.
That's right. Are you happy now?
I'm a single man.
What's the big deal?
It is a big deal. It's huge.
Hey, when did it start?
How did it happen?
I don't know.
There's no reason for love.
What? Love?
Did you say love?
Gosh, this is crazy.
Of course it's love.
Love isn't just for young people.
My heart is pounding hard,
and I feel so alive.
Can't you see that
my color has improved?
I can feel my blood
circulating these days.
You seem quite excited.
Fine. That's good.
So which one is it?
The taller one or the shorter one?
The round and chubby one.
Round and chubby?
None of them are round and chubby...
Hang on. Is it that...
Right. It's Cho Yeon.
Cho Yeon?
The leader?
The round and chubby one
who smiles a lot?
Right. She's got a fatal charm.
Sometimes she's cool,
and sometimes she's sexy.
She even has a dimple here.
It's really adorable.
My gosh. You must've lost your mind.
What's wrong about my Cho Yeon?
My Cho Yeon?
Hey, do you not know
about her temper?
She even singlehandedly took on
all the ladies from the market.
And do you still like her?
Yes. I like the braveness.
I like charismatic girls.
Hang on.
I just don't think this is right.
You'd better think again.
If things go wrong with her,
you'll be in big trouble.
I don't know. I don't care.
the bus has left already.
Once I make up my mind,
I just go for it.
I just give away my love
until she gets sick of it.
That's a man's love.
Don't you think so?
Don't be silly.
Look at you.
You totally fell for her.
What should I do with you?
My gosh.
Hey.
Hey!
Oh, no.
I made 20 rolls of kimbap today,
and they sold right away.
We need regulars
to run a restaurant in a market.
Mr. Yang from the butchers
frequents our restaurant too.
Cho Yeon,
that's not because of your kimbap.
You should know that
he comes to see me.
What are you talking about?
He comes here because of me.
I could feel it today.
Don't be silly.
You're making a fuss again.
You said Mr. Hong
from the gas station liked you,
- but he didn't.
- Yes, he did.
Then why do you think
he visited our bar all the time?
Do you think it was because of you?
Of course.
He ordered yellow peach
when you served him,
but he ordered assorted fruit
when I did.
It can't be you.
But he ordered a whiskey.
Did you have any customers
who ordered whiskey?
Hey, that's enough.
It doesn't matter whom he likes.
Do you like Mr. Yang?
- Are you crazy?
- Gosh, no.
Stop the useless squabble
and cook some more rice.
- Ga Yeon, make some egg garnish.
- Okay.
I'll go buy some carrots.
Cho Yeon, are you going
to the old lady again?
- Yes.
- We have to throw away...
half of what you buy from her.
Can't you go to
the grocery store over there?
I won't tell you to prepare them,
so just do as I say.
See you.
- My gosh, what's happening?
- What's the matter?
- My goodness.
- Are you all right?
- What happened?
- Call 911.
Ma'am. Ma'am!
Ma'am. What's wrong?
What's wrong, Ma'am?
What's with her?
It's so cold. Call 911.
- What do we do?
- Call 911 now.
The ambulance can't
come into the alley.
We should take a taxi
on the main street.
Carry her on your back.
I strained my back,
so I can't carry her.
My goodness.
- Help me carry her on my back.
- You're a man.
Ma'am, pull yourself together.
Move over. Clear the way.
My goodness.
Move over.
Is it because you're young?
You have such quick hands.
You fold 2 boxes while we do only 1.
I know. I'm grateful for your help,
but I'm not sure
if I can let you work like this.
My husband wouldn't like it.
It's okay.
This is good enough rest for me.
How are you doing
with the guys at the rooftop house?
It's good. They seem nice.
And they are fun.
If they give you a hard time,
just tell Mr. Song.
You belong to the house owner,
and they belong to his dependent.
You've got more power.
Don't you think so, Ok Boon?
How could you call your nephew
a dependent?
He's a tenant who pays rent.
I see. I made a slip again.
I'm so sorry, ma'am.
Hello.
I'm here to have some of Ok Boon's
cereal smoothie.
Hello. It's been a long time.
It's so good to see you.
I've been busy
with things these days.
Ms. Ok Ja, if you're not too busy,
will you make me a smoothie?
Gosh, you're ridiculous.
It's not like
you left your smoothie with us.
How brazen you are.
Hey.
Mr. Song.
Mr. Song, something bad happened.
The old lady who sells vegetables
just passed out.
What? Why? What happened?
I don't know.
But the kimbap lady
put her on her back,
and took her in a taxi
to a hospital.
- Cho Yeon?
- Oh, dear.
Chi Su, is your car parked here?
Yes, yes. Let's take my car.
Call me when you're there, okay?
The old woman has no kids
and lives alone.
I know. My heart is still pounding.
I made it nice and thick
so you'll choke on...
Where did he get to? Did he leave?
They're over there. That way.
- Cho Yeon.
- Hello.
What did they say? Is she okay?
I don't know.
They ran all the tests they needed,
but the results aren't out yet.
Who is Ms. Park Jeong Ran's
guardian?
- Me.
- That's me.
She doesn't have any family.
We work together.
Oh, I see.
Based on the test results,
she has postural hypotension
and malnutrition.
She's very old
and must be admitted for a few days.
Malnutrition?
She managed to
fall asleep right away.
Is it because of
the supplements she's getting?
It's a relief.
The color in her face is returning.
Thank you, Cho Yeon.
She must've been heavy.
How did you manage to carry her?
She wasn't heavy.
She was as light as a feather.
How is there still malnutrition
in this day and age?
She should eat decently.
We hired a carer to look after her,
and she must rest,
so let's get back.
Let's leave for now.
- Yes.
- Let's go.
Hello.
Hey, what...
Are you free this evening?
Let's meet without Na Hee knowing.
(Ga Hee)
- What?
- I'll be brief.
See me after work.
Gyu Jin, over here.
Hello.
You must eat as well.
It's fine.
- I'll cook...
- No, no.
This is what my energy is good for.
Were you surprised that
I called you over?
Not really.
I'm sorry. I have nothing to say.
You're right. To be honest,
I couldn't believe it
when I first heard.
And I was angry.
How little did you think of us,
that you'd do that and not say...
No, I don't think little of you.
I know that.
I know what you're usually like.
Gyu Jin. Let's talk, man-to-man.
Can you really not
make it work with Na Hee?
Gosh, Joon Seon...
Yes, I know.
Living with Na Hee
is not an easy feat.
She's fussy
and smacks you around with words.
To be honest, you deserve praise
for living with her so far.
No. Na Hee put up with a lot too.
No, no. I know you.
You know I do.
But the thing is,
she's not an evil person.
Don't just end it like this.
Think about the possibilities.
The likelihood of it working out.
Can't you do it?
Are you so sick of her that
just looking at her annoys you?
It's not that.
We didn't make the decision lightly.
I know.
Who makes that decision lightly?
To be frank,
I have no right to lecture you.
I was the first to get divorced
in my family.
But when I did get divorced,
I really worked myself almost crazy
to try to make it work.
To try to change Hyun Gyung's mind,
I went on my knees
on that stone floor...
and hurt both kneecaps and...
I was in a wheelchair for a while.
I clung to Hyun Gyung
while in that wheelchair...
and begged her to save me.
To be honest, it's not a crime
to want to look after others.
Shouldn't a man be loyal?
A friend I used to work and eat with
was about to become homeless.
What human being would ignore that?
That's not right!
That's not what a human should do!
You're right.
Hey, let's be honest here.
What did I do that's so wrong?
What did I do?
I really, really worked hard.
I wanted my wife and kids
to have a good life.
All I did was work hard
and torture myself to do so!
I know, Joon Seon.
How about you calm down?
Did I get hurt because I wanted to?
Did I guarantee a friend's loan
because I wanted to lose my money?
Can you be quiet?
Did you rent this restaurant?
What? Did I rent this restaurant?
You're a bit rude
considering we're strangers.
- What?
- No, no. I apologize.
He had a lot to drink. I'm sorry.
Gyu Jin. Call my ex-wife.
I have something to tell her.
Hyun Gyung!
- Hyun Gyung!
- Joon Seon!
- Will you get him out of here?
- Hyun Gyung!
- I'm sorry. Sorry.
- Let go of me.
Yes, I'm poor
and can't afford an apartment.
No, why...
My wife divorced me
and I moved in with my parents.
Get up, will you?
Shall I keep going?
- I'm...
- Get him out of here!
I didn't keep it from you
because I looked down on you.
Don't think so.
I know you didn't.
That's just our inferiority talking.
So?
How do you really feel?
Are you really over it?
Yes.
I actually feel more relieved
now that you all know.
No, not that.
Your feelings for Gyu Jin.
Are you really over him?
Of course.
Would I have divorced him
if I weren't?
I'm asking because I don't get it.
Our situations are different,
but I left with Ji Hun
before the divorce was finalized...
because I didn't want to
even breathe the same air.
That's how people are like
when they split up.
But not you and Gyu Jin.
You still live and work together.
That's because we'd lose too much
if we sold the apartment then.
And we hadn't told Mom and Dad yet.
So you stayed with him?
I don't think that's you.
Look carefully into your mind.
Is it really because of
those silly reasons,
or are you not yet ready
to leave Gyu Jin?
It's really not like that.
We couldn't ignore
reality and finances.
No?
If that's what you say.
It's really not easy.
For a man and woman to marry
and live an ordinary life.
You're not drinking?
I have to work tomorrow.
You're so firm.
Fine. Your jobless sister
will drink it all for you.
Where did Joon Seon and Ga Hee go?
Joon Seon said he has
an important meeting.
Mom too, Grandpa.
The only meetings they'd have
in the evening is with alcohol.
Don't say that.
He's a CEO now,
so don't speak of him like that.
We don't hear anything, ma'am.
Speak freely as if we're invisible.
Why? Did you just say something?
He says things
when he doesn't really mean it.
Don't take him seriously.
I almost forgot.
Auntie said this is
your birthday present.
It's from Hyun Gyung?
When did she buy this?
How sweet of her.
Why did she buy something
when she barely supports her family?
Just accept it.
It's not like
she can ignore our birthdays.
She visits all the time
to drop off the kids.
Gosh, it's a shirt.
Look at the lovely color.
Honey, let's see.
It suits you so nicely.
How sweet of her.
Thank her for me, will you?
I will.
You're done already? Eat some more.
I had enough.
I'll get changed. Pack some food...
I know. I already packed
some rice and side dishes.
You want to visit Ms. Park.
I was married to you for years.
I know you well enough.
I'm sorry, but could you
point me to the restroom?
Please turn right at
the end of the building.
- It's on the second floor.
- Thank you.
There's nothing on the left.
I said, "right", ma'am.
Yes, of course. I forgot.
Thanks again.
Sure.
Let me just take you there...
Good evening, traitor.
Mr. Yoon...
(Episode 24)
I'm truly sorry.
I had no choice but to tell them.
My big sister thought
that Gyu Jin was having an affair.
She was about to track him down.
She and my brother
are the temperamental types.
They usually take action
instead of talking things out.
They thought Gyu Jin was cheating?
How could they suspect that
of someone like him?
Exactly! That's why
I had no choice but to...
I'm truly sorry.
I don't deserve your forgiveness.
Forget it.
I'm hurt too deeply
to let this go with just an apology.
What?
Just so you know,
this has made me
lose faith in people.
I trusted you with all my heart,
but you stabbed me in the back.
I'm the idiot here.
I deserve what happened.
No way. This is all my fault.
I'm the one who betrayed you.
Do you have any idea
how my day has been?
Even though I was starving,
I couldn't go to the cafeteria.
I was afraid of running into Gyu Jin
and getting my butt kicked again.
I couldn't go to the lounge
to get a cup of coffee either.
Why? Because I didn't want
to run into Na Hee.
I felt so ashamed!
Mr. Yoon,
I'm truly sorry.
What can I do to appease your anger?
Go ahead and tell me.
I'll do anything.
I'm too shocked
to think of anything right now.
I need some time to think...
because nothing can possibly
make me feel better right now.
Mr. Yoon.
Let me go.
Oh, no. He must truly be upset.
Why didn't I keep my mouth shut?
Nothing was solved
and look where I ended up?
Gosh, she's so easy to fool.
Her response is priceless.
Talk about it being fun.
I should pretend
to be upset for a few more days.
Have another piece of this eel.
Go ahead.
There you go.
Why did you hold back
when you have an appetite?
I'm just grateful, that's all.
And I'm sorry.
This isn't for free, you know.
I'm taking all the spring onions
and peeled garlic you have.
Of course.
You can have all of my spring onions
and garlic.
- Really?
- Of course.
- You promised.
- Sure thing.
Let me get you some juice.
Mr. Song!
(JH General Hospital)
It was pouring earlier,
but now the sky is clear.
Aren't you coming?
Yes, of course. Impatient as always.
When did you get that close
to the vegetable lady?
You haven't been around that long.
Well, we bumped into each other
a few times, so...
I know I have a temper,
but I'm sweet to people,
especially the elderly.
Anyway, have you always
cared so much about the people here?
Are you trying to be responsible as
the merchant association president?
Well, I guess.
You're a softy, aren't you?
A what?
A softy.
You seem standoffish,
but you're nice to people.
The ladies dig that these days.
You see it on TV a lot.
Who comes up with these things?
Anyway, I hope she gets better soon.
I feel terrible
when I see old ladies get sick.
My mom fell ill
to lung disease, you see.
That's what happened to me too.
Wait. Did your mom
suffer from a lung disease?
Yes, it was common back in the day
among poor families.
Just so you know,
I suffered a severe fever as a kid,
so I have no recollection
of my past.
The memory of my mom being bedridden
is as clear as day though.
She would...
cough all night.
I was so worried that
she'd pass away any time soon.
I'd wake up
just to put my ears on her chest...
and I kept doing that.
I still have nightmares about it.
What I also remember is a song.
The one my older brother
used to sing.
Yes, hello? Dad!
I was going to call you tomorrow.
I guess you read my mind.
Right. Just a second.
Mr. Song, I'm going that way.
- Sure.
- I'll see you around.
Yes, Dad. You're not sick
or anything, right?
Of course, I'm doing fine.
- We're here.
- I'm getting off now!
Joon Seon...
Gosh, thank you so much.
Bye, sir.
Joon Seon, this way.
Call Hyun Gyung for me.
- Hyun Gyung, I miss you.
- You're at your house!
Gyu Jin?
Father.
Dad.
I miss Hyun Gyung.
Where did he get wasted like this?
He said he had plans.
Was it with you?
Yes, things got a bit out of hand,
I'm afraid.
I'm sorry.
Why would you be apologizing?
It's his fault for getting wasted
all by himself.
You should come in with us.
No, it's fine, Father.
It's late anyway.
You won't step inside?
I have work tomorrow anyway.
Joon Seon, take care.
Father, I'll get going. Goodnight.
Gyu Jin.
- Gyu Jin...
- That jerk.
Attention.
At ease.
Get a grip on yourself...
- and come inside.
- Sure.
Dad!
- Come on.
- Sure.
Bye, Na Hee. I'll get going.
Get home safely
and text me when you get there.
Okay.
You, smarty-pants.
Just do whatever you want.
It's not like others
can live your life for you.
Your life is yours.
Gosh. Hello.
So you stayed with him?
I don't think that's you.
Look carefully into your mind.
Is it really because of
those silly reasons,
or are you not yet ready
to leave Gyu Jin?
Dr. Song!
Jeong Rok?
Why is it that I always
run into you around here?
You didn't have
to give me a ride home.
The state you're in disagrees.
Why were you getting soaked
in the rain like a moody teenager?
I never felt this way
when I was a teen, you know.
So why are you
heading home this late?
I was in the neighborhood...
and the director made me
join him for dinner.
I couldn't even drink
because of tomorrow's surgery.
It must've been boring.
You have no idea.
He told me his life story
from when he was a medical student.
Then he talked about
you and Gyu Jin as well.
The man relies on you two a lot.
I'm confused as it is,
so why did it have to rain?
I could've just made a run for it.
It's fine. You'll really
catch a cold at this rate.
Come on.
Thank you for always helping me out.
It's not for free, you know.
I'll cash in a favor at least once.
I doubt you'll need anything.
You should get going then. Bye.
Were they together all day...
or did they meet up again?
When did they become best friends?
You're home.
Isn't it obvious?
Gyu Jin.
What? Why?
Can I ask you something?
Ask me what?
Why do you keep living with me?
What?
Why are you staying
in this house with me...
when our divorce has been finalized?
What?
It's because of the house price.
We'll lose 100,000 dollars
if we sell it now.
Is that the only reason?
Of course. Must I have another?
By the way, why didn't you...
shake off the water first
before entering the house?
There was water
all over the front entrance.
Have you no basic manners?
Of course.
I doubt there's another reason.
What was that all about?
This darn remote control
gets jammed all the time!
Let go of me.
Bring me Hyun Gyung.
Hyun Gyung!
I can't believe you got this wasted.
Get a grip on yourself.
Hyun Gyung...
Unbelievable.
Why can't you drink
as much as you can handle?
Get up, Joon Seon.
Here. Drink some honey water.
Mom?
Just so you know,
this honey is expensive...
and I'm risking getting
scolded by your dad.
Here you go.
Mom...
What on earth? Gosh, you stink.
Get away from me.
Get off me!
My poor mom.
You must've sinned
in your past life.
My gosh.
Are you kidding me?
Why are you wasted
when Gyu Jin was perfectly sober?
Mom...
My poor mom.
Unbelievable.
Just kill me already. My gosh.
Mom?
Mom!
You must've sinned
in your past life.
What did you do to deserve this?
Who are you to comment
on my past life?
How can you get wasted like this
when you have a son to care for?
Are you out of your mind?
- How insane are you?
- That hurts.
Mom, I'm sorry.
Stop it.
You're pulling my pants down!
That's enough.
I can't believe you two.
Why would she suddenly ask me that?
Now I can't stop thinking about it.
Whatever. Stop thinking
about it and go to sleep.
Let's go to sleep.
Only think about tomorrow.
I have to get to work,
so I must sleep.
Darn it!
Tall with long limbs.
Why would he stick
to part-time jobs?
If I were him,
I'd train to be an athlete...
and compete in the Olympics.
Jong Soo,
not everyone can get
on the national team.
Besides, his muscles are for show.
There are some bodies
that easily get pumped up.
I bet that his muscles
aren't even firm.
Jeong Bong,
did you apply
BB cream on your face?
No.
Yes, a little.
We live on the rooftop,
so the sun was getting to me.
- Is it that obvious?
- Yes.
You look like a ghost.
Really? Did I apply too much?
You're trying to look good
for Ga Hee, right?
Just tell her how you feel.
Ga Hee isn't someone
to be disgustingly drooled over.
She's someone I can't
possibly think of approaching.
An angel from above
is how I see her.
I guess you guys are working out.
That's good.
Good morning, Ga Hee.
Hello.
Well... Here's the thing.
Joon Seon is using
the bathroom downstairs.
Do you mind if I use
the bathroom here?
Sure. Go ahead and use it.
Okay.
It happens every time I drink.
I guess even the angel
has bowel movements too.
She didn't say what she was doing.
She might be here to wash up.
She says it happens
every time she drinks.
It's so obvious.
What?
Why are you always so negative?
You can't live like that.
You can't be happy that way.
Did you laugh? How...
Are you happy now?
Am I funny?
Do you think I'm hilarious?
Thank you for letting me use it.
You probably want to use the toilet
about five minutes later.
Bye, Ga Hee.
Come again if you need anything.
I should go to the bathroom.
What? Why?
She's even worse than Joon Seon.
No. That can't be right.
She's my angel.
She can't have caused this smell.
No!
You are coming out just now.
Hey, how did it go yesterday?
What about you?
I tried, but he seemed
quite determined.
- Gosh, I have to go again.
- My gosh.
- Wait, Joon Seon.
- What?
- Go.
- Hey.
What am I supposed to do?
Why isn't she coming out?
Even if she wakes up now,
she will be late.
What's wrong...
I don't know.
I don't care.
That's not my business.
I don't care
if you're late for work.
Why isn't it closing?
I'd like you to take care
of the parking fee issue.
Okay. Don't worry.
I'll take care of it.
Okay. So it's all settled.
Let's wrap it up then.
Okay.
- Mr. Song, I will give you a call.
- Okay.
I'm busy, so I should get going.
Okay.
- I'll see you at the next meeting.
- Okay.
- Bye.
- See you.
I should get going then, Mr. Song.
Are you going
to the kimbap restaurant again?
Well... Not necessarily.
Fine. I'm going there. Why?
I finally met the woman
of my dreams at this age.
Can't I go there?
She seems nice.
What?
The owner of the kimbap restaurant.
She seems better than I thought.
Really? Are you serious?
You said I lost my mind
the other day.
What changed your mind
all of a sudden?
Things can change.
What's the big deal?
If you don't like it,
it's fine by me.
Gosh, no. I'm just grateful.
To be honest, it weighed on my mind.
I felt bad to like
a woman you hated.
But now that you say it,
I feel much better.
Gosh, that's not true.
Don't say anything you don't mean.
Why did you frequent the restaurant
when you felt bad?
If it weren't for you,
I would've lived there already.
Fine. Go ahead and live there now.
Just go.
Then I'll go to see her
with a light heart.
- See you, Mr. Song.
- My gosh.
I'm going to see Cho Yeon.
Gosh, he's deep in love
late in life.
My goodness.
Did you get your hair done?
It looks pretty.
It's too long, so I got a perm.
Do you like it?
- You look pretty.
- Thank you.
Would he like my hairstyle?
Should I just go to
the butcher's shop to see him?
But I need a reason.
He used to hang around our store
all the time, but not anymore.
What is he up to?
I miss him so much.
I like it so much
What? Where is he going
feeling so excited?
Hello, everyone.
- Hello, Mr. Yang.
- You're here.
Why did you come so late?
I had a meeting
at the merchant association.
- Why? Were you waiting for me?
- Sure. Please come on in.
We will give you
a lot of freebies.
That would be great. Let's go.
What? So does that mean
he didn't come to our store...
because of those wenches?
(Unnie's Kimbap)
You should've come early.
Young Dal is out
for the merchant association.
Did you get your hair done?
So he's been in and out
of that diner the whole time?
Gosh, it looks great.
I don't think you got it done
in a local salon. How much was it?
Gosh, I don't know.
You startled me. What's wrong?
Do you not like your hair?
It's not like that.
You don't have to know.
Don't talk to me.
It must be 1 of the 2 wenches.
Those vixens.
My gosh. What's wrong?
Okay. I'm not talking to you.
Just go ahead and knead the dough.
By the way,
did Na Hee finish the bone soup?
How is her ankle now?
She won't give me a call.
I had a disturbing dream last night.
Is she working?
Hello?
- Na Hee.
- Mom.
What's up with your voice?
Are you sick?
What's wrong? Are you ill?
You're sick, right?
Where are you now?
Na Hee.
Gosh, you are sweating a lot.
If you're sick,
you should get a shot or something.
Gosh, you've got a high fever.
You didn't have to come.
What are you doing here?
What are you talking about?
You look like death.
What's the use of being a doctor?
You can't even
scratch your own back.
By the way, where's Gyu Jin?
Did he go to work alone
when you're sick like this?
Didn't he get you some medicine?
It wasn't this bad earlier.
Gosh, I can't believe this.
Wait here.
You should have some porridge
before taking medicine.
Why? You should finish it.
Take the medicine then.
Gosh.
Oh, dear.
I guess you worked too hard
for your dad's birthday party.
It was silly of me to make
a big deal out of it.
It's not like that.
I got a cold
after getting caught in the rain.
Why did you get rained on?
If you didn't have an umbrella,
you should've stayed inside...
or called Gyu Jin.
Okay. The medicine will
bring down the fever soon.
Get some good sleep.
Drink a lot of warm water.
I'll see you again next week.
Bye.
Are you busy, Dr. Yoon?
No, I can spare a few minutes.
What's the matter?
I have appointments all day,
but I don't think I can finish them.
If you have some time,
can you help me with that?
I'm all booked up too.
Let me see what I can do.
Why do you have
so many appointments?
Because I got Dr. Song's patients.
Did she have to call in sick?
Is she very sick?
- Is it a cold?
- What?
Yes, kind of.
I had dinner plans today.
She and I really don't click.
I'll call for help later
if I can't manage.
She was sick, not just sleeping in.
I should've checked on her.
Will she be in bed?
Oh, whatever. I don't care.
My gosh.
What a dreadful mess.
Why are there clothes
and blankets out here?
Did Gyu Jin sleep out here
to avoid catching her cold?
What's the point in wasting time?
They're busy.
I might as well clean up for them.
What a dreadful mess.
These two are helpless.
How come they never clean up?
The trash is full to the brim.
When was the last time
they emptied it?
They're terrible.
Oh, dear.
My goodness.
What happened? I don't believe this.
The bag was too full.
I should've gotten another bag.
This is a disease.
That's what I get for being
Song Young Dals' wife.
I just made more work for myself.
Darn it.
What's this?
(Cohabitation Contract)
A cohabitation contract?
My insides hurt.
I must be getting old.
I used to down 3,000cc of beer
and be fine the next day.
Me too.
I'm too hungover to train.
So we get the day off.
Drink with us next time.
You too.
My dear little Seo Jin.
Did you cook me dried pollack soup
because I'm hungover?
With an egg?
Seo Jin, me too.
I need some soup too.
A fish?
That was delicious.
Thank you.
Your soup was amazing.
Seo Jin, look over there.
Does he look ugly,
or does he look uglier?
They're both ugly?
Seo Jin, you have
amazing taste in men.
Oh, thank you, Seo Jin.
- Seo Young.
- What?
Oh, okay.
That was so good. Thanks.
What are you reading?
Articles on Aunt Na Hee.
The comments are really funny.
Half of them curse her out.
That's why they're funny.
Guess what I read earlier?
(Yoon and Song
are actually divorced.)
Oh? What's this?
"Couple doctors Yoon and Song..."
"are actually divorced
and pretending"?
What was that?
What did you just say?
Says who?
Someone said that
in the comment section.
I just read the comment.
"Couple doctors Yoon and Song..."
"are actually divorced
and pretending."
Oh, my gosh.
This is bad.
I bet she slept all day
and didn't take any medicine.
(Medicine)
This is for old time's sake.
I can't ignore a sick person.
That's right.
Good on me.
Mother.
When did you get here?
Oh, Na Hee.
You're here because she's sick.
She took the day off today,
so I brought some medicine.
Did you have dinner?
I will clean this up right now.
What...
What is this, Gyu Jin?
(Cohabitation Contract)
Mother.
I want water.
You're home.
(Cohabitation Contract)
I asked you what this is.
Mother...
This is...
Na Hee.
You tell me.
What's this cohabitation contract,
and why does it mention
the finalization of a divorce?
What is this about?
(Once Again)
Why would you get divorced?
Why would you...
What did I tell you from the start?
I said you two would never work!
Is there no way
you can get back together?
That means we're no longer in-laws.
Still, let's call each other
every now and then.
- What?
- Mom disappeared.
- Mom left home.
He woke up and she was gone.