(Episode 11)
- Who's that?
- Who are these people?
(Woori King Dumplings)
Is this the place?
The previous owner ran off
in the middle of the night, right?
We lucked out because of it though.
Shall we take a look?
- Okay.
- Let's take a look.
Are you kidding me?
Shouldn't we see
who our neighbors are?
No, keep your eyes on me.
What a mess.
It's as if a tornado
blast through here.
What's worse than a tornado
are creditors.
Still, it's not as bad as I thought.
The tables and chairs
are good enough.
Most of the cooking utensils
are still there...
and the stove
works perfectly well too.
It's a good thing we found a store
where the owner just took off.
All we need really is a new sign.
There's even a small room
where I can sleep.
The two of us
will be commuting anyway.
Cho Yeon, are you sure
about just selling kimbap though?
Shouldn't we at least
have some soup with it?
How about udon? Can you make one?
What about buckwheat noodles?
- There's one thing I'm good at.
- What's that?
- A fruit salad!
- Darn it.
It's of a liquid base, isn't it?
Let's just stick to ramyeon, okay?
Hold on. How about Unnie's Kimbap?
- What are you talking about?
- Come on.
I mean for the name.
We'll call it Unnie's Kimbap.
I think it has
a familiar ring to it.
I love it too.
Good then.
We have a name for our diner.
All we need to do now is make money.
Let's make it rain!
Yes, let's do it.
- Go, Unnie's Kimbap.
- Let's clean this place up.
- Sure.
Gosh, I'm late.
Darn it.
I'm late!
I can't believe you, you know.
Couldn't you have woken me up?
Keep getting dressed unless
you want to show me more skin.
(Seoul Family Court)
This came in the mail.
Free up your schedule, okay?
What's this?
(Finalization of Divorce)
Is it really over then?
Legally, it's over?
Yes, the mail came in this morning.
So much for
a dramatic turn of events.
Although, I guess
it's what I expected.
What now?
Will you keep on
working here together?
I get that about the house,
but isn't it awkward here?
Of course, it is.
One of us
will have to work elsewhere.
Have you had any offers?
I'm sure many hospitals
would like to have you.
I've been searching,
but none are close
to what this place offers.
We both want
to be professors one day.
I guess Hanseo University Hospital
can be an option.
Hanseo Hospital?
Right, it's the ultimate dream
for all doctors, right?
Except me, of course.
Not you?
I value my free time, remember?
I hate places
that make you work all day.
You should be able
to have some fun too.
Yes, do that
and never become like me.
I feel bad that you have to attend
a seminar today of all days.
- Is it this afternoon?
- Yes.
Ji Yeon said...
that all those related to
the Korea-US symposium will attend.
That includes all of those
in important positions.
It'll be a field day
for those who are free agents.
I guess.
Let's go.
Hold on.
Why? What is it?
It's nothing.
I need to get ready for the seminar.
Go back to work, will you?
But...
They must stand out a lot
for everyone to be making a fuss.
I don't know,
but I guess that's the case.
The lady at
the dried fish store...
said that they had
on sexy outfits...
and was wearing red lipstick.
They even had double the volume
in their hair.
Anyway, I hear that
they're quite crude.
The lady at the dried fish store
is probably exaggerating.
You know how she is.
No way. She seems
to be onto something this time.
They don't seem like ordinary women.
What else can they be though?
Oh, come on. This again?
Why does this always happen
when someone new joins the market?
Who cares what they did
before coming here?
How can you say that?
Now that they're here,
they're a part of this community.
A bad fish can disrupt the pond...
and one rotten apple
can ruin the entire crate of apples.
She's right. We're only worried...
about them ruining
the atmosphere of the market.
I doubt that's what
you're truly worried about.
You're just happy to have
something to gossip about.
We're not gossiping.
Everyone's saying
they seem quite odd so...
Don't be like this, okay?
Must you blindly follow
what others do?
You're supposed to be
an example to others.
Why can't you act your age?
He ended up yelling at me
because of you.
You spoke ill about them too,
so you're not innocent in this.
I never did such a thing.
All I did was
join your conversation.
Gosh.
What you're currently seeing
is the spread...
of the GI index in five categories.
The subjects that
weren't given antibiotics...
showed at least
more than one spike in numbers.
Patients who weren't
given specific antibiotics...
showed a significant increase...
of protective bacteria.
(Neulpuleun Children's Hospital)
That'll be all. Any questions?
(Hanseo Hospital)
So in conclusion,
young patients with
non-alcoholic fatty liver disease...
who don't suffer from
dermatomyositis or cirrhosis...
can't hugely benefit
from metformin and vitamins...
compared to medications
for stomach pain.
That is why
the most effective cure...
is exercise, the most basic
but most difficult solution.
Saying that doing so will make them
as handsome as their doctors...
will be even more effective.
Dr. Han doesn't seem too pleased,
so forget that I said that.
That'll be all. Thank you.
(Hanseo Hospital)
That concludes the spring seminar.
Thank you for coming.
- That was amazing.
- I should be thanking you instead.
- That was great.
- Hi, guys.
It was a nice summary too.
Congratulations.
Was what you said to the chairman
ad-libbed or rehearsed?
Rehearsed of course!
- I'll get going then.
- Sure. Take care.
- I'll call you sometime.
- Sure thing.
Did you book us the restaurant?
Of course.
We'll be clearing out
all the meat there.
I'm ready to have
my wallet burned through,
- so do your worst.
- Nice.
Let's go!
Good job, guys.
Let's grab a bite to eat.
It'll be on me.
Dinner?
Gosh, I'm sorry,
but it's my mother's birthday today.
And I've been suffering
from a terrible headache.
My friends are out front
and they've been calling me.
Is that so?
I guess
dinner is out of the question then.
I'll at least be saving money.
Good job today, guys.
You too.
- Good job today.
- Bye.
In here, guys.
I hear this place serves great meat.
Hey!
You guys...
When did you get here?
You move fast
when it comes to these things.
Gyu Jin, you're here.
We were going to celebrate
my mom's birthday,
but dinner was postponed.
He had a headache,
but now he's doing better.
I get it, okay?
I never said anything.
Eat up, guys.
Don't let the meat burn.
Go ahead. Here.
- Eat up.
- Gosh.
You all did great. Now, eat up.
- You too.
- Thanks.
Here you go. Go ahead.
Unbelievable.
They cast her aside
and she went home alone.
This is why she should've
been nicer to them.
What...
Hello?
Right? I knew it was a stretch.
Don't say that.
I'm the one who's sorry.
Let's grab a drink sometime
when you're less busy.
Right, of course.
Hello?
Honey, why are you standing there?
- Joon Seon, I'm here too.
- Hi Auntie.
How were things at the market today?
So much for the crabs
being nice and plump.
They're not like that at all.
Mom, save some for yourself too.
Just eat up.
You're home early today though.
What about your part-time job?
My boss wanted to close early
and go home.
She acts out on a whim
even when she runs her business.
She just blows hot and cold.
Are you sure she can pay you
working like that?
It's nice
that she gets to finish early.
How is your studying going?
Is it going well?
Not really. I'm just trying.
Don't overwork yourself.
It might shock your head.
I think it's shocked already.
My brain is so slow
that I can't keep up with the class.
All your hard work will go down
the drain if you get exhausted.
Studying is like a long-term battle.
You should take your time.
Okay, Dad.
I guess Mom and Dad
only care about Da Hee.
Joon Seon, maybe we should also take
college entrance exams...
or realtor qualifications
or whatever.
Joon Seon.
Yes? What did you say?
What's wrong with him?
Why are you distracted while eating?
I'm not feeling well.
Please excuse me.
I enjoyed the dinner.
What? He left all his food.
What's wrong with that glutton?
I know.
Is he upset because we didn't
leave him the chicken yesterday?
I guess he has no appetite
what with everything on his mind.
Ok Ja, you should eat some more.
Mix your rice in the crab shell.
Young Dal and Ok Boon,
I should get going.
I'll see you tomorrow.
Ok Ja, wait.
What? Why, Young Dal?
Well...
I need to ask you a favor.
I should've bought some sushi.
Hello?
Dr. Song Na Hee?
Yes. This is her. Who is this?
This is Nam Cheol Woo,
Chief of Pediatrics
at Hanseo Hospital.
We met at the conference today.
Oh, right. Hello.
To what do I owe the pleasure?
I enjoyed your presentation today.
Your paper was excellent.
And the alternative you proposed
sounded quite interesting.
Thank you for your kind words.
So I was wondering...
There's an opening for
a pediatric research lecturer.
You can also get tenure...
based on performance.
I won't beat around the bush.
What do you think, Dr. Song?
Would you be interested in
a job interview at our hospital?
Yes, I'd love to.
I'll have the documents
ready tomorrow.
Okay. I'll see you then. Thank you.
Yes!
Well done, Song Na Hee.
You did a great job.
What are you doing?
I think I have something in my ear.
Why did you come home so early?
You acted like
you'd drink all night.
I'm just trying to get in shape.
I have something going on.
Did you eat instant noodles again?
You should keep
your temper in check...
and try to get along
with the junior doctors.
Instead of scolding them,
you can buy them a meal
and offer a sympathetic ear.
Why are you being so nosy
all of a sudden?
I'm just worried about you.
You at least had me until now,
but what will you do now?
Jae Seok is on another team.
I had a harder time because of you.
Don't worry.
It's all over once I quit.
I know you will quit someday.
But before then, you should...
It's not someday.
I'll quit right away.
I got a job offer
from Hanseo University.
What?
Me too.
The research lecturer?
With a chance of getting tenure.
- The interview is tomorrow.
- At 12:30.
- At 1:00.
- That's good.
One of us might get the job.
We've been uncomfortable
working at the same hospital.
I know.
They also provide a residence.
Then the house issue
will be settled.
All right then. I'm tired.
Goodnight.
I have to go.
This is what I've been dreaming of.
Why does it have to be him?
All right.
Let's go our separate ways.
If one of us has to leave,
I should be the one to go.
And you should stay.
I've been feeling good
until just a few minutes ago.
I even played bowling
with my friends.
But why do I feel so down
when I get home?
She's not here.
Did she go somewhere?
(Business Hours)
Darn it.
Gosh.
I didn't do anything wrong.
Why did I hide?
So I got drunk in front of him.
What about it?
It can happen.
Jae Seok.
Yoon Jae Seok.
Jae Seok!
Jae Seok.
Yoon Jae Seok.
What? Why? What do you want?
Drink this.
What is this mysterious liquid?
Is it poison?
All right, Mom.
I guess this is more humane...
than torturing me to death.
You fool.
It's green vegetable juice.
Celery, beets, yam, and...
Anyway. It has everything
that's good for your health.
Mom, I don't eat breakfast.
And I never eat vegetables.
Do you not know I'm a meatatarian?
I know. That's why you should
eat it from now on.
You should eat vegetables
if you want to live long.
Drink it up.
My gosh.
I've given it some thought.
All the furniture and curtains
in your room...
are from before you went to Turkey.
Maybe we should redecorate the room.
Why? I'm fine with them.
I'm not fine.
We should buy
a new wardrobe and a bed table.
We should change the curtains too.
A light ivory one sounds good.
Okay. Just suit yourself.
All right.
What time do you get off today then?
Why?
Why else?
We should pick them out together.
It's for your room.
What? Why?
Why on earth?
- Where are you going?
- Anywhere.
I guess you're going to eat.
Hey, what's with your face?
Is something wrong?
No. Nothing.
I just can't eat or sleep
when I want to.
No problem.
Gyu Jin, I can't even pick a color
for the curtains in my room.
I can't listen to music I like.
Chopin in the morning
and Mozart in the evening.
Actually, I can still hear it.
Am I the only one who hears it?
That's what you deserve.
You slipped away from Mom,
so she's even more
obsessed with you now.
Admit that it's your fault
and humbly accept the whole thing.
Shut your mouth before I beat you
to death, you bystander.
How dare you?
I'm your older brother. You punk...
Mom doesn't drink a lot
these days though, does she?
I don't know. She just has
some wine when she eats dinner.
Why? Did she drink a lot before?
No, it's nothing.
Just make sure
she doesn't drink a lot.
You should take better care of her.
You don't do anything.
Where are you going
all dressed up like that?
What took you so long to ask that?
I have something important.
Something important?
Your outfit... Don't tell me
you're going on a blind date.
It's something like that.
Wish me good luck.
I might move
to another hospital soon.
(Neulpuleun Children's Hospital)
Dr. Song, we have a patient
with a lacerated wound.
The other doctors went to lunch.
Oh, really?
Bring her in quick.
The wound is quite deep.
She needs stitches.
Get a local anesthetic.
Will it be covered by insurance?
What's the injury code?
Pardon?
Give me a medical certificate,
and patch her up quickly.
How much will you charge me
for a tiny cut this time?
I'll give you a discount.
Let's treat her first.
Are you sure...
you got hurt when you fell?
It's okay. Tell me.
What are you doing?
A six-year-old female patient.
She came in with a laceration
on the thigh and a 4cm wound.
She shows symptoms of
a chronic illness.
There are multiple circular bruises
on her arms and legs,
and they seem to have occurred
at different times.
I observed red spots
with a 1cm diameter,
which are suspected contact burns.
Based on those observations,
I strongly suspect child abuse.
What are you talking about?
You don't know, do you?
That's what I'll put
on the certificate.
That this child
was abused by her father.
You're out of your mind.
This isn't the only hospital.
Hey. We're leaving.
Darn it.
You're not going anywhere.
Call the police now.
- Okay.
- Quick.
You're crazy. Let go. I said let go!
Darn you.
You met your match today.
Are you out of your mind? Let go!
Call the cops now!
- Okay.
- Darn you!
- Let go!
- I can't!
Darn you!
We're so late. Where's Young Dal?
At the office,
taking care of something.
Gosh, this is so heavy.
It's a dead-weight.
He followed you out
as you left last night.
What did he say?
Oh, that?
He told me off for
messing up the chicken order.
My gosh.
And I thought he was quiet.
There's no way the stingy man
would let that go.
He keeps his pockets tightly shut...
even when his own son needs money.
Exactly.
- My gosh.
- Goodness.
Oh, I'm sorry.
Cho Yeon! We're here!
(Unnie's Kimbap)
You look so well!
Congratulations on opening a store!
I can't believe
you're selling kimbap!
Why would you sell kimbap?
Are you out of your mind?
You can't say that to my face.
- Oh, sorry.
- Come inside.
Wait, wait.
Isn't the music just killer?
Let's dance!
- Not out here.
- Come inside.
- Come in.
- We're here!
Oh, my...
Ga Yeon, serve that table more jeon.
- Here you go.
- Thanks!
This is amazing.
- Cho Yeon, it's a decent space.
- It is.
You look like a real boss.
Thank you.
Eat your fill.
If you need anything, just say so.
Do enjoy yourselves.
You too, Dad.
We're here to congratulate you,
so we'll enjoy ourselves.
You should.
- Eat up.
- Cho Yeon, the rice cakes!
That was quick.
- Put three on each plate.
- Okay.
We might have more visitors,
so you stay here.
Ga Yeon and I will hand them out.
I'll visit the stores on this line.
The fried chicken place is
the association president's store.
I should visit in person and say hi.
- Okay then.
- Is it good?
(Original old-style chicken)
My gosh. I've never seen
that kind of an opening before.
How can something be
so loud and crazy?
Forget the noise.
Did you see the flowers?
They were all from bars or pubs.
The women were right.
They're not ordinary women.
The woman who led
all those girls is the boss, right?
She has the word "boss"
practically printed on her face.
Her aura was just...
She's stocky and glares like this.
Did you see her hairdo?
It would poke anyone in the...
Excuse me.
Hello.
- Hello.
- Hi.
I opened a kimbap store
a few rows over.
I brought rice cakes.
I'll take that. Thank you.
Are you the president's wife?
My goodness. You're beautiful.
Oh, no. I'm the younger sister.
She's his wife.
Oh, no wonder.
My goodness. You're beautiful.
Your skin is so clear
and you're so slim.
You look rich and elegant.
You look like this actress.
Who is it? What's she called?
The one with a pale face
who looks so elegant.
Oh, well, I'm not so sure,
but others say that...
I look like Jeon In Hwa.
Is your husband not in?
I hoped to say hello to him.
He went out to
take care of business.
He's in charge of everyone
and everything, so he must be busy.
If he's the president
of the merchant association,
that means he's the boss. The head.
Oh, did this
just come out of the fryer?
Gosh, it's a golden yellow.
What a brilliant color.
How much is a large box?
Is a large enough for three?
Three people can eat about...
Hello? Yes, what?
They're leaving already? Why?
Okay, I'll be right there.
Tell them to wait.
Okay, see you soon.
I have to go now.
Please look out for us.
When your husband returns,
give him our regards.
It was nice to meet you,
pretty madam.
Lipstick.
What just blew through?
Dad, can't you stay a while longer?
You rarely leave the temple.
I'll visit another time.
Why follow me out when you're busy?
Go back inside.
It's fine.
I'll walk you to the exit.
I'm proud of you, my daughter.
I always was.
Whenever you think
I'm not doing well,
you always say I'm doing well
and that you're proud of me.
That's how you got this far.
I look into the future.
Did you eat a lot?
Mr. Song!
What's the matter?
Will you please do something
about the new kimbap place?
I can't do business
with their loud music.
- The kimbap place?
- Yes!
Okay. I'll go right over.
Their opening is more like
a shaman's ritual.
It's so noisy!
Oh, dear. Gosh, it's so noisy.
Goodbye! Come by
for kimbap next time!
Excuse me. Just a moment.
Yes? We open for business tomorrow.
It's not about that.
I'm the president
of the merchant association here.
My name is Song Young Dal.
Oh, you're the president.
It's lovely to meet you.
Yes, hello.
I know that you're opening today,
but people are complaining
about the loud music.
Wait. I'm not the owner.
- You're not?
- No.
Where is the owner?
Ju Ri! What's the matter?
Cho Yeon.
He's the association president.
He has something to say.
Oh, Mr. President!
I was at your store to say hello.
Your wife is so beautiful.
Sir, Mr. President,
you're a lucky man.
What do you have to say to me?
Well, it's about...
Sir, you're as handsome
as your wife is pretty.
You have such a nice nose.
You could've been an actor.
Don't people say that?
Not really.
It's great to meet you.
We're here now,
and I hope we get along.
Oh, dear, I'm sorry. I forgot.
What did you want to say?
Yes, well, let me speak.
I know that you opened today,
but I got complaints
about your loud music.
Could you turn it down?
You brat.
I told you it was too loud.
I apologize.
We're used to working in...
spaces where the music is very loud.
- An occupational hazard.
Sir. It's our opening day though.
Could you let us off?
Well, I would like to,
but the others feel uncomfortable.
Okay. I see, I see.
I get it.
I'll turn it down.
Don't worry, I'm good at that.
- Is that for Unnie's Kimbap?
- Yes.
Line it up over there.
Who is this from?
No, that side's too crowded.
Put that here.
- Over there? Okay.
- Put it there.
Put it here, thanks.
Why did they send flowers?
Why isn't she here yet
when she works around the corner?
(Application for Hanseo Hospital)
What?
Where are you?
I'm outside. Is something wrong?
The police were here
and everything is a mess.
There was a suspected
child abuse case,
and Dr. Song wanted to report it.
The dad freaked out and broke stuff.
What? So what happened?
The police took everyone.
You should head over there.
Okay. Bye.
Did she have to get into trouble
at this exact moment?
Dr. Yoon?
The chief will see you now.
But...
I'm sorry but something came up.
I'm truly sorry!
(Jungang Police)
The suspect was just
put in a holding cell.
Dr. Song gave us her statement...
and headed back.
Most are reluctant to make a report,
but she sure is a strong lady.
Don't I know it.
She's not normal either.
How many fried chickens
do we have out there?
Enough for four large portions.
Of course, you're here.
You never walk past us
without coming in.
Why are you walking with a limp?
She's right.
Did you injure yourself?
I hurt my back on my way here.
I was out running an errand...
when I slipped on
the confetti sprayed out across...
the new kimbap place.
There's confetti everywhere.
Darn it. That kimbap place again?
(Unnie's Kimbap)
Unbelievable.
And the music... Darn it!
The kimbap was delicious.
Thank you for coming.
Stop by whenever
you want a late-night snack.
Got it. I wish you the best.
- Thanks.
- We'll get going then.
Bye, guys.
Mr. Song.
You're back again?
What brings you by this time?
Yes, I'm back.
I asked you to
turn down the music earlier,
but it's still pumping loudly.
You're wrong about that.
I did turn it down a little.
Isn't this all right though?
An opening ceremony
should have music.
- It's a party...
- This is not all right.
It's not all right,
so turn the music off.
Also, what's with the confetti?
Someone can slip and fall on these.
You're littering the street
and it's dangerous.
I can't believe
they didn't clean this up.
Unbelievable.
The girls earlier sprayed this
to congratulate our opening.
They always end up getting yelled at
even though the gesture was nice.
The last time...
Stop. I don't want
to hear your stories,
so turn off the music
and clear the street.
Got it, sir.
I'll have the girls clean this up.
Cho Yeon!
My gosh, you're here.
You said you couldn't come.
How could I miss it?
Let's head inside.
- Did you touch up your eyes?
- How did you know?
Unbelievable.
You've got to be kidding me.
Gosh.
(Unnie's Kimbap)
My gosh.
That is one odd woman.
She never listens
to other people, does she?
Unbelievable!
(Sort out your recyclables.)
What on earth is this?
Why weren't these recyclables
sorted out?
Do people have no common sense?
I put up an announcement...
saying that this was
only for regular trash.
You've got to be kidding me.
Darn it.
Plastic bottles and...
(Unnie's Kimbap)
Unnie's...
These came from that store too?
Darn it.
- Cheers.
- Amazing.
Don't tell me you still
live with that jerk.
Gosh, don't call him that.
He's my husband, you know.
Of course, you take his side.
I heard he stopped gambling though.
Try and turn him into
a better person then.
Got it.
Ga Yeon, can you clear that table?
Got it!
It's good, right?
Stop!
Oh, that's right.
I forgot about the confetti.
Ga Yeon, can you clean this up?
Tell me what this is.
What do you mean?
That's a 20-liter trash bag.
Does this look like
general waste to you?
These are recyclables!
How can you throw these out...
with other general waste?
Haven't you heard of recycling?
I'm sorry.
It's our opening ceremony,
so things are a bit hectic.
That isn't an excuse.
This isn't rocket science, you know.
Also, the waste disposal site
was set up for customers.
The stores must manage
their trash themselves.
Well, that's my bad,
so I'll be careful from now on.
I'm sorry about what I did wrong,
but must you be this way...
in front of my customers?
Are you always this petty?
Petty?
Do you have any idea
how many times I came here today?
It's my third visit here.
The music is hurting my ears...
and I cleaned up all the confetti.
I've been running my store
at this market for 13 years...
and the president of
the merchant association for four.
Never have I received...
this many complaints
about a new store before.
Do you know that?
Well, it's my first time
running a business in a market,
so I agree that
we weren't aware of the rules.
But isn't it the president's job...
to mediate any disputes
and have the other owners...
show some generosity?
This is supposed to be a community.
What?
I've worked at a variety
of places too...
and have met my fair share
of odd neighbors.
But never have
I come across a place...
that doesn't allow any leeway.
I guess we're even then, right?
Whatever.
Just sort these out.
I'll get to it later,
so leave it here.
You keep saying that
but you never do anything.
Do it right now.
Can't you see I have customers?
I'll do it later.
No, do it right now!
I said I'll do it later,
you old man!
We'll do it right away.
Plastics go together
and so do the cans.
- The paper...
- Girls,
open the door. He's leaving.
Sure.
Unbelievable!
Darn it.
You...
Darn you!
When the police call,
send over the medical reports
that I wrote via fax.
If the girl
needs to be hospitalized,
we're the affiliated hospital,
so tell the police we'll take her.
Got it, Dr. Song.
I'll take a 10-minute break
and go back to seeing patients.
Nothing fazes her, does it?
How can she be okay
after experiencing that?
Tell me about it.
My hands are still shaking.
How relentless.
Exactly.
Where's Dr. Song?
She went out that way just now...
for a 10-minute break.
How is she?
She isn't fazed at all.
You know how she is.
I developed a crush on her now.
Ta-da!
Unfazed? As if.
She's just too proud
to admit her worries.
(Wafer cookies, Coffee)
Is this too much?
I guess I can give her these
as a friend and colleague.
Yes, it's fine.
- Gyu Jin?
- Bo Young?
It really is you.
It's been so long.
I think we last saw each other
10 years ago.
I guess.
How have you been?
Good, I guess.
I had a child
and have been raising him,
so things were busy.
He was born with asthma, you see.
Asthma isn't easy to care for.
Your husband should have
to help out a lot.
Well...
Are you still working?
I run a small leather workshop
with a friend.
You've been good though, right?
I heard that you got married,
but I couldn't make it
to the wedding.
My son wasn't doing so well,
you see.
I never made it to yours either.
Hold on. I don't think
I heard that you got married.
You must've had a quiet wedding.
Anyway, it's really
nice to meet you.
Exactly.
I can't believe we never
crossed paths before.
Exactly. But then we meet here
of all places.
(We fry your memories.)
Don't laugh.
Why do you keep laughing?
What can I say? It's hilarious.
She's one bold woman though.
You're never one to lose your cool,
but she has you in a rage.
I've never met a woman
like that before.
You have no idea how brazen she is.
Now I'm dead curious.
It takes a special kind of person
to make this kind of entrance.
How old do you think she is?
Is she pretty?
What?
She sounds incredibly beautiful.
Just like a rose
with prickly thorns.
A rose?
She's more like a rose
that's been squashed by a truck.
If you're that curious,
go and see her for yourself.
Goodness.
I don't even know
how the day went by today.
I should take a bath...
before I get some sleep today.
You're right. It was a long day.
How many customers
did we have today?
Can you believe
that president though?
He looks petty too.
Cho Yeon, come on.
You're the one
who said that he was...
exceptionally handsome earlier.
I was only trying to be nice.
Handsome, my foot.
What will you do
now that you're on his bad side?
Won't he make it harder for us?
We're not the only ones
on his bad side.
He got on Cho Yeon's bad side too.
- Of course.
- You know who she is.
- Kang Cho Yeon.
Make way!
Come on.
Look at all these vegetables.
There's spinach...
Gosh, I love shepherd's purse.
- Is that so?
- I should buy some.
But they don't seem fresh.
I'll take all of these.
Thank you.
Still, let me take this eggplant
for free.
Of course. Take it with you.
Can someone give me 10 dollars?
Gosh.
I said we should go out
and get something nice to eat.
Why do you always insist
on eating seaweed soup?
We'll need to pay for another ticket
if we leave.
Besides, this is more than enough.
So why aren't you eating up?
Go ahead.
I'm eating.
Jong Soo, Jong Soo!
What is it?
- Who's that?
- The body scrubber who works here.
There has been
a misunderstanding between us.
What kind of misunderstanding?
We scrubbed the backs
of some elders...
for two dollars per person,
- but he caught us.
- What?
We scrubbed the back
of an elder this one time,
and he gave us some money.
We took it
because it was hard to refuse.
I guess the rumor spread
about us being cheap labor...
and that led to a lot of clients.
I guess we're not so bad at this.
Since you're here,
let us scrub your back.
Guys,
go back to Mr. Jang.
- Joon Seon?
- What are you saying?
I can't let you do this anymore.
Your lives won't get better
if you stick with me.
I don't have any money
or any connections.
With Mr. Jang,
you can at least work as stuntmen.
- No way.
- I don't want that either.
Don't just say that
and think about it.
You'll lose your touch
unless you keep training.
We work out here, you know.
We coordinate fight scenes as well.
We've decided to follow you
wherever you go.
Unbelievable.
Hey, do you know...
(Auntie)
Yes, Auntie.
Can I call you back though? I...
What?
Really?
Gosh, you didn't have
to run over here.
I was worried
that you'd change your mind.
Are you sure about this?
Will you invest in my company?
That's 20,000 dollars.
I don't need it back any time soon,
so set up your company
and pay me back when you can.
Auntie...
Don't tell the family though.
Especially your mom.
I don't want things
to be awkward between us.
Of course! I'm really grateful.
My junior colleagues
are looking up to me,
so you really
saved my life with this.
Gosh, there's no need
to put it like that.
Anyway, try your best.
This isn't just any money, you know.
Of course. Don't I know it.
You've been saving up
for your marriage, right?
I'll make my company a success...
and snag you a younger man
who you'll marry on a cruise ship.
Gosh, don't be silly.
I get seasick, you know.
Then you'll throw up
during the ceremony.
I love you, Auntie.
I love you, my dear investor.
Gosh, you're hurting me.
Look at you with your sweaty palms.
Yes, I gave him the money.
Judging by his big smile,
he must've been in a bad spot.
Must you do this though instead
of giving it to him yourself?
He needs to learn
not to be dependent on me.
You know how he is.
He's too kind for his own good
and bad at looking out for himself.
If he thinks
there's more money to spare,
he won't take this seriously.
You should at least
tell Ok Boon though.
I feel guilty about lying to her.
Your sister is the same.
When it comes to her kids,
she can never be strict.
We'll keep it between us for now.
All right.
If that's what you insist...
Anyway, thank you for today.
- I'll see you tomorrow. Bye.
- I'm home!
Mom, I found an investor.
Ga Hee,
someone invested in my company!
I'm afraid you lost out
on a chance to make money.
I offered it to you first
since you're family,
but now I feel bad for you all.
Look at you being
all boisterous again.
I really wish
this works out for you.
Is she asleep?
(Application for Hanseo Hospital)
(Coffee and tea)
Ms. Song.
Thank you for your hard work
as always.
It's almost time to close, right?
I had lots of bags to carry earlier,
so I couldn't say hello.
Were you not stressed
about anything today?
My mom is quite picky...
and very moody.
She's not easy to deal with, is she?
Well... I just bought
a few cans of beer.
If you want,
I can be your drinking buddy...
just like last time.
A drinking buddy.
Gosh, Jae Seok. Watch your mouth.
You said it wasn't you.
You look just like her,
so I was mistaken again.
- And you have the same handwriting.
- Fine. It was me.
I'm the pathetic loser who took
64 dollars from you at the cart bar.
I didn't say you were pathetic.
Right. I was so embarrassed
that I pretended not to know you.
That night, it wouldn't
have been strange...
for me to jump to my death
from somewhere.
But I couldn't kill myself,
so I got drunk with a stranger
whom I'd never meet again.
I was just so ashamed
that I made up a lie like that.
Can't you just be nice
and pretend not to know it?
Why do you keep mentioning it
and making fun of me like that?
Do you really have to do that?
Well... Ms. Song.
I didn't mean to make fun of you.
All right. I'm a nasty drunk.
I snatched your money.
And I was actually impressed
by the phrase, "Just be myself".
So I decided to try my best again.
Are you happy now?
Ms. Song.
Well... Ms. Song.
I just thought we had fun together.
I just did it because I was excited
to see you again.
I don't have a dollar bill.
I'll make sure to give you
the exact amount later.
So take this.
Wait, Ms. Song.
Well...
She keeps yelling at me without
giving me a chance to explain.
Was I being too mean?
I just feel really bad for her.
The radish soup is very refreshing.
Is this all we have?
No, we have a lot.
You can have some more if you want.
You seem to have your appetite back
after getting the investment.
I heard the news, Joon Seon.
There will be two business owners
in our family now.
Congratulations.
That's right. Thank you, Da Hee.
So are you going to look around
for an office today?
Yes. I'll find an office
and have some business cards made...
to promote my business
to film and broadcasting companies.
I have a lot of work to do.
It's not easy
to run my own business.
Of course not. It's never easy.
Stop making a fuss
as if everything's settled.
You have to be cautious
and weigh up what to do.
Don't get carried away
and ruin things.
Gosh.
You know what he means.
He wants you to do things right.
I get it, Mom.
I know what Dad is like.
You two should just wait.
I'll let you shut down the store...
and travel all over the world
within three years.
Dad, you will play golf as a hobby.
Mom, I'll get you a designer bag.
Dad, where are you going?
Anyway, you'll take lessons
for arranging flowers...
with a designer bag by your side.
Gosh, it sounds wonderful already.
All right, Da Hee.
Now that you're studying
for your future career,
you should go study abroad
for a language course.
Will you pay the tuition?
That would be great.
Joon Seon, what about me?
I just want you to get me
a small nail shop.
I'll let my employees work
and count the money.
A nail shop? Sure. It's no big deal.
Ji Hun, what do you want me to do?
Just tell me anything you want.
- Go ahead.
- I'm fine.
You're fine?
I knew it.
Ji Hun cares about me so much.
I'll go get ready for school.
Thank you for the breakfast.
Sometimes your son is
even scarier than Dad.
I feel the same way.
I guess it's Seo Jin.
Mom, stay here.
I'll go get the door.
You still look so sleepy, sweetie.
Gosh.
She had a bellyache last night,
so she didn't get good sleep.
Don't let her eat anything cold.
Make sure she drinks warm water.
Is that true, Seo Jin?
Are you all right now?
Okay.
Da Hee will take care of her today.
I have important work to do.
Okay.
Seo Jin, have fun with your aunt.
I'll come home early.
Bye.
Wait. Aren't you going to ask
what it is about?
Do I need to know?
Not really.
I'm going to look for an office.
I'm starting my own business.
Business?
Well... It's no big deal.
I'm starting a stunt company.
I wanted to stay as an artist,
but my junior stuntmen want it,
and I found an investor.
Really? Good for you.
I'll wish you good luck.
Sure. It will go well.
I'll do it right this time.
If you become a business owner,
are you not going
to do the stunt work yourself?
What?
Well... It's not like that.
I'll invite you to the opening
of my business.
You have to come, okay?
Seo Jin, your mom doesn't
seem to hate the idea.
Right, Seo Jin?
He seems really excited about it.
That's better
than looking down though.
I like my hair.
- Ma'am.
- Yes?
Please make sure to give some volume
on top of my head.
The volume of my hair
represents my pride.
Okay.
Make it higher. Even higher.
- Higher?
- Yes.
- Higher.
- Even higher?
- Even higher.
Even higher than that?
Gosh, I love it. Are you guys done?
It's done.
- It's perfect.
- Okay. Ready to go to work.
Let's go...
- and make kimbap.
- Make kimbap.
I just don't understand you.
He's not someone else's son,
you know.
Why do you pick
on every word he says?
What's wrong with you?
It's not like I was lying.
You shouldn't get your hopes up
too high.
It's not easy to run a business.
If things go wrong again,
he will just quit everything...
and curse his fate crying.
Forget it.
Maybe you know everything,
so you can be like that.
But I'm not like you.
I will keep daydreaming
about traveling around the world...
and carrying a designer bag
with my children's money.
So you should stop
discouraging him like that.
Even a stranger has faith in him
and invested money in his business.
How could you act like that
as his dad? My gosh.
Where are you going?
I'm going to buy pepper powder.
I will make kimchi for Na Hee. Why?
Gosh, why is she being so hostile?
My gosh.
Can you walk faster?
I'm starving now.
My stomach hurts
because I'm walking too fast.
Are you that hungry?
Sure. You know what time it is now.
It's past mealtime.
You're so punctual
when it comes to eating.
- Ga Yeon, you know what?
- What?
When she just started
working at a bar,
while other girls were busy
fixing their makeup,
she just ate the lunch she brought
in the corner of the room.
Really?
Hello, President Song.
- Hello, President Song.
- Hello.
So what happened?
Did you not get a scolding
from the owner?
I don't mind getting a scolding.
Whatever food they give you,
you will eat it deliciously.
So you guys should
never skip a meal.
You feel empty
when you are hungry.
We just never get to feel hungry.
Right. We can't even go on a diet
because of you.
Cho Yeon.
Come with me.
Are you all right?
It's not like you're a warrior.
You're just fearless.
We have emergency
response procedures...
and safety regulations here.
Is this your first time as a doctor?
Are you an intern?
Mind your own business.
How could I think
of those regulations...
when a kid was shaking with fear?
Did the interview go well?
Well... It wasn't bad.
Why would you say that?
You should've aced it...
so at least one of us
can leave this place.
I'll get a call and find out.
By the way,
you have a patient called Si Hoo.
Yoo Si Hoo.
He was admitted
with pediatric asthma.
Yes, so what?
He happens to be
the child of someone I know.
Take special care of him for me,
you know. Bye.
I take care of my patients
even if you don't tell me to.
How does he know the kid
that he'd even mention him?
Yoo Si Hoo. Si Hoo...
(Madam Jang Ok Boon)
Hi, Mom.
Na Hee, are you with a patient?
Can we talk?
I can talk. What's up?
Nothing's up.
When you came over for chicken,
I noticed that Gyu Jin
loved radish green kimchi.
I'll make that
and some cucumber kimchi.
Pick it up on your way home.
Forget it.
Why keep making kimchi
when you have a bad back?
I make it for you, of course.
Gyu Jin loves home-cooked food.
Forget it and forget about Gyu Jin.
I'm too busy to come by,
so don't bother.
Hey, hey.
If you're busy today, then tomorrow.
I'm busy tomorrow too.
Just don't make the kimchi.
Goodbye.
Gyu Jin, Gyu Jin.
Why does she love him so much?
She snaps whenever
I offer to make her food.
She always refuses.
What? Did she refuse again?
Of course.
She's too busy to come by.
What now?
We already salted the vegetables.
I know.
Gyu Jin seemed to love the kimchi.
No.
I shouldn't read his diary.
It's private.
Forget the privacy nonsense.
I should know. I'm his mom.
Dad talked on the phone
throughout the meal,
then went out for 30 minutes.
Dad looked like
he wanted to leave soon,
so I lied about
having a stomachache...
and asked him to take me home.
I had a lot to tell Dad.
Dad doesn't seem to
want to know about me anymore.
This... This scumbag.
(Son of a witch)
This jerk.
How annoying.
Seung Hyun, you...
Wait for me!
Why are you here, Mom?
I failed. I wanted to surprise you.
I saw your coat. It stood out.
Did it?
I dressed up. Is it a bit much?
Ji Hun.
How about skipping your lessons
and eating out with me?
Eat all you want.
Let's stuff ourselves.
You should eat too.
Don't keep feeding me.
Yes, of course, son.
Son.
Do you like skipping classes
to be with Mom?
It's not too bad.
Tell me if you want to do
anything else.
How about we go play VR games?
Or go sing at a noraebang?
I heard that
escape rooms are fun too.
Shall we try that?
There must be one... My gosh.
- Oh, dear.
- Are you okay, Mom?
My goodness.
What a mess.
I'm sorry. Did it get on you?
I'm fine.
It might leave a stain.
It's your favorite skirt.
Oh, no.
Ji Hun.
I'm sorry.
It's okay. It didn't get on me.
I wish you were a troublemaker.
You're too sweet.
I cause more trouble than you do.
I embarrass myself.
Hey. I need to order another drink.
What should I get?
(Neulpuleun Children's Hospital)
(Madam Jang Ok Boon)
What, Mom?
Where are you? Still at work?
Yes. I said I'm busy.
- What about Gyu Jin?
- He's busy too.
I know he must be.
About the radish green
kimchi I mentioned.
I said we don't need any.
We're really busy.
I know, you brat.
So I'm making a delivery
to your place.
I'll let myself in and put it...
in the fridge for you to eat.
It's fine, Mom.
Why would you even bother...
(Cohabitation Contract)
Mom, no!
No what?
You haven't left, have you?
If not...
I left already. I'm on the bus.
You can't, Mom. I said it's fine.
Go back to the store.
I'll come and get it.
It's fine. You said you're busy.
I know your house is a mess.
I won't touch anything.
I'll just leave the kimchi.
Don't worry.
Let's hang up now. You're busy.
Mom. Mom!
This is insane.
Yoon Gyu Jin, pick up.
To what do I owe the honor?
Be quiet. Where are you?
Why do you care where I am?
- My mom. She's on her way.
- What?
My mom is going to our place...
to put food in our fridge.
The Cohabitation Contract
on our living room door.
Your mother...
- Where are you?
- At work.
I'm leaving now. You must too.
- Okay.
- We must stop her.
We can't let her get in.
Okay, okay, hang up first.
Taxi!
- You fool!
- My gosh.
Are you trying to get killed?
Sorry. I'm sorry.
I'm very sorry. Sorry!
Thank you.
Hurry, hurry.
Move it.
She's getting in. Quick.
- Mom!
- Mother! Mother!
Mother!
What now? What do we do?
- What...
- What do you think?
Run. Quick!
You're dead if you lose her!
My arm almost fell off.
(Cohabitation Contract)
Mother. Mother!
Gyu Jin.
Mother...
Mom.
Song Na Hee. You...
(Once Again)
She's your first love, right?
The girl from church.
First love? As if.
Why is he so flustered?
Maybe his heart did skip a beat.
Let us be struck by wads of money.
- Something is really dropping.
- The ceiling is leaking!
Guys, the ceiling is leaking.
Water is dropping from the ceiling!
You're still beautiful
even though you retired.
Hi, Ga Hee. Have you been well?
Where on earth did they come from?
I can't help but be suspicious.
We're closed! My gosh.
We're here to give you a warning.