RUGAL
ALL CHARACTERS, PLACES,
ORGANIZATIONS, RELIGION AND INCIDENTS
PORTRAYED IN THIS DRAMA ARE FICTITIOUS
EPISODE 8
What are you doing?
Let me go.
Make sure you inhale as much as you can.
You won't be able to endure it
without this.
When I had my head underwater,
I didn't see how it would help train me.
But now, I've realized
that I owe my instructor big time.
Chief Choi, if this is Director Gu's trap,
there's a chance
that Dr. Oh might be just the bait.
So they have another agenda?
What could that be?
Me.
It crossed my mind
that he kidnapped Dr. Oh
because he is after my artificial eyes.
I'm a rare success case.
I'm ready to jump into their organization
and face anything that comes my way.
Are you willing to risk your life?
I'll lure them out, follow them,
and bring Dr. Oh out with me.
I will pay them back for everything.
Where are they now?
Hold on.
I can't stand this.
You didn't have a chance
to get it treated.
I can disinfect it later.
Or I can replace it if it's too damaged.
To me, this comes first.
You seem pretty experienced with this.
A third of my body consists
of artificial skin.
Of course, I'm an expert compared to you.
Try moving it.
It's much better.
Don't overdo yourself
until Bradley checks on it.
I'll handle all the physical dangers now.
All right. You're up.
Since you're up, why don't we use
this chance to get to know one another?
Here's my first question.
Where is this truck going?
Here's my second question.
What's this sewer smell?
What did you transport?
Look at you.
That's why I told not to move.
Here's my third question.
This is based on what I saw.
Give me a straight answer.
What are you doing with people you kidnap?
Did you just laugh?
I'll especially ask you
the fourth question.
You know the spray you used
on me earlier? Where's that?
-Here it is.
-No.
Now, you can talk?
Spare me.
Spare you?
When people begged you to spare them,
was there a time
you ever listened to them?
Back to my first question.
Where is this truck going?
You only need your mouth to answer me.
You prick, what took you so long?
Gwang-cheol!
This can't make a scar on me with this.
Why did you break the drone?
It did its duty by saving you.
-Are you all right?
-If I rest a bit.
-Where's Tae-woong?
-He came with me.
Let's go.
Answer me. Where is the truck going?
Choose.
Will you let your head get blown up
or try to remember the plate number?
Two, four, seven, eight.
No, is it two, four, seven, nine.
Tae-woong.
-Are you okay?
-I can handle it.
He was the lookout instead of the drone.
-Did you have a lot to take care of?
-No, not really.
I don't think Gi-beom made it out.
I know.
But he's not an easy match.
We'll focus on our task for now.
Do you even know where you're going?
I can tell that he does.
He's indeed my team leader.
-The roses are in full bloom today.
-Right.
-They look beautiful, don't they?
-Let's put them here.
But I was worried, you know.
In case they got cold.
-What about this one?
-Over there.
Did you enjoy the festival last time?
Before you sign the contract,
I'd like to hear how you're going
to eliminate Hwang Deuk-gu in detail.
Ma'am, how about these plates?
They look beautiful. I like both of them.
I actually picked out a plate.
Let me show it to you.
-Sounds great.
-Wait here.
Sure.
What do you think you're--
Why are you doing this?
Kang Gi-beom.
Kang Gi-beom?
What?
Did you think you wouldn't get caught?
You...
I thought you already knew
I wanted you dead.
Of course, I knew. I knew it very well.
Then, it's nothing to get upset about.
What? Were you scared
that you might get killed?
If that's not it,
are you jealous that I was secretly
working with Kang Gi-beom?
What are you
-talking about?
-I asked you if you were jealous.
That's a load of crap.
If you wanted, you could have
killed me on many occasions.
Why didn't you?
I doubt that
my assets made you hesitate.
I can sort of see why.
It's because you like me.
Get away from her.
I'll only warn you once.
Both of you are out of control.
Did you set this up
knowing I would be here?
I hear things, too.
Of course, I picked up a few things.
That's right.
Shoot me.
Get rid of that tacky silencer.
And just fire it away!
You don't think I can't?
The staff outside is Chairman Hyeon's.
Nothing good will come out
of displaying our dispute.
You are a vice-chairman, after all.
Behave like one.
Ms. Choi.
I thought it was too heavy
for you to carry.
I couldn't find the one I wanted.
I'll be out shortly.
Okay.
What's that jerk, Dr. Oh, doing?
Don't pretend you're that innocent.
I'm sure you've seen worse.
And must I mention
you've done worse as well?
You have
changed a lot.
I didn't change.
I adapted.
I'm sure you will adapt quickly.
You want me to kill
other people in exchange for my life?
Do you think your attempt of urging me
to keep a conscience will work?
We've worked for years
making progress and agreeing
to the sacrifice.
Don't you dare try
to justify murder with sacrifice.
Others must sacrifice for me to survive.
Dr. Oh, you must live, too.
Director Gu!
You just need to complete creating
the artificial eyes here.
Only then, you and I can live!
Kidnapping Dr. Oh,
luring us into this mess,
and doing all these crazy things
are to wait for me?
You won't do it even if it means death?
Don't expect me to help you in any way
unless it's for rehabilitation purposes.
All right, then.
Are you telling me your fancy artificial
eyes are a result of rehabilitation?
It was Kang Gi-beom who survived them.
He overcame the fear of death
and the pressure of the side effects
he may face his entire life.
His desperate need to live
made it possible for them to survive them.
Are you telling me that
all the technology I gathered so far
is less than a man's determination?
I only spoke the truth.
You'll be hearing the sounds
of your creations
falling apart from everywhere.
What are you planning to do?
The show starts
in a minute.
The truck with the plate number, 2478,
is in a different district.
The truck with the plate number, 2479,
started around where our team started.
I will share the route and the expected
destination of Truck 2479.
Hold on.
The truck suddenly changed its direction.
Let's follow the truck for now.
They were telling me the truth.
Their heads were about to explode.
Of course, they'd tell the truth.
I would've done the same.
What? No, you would let your head explode.
Look at you. Now that you're confident
about your defense,
I guess getting beaten up
doesn't scare you anymore.
Right. Definitely.
He makes a good shield.
Well, that was original.
You should specialize in that
and take the lead from now on.
I'm not modest
when it comes to my talents.
Just let me handle it.
I'll continue to be on the lookout.
Then, I'll trust you guys
and get some sleep.
-Step on it.
-Okay.
-Hello.
-How long will it take?
It's 10,000 won as long as it fits.
Come and check out these clothes.
This place looks pretty normal to me.
I shouldn't have broken the drone.
I'm sure Gi-beom is somewhere around here.
-Let's split and look for him.
-Okay.
What? That was a short ride.
Look at you transforming.
What? Are you happy to be back home?
-What's his problem?
-What?
What the...
Are you all right?
Hey, man.
-What's he doing?
-My gosh.
What is his problem?
-There's smoke.
-What's that?
-What's happening?
-What's going on?
-He's on fire.
-What is this?
-What?
-Smoke is coming out.
What a beautiful sight.
CHAIRMAN HYEON
He's finally calling me?
My gosh.
It's been a while, Chairman Hyeon.
There's been an explosion at the park
on the land that I own.
You did this, didn't you?
What will you do if I actually did it?
What?
Why did you ignore my warning?
-Do you know what this land was for?
-I sure do.
You and Choi Yong were planning
to build an apartment complex there.
But that plan of yours fell through.
I've decided to build a unique park there.
What do you think will happen
if you object to it?
What? Have you lost your mind?
What is this?
Bang!
Kill anyone and everyone
that gets in the way.
That's just beautiful.
What did they do to you guys this time?
First, can you please get off me?
Talk about perfect timing.
Hold on.
Tae-woong, it's dangerous. Run!
Those guys blew up?
Yes. Last time, it was just their heads.
They've gotten much stronger.
Both their strength and explosive power.
Is that possible though?
The abnormal thermal reaction
must be a side effect.
They're using
all of their physical energy in one blow,
until they turn into ashes.
Then we should deal with them
before they turn into ashes.
By the way, where are we now?
I don't think the lab is nearby.
It looks like those people are in danger.
Help!
It's time to put my treasure to use.
We need an ambulance.
-Take this guy to the hospital first.
-Okay.
An officer is hurt.
Send us backup and medics.
What is happening?
It's the top trending search now.
Even photos and videos of the scene
are circulating on social media.
Rugal might be exposed.
Delete them all.
But we can't do anything about the videos
that haven't been posted online.
We'll keep checking for new posts,
but we can't block everything.
They're spreading so quickly.
It happened just a few minutes ago.
Are they deliberately spreading
these things?
Sir, some media outlets
have already interviewed the victims.
A man showed up out of nowhere
and walked up to us.
Then he suddenly started drinking water
and blew up.
Gosh, I was so scared earlier.
I couldn't hear anything.
Maybe it was because of the explosion.
People were screaming,
but it felt so surreal.
Have you seen my kid?
Please help me find my kid.
My kid went to buy something to eat
but isn't back yet.
I'm glad you guys are okay.
We could've gotten rid of them all,
but they suddenly stopped attacking us
and ran off.
I don't think they ran away
because they were scared.
I think those weird guys
that look like test subjects
are following some kinds of orders.
Even in the trailer, they suddenly changed
and attacked me.
I'll go get the immune-boosting treatment.
He's bleeding.
It's the oil.
The machine is hurt.
There was an explosion
at the outdoor food market,
and the incident left
dozens of people injured.
The horrendous aftermath at the scene
reminds us of a war zone.
Reporter Kim Bo-reum is reporting
from the scene.
Reporter Bo-reum.
Hello. This is Kim Bo-reum,
reporting from the scene.
A mysterious explosion took place
40 minutes ago.
The police think it was a random attack
targeting unspecified individuals.
Some of the witnesses
who were at the scene
mentioned that they saw people
who looked like monsters.
Can you tell us about that?
Yes. One civilian who witnessed
the whole incident said
people who were wearing masks
fought with men with superhuman strength.
But the police denied it,
saying that the civilians probably saw
police officers,
firefighters, and paramedics.
What the hell do you want?
Some kind of order, shall I say?
I'm sure you've done this as a kid.
If you want to organize your toys,
you have to take them all out first
to start afresh.
All these sacrifices
for something stupid like that?
Take him.
You should get some rest too.
But I didn't do anything, Boss.
I brought that idiot here,
but you let Min-jun handle him.
I'm your right-hand man,
yet I couldn't even take charge
on this important day.
So? Did that hurt your feelings?
Or are you pissed off because you feel
like you're being pushed to the sidelines?
-That's not what I meant, Boss.
-Don't ever forget this.
We'll lose the big things if we obsess
over such little things. Both you and I.
We must never forget
who I used to be.
Welcome to your world, Hwang Deuk-gu.
-Was it you?
-No. Us.
And shoot.
I can sort of see why.
It's because you like me.
I will show you
what I'm capable of.
I have no appetite.
We have no idea
when Hwang Deuk-gu will act up again.
You should've just killed him in one blow.
I know I'm the one who taught you,
but it's not nice to be lectured.
Yes.
Neither of us
should get blood on our hands.
All we need to do is
make them hold the knife.
They'll fight and kill each other.
Exactly.
And we'll live.
Then he's probably dead.
Who?
Never mind. Just someone.
Ye-won, that being said...
In my opinion--
What brings you by at this hour?
You didn't watch the news?
The news? Did something happen?
Gosh, that bastard sent his boys
and caused a huge scene at the park.
-"That bastard"? Who?
-Hwang Deuk-gu.
I invested so much to build
an apartment complex by the park,
but that asshole totally ruined my plan.
I mean, who'd want to live there now?
My gosh.
Wait until things quiet down.
What?
I make all the decisions.
If you need fast cash, I'll help you out.
Look at you acting all generous and giving
with Chairman Ko's money.
Enjoy it while it lasts.
If you have another money source,
go ahead and mobilize it.
Then your position will be threatened.
You said we should help each other out.
Are you trying to say
it's every man for himself now?
Just so you know,
I don't like loud fights.
Is your arm okay?
Yes, it's fine.
But you seem upset.
Earlier at the park,
we saved an injured man and asked
the police to take him to the hospital.
But he was actually a member of Argos
disguised as one of the victims.
While I was looking away,
he shot two police officers.
We've seen them do shit like that
a number of times.
I know that it's nothing surprising,
but getting blindsided like that...
It just doesn't feel nice.
Right, that's what made me so furious
back when I was a detective.
Bastards like them
even take advantage of your sincerity.
I found it unforgivable.
Exactly.
That's what makes you really angry.
By the way, when did you get that?
When I was young.
-I got it done because I wanted to.
-What?
Oh, to survive?
"This is where I belong."
I guess I thought I needed
to separate myself from the world.
They probably didn't want
to let you go easily.
This is how I paid for my sister's life.
Why did you want to join Rugal?
Because Rugal was after me.
I thought I should join the enemy
to completely separate myself
from those bastards.
Simple and concise. I like that answer.
When I first came here,
your name was all over the news.
"The psychopath cop who murdered people."
Things like that?
Even back then,
I didn't believe any of it.
You'd never do such a thing.
You see, I don't open up easily.
Once I trust someone,
I totally confide in that person.
I'm the same way.
How about we have some beer
when you're done with that?
Sounds good.
Hey, "Made by Bradley." It was awesome.
Gosh, that's nothing.
I made other things too.
I'll show you later.
"Later"? Why later? Show me now.
Okay, I'll show you.
Okay, aim.
Here I go.
One, two, three!
You saw that?
That's like a lion's roar.
If it works properly,
you can completely destroy
your enemy with it.
Okay, it's a keeper. What's next?
-Something else?
-Yes.
Jeez, you're such a gearhead.
Hey, are you ready to spend some cash?
Of course.
Right, you're rich.
Okay, I'll show you.
Go.
It'll take a while
for the wound to close up.
You know I'm not the most patient person.
Wait until you're fully recovered.
I can work while recovering.
It's not like
we have all this time to waste.
You're strong enough.
You don't need to act all tough.
Had I actually been strong enough,
I would've beat them all up
and dragged Hwang Deuk-gu by the collar.
And I'm sure you were hoping for that,
deep down.
I'm always grateful to you.
After my father passed away,
everyone pitied me.
But you were always tough on me.
To be honest,
it hurt my feelings a lot at first.
But I quickly realized
that I had to be tough to survive.
And that I must survive
to get back at those bastards.
There were a lot of emotions
you had to digest all by yourself.
POLICE UNIVERSITY
No...
Gosh.
Dad.
Dad...
Why was my dad
working at this university lab
instead of the police station?
What the heck was he working on?
And why did he die?
Your dad
had volunteered to lead
the police's secret experiment.
And as you can see, it failed.
The test subject who fled
killed him.
His funeral will be kept confidential.
Not many will be invited.
Because he's a failure,
his death must be kept a secret?
But he was working for the police.
What about the bastard who killed my dad?
We'll do our best
to track down the culprit,
but he worked on a classified project.
The investigation will be sacrificed
for the sake of keeping it hidden.
You won't do your best
in order to catch my dad's killer?
Then I'll find the bastard
who killed him myself.
Making a move before you're strong enough
will only hurt you.
Then wait and see
how much I get hurt.
Name?
Name, you prick!
Hey, let's grab a cup of coffee sometime.
Have a good one.
At first, I ignored your warning
and took matters into my own hands.
It led to my demise.
Then I made a vow in front of you.
I will never
let my emotions sway me again.
If only I was a human weapon though.
If I'm injured again,
please make me part-robot like the others.
Being too strong could break you.
-I'm not afraid of that.
-Mi-na...
But still, you worry about me.
I guess it proves
your lack of trust in me.
That's not it.
Then say this instead.
"Get well soon.
We still have a lot to do.
I need you out there."
That's right.
I need you for many tasks to come.
Guys, why do you all seem depressed?
Here.
Where do you get all these?
Tell me if these aren't enough.
I have them stashed all over the place.
Tae-woong, there's one in the back too.
It's a moment like this where
I wonder about your past.
Rich, fancy, and super stylish.
That's who I was.
Does the rich keep
stashes of snacks around?
This is what you call being well-prepared.
Jeez.
I don't appreciate
being mocked for my generosity,
but I'll let it slide
since I'm the mama bird.
All right. Let's drink then.
Thanks.
Mi-na astonishes me
every time I think about her.
-This is out of the blue.
-When she was kidnapped,
she took on nine men.
That's right.
And they weren't some hillbillies.
She doesn't have
any mechanical improvements like us
which means she didn't have extra help.
She's not scared of anything, is she?
Has she always been this way?
She used to be even more reckless.
Anyway, she's the strongest woman I know.
I know I can rely on her.
She's a shoulder I can lean on.
No one can be strong all the time.
Anyway, we still don't know
where they took Dr. Oh,
so let's not lose our focus.
-Got it.
-Sure.
Welcome to hell, Kang Gi-beom!
Tae-woong, you were right.
I shouldn't have let him live.
Talk about perfect timing.
Let's not let those bastards
spread depression upon us.
We'll pay them back with interest.
You know,
didn't it feel like they were
controlled out of there in a hurry?
The enhanced soldiers
probably went back to the lab.
What more can they be up to?
Now that they can use Dr. Oh,
the damage they can do
will be even larger.
We must blow up Hwang Deuk-gu's lab first.
If you're going to go in there,
count me in too.
Sure thing.
Where did she go?
Hey, Mi-na.
What's this?
Had some beer, did you?
Yes, with the guys yesterday.
How did you know?
Because I know you inside out.
Wait, with the guys?
So you guys are having fun without me?
Alcohol is bad for your recovery,
so don't be too upset.
Still, I thought my pretty face
would help you get better.
Cover it. You're only annoying me.
Jeez.
Actually, I'm all better now.
Not according to Susan.
I know myself better than she does.
Like always,
you have everything under control.
No wonder the guys trusted you.
Trusted me with what?
Even when you were kidnapped
and in danger,
we were able to calmly plan our next move.
Because they trusted
that you'd find a way to stay alive.
What do you mean by that?
Tae-woong!
Take it. Gi-beom's on the line.
Why didn't he call HQ?
Well, it's a long story,
but his eyes stopped streaming live
after blacking out.
Things seem urgent.
Gi-beom, did you blackout?
Why? What's going on? Are you okay?
Keep it down, will you?
We need to be careful about this.
-Chief Choi can't know.
-Speak, Gi-beom.
I'm close to where Mi-na was taken.
Once I get there,
I'll be handing over this phone.
You'll give up
your connection to Choi Ye-won?
We'll have to offer a decent deal
to get what we want.
Won't you end up in danger too?
You'll have to come before that happens.
I can't fight them all by myself.
Got it.
This is a chance
to get close to Hwang Deuk-gu.
It seems like a worthy gamble.
What do you say, Tae-woong?
Wherever you are, we'll close in on you.
Gi-beom, just stay alive.
Sure, I'll see you soon.
So you used me being kidnapped
to make a strategic move?
It was an awesome one as well,
but the bastards went the other way.
We succeeded halfway.
For whatever reason,
we found out that Choi Ye-won
could be Hwang Deuk-gu's weakness.
I doubt this is the time
to share our thoughts,
but I'm glad that I could be of help.
Next time, I'll come up
with a more meticulous plan.
I'd definitely appreciate
an upgrade in the escape plan.
Of course.
Mi-na, first think about fully recovering.
Got it.
Don't you need prior approval
for a terror attack of this size?
Now that a different man is in charge,
the details of the contract
should be revised.
That's bold of you.
We can't be controlled
with carrots and sticks anymore.
Consider this as my message.
No.
It's my declaration.
Are we clear?
You're very close to crossing the line.
As if I've ever stayed within lines.
Those freaks made by the government?
I know very well
that their purpose is to handle Argos.
That is why I wanted to make a stand.
The damage will keep multiplying.
You think you can handle it?
Stop this right away.
It's what you get for crossing the line.
From this moment on,
things will only get more entertaining.
Mun-bok, did you sleep here again.
I was too busy writing up reports
of the Argos members arrested at the fair
to sleep anyway.
No one's admitting to anything.
Take it easy, okay?
I would if I could.
What the fuck!
-What?
-Holy shit!
What the hell?
-What...
-What is that?
-What on earth is that?
-Is that a person?
He seems to be dead.
Hold on.
What's the matter?
-Are you okay?
-Look over there!
-What the hell?
-It's a dead person.
-My gosh.
-Hello?
Yes, someone's hanging from the bridge.
-Over there.
-What's going on?
-Shit.
-Unbelievable.
Quickly. Take a photo when you can.
-What the hell?
-No way.
-Shit.
-Can you believe it?
-Take a photo.
-Who could've done this?
Bastards.
They won't stop playing dirty.
I WAS KILLED BY
THE SICK MURDERER KANG GI-BEOM
"The sick murderer Kang--"
That must be taken down.
Stay inconspicuous.
Subtitle translation by Hye-lim Park
My memories are shaky
and my emotions are changing often.
We found the place where Dr. Oh is.
I will put him on the game board
and play with him.
How can I kill people who don't die
even if I kill them?
I'll just make them want to die.
Run away. People know that you are alive.
The real criminal is the person
who is standing in the center of all this.
I can't end things like this.