ALL CHARACTERS, PLACES,
ORGANIZATIONS, RELIGION AND INCIDENTS
PORTRAYED IN THIS DRAMA ARE FICTITIOUS
What did the police say?
Bong Man-cheol was alive when
they released him, but now, he's dead.
They'll sweep it under the rug.
That's what Choi Ye-won wants, too.
But he's a big name in their industry.
Do you think they can make it go away?
The Commissioner-General
died this morning.
The Commissioner-General?
Public sentiment is already bad.
And now, the head of the police
was poisoned to death
on the same day when the gang leader died.
Revealing this won't help them in any way.
-Who on earth is on our side?
-Do you need more people on our side?
Aren't we enough?
What about the guys?
EPISODE 12
Let's see.
See? You should put that on sooner.
Do I have to wear this?
Even our stubborn team leader
put it on, too.
Let's do it for our teamwork.
Fine.
It never crossed my mind
that Seol Min-jun would help me.
He didn't talk as if he was bewitched,
and something was off about him, too.
He must've been resolute once he decided
to become an undercover agent.
He was good enough to fool Hwang Deuk-gu.
He stayed in there as long as
he could for his last chance.
He must've been lonely.
But you're not, right?
What?
Well, I'm not alone.
By the way, what happened to Choi Ye-won?
She called to ask for your help,
and Mi-na answered it.
She didn't have to answer it. Why did she?
It probably got on her nerves.
And she was pissed, too.
Ye-won was one of the people
behind this mess, too.
I bet it was intense.
We handled it pretty well.
Instead of perceiving her as a threat,
Mi-na decided to treat her as a resource.
She's learning.
She can see the bigger picture.
But Choi Ye-won isn't an easy target.
She can cut a deal
with the Commissioner-General.
She saw what we're capable of.
She'll call again.
Like you told me,
if Choi Yong has turned his back on her,
she has no choice but to team up
with us or Hwang Deuk-gu.
If she chooses Hwang Deuk-gu,
we'll be her target.
"We"?
I like the sound of that.
What?
Look. I told you I have sharp eyes.
I picked the perfect size and color
for them. Right?
Gi-beom, don't I look slick?
I want to buy this in every color.
You are way over the top.
I think I'll look great in blue, too.
Get me another one if you can.
Hold on. Are you implying that I should
go through a near-death experience again?
I know you'll come back alive.
Don't whine.
I'm happy that you guys like the jacket.
But don't you think we stand out
too much in these jackets?
That's not a bad thing, per se.
If we're going to get exposed,
we will choose when and how
we will show ourselves to the world.
Chief Choi gave us his permission.
30 MINUTES AGO
I can understand
where you're coming from, Gi-jun.
But I cannot let you do that.
-Why not?
-It's dangerous.
Your parents and older sister
were very scared.
I cannot let you go through
that pain again.
He's not a bad guy, right?
-What?
-The guy I saw.
Gi-jun.
My father taught me
that lying is the worst sin.
If I stay silent now,
I'll be a liar.
15 MINUTES AGO
I'll send you a video.
Let's talk while we watch.
What is it?
I'm a fifth-grader in Class Three
at Yuyeon Elementary.
-My name is Kwon Gi-jun.
-Let me see that, too.
This boy...
Do you remember the lawyer we saved?
The one who did YouTube streaming.
I see. That guy.
Yes, this is his son.
The men who harmed us
were wearing bloody masks.
The men in black masks saved me.
-I guess he remembers us.
-Yes.
But you won't post this online, right?
He wants to tell people about you.
I managed to stop him
from uploading this on social media.
But he's planning to film videos
post them when he gets a chance.
I was curious about your opinions.
Isn't this too dangerous?
A boy is willing to risk his life for us.
We can't hide now.
Please don't tell me you want to
reveal who we are.
Why can't we?
As long as the chief approves.
Our effort wasn't all for nothing.
We have a reliable supporter like Gi-jun.
I almost teared up. I'm serious.
Our records were always wiped.
Hey.
Our duty is to help and leave without
a trace. Why would you get emotional?
Goodness, you're so dramatic.
Mi-na, we have to leave proof
of our effort at least
for insurance purposes.
Or they should at least make a clip of us.
Boom, boom, boom.
And the eyes.
Something like this, you know.
Anyway, reveal us or not,
it's become a different fight now.
Hwang Deuk-gu is trying to bury us
out in the open. We ought to do something.
The only thing left to do
is returning the favor tenfold.
All right, then.
So we have somewhat of a plan now.
And our outfits are ready, too.
Where should we start?
We have some killer moves, don't we?
Don't be so shocked.
He brought this upon himself.
What I want to know is your opinion.
Should I kill him
or save him?
You go first, old man.
Well...
Kill him.
Kill him? What's your reason?
Reducing the pain he's feeling
is the humane thing to do.
-What if I don't want to?
-He won't be any use to us.
We can't even recycle him in that state.
Just end it.
My goodness, Director Gu.
Thank you for your fantastic video
and all of your help with the research.
No problem.
But what else
can you do for me now?
Pardon?
Your research was a failure.
And you're a weak old man.
Hold on. I will do a good job
if you just let me--
You told me to get rid of
what's useless. You moron.
Didn't I tell you that
he brought this upon himself?
You saved him once before,
so I need you to save him again this time.
If you didn't mess
with Seol Min-jun's head,
he could have died without any pain.
But you were the one who talked
about what's humane or not.
Come in.
What are you doing?
Do you want to be a YouTuber or something?
If I'm doing this, I'll do it right.
You just released the trailer.
Why release the movie now?
I've got to strike while the iron is hot.
I need to make the best
of the chance I got.
You're not putting out feelers with this.
You're taking it all the way.
An eye for an eye and a tooth for a tooth.
He exposed me, so I expose him.
I'll tell all of his dirty secrets.
Sure. Go big since you decided to do it.
Do you need my help?
No. Get out.
Okay.
Break a leg.
I'm not a murderer.
I neither killed my wife
nor harmed my own eyes.
I know this will be hard to believe
as it's contrary to what you heard.
Just because you can understand it,
it doesn't mean it's true.
And I had to live as a ghost
for the same reason.
I want to
set my life Argos fabricated straight.
You can criticize me
or choose to not believe me.
But shouldn't you at least
get all the facts?
What are you doing?
No!
Do you know how many cold cases got buried
without any evidence?
Will you let your loved ones die again?
Answer me! Answer me, you murderer!
Will you once again
become victims like fools?
Will you just watch these subhuman thugs
do whatever they want?
Starting now,
I'll do more than catch the murderer
who killed my wife.
I'm going to destroy all of this trash
that's causing our society
to collapse.
You can watch for yourself
and decide who's telling the truth.
Lastly, this is for you, Deuk-gu.
I'm sorry to break it to you,
but your good days are over now.
This is Yuyeon Police Station.
-You borrowed money from Mopin Trust?
-Argos?
-When was that?
-Your husband went missing a month ago?
-Yes.
-It's all Argos' fault.
It's Argos' fault if there's a robbery
or if their daughter comes home late.
And the taxes went up
because of them, too.
Our world is finally on the right track.
Is hijacking a bus the right thing to do?
IS HIJACKING A BUS THE RIGHT THING TO DO?
Is torturing people with poisonous gas
the right thing to do?
What are you doing, Gwang-cheol?
Gwang-cheol.
Hey.
Did you know we have a new nickname?
-What nickname?
-Argos Hunters.
They named us Hunters?
I'll read a comment.
"It's so obvious that they are dirtbags,
but the police can't arrest them.
Please come to the Cheongil Intersection
and catch them."
-Cheongil Intersection?
-Yes.
-Please spare us!
-I'm sorry.
-Please spare us.
-Spare us.
-Is this for real?
-Is a punch enough to fling a man away?
Obviously, it's a movie shoot.
I hated the very sight of Argos.
-That hit the spot.
-Every night,
-thugs cause a scene.
-How much, Hunters?
-Everyone's making a report.
-They might come.
I've been waiting with a camera
for two hours.
-Looking for people to wait...
-I'll wait until you come.
-...for Hunters together.
-K.O.
We didn't film this.
I'm glad that we finally have
the people on our side.
-People on our side...
-How many comments did we get?
I didn't know all these people
were rooting for us.
Tae-woong.
Where did you get this pose?
It's awesome.
I did that?
All right. It's my turn, right?
Where to?
Ready, action.
-The boss lady is here. Listen to her.
-I bet this is all scripted.
They are getting totally crushed.
I'll like and subscribe
as that's the only thing I can do.
I love you.
Repeat after me. "I'm sorry."
-I'm sorry.
Louder. "I'm sorry!"
-I'm sorry!
Dirtbags belong to the trunk of the car.
Everyone, go.
Left, left, left.
There are videos
that have recently gone viral.
In the videos, these individuals
show up at the crime scene
out of nowhere and round up the criminals.
What's interesting is that the criminals
that were rounded up in the videos
were transported to nearby police stations
from the crime scene.
It seems these individuals are trying to
set their act apart from terror attacks.
Check the trunk.
Wait...
Someone left the following comment
online about these videos.
A nationwide invitation
from the heroes in black masks
to bring down Argos.
V is dead.
The Commissioner-General who was
poisoned and V who was killed
had been in contact with Hwang Deuk-gu.
Serving our country comes with a price.
Do you think
I have never met Ko Yong-deok?
According to the analysis
of the yogurt drink,
it matched the narcotic drug
sold and distributed by Argos.
And I have confirmed Hwang Deuk-gu
was near the scene where V was killed.
Are you implying that
this was Hwang Deuk-gu's doing?
I have found evidence
that V tried to get into Rugal's server
before dying.
Put an end to this now.
Pardon?
I'm barely managing to keep
the press from having a field day.
Before this gets out of control,
hand over a few of them
and put an end to this.
You know what?
The people will be satisfied
once there's blood.
With your capability,
you can form another team of Rugal.
Don't you think so?
You'll change your mind
once you watch that video.
Secret research and illegal experiments.
The number of likes
is more than a simple number.
The people are showing their support
for the people who made
the impossible possible.
Here's how people will see Rugal.
Rugal
will be the heartbreaking sacrifice
of the police
and our country's last-ditch decision.
Take this twice a day after your meals.
-I won't be able to call you now?
-What?
I might feel a lot of pain.
If you are, you can take it three times--
And you might be curious
about how I'm doing.
I'm pretty famous on social media.
It won't take long to look me up.
Not you. You might be curious about me.
You'll probably be kind and beautiful.
I'm not kind.
Was I deceived, then?
I consider this my second chance at life
and live a good life.
I won't forget you.
-You won't say goodbye?
-I already did.
If I say goodbye to her,
I might not want to leave.
Let's go, Tae-woong.
We're really leaving.
That's their headquarters.
They seem new.
I hired a security firm.
Choi Yong is using this momentum
to win the guys over to his side.
I don't trust anyone now.
I can understand.
I was worried when I found out
that you were gone.
I'm glad you're okay.
I still can't believe
that Man-cheol is dead.
And he was killed by Yong
whom he followed like a brother.
Don't you remember
Man-cheol was going to kill you?
I do, but I doubt that
he was able to pull the trigger.
We've known each other for so long.
I'm sorry to ruin the mood,
but we don't have time to get sentimental.
What did you do with the body?
He was shot, so it must've been difficult.
It will be concluded as an accident.
Whatever happens,
I'll make sure that it does.
I'll take over Man-cheol's business.
It's better that I do, so that way,
I can give you more support.
I have something else in mind.
Like what?
Why do you think
something like this happened?
It's because I gave others power.
It may be peaceful when it's balanced.
But the smallest difference
will lead to its collapse.
So Mi-joo,
my plan is to take over everything myself.
-Ye-won.
-No need to feel anxious.
What's mine is yours.
So in the end, you'll have it all.
In order for me to do that, I must
get rid of Yong by using Hwang Deuk-gu.
Well, I wouldn't mind
if it was vice-versa, either.
Let me warn you.
You can never work with Hwang Deuk-gu.
Disbandment deferred for now.
PERSONNEL FILE
SIX YEARS AGO
KOKO ARCADE
Did all the informants get whacked?
WOO CHAN-MIN, KIM JAE-JUNG, KIM JO-HAN
KANG BEOM-U, NAM GWANG-U, CHOI U-YONG
YUN HYEON-SIK, SEOL MIN-JUN
Seol Min-jun...
This is where he was last seen.
COMPUTER GAMES
ARCADE
White fire.
I've gotten pretty good at these games
because you always suggest we meet here.
You still have a long way to go.
Many of us got busted.
I'm relieved
that you're alive.
-How did you escape?
-I never said I did.
Let me ask you one thing.
Can I
trust you?
I won't stop until you can return
to the police force.
That is my answer.
Will that day come?
I thought putting in a coin
would start a new game,
but I realized that reality is different
from these games.
However, I will not die
as a member of Argos.
Because I am
a police officer.
Yes.
Don't look.
Forgive me for this.
POLICE
-What? Hwang Deuk-gu?
-What's he doing here?
-Isn't that Hwang Deuk-gu?
-What's going on?
I'm an innocent citizen trying to get
some protection of the police.
What?
Those Argos hunters are harassing us.
Are you kidding me?
I'm not in the mood
to crack jokes with you.
Bring Kang Gi-beom to me.
I'm not asking you to do it for free.
I'll confess to a few things.
What do you say?
You've got nothing to lose.
Hey, quack.
Do you watch us all day long like this?
That's creepy.
Well, I need to do this to manage things.
Pay attention to the other members too.
Well, what's that called? "Likes"?
I'm getting all the likes.
I think you like it.
What's this?
Another one of these?
"Tell me where Hwang Deuk-gu is.
I have a deep grudge against him too"?
-Who is this?
-We've been getting messages like this.
What? Why?
Well, I commented as if I know some things
and talked shit to the internet trolls.
You must've already tracked
their IP addresses though.
Yes, I got construction sites
for all of them.
Construction sites?
Choi Yong?
I guess the rest of Argos are after him.
Hey, this is great. Go ahead and give them
a few pieces of information.
I think it's a good strategy.
We can create an opportunity for ourselves
by driving them into a corner.
Stop looking at these things
and get some work done.
I never see you doing any work.
-Hey.
-Gi-beom.
Hwang Deuk-gu is here.
Hwang Deuk-gu?
He's asking us to protect him from you.
He voluntarily went there?
I don't know what he's up to,
but he's even confessed to a few things.
I just wanted to let you know.
You don't need to come.
I thought I should let you know
before I call Chief Choi.
No, I'll come now.
Keep that bastard there.
He voluntarily went to the police station
and asked for protection against us.
-Do you believe that?
-No.
Then you don't need to go there.
Maybe he wants to stay out
of the internal strife.
He's even confessed to a few things.
-I have no idea what he's cooking up.
-Don't forget.
Bastards like him ought to be judged
by the law, no matter what.
Come with me.
Sure, if you need me.
I found something you'd like.
Put that away.
She looks so much like
Kang Gi-beom's dead wife.
Are you saying that dead woman
came back to life?
Or...
Is she one of them?
As you know, we use the dark web
to sell drugs.
What about it?
Porn videos are also sold on the dark web.
This face totally jumped out at me.
You fool, that's what you were doing
instead of working?
This is also part of my work.
I need to see
whether they'll sell or not--
Whatever. Go on.
Take a good look. She looks just like her.
-Are you sure?
-Pardon?
Did you confirm that she's actually alive?
No, I've only seen her on the internet.
If it's concerning Kang Gi-beom,
I should step in myself.
Officer Kim, come out for a second.
I heard you turned yourself in
to make me come here.
Lunatic.
Attempting to overthrow
the government is not a minor crime.
You're right.
It'll be difficult
even if I hire a good lawyer.
I'll have to rot in jail
for at least 20 years.
But you know what?
Why is everyone you are looking for
found around me?
What the fuck are you saying?
Min Dal-ho, Seol Min-jun,
and...
Kim Yeo-jin.
I do not want to hear the last name
coming out of that filthy mouth.
I heard he asked for police protection.
Why is he in the holding cell?
He said Gi-beom might attack him.
He asked me to lock him up.
And he even confessed to what he did?
Yes.
I want to go in,
but I can't ask a police officer
to violate the law.
Detective Yang,
you never violated the law.
-I'll take care of the rest--
-Conserve your energy
so that you can put it to better use.
I should use it
to deal with jerks like him.
Thank you.
I turned the CCTV camera off.
Don't be scared.
I'll beat you up to a pulp
and hand you over to the prosecution.
You won't even be able
to lay a finger on me.
And on your execution day,
I'll show up and kill you.
What do you say? Nice plan, right?
Look at you making a promise
you can't even keep.
You'll go crazy before that.
How did you know?
I'm so excited right now
that I feel like I might go crazy.
Kim Yeo-jin is alive.
What did you just say?
Shall I say it again?
Your wife, Kim Yeo-jin.
She's still alive.
I know where she is.
Why are you just standing there?
Go get your wife.
Don't let that bastard trick you.
Han Tae-woong.
I know a lot about you as well.
The traitor who lost an arm
after losing his sister.
People don't change
even if their environment changes.
Know your place. It's despicable
to see you acting like a hero.
Similar photos found
on a pornography site on the dark web.
-Track her down.
-Yes, you should.
Absolutely!
You must track her down.
Verify the photo.
Are you all right? What's going on?
I heard about your special eyes.
Hey, Kang Gi-beom.
I was right, wasn't I?
Did you see it?
Did you check the corpse
and made sure she was dead?
What's the matter?
Are you seeing Choi Ye-won or something?
You're not happy to see your wife again?
Don't bullshit me, you psycho.
Gi-beom! Don't let him trick you!
You'd better find her soon.
If she gets sold again,
then that will be it.
Shut the fuck up.
No matter what you do,
you won't get out in one piece this time.
I'm sure Kang Gi-beom thinks differently.
What?
Hey, Kang Gi-beom. Face your reality.
If you want to get something out of this,
you'll have to let me go
with your own two hands.
Gi-beom.
Kang Gi-beom!
BLISS
I can tell
it's your first time here.
This way, please.
It seems like you already know the drill.
Take your time and pick one.
Where is this woman?
Jessy?
Where is she?
She's pretty special.
Come with me.
Hey, what's up?
It seems like he's in shock.
What's going on?
The chip is pulsating so hard.
Hwang Deuk-gu told him
that Yeo-jin is alive.
That's bullshit.
Don't tell me Gi-beom believes him.
He verified it with his artificial eyes
before coming here.
Where are you now?
Don't tell anyone about this.
I'll find him and return to the HQ.
Okay, Tae-woong.
Call me.
Out of the way.
I'm just here to find someone.
Hey!
Tae-woong!
Hey, you're...
You're alive.
I'm pretty sure this isn't your turf.
Without you, we're like a doormat.
All the other guys left the gang
and found other jobs.
We meet up from time to time
and talk about you.
Help me find my colleague.
The thing is...
This place is pretty dangerous.
Who is dangerous?
-Bring her to me at once.
-You're a tough guy.
Be careful, or you might get whacked--
Go ahead and kill me.
Both you and I ended up here,
which means we're done for anyway.
What are you waiting for? Just kill me!
BLISS
They make and distribute
deep fake pornography.
What does "deep fake" mean?
It refers to a type of synthetic porn
that is generated by combining
specific people's faces and body parts
using AI technologies.
Do you want to see the real deal?
Then beg Deuk-gu!
Tell me the truth,
or I'll kill everyone in this building.
She's not here.
Did something happen?
You look so anxious.
Well...
Never mind.
I can't tell you at the moment.
Is it about Tae-woong? Or Gi-beom?
He'll call. Let's just wait for now.
Sure, if you say so.
But who will call?
Gi-beom or Tae-woong?
Gwang-cheol.
Well...
Come to think of it,
I never confirmed Yeo-jin's death.
The last I saw of her, she was dying.
Yeo-jin.
And I couldn't even attend her funeral.
Do you believe she's alive?
I believed that she was dead.
Let's tell Chief Choi.
I don't want him to be concerned.
Then,
Do you know what
Hwang Deuk-gu was right about?
I only heard things about Yeo-jin's death.
Would he
have told you the truth though?
It's why I want to find out
what exactly happened that night
and what I missed.
Then...
you'll need Min Dal-ho.
While keeping the chief in the dark?
Yes, for now.
I'm only telling you
because we never keep secrets.
Don't worry. My lips are sealed.
Is there anything I can help you with?
Just letting us do what needs to be done
is how you can help us.
But Tae-woong,
could her being alive
be a good thing at this point?
I'm not sure.
If this doesn't end well,
we'll be in big trouble.
Considering how Gi-beom could get hurt...
Well, it's hard to tell what's right.
Getting hurt
is the same for us as well.
I know.
But you know what?
Why is everyone you are looking for
found around me?
Did you see it?
Did you check the corpse
and made sure she was dead?
There's no evidence to suggest
that she didn't die that day.
I knew there wouldn't be holes
with the paperwork.
We must take another approach.
Yes, it's me.
I was craving bread when I was in jail.
Get some of the ones he might like, okay?
Kang Gi-beom?
Han Tae-woong!
I thought you were dead.
Is playing dead a hobby of yours?
That's not why we're here.
What?
Min Dal-ho,
you will answer my questions truthfully.
What the hell are you talking about?
Kim Yeo-jin.
Was it you who killed her?
Why ask when you saw everything?
Oh, right.
You didn't see everything.
Just kill him and save us our time.
No, wait. Hold on!
What's wrong?
I'm only doing what you did to me.
What makes me sick is that
your face was the last thing I saw.
It's only fair that I'm your last too.
I didn't kill her!
-That's a lie.
-It's not.
It wasn't me.
-Was it one of the guys with you that day?
-No.
Only you guys were there,
so don't fuck with me.
That's not true. There was someone else.
-What?
-There was someone else
before we went in.
Hey, who are you?
I took care of the girl. They want you to
take out the guy's eyes and not kill him.
What? Why?
It's easier to pin it on him.
Okay.
Who was that? Who was the bastard?
How could I have recognized
someone in a mask?
But you would know who sent him!
It was probably Deuk-gu.
He was the one who sent us to you too.
And once again
we're back with Hwang Deuk-gu.
RELIABLE, TRUSTWORTHY
Mi-na.
Over here.
It's been a while, Mun-bok.
Let's head inside.
Mun-bok,
you were the first
to arrive on the scene
the day Yeo-jin was attacked, right?
Yes.
I was nearby.
Did you have plans with Gi-beom?
Not exactly.
Gi-beom was in a terrible mood
after being grilled
by the disciplinary committee.
I was heading over to his place
to buy him a drink.
Did you spot anything odd
at his place that night?
Something odd?
According to the case files,
there was no sign of forced entry
into his house.
How could Min Dal-ho get in
without breaking the door?
Let's get this straight.
Officially, Min Dal-ho
isn't a suspect anymore.
An alibi puts him
somewhere away from the scene.
But you know that isn't true.
To have forced his way in,
the front door had to be broken
or at least be kicked in.
According to the case files,
none of that happened.
That's one of the reasons
why Gi-beom was made a prime suspect.
Is there a possibility
of a third-party being involved?
Not Gi-beom, but someone he knew...
Hold on a second.
Is that what you came here to ask me?
I'm being dead serious right now.
There's the man
who put himself behind bars.
The law sure has its perks, right?
Even a thug like you
can feel safe from people like me.
And who the fuck are you?
Finally,
I get to see your face.
It must because you lack presence,
Lee Gwang-cheol.
I see you haven't been updated.
Well, I took care of all your underlings.
I guess you don't use the internet.
I shouldn't have bothered
trying to track you down.
You would've flocked over to me
one way or another anyway.
Have you heard of digging your own grave?
It's like biting yourself in the ass.
Sounds familiar, right?
You're all the same, aren't you?
You and all your cheeky, arrogant advice.
Now get lost!
Enjoy your stay, then.
He truly is something else.
The bastard is ice-cold.
Gwang-cheol, don't be a wimp.
Damn it.
The records show
just how meticulous Argos was.
His colleagues died
and the disciplinary committee
suspended him.
His wife nagged him at home
and things escalated
leading to him killing her.
After coming to his sense,
he couldn't stand what he had done,
so he mangled his eyes.
That's a tight scenario
they cooked up for Gi-beom.
I asked all of the questions
and confirmed what we needed to know,
but something just doesn't feel right.
The security camera footage was erased,
so there's nothing but testimonies
to go on.
Gwang-cheol.
Why are you walking so fast?
While you were with Detective Yang,
I paid Hwang Deuk-gu a visit.
Hwang Deuk-gu?
How did it feel to meet him face-to-face?
I'm not sure.
Back then, I was too busy
fighting for my life.
I got the chills though.
Doesn't he seem like the type
to shred anyone who gets in his way?
Like the cannibal killer.
If you don't stay strong,
he'll eat you up in seconds.
It's why I admire Gi-beom.
Remember the jazz bar?
The eyes malfunctioned due to an error
and he couldn't see properly.
He held his composure though
until they came back online.
I should start training
my brain waves then
to develop mental strength.
Could it be possible?
I'll at least try.
Anyway, let's go.
Damn, he gives me the heebie-jeebies.
Compare the knife that attacked my eyes
to the one that stabbed Yeo-jin.
One wound's size is different
from all other wounds.
They probably stabbed her multiple times
to frame me, so why use a different knife?
Nothing found at the scene
could've inflicted the fatal wound on her.
Can you obtain footage
from nearby security cameras?
They probably erased the footage
since the storage period is over.
I don't carry you around
to tell me what I already know.
Find a way, you prick.
Why do you think Hwang Deuk-gu
is obsessed with you?
It's fucked-up nonsense,
but he says I have everything
to be his pacemaker.
It's true that you provoke him.
Is this all my fault then?
Stopping your crusade here
is also an option.
Letting our fight be controlled by him
isn't desirable.
You're right.
But let me look into one thing more.
If that doesn't pan out,
I'll go at him head-first.
Have it out with him then.
To get the answer,
what better way is there
than to just ask him?
YUYEON POLICE STATION
Min Dal-ho said
it wasn't him who killed her.
If it weren't for you,
I would've killed an innocent man.
How does it feel to face the truth?
Don't you remember him?
You sent him to kill Yeo-jin.
Did I?
Why lie about something
you'd easily get busted for?
Did you want me
to know it was you so badly
or were you so sure
you wouldn't pay for your crimes?
Let me ask you this.
Why wasn't Min Dal-ho
spotted on a security camera?
Because you tampered with them.
Bingo.
You'll never be able to find
what I'm truly willing to hide.
The fact that you found this
means I had no reason to hide it. Why?
Because it wasn't my doing.
Your reaction proves
that this was your doing.
You found what others couldn't,
so I guess I owe you a prize.
Please don't hurt Gi-beom.
I'm begging you.
Please don't hurt him.
Please. I'm begging you.
Please don't...
Please don't hurt Gi-beom.
I'm begging you.
That's more than enough.
Is that really my Yeo-jin?
I told you to stop the nonsense.
Whether you believe it or not
is up to you.
Just not that your choice
will come with a price.
Play it for me again.
Now,
make your choice.
Will you let another loved one die?
Where is she?
Tell me where she is.
You can't, right?
Because you faked it all.
Is that what you wish to believe?
Then tell me that I'm wrong, you bastard!
Where's Yeo-jin?
All that you have believed in
will start to crumble.
Even you
can turn into someone like me now.
Tell me where she is
or I'll rip you apart.
Sub by Netflix & Synced by skysoultan
♔ Follow @skysoultan on Instagram ♔
Do you still think we are different?
The problem is that Hwang Deuk-gu
is destroying Gi-beom.
Where is Yeo-jin?
You should have done thing my way
if you wanted to get what you want.
What are you doing, you bastard?
You will never be able to go back.
I have been waiting for this moment.
You still think
I'm the one who killed your wife?
The person that I have to avenge is me.
Subtitle translation by Liya Choi