ALL CHARACTERS, PLACES,
ORGANIZATIONS, RELIGION AND INCIDENTS
PORTRAYED IN THIS DRAMA ARE FICTITIOUS
Ta-da!
Jeez, this prick. I finally caught him.
Congratulations.
-He's that punk?
-Yes.
Inspector Song wasted a whole year,
yet you caught him in a month.
She's not me.
-You never let us down.
-Hey, you can sit there.
-Officer Kim, take him.
-Yes, sir.
You'll stay here with me all night.
Tell me your underlings, higher-ups,
everyone connected to the crime
and exactly what was traded.
-Gi-beom, can I help you with anything?
-No, I'm good.
Oh, actually...
Mi-na.
What is it, Gi-beom?
And what's up with his face?
Be nice, okay? I'll tell you everything.
What?
What's he saying?
Officer Kim.
Assistant Inspector Mun.
Detective Yang.
What was that about?
Dr. Oh.
Have you ever been flustered because
you couldn't recognize someone's face?
I guess I get like that once in a while,
when I'm very tired.
So is this common?
Are you saying you might have
face blindness despite your special eyes?
The thing is, I do recognize them.
Too well, if anything.
The problem is that I can't see them.
Who?
I had a dream
where I was with my former colleagues.
But all sorts of information popped up
suddenly and covered their faces,
so I sat there for at least ten minutes,
drawing a blank.
That sounds like a nightmare.
If it were real, it'd be even worse
than a nightmare.
Can the artificial eyes affect my memory?
Sometimes, your brain tries to
relieve those unpleasant memories
through nightmares.
If it's a temporary thing,
you don't need to be concerned.
The problem is, those memories
are a lot worse than "unpleasant."
You scared the crap out of me.
-What brings you here?
-The meeting will begin shortly.
Also,
other people can come here too.
Well. That's true, but...
I mean...
Well, let's go.
What was that weird prank about?
My gosh.
-You should go to the meeting.
-I will, you fool.
I'll leave in a minute.
I do see fragmented images,
but I can't put them together.
That's enough.
And we'll take care of the rest,
so don't worry.
At Rugal, everyone's got a lot of stories.
And I finally have one to share as well.
Just focus on your recovery, okay?
I'll recover as fast as lizards do
when I'm all charged up.
You make me laugh.
What?
-Do you have a crush on me?
-You idiot.
What I'm saying is, I don't want to worry
about losing a teammate ever again.
I get it. I know how you feel.
I'll recover quickly
so that I can make you laugh more.
Good.
Seong-min, what are you doing?
Let's go home.
What is that?
As for Assemblyman Park's case,
we can think of it as Argos
putting on a show after losing its leader.
But the recent cases are different.
Their power structure is being reshuffled,
And the crimes show
exhibitionistic tendencies.
It's very concerning.
It's probably because of Hwang Deuk-gu,
the psycho who shows up every single time.
Choi Ye-won could be the mastermind.
And we shouldn't underestimate Choi Yong.
Bong Man-cheol lost the power struggle,
but he won't stay quiet either.
What about Seol Min-jun,
who got whacked on his own turf?
Gi-beom will look into it.
-By himself?
-I'll supervise him.
He's got the state-of-the-art technology.
Let's put it to good use.
As for us, let's go after the evidence
Gwang-cheol remembered.
-Gwang-cheol...
Go ahead.
He can't sleep.
Yes, I bet. He's a tenderhearted guy.
-Are you all right?
-Sorry?
Can you sleep?
You eavesdropped on our conversation?
I just happened to overhear it.
Hold on.
You're worried about me?
We're short-staffed,
so just take good care of yourself.
Thank you for coming on such short notice.
I thought
it'd be more appropriate
to speak to all of you in person.
You basically slammed the door
in my face yesterday.
Why are you all polite today?
I wonder why she summoned us all.
Let's hear what she has to say.
I'm sure you all know
about the commotion
at Mr. Seol's jazz bar last night.
I'll tell you why that happened.
Seol Min-jun
was a police spy.
What?
What did you say?
Gosh, what kind of nonsense is that?
My goodness.
This is not an occasion for jokes.
Are we some gossipy neighbors?
Vice-Chairman Hwang Deuk-gu
found out about it.
There's evidence to back it up.
Gosh, the timing is just unbelievable.
The money just vanished overnight
as soon as Chairman Ko passed away.
And it turns out, this gangster dude
was actually a civil servant.
What's next?
Will I be found as a dead body tomorrow?
Well, the evidence you mentioned...
Is it trustworthy?
-What do you mean?
-It may have been fabricated, you know.
Maybe some fucker is trying
to eliminate us one by one.
I didn't catch the full sentence.
"Some fucker" is trying to do what?
Well, I was just saying...
I can't believe
that Seol Min-jun was actually a cop.
Ms. Choi.
Tell them.
What did you see and hear?
I checked the police records
with my own two eyes,
and he admitted it as well.
Ms. Choi was so angry
that she finished him on the spot.
You killed him?
I didn't get to check
whether or not I actually finished him.
I don't buy any of this.
Hey, Hwang Deuk-gu.
It's all good,
but you'd better not cross the line.
By the way,
some guys stepped in when my boys
and Seol Min-jun's boys were fighting.
Even some of the most elite,
seasoned members got whacked.
We did manage
to capture one of them alive,
but they even got him out.
Who could these people be?
That actually happened?
Does everything you say have to be
a question? You're annoying me.
Come on, guys. Don't fight.
You know I have a good eye, right?
I'll check the situation myself.
Let's meet again after that, okay?
We'll go to the junkyard together
later today.
You'll be bored but hang in there.
Don't say "together"
because I won't be there.
Why are you so cranky?
I need to see it myself to be really sure.
You'll be able to see the site
through Gi-beom's eyes, so take it easy.
We need to see what the eyes can't see.
My feelings will be hurt
if I'm being excluded
from the mission
for failing to fight back.
What's he saying?
We're just worried about you.
You need to take it easy now.
Inspect the scene thoroughly.
-Don't miss even the littlest things.
-Look at this punk.
Don't worry. Just focus on your recovery.
FOR WORK, COMFORTABLE OUTFIT
FOR GOING OUT, CASUAL OUTFIT
She did all this work
just to make sure
her husband would look good.
Come in.
Are you ready?
Yes, I was just trying
to decide what to wear.
I know you'll faithfully follow
Chief Choi's instructions,
but I want to say something
as your team leader.
Sure.
If things start to get
even a little dangerous,
call me right away instead of trying
to sort things out on your own.
Everyone will be worried.
Okay, I won't make you worried.
Good.
What's that? Is that the notebook
Gwang-cheol was talking about?
Yes.
It's my wife's.
I didn't make much money
back when I was a detective,
so she wrote down the things
she wanted to do for me.
Now, this almost looks like
her will to me,
so I'll try to do these things.
Gosh, Gwang-cheol was so curious.
To be honest,
it was hard for me to read this
after such a long time.
But I should tell him
because we're on the same team now.
You wear quirky clothes sometimes
and have teamwork problems,
but I'll try to understand.
Thank you.
-Have a good day.
-You too.
Kang Gi-beom.
Neither of us will stop.
You're still here?
Is this your living room or what?
How dare you start cohabiting
with that bitch in this house?
Jeez, what a nuisance.
I'm trying to work,
and you're interrupting me.
I get that you're going bonkers
because you're anxious,
but being rude to me
will get you in trouble.
Get out of Chairman Ko's house.
What makes you think
that you have the right
to order me to get out?
You bastard, what kind of ruse
are you cooking up?
Hey.
Do you feel like the world is yours
because we let you win once?
We'll never let you
reap all the benefits of our hard work.
Do you even know how to work hard?
You folks make ends meet
by running your mouths.
How dare you. My patience is wearing thin.
Boss.
I'm here.
What are you doing here?
-Hey, Dal-ho.
-Yes, Boss.
From now on, do thorough security checks
before letting anyone into the house.
Have you lost your mind?
Do you think I'm a big joke?
When I say I'll do something,
I follow through. I'm sure you know that.
-You talk too much.
-Unless you want bullet holes all over--
You see, I would've already fired
at least ten shots.
Just shoot me.
What are you waiting for? Shoot!
-Dal-ho.
-Yes, Boss.
The guests are leaving. Escort them out.
-Yong, don't be like this--
-Hey, back off.
-Yong.
-Fine, let's put an end to this today.
Min Dal-ho!
Man-cheol! Are you all right?
What did you do to me just now?
Well, that was...
On top of breaking and entering
into Chairman Ko's house,
you even shot a member of the family.
I can consider this a coup, right?
This is...
Help!
We should save him
so that he can be punished. Take him.
Yes, Boss.
Put him down!
Look at you feeling all guilty.
You really didn't know?
About Seol Min-jun.
"A good-looking, polite guy
who gets things done."
You praised him nonstop and said
he'd be useful. He was just that.
You've gotten quite gutsy, Ye-won.
I have to be this way,
or I'll get eaten up alive.
But you still have a long way to go.
I did say he'd be useful, but I never
told you to let your guard down.
I never let my guard down.
Well, anyway...
The more I think about it,
the angrier I get.
I soiled my hands with blood to groom him.
That hypocrite must've acted
all righteous behind our backs.
In a way, I'm very impressed.
-He totally fooled us, you know.
-Right.
Regardless of his background,
he blended in with us pretty well.
And he's made enough money
to not want to go back.
I wonder why he did that.
And what about Hwang Deuk-gu
who figured it out?
Gosh, Hwang Deuk-gu...
This is all that bastard's fault.
Your husband's death too.
Everyone else is suspecting me.
You're the only exception.
Just my gut feeling.
It's my secret to surviving amongst men
who have nothing but their fists.
I picked you.
Doesn't that tell you enough?
What does your gut say?
You look all delicate and naive,
but you're actually burning
with insatiable ambition deep inside.
People who have that combination
is hard to come by.
That's why you sent me
to Ko Yong-deok as a bribe.
"Bribe"? Come on. Watch your words.
"Bait" would be a better word.
To catch my prey more easily.
Aren't you afraid of me?
You?
Me? Afraid of you?
I'm sparing you only because
I practically groomed you.
I can easily kill you using your affair
with Min-jun. If you don't want that,
you'd better behave yourself.
I'd like to plant an informant
inside Argos.
Who?
Those small flies won't really be helpful.
I already have a plan,
which will allow us to infiltrate them
directly without getting ratted out.
Even Seol Min-jun wasn't able
to gain Choi Ye-won's total trust.
Be careful.
How did you know?
I have full control over you.
That includes all the information you have
as well as your thoughts.
You'll know everything
even without me telling you,
so I won't report the details to you.
Use this to contact them.
They won't be able to track it.
The door.
Why did he even open it for me, then?
My gosh, she scared me.
Can you be quiet?
Okay.
You still got those eyes.
It takes skill to let your guard down.
My suit will get all wrinkled
because of you.
Get off me, will you?
Eyes cannot lie.
What is it that you want?
You pulled out your knife
before I could even say a word.
I'm too scared to talk to you now.
I had to test you
to see how gutsy you are .
Okay. Then I guess
I don't need to be all polite to you.
Can you tell me what you can do for me?
What do you do for a living?
I wonder why you're so on edge.
You tell me first. You're very nimble.
A soldier? Or are you an athlete?
My background shouldn't matter
as long as I'm good at my job.
I'm a little sensitive about that
these days.
I'm like a mercenary.
-I hate being tied down to places.
-Perfect.
I won't have to take responsibility,
and you'll never feel tied down.
-All right, so what do you do?
-Argos.
I'm the new leader of Argos.
It's nice to see that surprised face.
Now, you're interested?
Of course. If it's true, that is.
I need you to protect me.
You said it takes skill to be unguarded.
-You're trusting me too easily.
-You were the first person
that helped me
without expecting anything in return.
You even risked
putting yourself in danger for me.
I don't want to have to explain more.
Just tell me if you'll do it or not.
You'll have to pay me case by case.
Pass me your phone.
And you must book in advance.
CASE BY CASE
You're my only client, but let's not pry
into each other's personal lives.
If you do a good job,
I'll hire you on a permanent basis.
I said I hate the feeling
of being tied down.
Pull over.
-Get out.
-Here?
That's your upfront deposit.
I won't call more than twice.
Keep your eyes glued to your phone.
What a princess.
We shouldn't underestimate Choi Ye-won.
That's why Gi-beom is doing this himself.
Let's wait and see.
You all saw that, right? My gosh.
"So? Now, you're interested?"
"I said I hate the feeling
of being tied down."
So cool.
I need to...
I need to use the washroom, sir.
That was good though.
To sum it up,
he's now able to enter Argos' lair
whenever Choi Ye-won calls.
So meeting Choi Ye-won
is the urgent business he mentioned?
Exactly. It must be because
they're acquainted,
but the banter between them
has been quite entertaining.
I see.
Not even we knew about this
which indicates a secret mission.
Are you sure you should be telling us?
I just thought you'd want to know.
We never said anything,
so keep things professional.
See you.
Damn it. My big mouth
might put me in solitary.
Why would he meet Choi Ye-won by himself?
Kang Gi-beom...
Do you like him?
No.
I see.
This I want to say to you.
What?
Even a tiny nick
could hinder my performance.
What are you yapping on about?
Isn't a conversation what you wanted?
Would you like to converse?
Find everything about Hwang Deuk-gu.
HWANG DEUK-GU AGE 51
ARGOS VICE-PRESIDENT
You not only talk but can think too?
Are you saying you have an identity?
You may ignore the words you received
from the transplant specialist
at 10:05:57 a.m. this morning.
-Who?
-From now on,
I'll address him just like you do.
Dr. Oh may have linked memories to dreams,
but his interpretation is wrong.
So you're smarter than your creator?
My analysis is only based on facts.
Cheeky, aren't you?
Gi-beom, are you there?
Gwang-cheol.
I arrived at the junkyard.
Let's have my eyes and your memories
complete the puzzle.
Sure. Let's do this.
They probably hid everything here.
In the past,
reliving my memories was a nightmare,
but now I'd like nothing more
than to be there.
That's the one.
Everything has been burned, though.
It's what they always do.
You went there for nothing then.
Not exactly.
This part of the truck is untouched.
I don't know
where to begin investigating though.
Where's Tae-woong?
Heavy-lifting is his specialty.
Exactly.
What the...
You're the worst kind of person
to have as an enemy.
-You're here too.
-Right.
Did something happen? Why the long face?
Ask her yourself if you want to know.
-What's up?
-Gwang-cheol, what's next?
Do you see anything inside?
Tae-woong, can you let us in?
-Me?
-Who else?
Come on.
Damn it.
Gwang-cheol was right about what he saw.
What I don't get is this though.
I clearly remember hearing orders
to freeze and then pulverize.
So instead of hiding the body,
it was burned here.
It's for us to see. They're taunting us.
If we spend our resources
identifying the victims,
notifying the family, and investigating...
We'll be playing right into their hands.
They're hoping we'd do all the work.
Bastards.
You think you can laugh
after doing such a thing?
Let's see if you can keep
that smile on your face.
Look at this. I had no idea
there was such a place.
What's so surprising about a hospital?
Tell me.
What are you planning in here?
Well,
we fix people
and treat them with medicine.
If that doesn't do it, we even perform
acupuncture.
What the fuck did you do to me?
Stings, doesn't it?
-Endure it if you want to get better.
-What?
You don't care about the organization
and are selfish to the bone.
You have no vision
and only do the least
that is expected of you.
You're a cancer, Choi Yong.
Carving you out is how we survive.
You're the one who killed the Chairman.
I know it was you, you ungrateful bastard.
-Where's your proof?
-Choi Ye-won
is on top of your head.
You'll never be able to fully control her.
As if you know what I want.
You want to destroy the organization.
You think I don't know?
Listen up.
Argos is only a stepping-stone
to my true objective.
What's important though is that
even I don't know how high I'd like to go.
Where are you keeping
the list of lobbied politicians?
There's no such thing.
Did you think I wouldn't know?
Someone as skittish as you
is bound to have a ledger.
I've already discussed it
with Chairman Hyeon,
so stay down.
You now have two minutes.
Make your choice.
Either let your head explode
or write everything down
and live as a puppet.
Okay, fine. I'll tell you everything,
so take these out!
Start writing.
Make sure the letters are neat and tidy.
VIP SAFE AT MOPIN, UNIT 1004
Why keep a weapon at hand
if you're not going to use it?
You should
also step up your game.
Yes, of course.
Fucking idiots.
A total of four victims.
None of the bodies are fully intact.
They're all missing at least
one organ or body parts
that were removed surgically.
They were harvested.
The bodies were then frozen
to cover the smell of decay.
I'm sorry to tell you this,
but all four of them
were police.
They were officers of detectives that
went missing while investigating Argos.
They'll be reported as corrupt officers.
Ones that worked for Argos
who were abandoned
after serving their purpose.
Instead of being undercover officers?
The truth has no value.
Lies will be spread to make
them seem like evil corrupt officers.
You've got to give credit
for their craftiness.
Track the refrigerator truck
and come up with possible locations
to where they kept their victims.
Susan, I want the names
and contact information
of the fallen police officers.
Yes, sir.
Isn't it suspicious
how all the undercover police officers
showed up in one place?
Because they're not scared
of the police at all.
This is a message.
They're taunting us
while also provoking us.
I think I finally understand
why you didn't offer
to clear my name first.
What do you mean?
The truth holds no value.
They should know though
that the truth does matter.
Of course.
It must've been a hard battle for you.
You had to form a team,
have officers infiltrate Argos,
and fight off those coming at you
from all corners.
I only tried my best
because I had a mission.
How about I add rocket fuel to your tank?
I'll put my trust in you,
not go rogue on any of the missions,
and promise my loyalty.
And here I was thinking about using
that temper of yours to my advantage.
As you please.
-Well, that was one smart move.
-Of course.
-Jeez.
-Make your move already.
-Here?
-There you go.
-What's this?
-What?
-What is it?
-What's going on?
Wait, hold this.
Yes, sir.
-What is it?
-My gosh!
My goodness.
My gosh.
Oh, dear.
That...
I can't believe it.
-What was that?
-Gosh.
-My goodness.
-My gosh.
Right.
-Have the bosses been informed?
-Yes.
The media will soon
get a hold of the news as well.
It'll be better if you try
to put a lid on this yourself.
-Right.
-Sir.
Is Gi-beom
doing well?
Yes, somewhat.
Is there anything I can do to help?
You're already doing what you can
in your position.
What's that, sir?
What is it?
Isn't he the guy from the jazz bar?
What did he ever do to deserve this?
He uploaded a video for his fans
explaining why the performance
was interrupted.
Guys, I'm Lee Jae-han.
You will not believe
what just happened here.
Our performance has been called off.
I'll explain why when I can.
He never mentioned Argos by name.
It doesn't really matter
because whatever he said
could've implicated the organization.
Sick bastards.
Without emotions,
one can never see the truth.
Hold on a second.
I see. It's a job well done.
What? What do you mean?
Wax was used to shape the skull and...
Wait. Hold on.
The skin is from a human though.
No wonder the head looked so real.
It's a fake, guys.
How detailed it is
indicates that his face
wasn't copied off a photo.
He must've been kidnapped.
Then he'll still be alive.
We must find him as soon as possible then.
He could actually die.
-Susan?
-Yes, sir.
This is the lead I found.
It's a closed factory.
According to Detective Yang,
he's the man who delivered the box.
He went off the grid from here
and resurfaced two hours later
to drop off the box.
The police is looking from him
as we speak.
Is that place...
That's right.
It's the place we've been searching for
and the one we must shut down.
That's probably
where they took Lee Jae-han.
Is this a rescue operation
or must we even crush the place?
Those who taunt us
should see
what we're capable of.
All responsibilities will be mine to bear.
Then are we allowed to take lives?
The factory is in a remote area.
I'll only read your after-report.
We'll make sure everyone lives.
Move out.
Yes, sir.
Lee Jae-han, the leader of
a famous jazz team has gone missing.
Mr. Lee recently posted a video explaining
why his latest show was canceled.
His agency hasn't been able
to get in touch with Mr. Lee since.
The police have immediately
launched a search operation
and they have openly dismissed
the gruesome rumor regarding
the involvement of body hunters
that have been terrorizing people online.
We relaunch this investigation
to show how our thoughts
are with the bereaved.
From what we know so far,
this particular case has revealed
no ties to a certain criminal organization
despite what many believe.
DISMANTLE THE PUPPET OF A POLICE FORCE
SUPPORTED BY 273,948 PEOPLE
We want proper police.
We want to see action,
not hear your words.
I can't send my kids anywhere.
-Who knows what can happen?
-Where's the prosecution?
-You should
-watch what you write.
-Dismiss the incompetent
-team leader.
-Even I'd be
-scared of Argos.
-What's Argos?
A nation must protect its citizens.
I'm too scared to leave my house.
YOU HAVE SUPPORTED THE PETITION
The now emotional victims
have been raising their voices.
Finally, it's the moment
we've been waiting for.
Are you saying we should
bring Rugal from out of the shadows?
The bosses want results.
Whatever you have
that'll shock the public,
we'll take.
May I take what you just said
and interpret it my own way?
By all means.
What is all this?
Are those people?
Damn it.
This is how they hid the bodies.
There may be more.
Bastards. How many have they killed?
Should we look around?
Wait.
That seems refrigerated too.
It doesn't match what's on the blueprint.
These were newly built.
So they built refrigerated warehouses,
stored corpses in them,
and then built more?
They built more when they needed more.
This entire factory
could be a big burial site.
Let's check the basement.
Hey, you. Come out
when we're asking you nicely.
My gosh.
-He's still alive.
-I'll call an ambulance.
Why is there no connection?
Isn't that the sound
of a refrigerator motor?
They're trying to freeze us alive.
We're running out of time, guys.
Try punching your way out.
Sure.
It's not your everyday wall.
Tae-woong, you could have better luck.
I could get through, but it'll take time.
We'll probably all die while waiting.
Shit.
It's not like we don't have a way.
What is it? Speak up.
It's too brutal though.
It doesn't matter, so just tell us.
Not right now.
Let's think of another way first.
There isn't another way, so tell us.
Just consider this
as one of the options then.
Only decide after hearing me out.
I watched the entire process
of Gwang-cheol's surgery
and the our transplanted body parts
can be modified
to be turned into explosives.
I'm in. I have a number
of artificial organs within me.
We'll modify one into an explosive.
No can do.
-Why not?
-Because your organs are all connected.
It won't be easy to safely remove just one
especially since you're still recovering.
That leaves my eyes and Tae-woong's arm.
You'll have to modify the body part
into a bomb.
Tae-woong...
I have two eyes,
-so one--
-Enough.
Tae-woong, are you nuts?
Tae-woong!
Are you sure about this?
I don't know
how to make it less painful though.
You probably know this,
but your arm has been welded on.
Are you sure you can endure the pain?
-Let's be rational--
-Gwang-cheol, shut it.
Do it before I change my mind.
I'm putting my trust in you.
Do it fast.
I'll do it on the count of three.
One...
Two.
Two and a half.
Two and a half. I can't.
I really can't do this.
I'm the one who'll feel the pain,
so what's wrong?
My heart breaks even when I cut
my dog's toenails,
so how do you expect me to do this?
What?
"Dog"?
I'm not calling you one.
Anyway, I'm sure we can find
another way to go about this.
Hey, if you want to take your revenge,
you better listen to me.
I know you're the type who'll do anything
to fulfill your wish.
I don't need you to feel sorry for me.
And I have no plans to whine about this.
So do it right now.
Got it?
-Are you sure about this?
-I'm just as desperate as you are.
If my arm doesn't work,
your eyes will be next.
I'll take both of them out if I have to.
Go.
I'll do it on the count of three.
One.
Two.
Tae-woong, are you okay?
-Gwang-cheol.
-Yes.
This is crazy.
Are you okay?
If it doesn't go off,
I will
kill you with my own hands.
It'll work.
Be careful.
Gwang-cheol, take him.
Okay.
Mi-na, escort him out of here.
I'll take care of this.
Okay.
Seol Min-jun might be dumped here as well.
Let me see the regular reports on him.
SEOL MIN-JUN
Let me see the ones related
to Hwang Deuk-gu.
PURCHASED A GALLERY IN SEOUL-INCHEON
FUND TRACKING
AN EYE FOR BEAUTY, OWNS A GALLERY
"An eye for beauty," my foot.
"Gallery"?
Tae-woong, stay with me.
Hang in there.
I'm fine. It's bearable.
Dr. Oh, please take care of him
first.
Your condition isn't any better.
Once again,
thank you.
Let's create another miracle.
-Bradley?
-Yes, doctor.
-Where's Gi-beom?
-He's not back yet.
He's investigating
the full extent of the damage.
-Put me through.
-Yes, sir.
What? I can't connect to him.
What do you mean?
Something is preventing us
from connecting.
This can't be.
Keep trying.
If it's an error, it can be fixed.
If it's intentional,
there must be a pattern.
Find it out.
CASE BY CASE
Kang Gi-beom.
You're living quite the sophisticated life
for a murderer.
Would you like some wine?
I have my favorite.
Oh, right.
Are you still working right now?
I don't set aside time
to catch scumbags like you.
I catch them whenever I see one.
Maybe it's because you barely avoided
getting frozen to death.
You look quite excited and confident.
Your men were so weak.
That's why I came to you.
-You're desperate to meet me.
-If you hadn't visited me,
I was going to visit you myself.
Thank you for sparing me that trouble.
What do you want?
Why are you doing all this for?
When it comes to my work,
you guys keep me busy,
add meaning to everything that I do,
and analyze it.
But then again, they're all bullshit.
But I have to say, I liked that question.
I also liked how you acknowledged
your ignorance.
I could feel your sincerity
of wanting to know about me.
Nice timing.
I have a bit of free time right now,
so I can be patient.
Blabber all you want.
Sir.
What do you mean you can't locate Gi-beom?
We're still locating him.
We shouldn't have left him there alone.
There could've been more traps.
Give us your order,
and we'll go look for him.
The AI has begun to whisper.
"Whisper"?
He's acting out.
He must have a reason for acting that way.
Isn't that dangerous?
We should stop him.
No. If he uses it well,
we may be able to reach
our destination more quickly.
Even if he's acting out,
there's only one thing that he wants.
How many people
do you think actually know what they want?
I want to sleep when I'm tired
and eat when I'm hungry.
I also want to beat the shit
out of scumbags like you.
That's not hard, is it?
My wishes are very simple.
I like you
for now.
It may be difficult to believe,
but I wanted an ordinary life.
I wanted to go to school,
have friends,
and find a job.
It may sound boring,
but such is life.
But
after having blood on my hands
for the first time,
a new world opened up.
I could never
go back.
I could never turn back time.
I felt exhilarated.
Gosh, you really know how to sugarcoat
"I'm crazy."
The difference is that this society
allowed you to do it.
When you were a cop,
you were also trained
to be violent and destructive.
You must've loved it so much
to repeat the same thing
after coming back from the dead.
There are things I need to put an end to.
And you're one of them.
See?
We're special to each other.
Thanks to my existence,
you believe you're being righteous
and justify your actions.
Aren't I right?
What are you? A philosophical thug?
But you see,
there's something you don't know.
You're just garbage.
We're special to each other?
I justify my actions?
Don't be absurd.
You're probably the chattiest murderer
of all time.
It's a shame that you lack dignity.
You'll become an excellent pacemaker.
Do chase me to the ends of the earth.
I'm going to put my trust in you
and become freer.
Sure thing. I'll make sure you get
enough books to read behind bars.
I hope you live a long, delusional life.
To thank you for making this trip,
I've prepared a gift. You'll love it.
Seol Min-jun?
Say hi.
He's a former senior of yours.
But now, he's a brother of mine
who'll kill you.
-Please spare us!
Please spare us!
We won't do that anymore!
-Please spare us!
-I promise!
Please spare us! Please!
If you go right now,
you'll be able to save them.
I'll give you their location.
It's not that far from here either.
But if you fail,
it'll cause quite a commotion since
their parents are high-ranking officials.
We won't do that ever again!
Is it
really that difficult?
Just do as you please.
You're not an idiot, are you?
You can take me,
or you can save them.
-What's your answer?
-I'm going to do both.
Move aside. I don't want to hurt you.
We don't have much time to enjoy.
For you
and me.
He wasn't going to let anyone live,
to begin with.
The victims or us,
who went there to save them.
We can't be the only ones that suffer.
You don't have to know
why you have to do this.
Just let them hear about it.
You want an incident
that will make them get scared of you.
I'll handle Hwang Deuk-gu after that.
It's a reservoir.
Let me first hear what you saw
and how you found it.
Isn't destroying them to the root
the real revenge?
You don't have the right
to die peacefully.
Subtitle translation by Hye-lim Park