RUGAL
ALL CHARACTERS, PLACES,
ORGANIZATIONS, RELIGION AND INCIDENTS
PORTRAYED IN THIS DRAMA ARE FICTITIOUS
Why did you do this to me?
-Put it down!
-Why did you do that to her?
That's enough.
-Move aside.
-You can blame him for his mistakes.
But you can't blame him
for not being perfect.
He did the best he could.
Do not look down on his sincerity.
I told you to move.
Protecting him is also part of my job.
How can you say that after all this?
Hwang Deuk-gu is the one
who killed Kim Yeo-jin.
But Choi Geun-cheol put her in his hands.
Your gun shouldn't be pointed at him.
Get a grip.
Let me ask you one last question.
Why was it me?
I considered you the most suitable weapon
to join Rugal.
Shut the fuck up, you bastard!
Shoot him.
Get rid of him.
Please get out of my way.
You'll regret this. Do you think
everything he told you is true?
One is enough for me.
Is that coming from your eyes
that mistook me for a test subject
and made you attack me?
You can't let him get away.
End it.
This is for disobeying my orders.
EPISODE 14
It happened over ten years ago.
Sergeant Song Gyeong-su
who was dispatched
to the National Police Agency
suggested forming Rugal.
He had been my partner for a long time
and was Mi-na's father.
Mi-na's father?
Did you already know?
Go on, sir.
Even before he became a police officer,
Sergeant Song was on the advisory council
to make robots with increased abilities
for the Ministry of Defense.
He was a distinguished scientist.
It was hard to keep Argos under control
with the manpower from the police.
So the confidential project we started
became you guys.
The Rugal Project.
That's enough history lesson for today.
People who had been on this project,
including my father,
were aware of how dangerous
this project could be.
But they still applied to be on it.
That's right.
Only those who were resolute
to make a change have joined us.
But that determination
wasn't enough to change reality.
Chief Choi.
Did we...
No.
Did I end up joining the team
based on your plan?
You guys are different.
Your involvement wasn't planned.
And I was lucky to have you.
Tae-woong became
the first successful member.
And then, you and Mi-na joined, too.
Seeing how you became part of the team
gave me this thought.
"I shouldn't just be waiting.
Why don't I look for one myself?"
Is that how you found
Gi-beom?
PERSONNEL FILE
We had just finished developing
the artificial eyes.
And I needed an individual
that could handle the eyes.
PERSONNEL FILE
He was physically gifted.
He had ambition and was competitive
which was typical for a cop.
On top of that, he was mentally stable.
He was the perfect fit.
Why didn't you tell him the truth
from the start?
That you needed Gi-beom's help.
I had no idea that
he would go after Ko Yong-deok.
The situation changed rapidly.
At that rate,
I had to watch Gi-beom getting killed.
Is that why
you devised such a plan
with Detective Yang?
I thought it could be our opportunity.
I decided to take the role of giving him
a nudge in the right direction
to reach his full potential.
Is that why you got his wife involved?
Even at the expense of killing Yeo-jin?
I didn't think this would happen
to Yeo-jin.
Logically, I follow your plan,
but it's hard to emotionally accept it.
While I wish Gi-beom to understand you,
my heart breaks for him.
I think you need time to process this.
For you, chief.
And for Gi-beom.
Water.
Water...
Help me.
Did you find her?
Did you see your wife?
I was the one who found her.
I'm not trying to take credit.
Can you give me some water?
Kill him.
Dead.
Find me everything
Choi Geun-cheol hid from me.
It scared the crap out of me earlier.
What do you mean?
When you two were fighting.
"What if I lose one of you?
Does it mean I have to take revenge?"
But both of you
are my close friends
and I like you both.
That won't happen.
But you weren't worried about Chief Choi?
I felt reassured
because you were protecting him.
Or I could've sacrificed my body.
If Chief Choi hears that,
he might be disappointed.
Gi-beom was probably disappointed, right?
In you and me, right?
He's not that petty.
Seeing how he took a step back,
he probably understands our situation.
That's what worries me more.
That he might try to shoulder
all the burdens and pain by himself.
No one would be able to forgive
after seeing this.
Did you find out more
about how she'd been living?
I didn't have time to talk to Gi-beom.
And what you already know
is the extent of my information.
I should have looked for her
no matter what it took.
I can't side with you
on this matter.
Okay.
Thank you for being honest with me.
Gi-beom's feeling
is the most important thing right now.
Why did you do it?
It would've been better
if you were honest with him.
What if his surgery didn't work?
What were you going to do, then?
Do you think there's anyone
who knows Gi-beom as well as I do?
The thought of the surgery failing
didn't even cross my mind.
No.
If you knew him that well
and believed in him,
you should have told him the whole truth.
If this was between two people,
that would've been the right thing to do.
But Mi-na,
this matter is on a whole new level.
My faith in him won't solve it.
If he fails to free himself
from the restrictions of a human,
there's no future with Rugal.
And I'm hoping
that Gi-beom will overcome
this hardship on his own.
I don't want
to lose Gi-beom.
I feel the same way.
You should've aimed for my neck
or my heart if you were going to try.
You and Choi Yong don't know
anything about a final strike.
You'll just leave like that?
I don't want to spoil my mood today.
Why do you think Choi Geun-cheol
isn't trying to rescue you?
Or is someone helping you out
behind my back?
If not that, you must have been trained
for a situation like this.
Then, you must know that
I won't answer it even if you ask.
Fine.
How about this, then?
Why don't you fix me up?
What do you want to fix?
My body?
You must be better than Director Gu
who is over the hill.
Are you in your right mind?
That's a load of crap. No one lives
their lives in their right mind.
Then,
are you really willing
to try it?
Excuse me. Could you be thorough
when you finish that up?
Sure.
Given the looks of it,
this turned out pretty well.
-Anyway, thank you for your work.
-Sure thing.
Okay.
UNDER CONSTRUCTION
It's another dead end.
Same here.
Have you located Gi-beom yet?
I'm tracing the signals, but I think
someone is jamming the signals.
As of this moment, cut the artificial
eyes' access to our servers.
And strengthen the HQ's server.
-Yes, sir.
If you cut off all the access,
how will you protect Gi-beom?
His behaviors towards you seem to stem
from an error of the artificial eyes.
We must prepare ourselves
before analyzing the problem right now.
I'm against treating him as a threat.
As long as Gi-beom is in Rugal,
you can't do that.
-Did you find it?
-As of now,
I don't have access to the HQ's servers
and National Police Agency's.
So you don't have access.
Does it mean you can't find it?
I only told you I don't have access,
but I didn't say I couldn't find it.
-However,
-What?
it's not a standard method.
So the targeted servers
will suffer great damage.
Just do it.
CHOI GEUN-CHEOL AGE 52
GENERAL MANAGER OF RUGAL
I found a video from
Chief Choi Geun-cheol's secured files.
Play it.
-I can see him soon, right?
-You can't.
Why not? If he knows that I'm alive,
-he'll try harder--
-If there's a change in our plan,
it will be impossible to take him out.
If he finds out you're alive,
do you think he can focus on other things?
Don't let this discourage you.
Gi-beom will be stronger than anyone.
And he will do what no one was able to do.
And we cannot let anyone find out
about your existence.
When that happens,
I cannot guarantee Gi-beom's safety.
NAME: LEE EUN-JEONG
-Find out about Lee Eun-jeong.
-None.
Try again.
There's no record
of the police's attempt to find her.
Since he made sure that she'd stay silent,
he was never going to look for her.
-Let me ask you something too.
-Sure, go ahead.
I'd like to go back to training.
It must've been a hard battle for you.
I only tried my best
because I had a mission.
How about I add rocket fuel to your tank?
Mi-na.
Where are you going all alone?
I'll be late. Don't worry.
Let me come with you.
No. I'll go alone.
Is it because of yesterday?
Even if that moment comes again,
I'll take Gi-beom's side.
Why do you keep splitting sides?
We don't have to agree on everything.
But I cannot allow insubordination.
Gi-beom must feel abandoned by us.
And Gwang-cheol...
The moment you and Tae-woong
stopped Gi-beom,
you took your side.
I only did that because
he was going to kill the chief.
No. He wouldn't have killed
the chief. Never.
I agree with you on that.
But securing the chief's safety
is a different matter.
That was the only thing
you could do for Rugal.
We must always be patient
and understanding.
If we don't, we'll be treated as threats.
But Tae-woong. Gwang-cheol.
We were also victims.
We were the weak who couldn't do anything
when we were unfairly treated.
I thought Rugal was formed to help
the weak of our society. Am I wrong?
But I'm asked to turn my back on Gi-beom
who was unfairly treated for Rugal.
I can't do that.
I have to meet with him.
Do you know where he is?
No.
But I know whom he'll go to.
Who?
Hwang Deuk-gu.
Whatever he said to Gi-beom
is breaking him down.
I'm sure he'll try to confirm it again.
You want to ambush him?
I'll find him before Gi-beom does
and get rid of him.
I'll get even with him.
But how will we find that jerk?
We have Choi Ye-won.
I'm sure we'll find a lead.
FAIR AND KIND POLICE FOR THE PEOPLE
Detective Yang.
Sir.
I heard you're facing disciplinary action.
I lost Hwang Deuk-gu.
I have nothing to say for myself.
Is it true that Gi-beom was
never mentioned at the hearing?
I guess the higher-ups consider
Argos Hunters pretty useful.
People stopped criticizing the police.
And they won't be blamed
for losing Hwang Deuk-gu as long as
they punish a cop like me.
Right.
About Kim Yeo-jin...
She's dead.
-You found her?
-Not me. Gi-beom did.
Then,
does he know about what I did?
That's not good.
Is Gi-beom here too?
No, we can't get a hold of him
at the moment.
Detective Yang.
What we did was for the greater good.
Right, it was.
The person you're trying to reach
is unavailable.
HWANG DEUK-GU
The person you're trying to reach
is unavailable.
What happened at the hospital?
Did you search everywhere?
What about the hideout?
How could a stabbed man drive himself?
Someone must've given him a ride.
Send me the address.
BANMO PARK INN
This is the room.
She'd come back at dawn
and not even step out of the room
until going out again at night.
Sometimes, I heard her moaning in pain
all night.
I also heard her cry.
On some days
when she seemed calm and collected,
she said she might be able to meet someone
again if she held out and stayed alive.
It seemed like she had no one,
no family or friends.
But it looked like
she was waiting for someone.
HWANG DEUK-GU, CHOI GEUN-CHEOL
LOCATION FOUND
"F100H"?
Subject F100H. What's this?
Open it.
Will this give me an insight
into Rugal's earlier days?
You'll need Chief Choi's authorization
or access the data on his computer.
CLIENT
I heard Hwang Deuk-gu came here often
before checking into the hotel,
so I thought I should check this place.
Who knew I'd see you here?
A coincidence, would you say?
Did you help Hwang Deuk-gu escape?
You said catching him was your goal.
Yes, you as well.
Argos Hunter.
If you really want to do it, you need
to step up your game. I'll help you.
I'm so sick and tired of those gangsters.
I'm not like them.
I'll spare the company
and get rid of everything else.
If you don't believe me,
just wait and see. Right by my side.
I want you by my side.
Can you do that?
I want you to protect me.
I no longer need to protect anyone.
Hwang Deuk-gu is the only
common denominator between those two.
They're going separate ways.
We should split up too, right?
Mi-na, follow Gi-beom.
Gwang-cheol and I will tail Choi Ye-won.
Okay.
It's about time you stepped down
from the stage he fabricated.
I told you. It was all fabricated.
He fabricated her death,
acted like he cared for you,
and pretended to be a victim.
Don't you get it? He did it.
I laid out everything for him,
so he'd better not
come empty-handed again.
I hope he brings a few heads at least.
How's Seol Min-jun?
All fixed?
Tae-woong.
Ye-won.
Mi-joo.
What are you doing here?
Can we talk?
What's up with them?
Are they leaving?
Familiar faces are showing up,
which tells me that Hwang Deuk-gu
is definitely here.
You take Choi Ye-won.
Does this mean Hwang Deuk-gu isn't here?
This is a trap.
If you go in there now,
you'll come back out dead.
Hwang Deuk-gu can't get rid of me
that easily.
If you must see for yourself...
I won't stop you.
I'll believe you.
Follow me.
Where are we going?
To catch Hwang Deuk-gu, obviously.
It's over there.
Okay.
Ye-won.
You're awfully slow-witted.
What should I do with you?
What's going on? What the hell? Let go!
Who are you guys?
Let go of me!
Let go!
Damn it.
I must warn you.
Don't take my side.
Let's go back together.
I don't want the people I like to hate me.
You know that Yeo-jin
meant a lot to me as well.
So don't do this alone.
Let's go back and fight together.
I don't want you to get in trouble
because of me.
Pretend you didn't see me and go back.
Gi-beom.
Nothing you say now
will change our situation.
Hwang Deuk-gu.
Han Tae-woong.
You were just Ko Yong-deok's minion
engaging in trickery, driving a wedge
between others,
and stabbing people in their backs.
You've come a long way.
Kang Gi-beom is obedient to me these days.
Do you know why?
It's because he's discovered the truth.
Telling people what they didn't know
has a humbling effect.
Shall I tell you something too?
Shut your trap.
Han Tae-yeon.
Her name was something like that.
Boss told me what he wanted,
and I got the job done.
I killed all the bastards
that had anything to do
with my sister's death.
No, not all of them.
You didn't kill the one
who planned everything.
Are you saying that was you?
If you're curious,
go dig around everywhere
like Kang Gi-beom is doing.
You're strong
but not as fast as Kang Gi-beom.
As for Gi-beom, I think
we'll need more time to persuade him.
All right.
You said Choi Ye-won is gone.
Can you elaborate?
Yes. I followed her to the parking lot
but only saw Madame Jang when I got there.
She vanished.
Madame Jang and Choi Ye-won
are in the same boat.
But they can push each other
off the boat anytime.
That's how they are.
What about you?
Did you meet Hwang Deuk-gu?
Yes.
Very briefly.
Are you back?
Not sure.
I can't really answer that now.
You're going in, right?
Yes, but...
I can't really let you in now.
Why not?
I'll just grab my stuff and leave.
No one's here now,
so I can let you in for a few minutes.
I heard you witnessed
the Commissioner-General's death.
Yes, sir.
This position will be mine soon.
When that happens,
I wish to restore the police's dignity
which has hit rock bottom.
To do that, I need capable people
in important positions.
Chief Choi, I'd love your help.
I will continue to do my best
in my current position.
I won't do anything to Rugal.
You've put together a very useful team.
You'll have my full support.
Come out into the open and do your best.
Everyone in Rugal has a hurtful past.
If everything comes out in the open...
Keep managing them
the way you're doing now.
Let them loose sometimes so that
they can scratch the people's back.
When there's trouble,
discipline them however you see fit.
You're already doing a good job.
I'll guide you,
so just bite the bullet
and follow my lead.
One, two, three, four...
Oh...
SUBJECT F100H
Hang in there.
Just endure it!
You must endure it!
Find Choi Geun-cheol.
He will arrive at the HQ soon.
Hey, did you get everything?
Gi-beom.
Gi-beom! Wait.
Shit.
SUBJECT F100H
Damn it.
What's wrong? Did something happen?
Tae-woong, did you see Gi-beom
on your way in?
Gi-beom was here?
Yes, what happened was...
I told him I couldn't let him in, but
he said he came to grab his stuff, so...
Mi-na, come in.
Gwang-cheol, I need you to wait there.
Sir, come to Gate Four,
not the main entrance.
The emergency exit? Why?
Gwang-cheol is waiting for you there.
You should have him guard you.
Is this about Gi-beom?
Why did you hide that Hwang Deuk-gu
was Rugal's first test subject?
You even found out about that?
Then you wouldn't need my explanation.
If they die like that,
no one takes responsibility,
and the country feigns ignorance.
I pitied them so much.
But it turns out, I was one of them.
You would've used
and abandoned us like that too.
I admit I can't say
that it was an honorable beginning.
I had to produce results at all costs.
However,
Hwang Deuk-gu was never part of Rugal.
Do not compare him to you guys.
Lives were lost
while you were trying to play a hero.
When you were trying to lure them by using
nice words like "justice,"
did you ever think that
they might end up going through hell?
Do you think those who are rooting for us
are idiots?
The world wants you guys.
Stop telling me any more of that bullshit.
It doesn't change the fact
that my life's been completely destroyed.
Deal with me first.
-You'll get hurt.
-I won't step aside.
Are you all right?
Yes.
-Return to the HQ with the Chief.
-Okay.
Sir.
Are you okay?
Kill them all.
Step aside.
Min-jun, are you all right?
I'm sorry.
I still have
things to do.
I must ask you for one last favor.
Can you please plant a bomb...
No, I can't do that for you.
A bomb would be nice!
I've been wondering
what I should give him as a gift anyway.
A bomb is a great idea.
Take him.
It's still too early to be sure.
He needs more treatment...
You told me to save him!
Min-jun.
Feeling all right?
There's no place like home
when you're not feeling well.
Go pay them a visit.
Come back to us.
I don't want us to be on different sides
and the last thing I want
is for us to be enemies.
We'll also end up used and abandoned too.
I'm done caring for anything anymore
and that includes Rugal.
Don't make your decision
on what your eyes see
but follow the determination
once set from within your heart.
Come back to us free of any guilt.
I'll have your back.
You could've just called me over,
you know.
It's not like we're strangers.
How does Madame Jang expect to do business
when she has no balls?
I guess it was hard for her
to get rid of you personally.
It was a nice experience though.
-What?
-Madame Jang...
I always felt like I owed her,
but now I'm free from that feeling.
You...
You think you can leave here alive?
I guess you'll let me live
if I'm worth it.
This again?
Money makes you worthy, is that it?
To hell with that.
I know you want Argos for yourself,
so why do it by
getting blood on your hands?
Take me in instead.
That's the fastest and easiest way.
What?
Why?
Don't you want me?
It's funny how you seem startled.
Gi-beom...
You knew this day would come.
You're startled even though
you knew this would happen,
so imagine how terrified
Yeo-jin must've been
to be ambushed by you.
I'm truly sorry.
There's nothing more I can say.
My friend,
were you actually my friend?
I tried to persuade Yeo-jin
and make her understand,
but she wasn't having it.
Well, don't worry.
I'm also not in the mood
to make you understand either.
Gi-beom...
See you in hell.
I knew that he'd be
the next target on your list.
I made a fair warning.
I also read the files on the chief.
I'm now aware that Hwang Deuk-gu
murdered my father.
Is that your reason for shooting me?
What Chief Choi did was despicable,
but Hwang Deuk-gu's worse.
What Mun-bok did was wrong,
but killing him isn't the answer.
Hwang Deuk-gu is the one
we must truly eliminate.
So why are you going after others
instead of tracking him down?
Gi-beom, don't do this.
Please, stop.
Because you show them mercy,
they think they can challenge you.
Gi-beom, are you all right?
Kill her.
Shut up.
Gi-beom?
Gi-beom!
He's been dead for a while.
Is he really
going to kill them all?
Detective Yang would've died too
if Mi-na hadn't interfered.
Instead of waiting for him to return,
shouldn't we put him down?
We'll do what it takes to help him first.
Attack.
Kill them
all.
If my artificial eyes are like computers,
could they be formatted or reset?
Can installing the software again
erase any errors?
Broadly speaking, they're similar.
But the smaller details are more complex.
Imagine a big factory.
There are a lot of processes
that are operating.
If pressing a button could mess it all up,
the system wouldn't be stable.
You need backup generators
and backup files
to fill in the parts that get broken.
Still, when things get out of hand,
you want to wipe the slate clean
and start over.
You'll need more than your regular trauma
to see any changes in the eyes.
However, if the tree trunk won't budge,
we can go after the roots.
Remember the chip
embedded in the back of your head?
That...
I shouldn't be telling you this.
You want to get rid of me?
If you do, it'll be the end of you too.
We can do this ourselves.
Stop this.
Why do we need Rugal anyway?
We can kill them all.
I won't do that.
You will end up doing so.
Did you just make me kneel?
You've chosen the wrong guy to mess with.
I won't go down without a fight.
I can do
so much more.
Is that coming from your eyes
that mistook me for a test subject
and made you attack me?
Calm down, Gi-beom.
Compose yourself!
Don't do this.
Please, stop.
I won't let you have it your way.
Even if I do this?
ON WEEKENDS? I GO AFTER ARGOS
I hope he gets well soon.
How are you holding up?
I doubt any of us is unfazed by all this.
We have more people now
praising us for the work we do,
but look at what we've become.
We break and hurt each other.
I'd like to meet.
Did you change your mind?
Mi-na, what's wrong?
Mi-na?
Mi-na!
Damn that punch of yours.
Why didn't you dodge it?
I need to erase Yeo-jin from my memories.
What do you mean?
If I do,
I may be able to forgive the chief.
I never said you should.
If I don't,
I won't be able to move on.
Rugal
can go on without me...
No, never without you.
Come back home with me.
I'm sorry.
This was the only way.
Gi-beom?
Gi-beom!
Subtitle translation by Hye-lim Park
I came to find something.
Hwang Deuk-gu came to the HQ.
Gwang-cheol was taken by Hwang Deuk-gu.
Rugal, the toy you've made
was pretty useful to me as well.
Can you still not realize
who brought us here?
Beg me to spare your life.
There is only one person
who would do such a thing.
Now we have to move on to
our real mission.
Hwang Deuk-gu... Where is he?