ALL CHARACTERS, PLACES, ORGANIZATIONS, RELIGION AND INCIDENTS
PORTRAYED IN THIS DRAMA ARE FICTITIOUS
EPISODE 10
They restored the power.
Gwang-cheol, turn the lights on.
I expected this, but this is worse than I imagined.
What they did to us doesn't even come close to this.
There's no point talking about it.
Should we catch the guys we saw at the entrance first?
Let's not catch them. Instead, we should crush them there.
Securing Dr. Oh takes priority.
MISSING PERSON AN YU-MIN
He's a missing person.
He went missing in 2018.
A professional basketball player, An Yu-min.
They'll take anyone they can get their hands on.
If they want to create an army, they should use their men.
This isn't research, but a massacre.
This ends today.
This is the only exit. Let's split and meet back here again.
And we'll let the police rescue the victims as always.
Gi-beom, check the entrance.
Mi-na, sweep the area where the electrical accident took place.
Gwang-cheol, search the basement.
DANGER: ULTRA-HIGH-VOLTAGE TRANSMISSION
Who are you?
Have you seen a man named Oh Gwang-su?
Oh Gwang-su?
I see. The former doctor from K Hospital...
Who the heck are you?
What's your problem?
That can't be.
The subbasement is cleared.
The electricity room is cleared.
It seems like Dr. Oh was moved somewhere else.
What? When?
Someone saw us when we entered.
-Then, Dr. Oh isn't here? -That's my guess.
I'm sure it was part of their protocol.
Given the incident, he was the first one to get moved.
-We'll be on our move, too. -Okay.
But we can't leave this place like this, Tae-woong.
As Dr. Oh isn't here, there's no point for us to be careful.
Let's meet back safely at where we parted earlier while leaving
a lot of damages behind.
I'm so glad to hear that.
I must check where he might be. I'll meet you there.
-That's my plan, too. -Same here.
I need to check something.
My parents must be worried.
Can I call them
to let them know I'm fine and they don't have to worry?
Or I can just text them.
Who are you?
The way out of here will be rough.
Do you want to wear this?
Can we slow down a bit?
My goodness. What's happening?
Just kill me already.
It's a waste of time.
I did everything I was asked. Why are you doing this to me?
The number you are calling cannot be reached.
YE-WON
She's not answering my calls. Did the negotiation fall through?
According to Man-cheol, Deuk-gu was going to get him out right away.
You know what? Chairwoman Choi confuses me these days.
What do you mean?
She gathered us up and asked for our help to bring him down.
But this afternoon, she stuck up for him because he's the vice-chairman.
Don't you know that the position shapes the person?
If she's not qualified for it, she's out.
I'm worried about my later years.
I can't even retire with some peace in my mind.
What? Do you want to join the game?
Let's do a few rounds when Man-cheol gets out.
WHERE ARE YOU?
CASE BY CASE
Are you planning to jump?
We're almost there. Be patient.
What's that watch?
What the heck are you up to?
You're the chairwoman.
Why are you so scared?
Who would believe that?
The almighty chairwoman of Argos reached out to the police
because she felt threatened by her loyal vice-chairman, Hwang Deuk-gu.
Stop the car.
Pull over now!
Excuse me.
Hey.
Please put something in my eye sockets.
Please.
Dr. Oh, you said you would never do it,
but did you know
that I'm even more scared now than the time when they brought me here?
I must be able to see if I want to do anything.
What happened?
Who are you?
I'm sorry.
Pretend you didn't hear that.
I don't know anything!
Tell me what they did to you.
I don't care if you kill me,
but please spare my daughter.
Was she kidnapped here, too?
You killed my daughter, didn't you?
You came in to tell me that, right?
Answer me!
Answer me, you murderer!
Bring her back!
Murderer...
THE SICK MURDERER KANG GI-BEOM
Kang Gi-beom is a murderer.
Kill them.
Gi-beom.
Test subject.
Stop it.
Calm down, Gi-beom. Compose yourself!
I did this, didn't I?
Yes.
-And I attacked you, too, Tae-woong? -What happened?
I don't know.
Everyone looked like test subjects to me.
-That's not exactly wrong. -It's not right, either.
Is it some kind of error?
If you didn't stop me, I might have killed you, too.
I couldn't control myself.
If it was an error, we can fix it.
If I can bring you back like now,
that's good for me.
Are you okay now?
Yes.
-You're back. -Yes.
-Is it just the two of us here? -The two of us?
Yes.
Who else is here except for you and me?
Well...
-Don't try to talk me out of this. -Hey.
I'm sorry. I wasn't talking to you.
You come here.
How could you bring her here?
What are you going to say to Tae-woong?
-If the chief finds out-- -He'll destroy me
and put me in the solitary cell.
So what's your plan?
Let's just bring her outside. Deal?
You're not offering me anything. That's not a deal.
You're on your own.
Who is she?
Let's escort her outside the building.
Leave her here. The police will be here any minute.
It's too dangerous for us to leave her here.
They put a chip in her body. It's dangerous.
Chip?
I want her to be the first person the police find.
There might be more of them here.
Mi-na and I will guard the front and back.
Gi-beom, you'll lead.
Thank you, Tae-woong.
-Let's go. -Gi-beom.
Are you okay?
Yes. I'm fine. Let's go.
Once we leave, take off the blindfold.
And keep walking this way.
The police will be coming from there. You'll see them soon.
Take me with you.
I'll keep this a secret.
Please protect me.
-Take her to the headquarters. -What about you?
I'll go back on my own.
See you at the headquarters.
This got exposed?
The police are everywhere.
I doubt that you called the police
to turn yourself in out of guilt for what you did to me.
Don't hold your breath for it.
If your businesses keep getting exposed,
how will you make up for the monetary losses?
What happened to Director Gu and that darned doctor?
Seol Min-jun moved them to a safe place.
Everyone is doing their job.
What have you done to stop this getting out of control?
I was guarding the gate.
There's only one entrance here.
-I thought guarding the gate-- -So,
did you stop them?
Logically speaking, it worked out in my head.
But you know, our bodies need us to discharge some stuff.
And I had to smoke a few cigarettes--
I can assure you that it wasn't Kang Gi-beom.
It's as clear as day this is his doing. You're telling me it's not?
I even checked the face myself.
He waltzes into Argo's operations as if it's his own.
He makes a royal mess and finishes up with the police.
Can't you see?
We're getting exposed more and more,
but those bastards are getting cocky.
I'm so busy, straightening out the people who betray us.
But you failed to do one simple task of guarding the gate.
How dare you talk that nonsense to me?
You bastard. You too. Just die!
Die. Just die, you bastard.
Boss, wait.
Boss...
I'll go catch her. Please?
You seem
to be destined to live a long life.
-Go get her... -Yes, sir.
-...unless you have a death wish. -Yes, sir.
Hey, we need to report first.
My gosh.
Hello.
Who is she?
We brought her from there.
Does Chief Choi know?
He will. Soon.
"Soon"? I never saw her, then.
Gosh, come on.
Just remove the chip behind her neck.
Gwang-cheol, ask Susan if you need help with something like that.
It can blow up anytime like Kim Dae-sik and other test subjects did.
Gwang-cheol, please don't test me like this.
Just follow his instructions.
Whose instructions? I never saw her.
Come on.
Follow this handsome guy's instructions.
You'll remove the thing on the back of my neck, right?
Gosh, what a headache.
Why is everyone doing this to me these days? Gosh, my head hurts.
Gi-beom found the person who had come in contact with Dr. Oh,
but we couldn't find anything else.
I knew it. Dr. Oh sent us a signal.
What if he's alive, but this imperils his life even more?
Now, one thing is certain.
They abducted him to use him, not to kill him.
Isn't that more dangerous?
I'm always prepared to deal with something like this, and so was Dr. Oh.
He'd never cooperate. And even if he does,
I'm sure he has a plan, so don't worry.
Then what should we do now?
Leave this to me.
What about Gi-beom and Gwang-cheol?
Gi-beom is on his way back.
Gwang-cheol has a minor injury, so I sent him to Bradley.
Okay. You two should get some rest too.
Yes, sir.
Right, it's understandable.
Those bastards deserved something even worse.
Test subject.
Why did I do that?
Did I mistake him for a test subject?
Aggression detected.
-Shit. -Has the defensive instinct been upgraded?
-Are you all right? -Don't touch me.
Murder success probability, 73 percent.
What the heck is this? Get rid of this.
Why are you suddenly all quiet? Get rid of it!
I will delete it.
Jeez, today is not my day.
That goofball. When did he have time to do this?
Good to see you alive.
People are still debating whether or not you're the killer and if you're dead.
It's not that simple.
What is your real job?
I'm after Argos.
Then did you approach me intentionally?
Will my answer change anything?
I was going to say, it won't.
Our contract is still valid, right?
-What if the answer is yes? -You'll need me.
Do you trust me?
Someone's tailing us.
All knocked out.
Look at this bloody mess. Don't you feel a sense of despair?
He risked his own life and walked into it just to provoke me.
I really want to get my hands on him.
Are you all right, sir?
Don't worry about me.
I'm seeing what you probably can't see.
He's different.
He doesn't go all bonkers, swept up in anger.
He wants to play with me, so he's coming at me with everything he's got.
If that's what he wants,
I shall put him on the game board and play with him.
You can get ready, right?
Yes, sir.
Let's go eat something.
Gwang-cheol is so stubborn.
He's usually easy going though.
-He's not like that all the time. -He's reckless.
Sure, the surgery is fine. But what about after that?
We should save her life first.
It'll take her a while to fully recover.
You sound so unconcerned.
You're making me look petty-minded.
I'll worry about it later.
There's something more important right now.
What's going on?
It's about Gi-beom.
What about him?
I saw him getting out of control.
Did he have a shutdown?
No, I think it was a different kind of error.
I guess he acted recklessly.
Yes.
"The whispers of the artificial eyes."
That's what Chief Choi calls it.
"Whispers"?
When you get used to relying on the artificial eyes,
you experience moments when you're not thinking of your own accord.
That's when they whisper to you to lure you.
"Hand over full control."
So, the more you use them,
the more they control you?
They're a strong tool, so there's a big price to pay.
That's why...
What?
To tell you the truth, there's a safety device.
I have it.
You?
Gi-beom and I are the only ones with the chip, you know.
The thing for your blood flow and body balance?
Yes, Chief Choi linked it to that device.
-They're linked? -Not always.
When Gi-beom loses his sense of self
or gets emotional,
I get a signal.
His emotional state is shared with you?
Yes, you can say that.
To tell you the truth, I felt it when we were at the lab earlier.
Well, it does catch me off guard at times.
But it's not always bad.
Maybe that's why.
From time to time, Gi-beom and I feel and act the same way.
We even wind up in the exact same places at times.
I worry about him.
But in a way, it's nice.
I envy you guys for that.
Being able to share so much as teammates.
Well, I guess.
I'm just not cut out for that.
Understanding others and being communicative.
Gosh, what are you talking about?
You're so good at it.
With you?
Well...
Yes.
This is Hwang Deuk-gu's car, so he'll track it down soon.
Let's have some tea and part ways.
So we can call it even and start afresh with a clean slate?
That'd be nice too.
Shit. Damn it!
Fuck!
As for the plan to whack Hwang Deuk-gu at the party...
Some stuff happened.
Yes. The same goes for me,
so you don't owe me an explanation.
One of his businesses got destroyed.
Was that also you?
It wasn't intentional.
But you know what? If I seem a little off
next time you see me,
just avoid me.
Okay?
I have to say,
there are so many obstacles between us.
But one thing is for sure.
We're bound to cross paths again.
Right?
Can you explain why Hwang Deuk-gu had this?
Well, there was a bit of a situation.
Can I call you when I want to hear your voice?
If you need to talk to me about something, I won't avoid you.
Get in. I'll take you to your master.
Thank you, ma'am--
Come on. Don't be like this, ma'am.
Jeez, whatever.
"Mentally and physically incompetent"?
Did you really have to make me look like a crazy moron?
Who cares? You got out.
That's all that matters.
Madame Jang, would you trust me with your money?
The CEO is a moron.
Would you do business with his bank?
Private loans won't be affected at all, you know.
If you're that worried,
you can let me handle the secondary market.
-What? -Gosh, enough.
She's just worried about you.
In any case, you got out.
Let's drink to celebrate.
Well, I heard that Hwang Deuk-gu got attacked too.
What? That bastard?
Do you remember the place
where he took us after we got shot?
Yes. It looked like a hospital.
I heard it got destroyed.
Really? Who did it?
When Hwang Deuk-gu visited me,
he said some punks are after us.
We're not their target.
It's Hwang Deuk-gu.
I don't know who they are, but they're clearly
after Hwang Deuk-gu.
I don't know who those lunatics are,
but I want to start their fan club or something.
Come on. Don't laugh.
Can't you see that I got hurt too?
If you don't want to deal with something worse,
you'd better listen up.
Gosh, Madame Jang. Is this the only booze you have?
Give us something better.
Why now? We're talking.
Gosh, seriously.
Hwang Deuk-gu has the key for the safe in your office.
What? It needs to scan my palm to be unlocked.
You know he'd do anything to figure out a way.
You'd better protect the VIP vault from him.
Hwang Deuk-gu, that fucker...
Gosh.
I'm pretty sure no one invited you today.
Don't let anyone in.
I want to drink alone.
Get him a separate room.
Hwang Deuk-gu is here.
You mean, now? That fucker is here?
Yes, he just got here.
He's in a room over there.
I should give back what I received.
Hey, Hwang Deuk-gu.
You don't need to thank me.
If you're that grateful,
just shut up and lie low.
What the hell are you saying?
If I'm "grateful"?
You can either shut up and drink with me or get out.
Choose one.
What? Does this piss you off because I snatched your drink
when you're so used to stealing shit?
You thief.
How dare you go through my vault?
Who do you think the real owner of Argos is?
Argos?
It belongs to us, who faithfully served Chairman Ko.
At this very moment, who can decide whether you can live or not?
What's going on?
I heard your business got destroyed.
Apparently, so many people are out to get you.
Gosh, don't be like this. My goodness!
I was rude, wasn't I?
You can't really say that thing is yours.
Sure, I went through it.
What's wrong with that?
God, seriously! Drop the gun, will you?
You shouldn't have made me pick it up in the first place.
I gave you a chance to make your choice.
-I'm already holding the gun, -Gosh.
so I should finish the job.
What? "Finish the job"? What job?
If you want to be spared, choose one.
Choi Yong or Madame Jang?
You'll have to kill one of them.
What? What did you say?
You need to pay for acting rashly.
Gosh, hey. Please drop the gun.
My goodness, I'm injured. Gosh!
Change the D-day to today.
Get started.
You told me something
about the blackout.
You said an error could occur
if the recovery process is ignored.
You said it was like opening Pandora's box.
Right.
I guess I said something like that.
You guess? Unbelievable.
The resetting process didn't work this afternoon.
Are you sure it's not an error?
Like I said, no technical errors occurred.
But...
But what?
Well,
I still don't know whether it's a bug or a major error,
but your artificial eyes sometimes reveal themselves.
What? When did that happen?
There are gaps among the synapses in our brain
that conveys electrical and chemical responses.
A highly developed deep learning process of the AI
could lead to your artificial eyes
reading that information too.
Are you saying that my artificial eyes could hijack my thoughts?
It will seem foreign to you at first,
but as time goes by, you'll be confused as to
which are your own thoughts.
This is just my theory though,
so it can't be applied to your case.
What if,
and this is a big if...
What happens if the artificial eyes take control of me?
You will lose yourself and live by its orders.
What can I do to stop it?
What about the young lady?
The procedure was a success.
She'll be sent away once she recovers.
I'm ready to be tossed in solitary,
so I'll be telling the chief what happened.
-Sure. -Thank you
for letting me do this.
I didn't do anything. It was Tae-woong who approved.
This response is unexpected.
I don't want to go into solitary
for being on the same page as you, that's all.
Right.
This is new and I brought it here for a wash.
Take it into your solitary cell.
-You're mocking me, right? -It's a solitary cell.
You should go in there with a clean mind and body.
Try them on.
I have good personal hygiene.
Hold on a second. Haven't you had those on for days?
I have ten of the same design.
As if.
Now, go to the chief.
I will after I change.
Breaking news, Director Gu Won-bong
who went missing from K Hospital turns out to be alive.
Just a moment ago, we received a package
from an anonymous sender.
It contained a recorded video
of Director Gu's crucial announcement.
What he has to say is quite shocking
and we will play it for you right this moment.
I sit here before you today to expose
this nation's evil government and police force.
Several years ago, under the pretext
of eliminating The Red Ants before it became Argos,
a proposal was made to our lab
regarding the creation of enhanced human weapons.
K Hospital's research lab was a leading force
behind rehabilitation medicine
and therefore clearly expressed its objection to using technology
to create weapons that can take human lives.
However, the government and police pressured us
into joining the experiment with its threats and trickery.
We had no choice but to launch unethical human experimentation.
-Director Gu... -However,
once we found out that the experiments
were to be made on the most vicious criminals,
we took a strong stand and
-the experiments were ceased. -Chief. Why is Gi-beom's photo there?
The government and the police stressed social responsibility
-and squashed our opinions. -What the hell are we seeing?
-He's the whistle-blower. -Despite our achievements,
-we were abandoned though. -But they are all lies.
All the researchers including myself were abducted and murdered.
That son of a bitch.
-He tried to kill us. -The government
and police must acknowledge their unethical and illegal ways.
I, Gu Won-bong, strongly urge them
to genuinely apologize and generously compensate those
who were coerced into participating in this project.
No matter how many times you hear it,
the content is too shocking to believe.
However, there is something
that the viewers should be well aware of.
This is only Director Gu's unilateral claim
and investigations must be conducted to verify his allegations.
-Hello? -You son of a bitch.
Is this the best you can do?
Do you want to see my head on a spike?
You're done for.
Any more exposure will bring an end to Rugal.
Don't let this explode.
I'll do whatever it takes.
With just your words?
It's time to cut our losses.
Kang Gi-beom's the issue,
so sever him from the operation.
Deal with what's urgent
and I'll take it from there.
We will try our best to check the facts
to see what is true and what is not.
Do you finally get it?
Argos isn't a criminal enterprise.
The true criminals of this nation are government officials
and police officers living off our tax.
They are our enemies.
My fellow people,
open your eyes.
What they did was put on a show
to create human weapons.
Fuck. Is this true?
They did so by pointing all the blame at Argos too.
All the cold cases,
the missing people, and violent crimes
were created by the leaders of this nation.
He can't just spit lies like this.
What's going on? Were we hacked?
I can't pull down the video.
It seems recorded,
but every network's server
has been breached as well.
The man at the center of this scheme...
He will come out and reveal all the truth.
What if he refuses?
All the tragedies
Argos was accused
of masterminding and executing
will be reenacted by Argos in person.
You hear me,
Kang Gi-beom?
Sure.
I hear you loud and clear, Hwang Deuk-gu.
Kang is a killer and a fugitive.
No one knows if he's dead or alive.
Please get to the truth.
If things go this way, we cannot be sure that we are able to live safely.
We have a right to know if we're safe or not.
Don't let this get to you personally, Gi-beom.
We might be played by Hwang Deuk-gu.
Over my dead body.
We're to give Gi-beom up?
That will never happen, so don't you worry.
I have your back.
Your sacrifice won't clear up this mess.
He's right.
Playing into his hands could destroy Rugal too.
Hwang Deuk-gu's move isn't all that surprising though.
We all knew this would happen.
He plastered my name on dead bodies.
Of course, he'd go all the way.
But that got me thinking
about what would happen if my identity were to be revealed.
I believe my sacrifice will put an end to him.
I am who Hwang Deuk-gu wants.
You think he'll keep his promise?
Hwang Deuk-gu of all people?
I can make him.
That won't be the end though.
It'll be up to you to do the rest.
Rugal will still have you three.
Gi-beom...
What the hell are you saying?
Do you know what's funny though?
Although he looks like pure evil, the people are swayed by his words.
We worked hard, didn't we?
We fought through our injuries
to protect those we don't even know.
I didn't care about being acknowledged
because I believed
in what we were doing.
But...
I guess that wasn't it.
It's heartbreaking actually.
Our good intentions have been ignored,
and it burns.
Do I really deserve to be this hated?
What on earth did I do anyway?
On the other hand, I'm just sorry.
I'm sorry about everything
and that guilt is hard to bear.
-Are you sure it's a bomb? -It's homemade, but the maker is talented.
Trying to dismantle the timer bomb without proper knowledge of it
will blow up the bus.
If Gi-beom doesn't show up at the designated location by 9 a.m.,
he'll blow it up.
I'll go alone.
Go where?
It's me he wants.
I want to stop being the cause
of other people's pain.
Please let me do this.
POLICE
KANG GI-BEOM
Tae-woong, move out of the way.
CLIENT
KANG GI-BEOM
Is it really worth it
to protect the things you want?
You know you will all be fugitives if your team is dismissed.
Don't get caught until you catch them all.
The ones who are worse than me
are your higher-ups.
Tell me the truth before I kill you all.
You arrogant bastard.
One of us has to die for it to end.
Goodbye, Kang Gi-beom.