RUGAL
ALL CHARACTERS, PLACES,
ORGANIZATIONS, RELIGION AND INCIDENTS
PORTRAYED IN THIS DRAMA ARE FICTITIOUS
Kang Gi-beom, where are you?
Take him to the HQ.
-Just me and him?
-Get going.
-Get back here!
-Gosh.
Where the fuck did you go?
If you leave him like that,
he'll die soon.
You'll need to do something.
Isn't capturing him enough? I have to
escort him now so that he won't die?
Rugal doesn't have a murder license yet.
Hey, you can't say I killed him.
If you just leave him here,
it will be considered murder.
That bastard is a weakling.
Why is that my fault?
Connect me to the HQ.
Connecting to the HQ.
I CAPTURED HWANG DEUK-GU
It's connected now, sir.
Agent Kang sent us a message.
-Enable live streaming.
-Yes, sir.
Well done, Gi-beom.
EPISODE 7
Who are these morons?
Please don't kill us.
We did everything we were told to do!
Who put you up to this?
He said he'd kill everyone
if I didn't do this.
He said he'd kill me and my family.
Right, but who is "he"?
Chairman Hyeon.
-Did you say "Chairman Hyeon"?
-Yes.
If you get caught in any way,
say you were following
Chairman Hyeon's orders.
Don't care about whether it's true or not,
or why you're saying his name.
We were told that we must carry out
Chairman Hyeon's order to be forgiven.
What the heck is going on?
Gi-beom was right.
We must do whatever it takes
to fight against them.
You can go.
All those people are actually victims.
It's so upsetting that we can't catch
the real bad guys.
We can't say
they're completely innocent though.
They're all from powerful families.
They touched the political slush funds
their parents were delivering.
And that's why they needed
to be forgiven by Chairman Hyeon.
It's all for show.
Detective Yang is just pretending too.
So what, then? Is this it?
The higher-ups want us to let them go.
It's odd that a tycoon
like AH Group's Chairman Hyeon
admitted he's behind this.
And why did he request police protection
when he ordered them to do this?
Odd, right?
It doesn't make sense.
If you take Chairman Hyeon
out of the equation,
it actually makes more sense.
A mysterious third party did this
and pinned it on Chairman Hyeon,
so he got all angry.
Then he realized
that the police can't handle this,
so he rushed to get us involved.
He won't even get any credit for this.
He's doing all the work for nothing.
I feel so useless
because there's nothing we can do.
Yes, sir.
Pardon?
Okay.
This will make you feel better.
You know that you're no match for me.
Did you act weak back then?
To see what I can do?
What did they do to your body?
You're burning up.
Min-jun...
Get out of my way unless you want to die.
Help!
Gi-beom!
Kang Gi-beom!
Gi-beom, help me!
-Fuck!
-Hey, what's going on?
-Gi-beom!
-What's wrong?
Get him off me. Quick.
Fuck.
Gosh, I nearly died.
Hey, you shouted at the top of your lungs
because of this?
This man even bit my ear.
You have no idea what happened.
Can you not gauge the situation?
I'm sorry.
I guess you lost him because of me.
Damn it!
I'm really sorry.
Shall I take this guy instead?
Boss.
-You're on your way, right?
-We're almost there.
By any chance,
did you see a car leaving the reservoir?
A car leaving the reservoir?
Why do you ask?
Damn it.
I think Mi-na saw the car.
We'll go after it.
It was Hwang Deuk-gu.
-He's gone.
-I got a weird feeling when he drove by.
I should've known.
He could ditch the car
because someone helped him.
Should we search the area?
First, let's go to where Gi-beom is.
We'll find out why he couldn't chase him.
-Let's go.
-Okay.
You would've gotten in trouble
had I arrived a few minutes late.
We must've been brothers
in our past lives.
Whenever anything bad happens to you,
I break out in a cold sweat.
When I managed to collect myself,
I was already driving like a mad man.
Be quiet.
Just go wake Director Gu up.
MERCENARY
You invited all these important guests.
How come you're not here yet?
Sorry.
Some stuff happened.
Do you know how hard it was
to organize this meeting
for a private military company?
I am aware that it was difficult.
And that is why
I paid you generously
and gave you all the support you needed.
Show up within the next 30 minutes,
or the project will be put on hold.
Damn it.
Kang...
Gi-beom!
What? Where is Hwang Deuk-gu?
We lost him.
He ditched the car and ran off.
-Damn it.
-What happened?
-Are you okay?
-Yes.
I'm all right.
By the way, who's this?
Argos chairwoman's groom-to-be.
If we're talking about those bastards,
I only know of one groom-to-be.
Ko Yong-deok?
But Ko Yong-deok is dead.
-You found his corpse?
-He's still alive.
To be more accurate,
they're not letting him die in peace.
Boss.
-You, get out.
-You're in pain. I should stay--
-Get out at once!
-Yes, sir.
I'll begin.
I'll have to cut it all out.
I will give you anesthesia,
but you'll die if we wait.
Just...
Just begin.
He brought a dead man back to life.
TO THE EXECUTION SITE
And he took care of those fuckers
whom I wanted to punish.
I'm glad you like it.
On top of that, he even laughed at me.
That cocksure bastard.
Can you explain this to me?
Hwang Deuk-gu and Choi Ye-won
did this together.
They drowned the leader of Argos
at the execution site they built.
But what they didn't take
into consideration
is the fact that the divers
are just as greedy as they are.
To the divers, Ko Yong-deok
wasn't just a dead body they had to lift.
They saw it as a chance
to turn their lives around.
-One, two, three.
-Life never turns out the way you want.
They knew they'd be blamed for it,
so they couldn't tell the higher-ups.
One, two, three!
However, they couldn't kill him because
they thought he'd be useful later on.
Where are the divers?
Did you take care of them?
You don't need to worry.
Then now, it's my turn.
Good work. Go home and get some rest.
But you won't be able
to communicate with him.
Communicate with him?
-I'm just going to extract stuff from him.
-Shall I do it?
I can extract whatever you need.
No, it's okay.
Susan, it's dangerous.
You might get hurt. You might...
No way. Will Susan...
You guys shouldn't see this
so that you can avoid
being held responsible.
Let's go.
But...
They didn't just take care of the corpses.
Then what else?
They told the victims' watches,
cell phones, and jewelry.
They even sold organs.
As people say, old habits die hard.
They even sold
Ko Yong-deok's wedding presents.
They're actually pretty well-known
on resale websites.
I see comments vouching for the quality
and their after-sales service.
They're unbelievable.
Thanks to them, Hwang Deuk-gu
got blindsided by someone he trusted.
That serves him right.
These jerks have been taking advantage
of those evil bastards.
I bet Ko Yong-deok regrets
coming back to life.
He obviously didn't know
that he'd become the prey
in the ecosystem that he built.
He's alive,
so they're guilty of attempted murder.
If we manage to get a statement
from Ko Yong-deok,
we should be able to put both Choi Ye-won
and Hwang Deuk-gu behind bars.
That will be great, but why do I feel like
this is too easy to be true?
I should've killed Hwang Deuk-gu first.
Why didn't you kill him?
I obviously wanted to.
I guess that was enough
to get your revenge.
I was told to capture him alive
and not kill him.
-What was I supposed to do?
-What I'm saying is,
what you did
isn't a true representation of Rugal.
But thanks to your decision,
we could abide by our rules.
Let me ask you something
since you keep talking about rules.
Let's say I killed him.
Then who will take responsibility for it?
Will you go to jail with me?
I'll take responsibility
for anything Rugal does.
Even if that entails
something a lot worse than going to jail.
Hwang Deuk-gu! Choi Ye-won!
I'll teach you a lesson--
Do you feel alive now?
You bastard.
Do you know who I am?
I'm Ko Yong-deok.
One vial keeps you awake for five minutes,
but you lose a year of your life
every time you get a shot of this.
I don't think you have time to whine.
What is it that you want?
We might have similar goals.
I'll let you take Hwang Deuk-gu.
If you want to get your revenge,
you'll have to tell me
everything you know.
Your anger level
is in the dangerous range.
You must relieve your anger.
Thanks for bringing that up.
Had you not stopped me...
-I never did.
-What?
All I do is tell you
the results of my analyses.
-So what's your opinion?
-You want to hear my opinion?
Forget it.
It's no use talking about it now.
I suggest you eat vitamin-rich fresh fruit
for your mental health.
Doing a handstand before bed
will be helpful as well.
I have to eat fruit this late? Forget it.
We should kill Hwang Deuk-gu first.
You wanted to cook up a scheme.
I guess you had a change of heart?
The situation must be changing rapidly.
The order changed, but that's all.
That position sounds very stressful.
You must be anxious at all times.
In conclusion, you killed him.
I know nothing about it.
Sure, whatever.
But I decide how it'll be done.
Let's discuss the details in person.
I'll call you
when I have the location and time.
D-Day, all of a sudden?
Forgive me for the sake of our friendship.
A gift? After what you did?
It's not like we'll never see each other.
And I never come empty-handed
whenever I see you.
But whether you buy that gallery or not,
you can't go up against Hwang Deuk-gu
with the little bit of money
you embezzled.
It all depends on how I stage it,
as long as I have a reason to kill him.
That's true.
I can't believe it though.
What did Hwang Deuk-gu do to Seol Min-jun
to turn him into his loyal dog?
That I don't know.
But if it's Hwang Deuk-gu...
It's not so surprising.
Right.
The old farts are scared shitless too.
Choi Yong and Bong Man-cheol
said they'd help too.
Seriously?
Those stiff old farts?
They need to turn things around
quickly as well.
And you become tenderhearted
when you're old and sick.
But you also
had to lower yourself.
I think Hwang Deuk-gu got
on Chairman Hyeon's nerves.
If I can make him feel better
and end the power struggles
once and for all,
putting my ego aside isn't a big deal.
Him being the vice-chairman,
I'd like the actions to be somewhat grand.
What do you have in mind?
I'd like to test the waters,
but I haven't seen him around lately.
Could he have caught on?
Weren't you taking a break?
I get it.
Physically activity clears the mind
when it comes to people like us.
Come on. Let me help you with that.
How about another round?
I'm good for many.
Wearing yourself out
won't solve your problems though.
Have we been doing a good job?
-Of course.
-Then why is it
that I can only remember
their gruesome crimes?
I feel like we're losing.
Then we'll find a way to win.
Forget about approvals and justifications.
We need something
that'll turn the tables around.
Can anyone guess
what I have in this envelope?
-Money!
-No, that's not the case.
In this envelope are gift vouchers
that you can use to consume products
and services provided by Argos.
I see you couldn't trust me.
Let's now welcome Chairwoman Choi Ye-won.
Ms. Choi will personally drop
the envelope in the letterbox.
One, two, three.
Please give her a big round of applause!
Envelopes like this will be delivered
to 5,000 disadvantaged families.
Please give Ms. Choi
another big round of applause.
Next, we'll begin the raffle.
We have many prizes ready today.
Green tea, potatoes, and kiwi!
Let's now begin the raffle!
-Make it seem like you're guarding me.
-Would you like a box of kiwi?
-Yes!
What an angel you are.
We also do good in this world, you know.
Before you speak shit of our blank money,
I dare you to take away the envelopes
from the kids who'll receive them.
I doubt you called me over to boast.
I'm the only one in the organization
interested in charity.
It's good in a way
since no one bothers to interfere.
No one suspects anything either
because I've been at this for a while.
It's a smart move.
Why don't we take a walk elsewhere?
It's been a while since I've walked
among a crowd.
I didn't know we were close enough
to share such information.
There were men earlier
eyeing my every move.
I should take precautions
considering I hardly know you.
Well, I'm the type to perform better
under pressure.
Soon I will throw a party
with all the middle bosses.
Hwang Deuk-gu will be there, too.
-The venue?
-My residence.
No one will raise questions
since it's where we normally gathered.
So big names
will be gathered in one place.
-Talk about a top-security event.
-Of course.
A mistake will lead to your death.
Your concern isn't necessary.
It's pretty here.
Enjoy the view.
Enjoy the night view and
fit me in for a consult tomorrow morning.
I found the perfect place.
You're here.
Hi.
Why did you call me here this morning?
So what's this about?
I wanted to clear my head
and apologize to you.
Apologize for what?
Well,
you and I keep clashing.
We may have the same goal,
but I'm sure it hasn't been easy for you
because of one certain teammate.
I guess you can say that.
But was it necessary to ask me out here
just to tell me that?
What do you really want to say?
I've been trying hard not to address this,
but it's easier said than done.
What is?
Ms. Han Tae-yeon.
In order to save her brother,
she bet everything she had
on one detective.
I couldn't help her in any way though.
I'm even partially responsible
for you losing your arm.
You must've known,
so why didn't you say anything?
You
did your job
while I only did mine.
I don't want to be
at wits' end thinking about
what couldn't have been helped.
You never bring your personal emotions
to the office, do you?
The outcome wouldn't have changed
-no matter who had taken the case.
-But I
feel sorry
and of course awful.
If only we all face the same direction.
Then no one would have to get hurt.
Probably.
What's with the sudden training session?
Beats me.
Gi-beom will bite our heads off
if we don't show or are late.
Oh...
-Did you receive this text too?
-Yes.
He probably has something to say
but your guess is as good as mine.
There. I see Gi-beom and Tae-woong.
How about a run to get the blood flowing?
Why waste a fine day by the water?
Can I believe that your priority
lies with Rugal then?
That's right.
The make sure you protect it
until the very end.
Of course.
What's taking you so long?
Coming!
Did you tell them to come?
Why aren't you running at top speed?
Stop slacking off.
We haven't trained together in a while.
Let's make the most of it then.
I'm all warmed up, so let's do this.
-Let's go.
-Let's do this.
The dead skin on your body
has been removed.
It has been replaced by artificial flesh.
And everywhere else?
Fortunately, your organs were unscathed.
You might've not made it
had you come back too late.
Of course. You're a doctor, right?
All the cutting and sawing you do
made you seem like a butcher.
And also,
if what you're hoping for
is a device
that can outsmart a human being--
-We have to move up the plan.
-Sorry?
I'll provide you with anything you need,
so make it happen this time.
Yes, sir.
CHOI YE-WON
Let me start by
cleaning out my house first.
-Does this hurt?
-No.
Then...
That hurts!
Really?
Maybe the wires
weren't connected properly.
Hey, be grateful for this though.
Susan would've been way worse.
-What?
-Jeez,
you're clueless, aren't you?
Gwang-cheol, the devil lives among us!
What? The devil?
That's right.
Don't be ridiculous.
Isn't it weird
how the chief chose Susan over the others
to accompany him at the solitary cell?
You're right.
That is weird.
She's a sweetheart,
so I'd think she'd scream in fear.
Don't say that when you know nothing!
Ko Yong-deok
will end up spilling the beans.
It won't be easy.
The man once led a crime organization.
But I've seen her at work.
She cuts, saws, combines,
and assembles people
as if they're toys.
The blood is just too gruesome.
You have no idea
since you were anesthetized.
But I've seen it all.
Her face carried a blank expression,
but she was enjoying it--
Oh, right.
Hi, Susan.
Yes, right here.
Thanks, Bradley. That feels better.
-Can you double-check?
-Right here.
Right...
I'm scared!
No, I'm terrified!
Sir, you asked for me?
Are you all right, sir?
And here I thought you'd never show up.
So what has Hwang been up to lately?
We've been wanting to see him,
but he's been off the grid.
Mr. Hwang only keeps
Seol Min-jun by his side these days.
We already heard.
I won't accept silence,
so at least give me something.
Bring me Hwang Deuk-gu
or it'll be over between you and me.
Well, you see...
Boss, you're here!
I see you've been busy...
behind my back.
That's not the case.
In your absence, I'm supposed to--
I see that life goes on for you.
You sure can hold a gaze
for someone who lost everything.
What you took from me doesn't matter.
Without Yong-deok,
you won't be able to do anything
with that address.
What do you mean?
Who cares that you have a weapon
when you don't know how to use it?
You'll never be able to.
Are you implying
that you have
the late chairman hidden somewhere?
If you're that curious,
go ahead and dig up his grave.
If I must,
then I will.
What?
What was that all about?
Is there something
that only the two of you know?
It's nothing you need to know,
so forget about it.
Damn it.
Shit.
Where are you keeping
the list of lobbied politicians?
VIP SAFE AT MOPIN, UNIT 1004
Must I start from the beginning again?
Min-jun, give Dal-ho the information
on K Hospital's Dr. Oh Gwang-su.
Boss, who is this?
Watch him around the clock.
Around the clock?
Yes, you'll bring him to me
the second I give you the order.
You will not fail or get caught.
Yes, Boss.
Stop the car.
Get out.
-Sorry?
-Get out.
Do you mean me?
Don't you know what
"around the clock" means?
Sure, I'll get going.
Damn it.
We might need Ko Yong-deok.
I don't have to tell you
what you need to do, right?
JUDGES
-Thank you.
-Thanks.
She's been in musicals...
-We'll keep her in mind.
-Right.
-Let's take a short break.
-Sure.
Can't you see that I'm busy?
There's something only Choi Yong knows.
What do you know about Chairman Ko?
How do I know?
You being in the dark implies
that it's something important though.
It's something big, right?
It seems like he and Hwang Deuk-gu
stroke some kind of deal.
-Money?
-No, something more than that.
It's something
that could give him control of Argos
and push Hwang Deuk-gu aside.
If that's the case, we should team up.
Are you sure us working together?
You wouldn't have come to me
if you weren't sure.
Of course not.
No wonder my feet naturally led me here.
So what can I do to help?
Ye-won seems to be making plans
to have us gathered.
Sounds like we'll be able
to paint a nice picture.
Wait, what the hell?
-Gi-beom.
-Yes?
-Dr. Oh has been kidnapped.
-What?
Are you sure
it's Director Gu of K Hospital?
Yes, it most definitely is him.
He called for help
and said he knew where Dr. Oh was taken.
Are you saying Director Gu escaped?
He said we needed to rescue him first
since Dr. Oh won't have much time.
I can't be sure of what's going on.
I'll dispatch my men first,
so assemble two teams and
set up a perimeter around the location.
All we have at the moment
is Director Gu's intel.
I doubt there's a security camera
in the parking lot of a closed hospital.
Dr. Oh never installed
a GPS system or a dashcam
in case it could lead anyone
back to headquarters.
Bastards.
How dare they kidnap Dr. Oh.
Can Director Gu be trusted?
We'll have to see for ourselves.
Chief, the fact that
they know about Dr. Oh
might be a danger to our organization.
Exactly. It's why this operation
will shape the course of this war.
You must rescue him.
-Of course.
-Yes, sir.
Everybody, stop.
Gi-beom, check our location.
I see three points at
our two, eight, and eleven o'clock.
They're all about a kilometer from here.
Mi-na, take 2 o'clock,
Gwang-cheol, take 11,
and I'll take eight o'clock.
Send a signal if you see anything.
Hold on. What about me?
There could be men hiding.
You are to watch our backs.
I can multitask, you know.
If you're not going to take orders,
tell me now.
That's not what I meant.
It's dark and also quiet out here.
Stay off the radio as much as possible
and only communicate when needed.
There's no time to waste, so move out.
Got it.
Excuse me.
Director Gu Won-bong?
You really came.
I was worried that
you might not find the place.
-Are you injured?
-I'm fine.
I've been crouching down
hiding all this time,
so my legs are a little numb, that's all.
So where's Dr. Oh?
If it's that way...
I found Director Gu.
I'll escort him to the police
and join you guys.
Please note that Dr. Oh is at ten o'clock.
Let me take you to safety.
-What are you doing...
-I'm sorry about this.
What's going on? There's nothing here.
This doesn't seem like the place.
Besides, Mi-na can't be seen.
Mi-na, where are you right now?
Mi-na?
Mi-na!
Mi-na...
How did it go?
An officer at the scene radioed in.
Director Gu has been secured.
Good job. Send him here.
Yes, sir.
Did you find Dr. Oh?
Not yet, sir.
But Mi-na can't be reached.
I told her to stay off the radio
as much as possible,
but she's just not answering.
Head back for now.
I'll contact both
Gi-beom and Mi-na separately.
-Still--
-Director Gu has been secured.
We can get Dr. Oh's location out of him
and rescue him.
Yes, sir.
We'll head back to HQ for now.
What the hell?
Mi-na.
What's going on?
Bradley.
The number you have called...
It's me, Gi-beom.
How did you get my personal number?
Forget about that. This is urgent.
My eyes are having a blackout.
Tell me how to fix this.
Okay, hold on.
Judging by the wavelengths I'm seeing,
I think the linked chips are interfering
with one another.
Linked? What do you mean?
You probably won't get it.
Didn't you say this was urgent?
It is, so recover my vision.
I'm sorry.
I can't do that.
Mi-na was abducted! Hurry!
The restoration process isn't that simple.
It may cause unknown errors.
Just do it.
You can fix those errors later.
Look. It's not as easy as it sounds.
Just do it!
It's the same as opening Pandora's box.
Susan did her utmost best to secure that.
I don't want to hear it.
Just fix my eyes.
I need to find her
before she gets in danger!
I won't take responsibility for this.
Damn it!
Find Mi-na.
Hwang Deuk-gu?
Do you know me as well?
I must be quite famous.
Hwang Deuk-gu!
I love how feisty you are.
Fish taste the best
when they're still flopping about.
I was dying to meet you.
And finally, here we are.
I'm not after you.
I'm after the person
who is crazy about blood.
Look who's talking.
You seem
quite useful.
Don't kill her.
Please spare me!
I just did as I was told!
Please...
Please show me mercy!
Do you think this is a trap?
Gi-beom and Mi-na haven't returned yet.
They're not the type
to get easily subdued.
Right?
They may be looking for Dr. Oh.
Or perhaps, they've already found him.
I know the easiest and quickest method.
Ko Yong-deok.
Let me talk to him.
Have you been alive all along, Tae-woong?
Thank you
for taking care of me.
Who?
Me? Took care of you?
You crazy bastard.
If you're so grateful,
untie me.
I'm a geezer now.
I'm sure I'm not a threat.
You will die
in this room.
Is that bitch, Han Tae-yeon, here too?
I bet she's not.
I made sure I took care of her.
The people dear to me
have disappeared.
Repent for everything you've done
and answer my question.
Repentance is nice.
Repentance...
By the way,
could you speak louder?
My ears must've given out.
I only hear ringing.
Where are the doctors from K Hospital?
You impudent son of a bitch!
How dare you lecture me?
Tae-woong!
You will never be able to conquer
Argos, my masterpiece.
Tae-woong, something's not right.
Welcome to hell, Kang Gi-beom!
Run!
Hey, you small-time gangster.
Let her go and deal with me.
That's a bit rich coming from someone
who toyed with a living corpse.
I see.
I won't put up a fight, okay?
I surrender.
What are you scheming?
Am I not the target?
I'll let you have it your way.
Turn on the lights.
Both of you will die anyway.
Take her.
-Are you okay?
-Gi-beom.
There's downhill when you go out.
-You're good at rolling, right?
-Of course.
Run as soon as you get up, got it?
Okay.
Now.
Come on, now.
I said I surrendered.
Tae-woong, can you hear me?
-Come here!
-Gwang-cheol.
What?
Did you think she'd survive
if you got her out of here?
It's a lot more like hell outside.
Did you enjoy the festival last time?
Before you sign the contract,
I'd like to hear how you're going
to eliminate Hwang Deuk-gu in detail.
Hello?
CLIENT
I see.
So this was it.
This was why it was possible.
Catch the bitch
who ran away.
And for that asshole in there,
show him what hell truly looks like.
Yes, sir.
What are you doing?
Let me go.
Make sure you inhale as much as you can.
You won't be able to endure it
without this.
When I had my head underwater,
I didn't see how it would help train me.
But now, I've realized
that I owe my instructor big time.
Hwang Deuk-gu,
I will destroy you from the inside.
Subtitle translation by Soo-ji Kim
Where is this truck going?
The damage will keep multiplying.
You think you can handle it?
They've gotten much stronger.
Both their strength and explosive power.
Kill anyone and everyone
that gets in the way.
Gwang-cheol!
You shouldn't have crossed the line
from the beginning.
Did you think you wouldn't get caught?
I will show you what I'm capable of.
It crossed my mind
that he is after my artificial eyes.