RUGAL
ALL CHARACTERS, PLACES,
ORGANIZATIONS, RELIGION AND INCIDENTS
PORTRAYED IN THIS DRAMA ARE FICTITIOUS
POLICE
KANG GI-BEOM
EPISODE 11
Hello.
Yes, hello.
-Hello.
-What the...
-Why is it leaving?
Sir, I need to get off.
Could you please open the rear door?
Please pull over. I need to get off.
Excuse me?
What's he doing? Gosh.
I said I need to get off.
Why isn't he letting me off? Jeez.
-What is this place?
-Where are we now?
-Look.
-What is it?
-What's going on?
-Gosh! What the...
-What is going on?
What the heck? Hey, look at this.
-You scared us.
-What is that?
-Flowers?
-My gosh.
It's a real gun!
KANG GI-BEOM
Look at you trying so hard. Over.
No one will give you credit for this.
Over.
I thought you'd use Ko Yong-deok
to buy some time.
What's going on?
Don't tell me you killed him.
I suppose he was the one
you were really after.
Well, he is one of them.
I feel bad about the lab.
You must've put a lot of work on it.
Gosh, you have nothing
to fall back on now.
You don't own
a single building or business.
All your limbs have been caught off,
and you'll go to jail.
Playing with you a little
doesn't mean I take you seriously.
Sorry to disappoint you,
but you're like an abandoned puppy.
Don't forget who you're talking to.
Do you think anyone can push me around?
If your late wife sees
the mess you're in now...
You've never even met her.
So many assholes
use spy cameras these days.
You wouldn't be able
to do other things either.
This room is filled with jammers.
The system freezes?
That's a misunderstanding.
You can't do anything when I blackout.
That's why I'm training so hard.
To be ready for when I can't see.
Turning the computer off
doesn't shut off the motherboard.
The notion of sleep doesn't apply to me.
What the heck are you saying?
Anyway, do you have a plan or not?
It depends on what's causing it.
If it's caused by jamming,
I can offset it indirectly
by analyzing the frequency.
However, I'll need some time.
Oh, that...
Although it all depends on the type.
Be quiet.
I already told the quack to meet me here
to train for that.
I've been studying.
-Hey.
-Hi.
-Are you ready?
-Yes.
What do I do first?
The first thing.
Guess where I am.
Jeez. Oh, my.
The things that you're trying
to protect...
Are they really worth it?
Shut your trap.
Let's just shoot the movie, as planned.
Where's the script?
There's no script?
So I have to improvise?
Jeez, have some manners.
You see the world through a camera,
so you think life is like a movie.
Do you want a spoiler?
Sure, let's hear it.
You'll die
as the worst bastard in history.
And all your friends will be taken
to my new lab, which will be built soon.
We'll cut them up, grind them,
and pull out their organs.
We'll prick and rip their flesh to shreds.
So predictable. It's not even touching.
The movie will be an epic fail.
Frankly, we have nothing to lose. Why?
Because we've always done those things.
We just did what we always do.
Then who do you think
will be the target of criticism?
Those who failed to protect
what they had to protect.
The incompetent, pathetic,
responsibility-dodging pathological liars.
The country that embarrasses its citizens.
The country where you people live.
Even those who you risked your life for
are deserting you.
I'm sure your higher-ups are busy
blaming others to evade responsibility.
You see, you're just being used.
You're nothing but a scapegoat.
I just need to accomplish my goal
in this mayhem.
Instilling fear toward Argos.
Stop spewing complete nonsense
and just get down here.
Or shall I go up?
I guarantee you.
You guys will never catch me.
The ones who are worse than me
are your higher-ups.
He actually went alone?
I want to yell at him when he does this.
Then we should go too.
Right, Tae-woong?
All the tragedies
Argos was accused
of masterminding and executing
will be reenacted by Argos in person.
On the other hand, I'm just sorry.
I'm sorry about everything
and that guilt is hard to bear.
So you're saying the video
of Hwang Deuk-gu is like a decoy?
Unlike the video of Director Gu, it was
only disseminated to the police intranet.
It's fishy, I must say.
They act all righteous,
but they threaten the police
behind the closed curtains.
The trap they set up for Gi-beom
can't be the only thing they're after.
That's what we must stop.
Did you stay up all night
pondering whether you should go alone?
I'm Hwang Deuk-gu's target, you know.
Right, so far.
Earlier, I couldn't cry
even though I was so sad.
It made me wonder,
"Am I really sad or not?"
Right.
I can't remember the last time I broke out
in a sweat with cold, clammy hands.
No matter what I decide to do,
I'm sure you'd do the same
if you were in my position.
But it's different.
You're making a sacrifice,
whereas I'd just be paying
for my past deeds.
The outcome would be the same though.
Because I will stop you.
So?
You'll actually go there alone?
If Hwang Deuk-gu is still after Rugal
even after I step in,
then you'll have to stop him.
Each of us has our own tasks, that's all.
Right.
We all have
our own tasks.
Good luck.
Thanks.
Don't be afraid.
Come on. Your arm can kill people.
See you later.
It's not over until it's over.
The video of Hwang Deuk-gu
that was on the news last night
wasn't revealed to the public.
Sorry?
But all of us saw that
on the news together.
Just before
the video of Director Gu ended,
the police intranet was breached.
So the video of Hwang Deuk-gu
was disseminated to the police only,
which means the public
only heard Director Gu's confession.
But that's such a hassle. Why bother?
So that the media would focus on Gi-beom
and only criticize the police.
They didn't want to be out in the open.
It'd also serve as a warning.
The cops who have received bribes
from Argos
would either lie low
or avoid dealing with them altogether.
Hwang Deuk-gu will focus on Gi-beom.
The bus will be his next target.
The cop who disseminated this information
is also waiting for the right time.
The cops are nowhere to be seen.
I'll keep on driving
until further instructions.
-We should go after the hijacked bus.
-The police are tracking the bus secretly.
We'll be exposed if we aren't careful,
and they'll focus on our mistakes.
And they might use it
to instill fear in the public.
Are you saying we should wait
for the right time
because Gi-beom stepped in
as per Hwang Deuk-gu's request?
That's right.
Stay focused and be on standby.
-Yes, sir.
I hope they're okay.
Gi-beom and everyone on the bus.
I think
this is Choi Ye-won.
You picked up. I guess you're okay, then.
What's going on?
You probably know more than we do.
Who's this?
One of you summoned him.
And now, you're calling him.
What a disaster.
There's a woman
among those who are after us?
You're a woman yourself,
as the leader on that side.
It's not surprising.
-You intrigue me.
-Mind your own business.
Everyone who gets involved with you
ends up suffering.
My gosh, am I that bad?
Just wait.
We'll meet soon anyway,
so do not contact us until then.
What? I thought you'd try to get
some intel off her.
-You just wanted to warn her?
-I hope she took that as a warning.
We fight with actions,
not words.
If she calls again...
For the past 30 years,
KANG TAE-HUN
...I never succumbed...
LETTER OF RESIGNATION
...to external pressure...
I'm writing it now,
so you don't need to hound me.
You're still the Commissioner-General,
so don't let your guard down.
They said there will be
terror attacks all over if things go awry.
We're chasing them,
so don't worry too much.
Get it sorted out as soon as possible.
We can't have the public get all anxious,
so keep the media out.
When you're in this position,
you're anxious almost every day.
Still,
I should...
COMMISSIONER-GENERAL KANG TAE-HUN
...look after myself.
You should hire more guards.
And try not to be seen in public.
Okay, will do.
By the way, how can you be so well versed
in both sides' situations?
Why are you curious about that?
Well, I was just...
SEOUL METROPOLITAN POLICE AGENCY
Chief Choi.
Gosh, what is happening?
-They want to keep us on standby?
-Yes.
Shouldn't we be doing something
like raiding Argos?
Well...
Did you hear?
That guy, Kang Gi-beom,
is the Kang Gi-beom we know.
What are you talking about?
I'm talking about your friend,
Detective Kang.
Stop spewing total nonsense.
I heard he's walking around with a mask on
to find the bastard who killed his wife.
He's even committed crimes.
I heard the man who caught Bong Man-cheol
was also wearing a mask.
How will you explain that?
Really?
I don't know who to believe.
How could you spread a false rumor
when you're a cop?
Did you find out
who sent the video of Director Gu?
I'm working on it.
What happened?
Find out.
If you leave like this,
you'll be considered a suspect.
You can't make this position yours
by threatening me.
Maybe if you sort out the bus incident.
Why did you let Bong Man-cheol go?
Why ask me?
Take it up with Yuyeon Police Station.
He is the real power behind Argos.
You aided his release
when you should be putting
shackles on him!
Seeing you so on edge
is bringing back the old memories
from over ten years ago.
A woman died, and a man persistently tried
to avenge her death.
That's how Rugal came into being.
Enough. That has nothing to do with this.
Collect yourself
and try to see the essence.
Then you'll find the answer.
Pin everything on Kang Gi-beom.
The murder, the robbery,
and even that darn experiment. All of it.
You even think like Hwang Deuk-gu now
because you've been hanging out with him.
-What?
-When it comes to Argos,
no negotiations can be made.
Have you been tailing me?
With the authority that we have,
we should be helping that young man
who's been through hell.
How could you want
to destroy him like this?
The people of this country come first!
Gi-beom
is one of them.
Sir, the police just pulled up
in front of our HQ.
The police
are at the HQ now.
Oh, is that right?
Do not
mess with Rugal.
You know you will all be fugitives
if your team is dismissed.
At least try to be useful
if you know that you're useless!
We'll work on the case
and catch the person
who killed the Commissioner-General.
-But...
-But what?
"Dismissed"?
Don't say that ever again in front of me.
I decide
the future of Rugal.
Tae-woong, things got complicated.
Yes, we saw what happened.
I'm sure you saw it coming,
but your identity could be revealed too.
Don't worry about me, sir.
I can handle what comes my way.
There won't be any need
for you to take responsibility.
We'll end up being abandoned,
-so let's power through in our own way.
-Yes, sir.
Those in league with Argos
will be fished out.
We will have more work to do then.
Don't get caught until you catch them all.
Roger that.
Let them in.
Isn't our purpose in life
to put food on the table?
You're the craziest.
I'm glad you finally know.
I don't poison people like others,
so go ahead.
Recovery and interference control
complete.
Okay.
So,
shall we begin?
This is actually good.
For some reason,
steaks have never been my cup of tea.
You can have it.
Chew.
Kang Gi-beom,
how about you work for me instead?
What?
What's there to life
other than doing what benefits you?
You held back for your wife
and once again to save the world.
Holding back like that
will only make you ill, you know.
-So?
-Your job will pretty much be the same.
Operate under hidden identity,
shadow people, and punish them.
And then at times, you kill them.
Taking my hand will be quite entertaining.
Choose to enjoy your life a bit more.
I'm not the type to hold hands with men.
You know,
I was going to hear you out today,
but it's just too revolting.
It may be all right for you,
but what about your friends?
Tae-woong, leave this to me.
What are you going to do?
You're not comfortable
getting involved with the cops,
even corrupt ones.
Not for you though?
I'm more flexible in a way,
so let me handle this.
No, this is my business to solve.
How will you do it though?
-We'll now move in.
-Sure.
Moving in.
Freeze!
You are under arrest
of obstruction of justice.
Don't come after me until I show myself!
Arrest him.
Tae-woong!
What are you thinking?
Them being here means
that they can come at us at any time.
The chief can fend them off once,
but not forever.
How could they have known our location?
We don't have a choice.
I don't know anymore.
Whatever happens, happens.
All I'm protecting now are Rugal
and the victims of Argos.
It's not like he's wrong, I guess.
Gwang-cheol, you drive that one.
-Why?
-We should take them to a hospital.
Right, of course.
Fuck, where was it embedded?
Damn it!
Let go of me.
"Mentally and physically incompetent."
You didn't think I meant it?
-You have one day.
-Hwang Deuk-gu!
Eliminate one and you'll live.
Eliminate both and I'll take it out.
I heard there was a commotion yesterday.
Does it perhaps have anything to do with
Hwang Deuk-gu running wild?
You're saying that like it's our fault.
He's not one to be reasonable
with his actions.
And judging by the way you ask,
it seems like
you're out of your depth with him too.
How about I show you otherwise?
Mr. Bong.
Yes?
Didn't you
make dinner plans
with Hwang Deuk-gu this evening?
Yes, of course.
We'll eliminate him then.
Sure.
-Have you finally made up your mind?
-But first,
I'd like to see if everyone here is loyal.
There's secret information
you share with Hwang Deuk-gu.
What is it?
-What?
-Are you hiding something from us?
You're ganging up on me?
Madame Jang, I'm disappointed.
What are you talking about?
I'm only asking
because I heard the rumors too.
You rat bastard.
You've been looking into me
behind my back?
Bong Man-cheol, you!
What the hell are you doing?
One of you
must die I'm afraid.
And there we have it.
-The traitor.
-Shut up!
Hwang Deuk-gu ordered this, didn't he?
Calm down.
Calm down and listen to me.
You're just the same.
After all the crap you threw my way, you--
This evening...
This evening?
You, Choi Ye-won,
listen up.
I am now declaring war.
If you manage to stay alive,
you'll either bow down to me
or just disappear.
You...
The same goes for you too.
-Mi-joo.
-Yes?
Just stay here.
Are you insane?
Bong Man-cheol...
You're telling me
to stay here with a corpse?
A corpse or what-not,
it's our policy
to personally deal with our own.
So just stay put for a while.
This isn't the time to uphold principles.
One wrong move
and we'll meet the same fate.
CLIENT
Didn't I tell you not to call?
Can you come over?
I need protection.
Who the hell are you giving orders to?
Think of it as a deal. Give and take.
Will you pass up on a chance
to catch Argos?
Tell me your offer first.
Hear it for yourself in person.
See the merchandise
before putting a price on it.
Send the location.
If the deal isn't worth it,
I'll come after you first.
That'll never be the case.
Now, hurry.
You said actions speak louder than words.
She seemed urgent
and has asked for our help.
Should we take the offer?
Was it Choi Ye-won?
We should.
Sounds exciting to me.
KO YONG-DEOK'S RESIDENCE
It is Ko Yong-deok's residence.
An outsider was asked
by Choi Yeo-won
to enter Arogs's headquarters.
Someone might lose his or her life today.
Or maybe someone already has.
You called me here today
to kill me, right?
But you still came anyway.
The camera was probably set up
to film my death.
The video
will then be used
as leverage within Argos.
You killed the nation's evilest killer,
so you'll be applauded for it, right?
However,
your grand finale would be
this.
It won't be able to
properly function in here.
Who knows its function
better than its owner?
I admit that my artificial eyes
are desirable to just about anyone.
-It truly is mesmerizing.
-Is that so?
A taxidermy animal head
is worth more if it's smiling.
So smile, Deuk-gu. You never know.
I just might graciously forgive you.
I'll crush you
and dig those eyes out myself.
One of us has to die for it to end.
Being the generous one,
I'll let you die instead.
You arrogant bastard.
This sure is a lot.
Don't just stand there. Get him.
You foolish idiot.
Ta-da. Got any more left in you?
Where should I shoot first?
Your brain isn't a robot too, is it?
Goodbye,
Kang Gi-beom.
What the fuck?
Seol Min-jun?
What the fuck do you think you're doing?
That's enough.
Why the hell are they fighting each other?
I'm grateful.
Choi Ye-won lacks followers.
No wonder she's urgent.
Shall we go in?
The place once used to be impenetrable,
but now it's nothing but a mess.
It seems like
fate is not on your side.
Get them.
Head that way.
Chief, I made it out.
It didn't exactly go as planned,
but Seol Min-jun came to my aid.
Seol Min-jun?
-What about Hwang Deuk-gu?
-He lured Hwang Deuk-gu out to help me.
He texted me once
after we saw him at the reservoir.
He seemed to come back to his old self.
It didn't seem like
he was under someone's control.
Dr. Oh probably helped him too.
He wouldn't have blown his cover
unless things were urgent though.
I'll look for Seol Min-jun, sir.
Good.
I hope he hangs in there.
Don't be too hurt over this.
Gwang-cheol.
-He's dead.
-It wasn't Madame Jang.
She's not bold enough to do this.
Then could it have been Choi Yong?
Probably.
He'll also target Hwang Deuk-gu
then oust Choi Ye-won.
How savage.
This is the only place I haven't searched.
I'm coming in.
First, let's see what you can offer.
You perfectly fooled me.
How did you do it?
I thought you were loyal.
Were you just anticipating a chance?
You don't even deserve this bullet.
Dr. Oh refused to help you.
-But not me.
-What?
Are you telling me that he took a look
at your head?
I was planning to wait it out,
but I couldn't bear
with your filthy deeds.
That's a bit rich coming from you.
You've done a lot of filthy shit for me.
You won't get your way.
You won't die as you wish.
Do you think I'd allow that?
I don't see him.
I'll keep searching.
Since he failed to kill you,
he'll try to blow up the bus.
We're running out of time. Hurry.
Yes, sir.
What the fuck?
I didn't know I'd bring so many people
over through one call.
First, thanks.
But next time,
I'd like to see Gi-beom as well.
Life is no fun if you always get your way.
We'll take that body.
It's crucial evidence,
but you just abandoned it.
I wasn't planning on this,
but I guess we're even now.
This will put me in a tight spot.
That's like a trophy to us.
We still have business between us,
so don't misunderstand.
I'll see you next time.
I know that we've become acquainted,
but isn't it best
that we don't see each other often?
Make Bong Man-cheol's death
look accidental.
I don't want to get involved.
Tae-woong.
One minute.
-Are you hurt?
-No. Where are you?
We're at Ko Yong-deok's place.
Bong Man-cheol was killed
by someone inside.
It must be a mess over there.
You're right.
I have a lot to tell you.
I have a lot to tell you too.
We'll be there soon
after handing a body over to the police.
I knew it, you betraying asshole.
Don't touch him.
Sir.
He's not yours to punish.
You're supposed to be the vice-chairman,
but where in the world are you?
I guess something happened
for you to take interest in me.
Choi Yong killed Bong Man-cheol
before my eyes.
Oh, dear.
He should've died as well.
What a stupid scumbag.
-What did you just say?
-Never mind. So?
I doubt you were even slightly fazed.
They took the body.
I think they're Kang Gi-beom's people.
By the way,
why were you all gathered except me?
You're always so busy.
What happened to Gi-beom?
I wanted to stuff his body
so that you'd get to see him
for a long time.
But he's a tenacious one.
Any hindrance to our organization
should be eliminated.
You're finally sounding like a chairwoman.
Come here right now.
Okay, I'll be there soon.
I read the files.
"Rugal," was it?
That's enough.
They seem hardworking,
so why are you throwing them away?
What can you do with high-maintenance dogs
without leashes?
I need to take measures.
It sounds like
you want me to hear it.
You interfered during the news,
messed with the Commissioner-General,
and even abducted people
in the middle of the street!
If you keep this up, I won't be able
to cover for you any longer!
Is that so? Then how about this?
How about a gas massacre
or a carnage brought on
by mechanized humans?
I don't want to lose two of my dogs
that I raised so well in a single day.
Then buy everything.
Prepare enough cash.
I'll think about it.
Your thoughts are not needed anymore.
Hey, there.
What's wrong?
Are you okay? Where does it hurt?
You'll be okay.
Are you okay?
You were cowards
and used pre-recorded footage.
But we're going to do it live.
Do you see what you've done?
Do you regret hijacking the bus?
You asshole...
Do you feel sorry for gassing them?
Listen carefully.
We've already located your headquarters,
where you go,
your identities, and more.
We know what time you get up,
what you have for lunch,
and whom you meet in the evening.
BRED ANIMALS
RUGAL'S PERSONAL INFORMATION
HAN TAE-WOONG
KANG GI-BEOM
RUGAL'S PERSONAL INFORMATION
SONG MI-NA
LEE GWANG-CHEOL
Hey, human garbage.
Get ready to get whipped.
It's time to receive your punishment.
Subtitle translation by Hye-lim Park
I'm an innocent citizen trying to get
some protection of the police.
I told you to stop the nonsense.
Why is everyone you are looking for
around me?
I only heard things about Yeo-jin's death.
What happened that day...
And what I am missing...
There was someone else before we went in.
Who was that?
How do you feel to face the truth?
Your wife is still alive.