ALL CHARACTERS, PLACES, ORGANIZATIONS, RELIGION AND INCIDENTS
PORTRAYED IN THIS DRAMA ARE FICTITIOUS
EPISODE 6
Those who try to do everything will fail.
You said it was simple.
Hey, Hwang Deuk-gu.
Don't be an asshole.
You were going to tell me the address to those people.
It's 17, Chungsan-ro 24 beon-gil.
How can I believe you?
Don't believe me, then.
I don't know what happened to you,
but I'm busy right now. Don't expect me to go easy on you.
Please spare us! Please!
-Please. -We won't do it again.
We didn't know who the money belonged to.
-I swear. -It's your fault! You stole it.
-When did I do that, you asshole? -You stole it.
I told you we shouldn't touch it!
-It was all his doing. -Why is that my fault?
-It's not my fault! -Hey, what do you think?
-Aren't I pretty good? -You're the best driver.
My gosh, you and your flattery.
-Please spare us. Please. -Please spare us.
Please spare us.
My dad will meet all your demands. Please let me call him.
We really didn't know who the money belonged to.
Fine. You ought to know the truth.
You know what? My boss hates delivery mess-ups.
If you
somehow
make it out here alive,
tell him this.
"Dad,
we won't touch Chairman Hyeon's money.
Don't think about stealing his money, Dad."
Got that?
-Spare us! -Spare us!
-We'll pay it back. -Spare us.
-Spare us. -Please spare us.
-No! Please! -No.
-Nice vocalization. -Spare us. We really didn't know.
-Spare us. -Spare us. Please spare us this once.
-An emotional performance. -We swear.
-We really had no idea. -Please spare us.
Damn it.
Wait. Sir.
We will tell you everything we know. Everything.
He can figure out a difficult passcode without a problem.
I guess his eyes are indeed unusual.
What a waste. I will have to discard this place.
It's been a while since I had a place I actually liked.
Kang Gi-beom might show up there. Make them look presentable.
What?
Did they tell you that? Are you sure?
I don't think they are in any position to lie to us now.
Yes, sir.
But sir,
what if this messes up our initial plan?
Do you have the capacity to understand my plan?
Just do your job right.
Damn it!
That turncoat, Chairman Hyeon.
He never learned to compliment others.
Let's go.
Damn it.
Hey, be careful. Watch where you're going.
Goodness.
If two or more people stand on it together, they'll be done for.
Let's go.
Hold on.
Let's clarify why we're fighting each other.
Did you switch your side? To Hwang Deuk-gu's?
Hwang Deuk-gu.
I knew it. He's the problem.
Let's meet again when you're yourself.
What just happened?
DISPATCH AGENTS TO 17, CHUNGSAN-RO 24 BEON-GIL1
Sir.
Dispatch agents to 17, Chungsan-ro 24 beon-gil.
-Two abducted victims. -Are you sure it's from Gi-beom?
It matches the unique signal of his eyes.
There might be bugs here, so I'm using this channel.
Hwang Deuk-gu got away again.
But it's not over yet. Keep watching.
It got cut off again.
I failed to reconnect.
By the way, he doesn't seem to know we go disconnected from him.
Right.
Send Mi-na and Gwang-cheol to the address now.
Yes, sir.
You seem so carefree.
Choi Yong and Bong Man-cheol.
One of them got shot. And the other one got a hole in his head.
They might as well be dead.
But they are not dead, are they?
Seeing how you're asking me that,
you haven't grasped the gravity of the situation.
Let's talk face to face. Do you want to come over here now?
Do you think I'm crazy?
Why would I go when Deuk-gu is there? I won't put myself in danger.
I'm the only one left.
Before he eliminates me,
I'll make my move first.
We should figure out why he's doing this.
-If you're rash-- -Instead of agreeing with me,
you're talking back to me.
Does it mean you don't trust me?
I can see that you're anxious even after you gave me this seat.
Doesn't that mean you don't trust me?
I'll talk to you later.
That insolent girl.
CASE BY CASE
Hey, man. I'm sorry to do this, but this is the only way.
I'm sorry.
CLIENT
I like making money, but calling me at this hour is a bit unreasonable.
-I need you to come now. -I would like to,
but I'm kind of in the middle of something.
Are you telling me you can't come?
No, I'm not saying no.
I am dying to find out what you need me to do.
And I think I'm at the perfect place to discuss our nature of business.
They are simultaneously being assholes.
They're meticulous and diligent.
When we take care of one problem, there pops another.
That's why we must follow our instincts.
If we keep evaluating the situation, we'll achieve nothing.
Can't they make a few clones of us?
-Dispatch them in every region-- -Just step on it.
By the way, Chief Choi was saying that his artificial eyes have a problem, right?
He said it was a matter of one's perspective.
He meant that we should help him, so he doesn't get off track.
You make them sound like they are alive.
-How are his eyes any different? -Didn't I tell you to step on it?
I will comply with Mi-na One's order.
I am inclined to get to the bottom of my curiosity.
You're making a mistake.
I willingly provided safety to store your money.
But there was some money I didn't know about.
Your job is to keep it safe. How dare you open it up to see the inside?
-Are you screwing our deal? -Why is Chairwoman Choi's money
mixed with your political slush fund?
Just make the delivery.
Instead of backing the late chairman,
are you planning to support the chairwoman to run for office?
I am the chairwoman of Argos now.
I don't want a deal with a third party like Hwang Deuk-gu.
I showed you where my confidence lies.
Please give me the chance to join hands with you, sir.
Why? Are you disappointed? Because I didn't choose you?
You crazy jerk.
Don't think about interfering with the matters of Argos behind my back.
You're making a mistake.
You know, the thing is I'm way too old to think about others.
Same here.
Oh, my. My valuable client is here.
I'm sorry, but could you press that button over there?
If it weren't for your help, I would have been here all night.
-Do you have a death wish? -What?
This may be your last excuse alive.
Choose your words carefully.
Why did you ask me to come out here?
Hwang Deuk-gu.
-Keep talking. -I can't give away my trade secret.
The important thing is that this is his hideout.
And I was almost killed by that man over there.
Seol Min-jun.
Didn't I hit the bullseye for you?
I'm worth the money, you know.
Not yet.
Explain to me how you ended up here.
I didn't know I owed you explanations.
You were the one who said explanations would make things dull.
So what?
Did you hire me
to protect you from Hwang Deuk-gu?
Are you good at killing people?
It depends on who it is.
I like that answer.
Do you get hurt that easily?
I don't want to be concerned about your well-being.
I see. This?
I only got a minor injury.
But other people would have been dead.
Despite the fact that I'm the chairwoman of my organization,
most of the people in Argos fear Hwang Deuk-gu.
I must let them know,
to survive, they must cling onto me
and side with me.
You need an incident that will breathe fear into them?
I'll handle Hwang Deuk-gu after that.
Then, it's very important that you and I work well together.
It sounds like we're on the same page.
As for the damage,
the house owner and I will take care of it.
You can go. When I call you, answer it right away.
Will do.
By the way,
he's totally out of it.
Are you all right?
Are you okay?
Wake up.
Take good care of him. I'm leaving.
Guess where I am now.
A good place, I presume.
I'm at your place.
Where?
-What's wrong? -Electrical currents.
They are electric.
Mi-na's direct number.
MI-NA'S DIRECT NUMBER
-Mi-na. -Yes, Gi-beom.
I don't have time. Where are you?
We're at the location you told the chief.
Are the victims all right?
Yes, for now.
But they are locked in a cage where electrical currents run.
If you touch it, you'll get hurt.
As a matter of fact, we're trying to figure this out with Gwang-cheol's gloves.
It's not going well.
Tell him to go to the other side and hold it for five seconds.
He'll still be in danger.
That's the only way we have. Just do what I say.
Okay. Hold on.
-Gwang-cheol. -Yes.
Go to the other side and grab the cage.
Like this?
-What's next? -The timing is the key.
The moment he grabs the cage, you must break down the cage door.
-Okay. -I'm almost there. I'll be there soon.
Okay.
Let's do this.
One, two,
three.
Mi-na!
Jeez.
Let's get out of here.
Hold on, Gwang-cheol.
There might be other traps in this case. Let's wait for Gi-beom.
Mi-na, don't you remember the closed factory from before?
If we hesitate, all of us will be dead.
Let's save him first.
Gwang-cheol, you have a point. But...
What is this?
You did well. You managed to save someone.
-If you didn't stop me there-- -Hey, Gwang-cheol.
The second trap was the cage collapsing.
It didn't matter if we knew it or not. We should've gotten everyone out.
Don't you think you were rash?
If you didn't rush it, no one would have been dead. Got that?
How could you be damn calm all the time?
How much more must we think when people are dying?
For you, saving at least one is important,
but to me, not losing even one person is important.
-I won't lose anyone. -Both of you, cut it out.
Is this something we should fight about?
Are you fools?
This is what those bastards want. Feeling guilty after saving a man,
blaming each other, and feeling worthless.
Why can't you break out of that cycle?
He wasn't going to let anyone live, to begin with.
The victims or us, who went there to save them.
So he set up a trap even to the end.
More importantly, he doesn't know about Rugal.
He was toying with me this whole time.
The number you have called is not available.
Why did the prosecution take the case?
We transferred the survivor to the hospital right away.
But we have a problem.
They are raiding the place to take over the entire case.
Send me the background information
of the victims and what you have gathered so far.
Check how the investigation is progressing.
Okay. Thanks.
Well done. I was just debriefed.
Get some rest today. We'll talk tomorrow.
Rest up, you two. That'd be better.
Tae-woong is okay, right?
It was a difficult surgery.
I would have given up midway through it if Tae-woong couldn't handle it.
All of us would have been dead if it weren't for him.
He was so determined.
How could he endure it?
He's acting standoffish because of the agreement he signed.
-What agreement? -Given his background,
he had to sign an agreement to promise his loyalty.
I've never seen such a short and clear agreement.
But I bet Tae-woong is working his ass off to follow through on that.
Enter eternal paradise
Tae-woong, it's pretty chilly today.
Make sure you bundle up.
Taking my advice won't do you any harm.
Han Tae-woong!
-I told you to be good. -Hey!
-I can't believe you stole it. -Hey!
What? You do it too.
Just for a little while because I have no choice.
I'll pay them back later on.
That hurts!
-Okay, fine! -What will you do?
Gosh, it hurts.
You can eat this too.
-Really? -Yes.
Is it good?
Eat slowly, or you'll get sick.
Tae-woong, I came to pick you up.
I said I didn't want to see anyone.
I'll be back after the 49th day memorial service.
I'm sorry. The higher-ups keep asking for you.
Leave. Don't make me repeat myself.
These people here...
-Did you do this? -What if I did?
They had nothing to do with it.
Why did you kill them?
Since when did you care about such things?
I said I'd return after the 49th day memorial service.
Sure, your sister tipped off the police. But did she really do it alone?
The police
used my sister
and ditched her.
As for all the damage,
I will
make up for it.
Now, I'm going to kill you
because you ignored
my warning.
Did you think I came empty-handed to catch a monster like you?
This is the end of
Han Tae-woong, the so-called hotshot.
You got that?
Tae-woong!
Tae-woong, let's go home!
It's okay. You don't need to get up.
Did you have a nightmare?
I heard they had to cut out some parts that were totally fine
to connect your wounded arm.
I should and will endure this.
Even if I end up getting all my limbs exchanged,
I will not break my vow.
It's not an exaggeration to say that Rugal was founded upon that promise.
I needed a lot of time to believe that promise.
Yes, of course.
We were enemies
who were after each other.
But things have changed.
Now, living as a member of Rugal,
as an undercover cop,
and as well as working
with the members
makes me happy.
I want to get used to
a life like this.
"But things have changed."
And he wants to get used to this?
I really want to know what that "promise" is about.
You should've just waited there quietly.
Where on earth have you been?
You said you'd do something fun with Seol Min-jun.
Was that it?
Let me first hear what you saw
and how you found it.
Even if you're curious, just suck it up
because I won't tell you.
You couldn't have done it on your own. To think that there was someone else...
I just can't picture it.
If you needed money, you should've just told me.
What is this about now?
Buying properties under someone else's name and collecting artworks
to avoid paying taxes, all with Chairman Ko's money.
I knew you were a douchebag,
but you're a thief on top of that.
-Are you done? -Since we're in the same boat,
I'll say one more thing.
A long tail is bound to be seen, and it'll lead to your downfall.
So...
you'd better behave yourself.
I guess you feel threatened by Madame Jang.
What?
If we're actually in the same boat,
you should be encouraging me.
The less competition there is, the better.
Do you still need someone to watch your back?
-Watch your mouth. -You'd better watch out.
Words are not my weapon.
What did you do to Seol Min-jun?
What will you do with him?
Just leave him be.
A dog knows when to crawl,
and he will find his master.
Why didn't you kill him?
By any chance, is it because
you feel guilty about what you did to Chairman Ko?
Choi Ye-won, you're so funny.
"Guilty"?
Me?
You're the one who killed him.
At the reservoir. Don't you remember?
One, two...
Bang!
Choi Ye-won killed Ko Yong-deok?
Do you know why that place became a popular fishing spot?
It's because there's a ton of fish feed at the bottom.
We should go there sometime.
Who knows?
Thanks to Ko Yong-deok's rotten corpse,
you might be able to catch a gigantic fish.
Let go.
I said, let go!
How dare you...
A fight between two people who used to be friends. What should I do?
Shall I step out for a moment?
But if I'm not here,
it'll be a little dangerous.
Good. Keep bickering and fighting with each other.
We can't be the only ones that suffer.
A reservoir...
SNACKS, FISHING GEAR AND SUPPLIES
You're early, sir.
I told you to get some rest.
I need to keep busy when I have a lot on my mind.
Things will get even worse.
Regardless of the reason, a civilian died.
I found Seol Min-jun, sir.
But he's no longer the Seol Min-jun you used to know.
Is he totally on their side now?
Not sure yet. I haven't had a chance to find out what happened.
By the way, how did you find Hwang Deuk-gu's hideout?
Based on Min-jun's report from your pile of confidential documents.
-I knew it. -Pardon?
No one can access my confidential documents.
What do you mean, sir?
If you didn't know,
that means it wasn't intentional, so I'm relieved.
You didn't know you could access them because of your artificial eyes?
Not really.
When I was searching for information in the past,
there were times when I was denied access to some information.
But with this, it was so easy.
So I just thought I was allowed to access your confidential documents.
I'm not trying to blame you.
-Maybe it's an unfounded concern. -What do you mean by that?
That question. Are you the one who's asking it?
Or did the artificial eyes order you to do it?
Of course, I...
That's my concern.
The AI technology in those eyes
can read your brainwaves and even predict your thoughts.
At first, you doubt its judgment.
But as you begin to trust it,
you start to rely on it for all decisions.
Did you give me the artificial eyes?
Or was I given to them?
It depends on how you handle them.
Don't let them take over.
Okay.
I feel like I've known you for about ten years,
but we really don't know much about each other. Right?
Let's begin.
Access denied.
Access approved.
Why do I even have you if you can't even figure this out?
Just figure it out.
CRIMINAL RECORD COMMITTED CRIMES
TO MAKE ENDS MEET JOINED ARGOS AT THE AGE OF 9
What is he wearing? That looks ridiculous.
Open "Criminal Record."
What?
That can't be.
What about someone with the same name?
HAN TAE-WOONG DATA MISMATCH
So he was never caught, not even once?
FAMILY
PARENTS: DECEASED SISTER: HAN TAE-YEON
"Han Tae-yeon."
Hold on.
You decided to report the crime to us,
so please muster up a little more courage.
Please tell me if there is anything you know.
Please catch my brother, Han Tae-woong.
I don't care whether it's a holding cell or prison.
Arrest him at all costs and lock him up.
Otherwise,
both he and I will get killed.
I assure you that won't happen.
Trust me.
They said they'd kidnap me.
So, please...
I remember her.
She put her trust in me and told me everything.
-Take him. -Yes, sir.
TRUSTWORTHY, RELIABLE POLICE FORCE
We received the tip from Han Tae-yeon.
Don't even think about playing dumb.
That Han Tae-woong is the team leader?
What? Got a problem with it?
Get me locked up again if you think you can do it.
When did you wake up?
Well, are you in a lot of pain?
I'm sure you can't access the members' personal information.
Well...
I didn't see everything. I just got a sneak peek.
I assumed you'd have criminal records
because you were one of Argos' foot soldiers.
I didn't want to get caught.
But you got unlucky and got you.
No, I got caught because I was lucky.
Thanks to that, everything changed.
Still,
you're probably uncomfortable with us being on the same team.
Not at all.
Every day, I'm grateful to be
the team's leader.
If you want to get used to this life,
you should focus on the present rather than your past.
That conversation earlier...
Were you eavesdropping on me?
We can't afford to be chatting around like this now.
You have to recover soon so that we can catch those jerks.
Yes, I should.
Back then, I didn't know my enemy well,
and I could neither see nor prevent
another tragedy that was awaiting me.
All of us have stories to tell, and we somehow ended up on the same team.
At first, I thought it was just a coincidence.
-Here I come. -Okay.
But I was wrong.
Wanting revenge wasn't the only common denominator.
We were all connected in our hurtful stories.
-Tae-woong. -Tae-woong.
Keep going.
Do it again.
-You start. -Here I come.
It used to be known as Argos' place of execution.
I'm aware.
Assistant Inspector Mun and Officer Kim died there.
We found out about the place thanks to Tae-woong.
And that's how we were able to save Mi-na.
It looks like it became a fishing spot
after it got exposed.
The execution ritual is gone too.
By the way, did the car accident that killed Ko Yong-deok
take place somewhere around the reservoir?
Yes, it's 30 minutes away by car.
-What are you doing? -Hey.
-There's an interesting piece of intel. -What is it?
I have evidence that Choi Ye-won and Hwang Deuk-gu
killed Ko Yong-deok together.
How did you find out?
I planted a bug.
Did that come out of your one-on-one with Choi Ye-won?
Since she's the leader now,
she says many things that can be very useful to us.
So?
What's next?
I think the best way to weaken them
would be using the distrust among them.
The same goes for Hwang Deuk-gu, who thinks he's the boss.
Gi-beom.
Do you think driving a wedge between them is enough to destroy Argos?
Let's not worry about weakening them first.
Let's just do what we do and whack them.
No, we need a strategy.
We need to soften them up and destroy them inside and out.
Only then can we say our mission succeeded.
We all had to pay the price to join Rugal.
As you know, it was quite cruel.
Just whacking them
wouldn't be a true revenge.
Isn't destroying them to the root the real revenge?
Everyone here wants to destroy them
as much as you do.
Go find out.
Trust those eyes' intelligence capabilities
and your judgment.
-Give it a shot. -Sir.
Sir, you were the one who was concerned about the dangers
Gi-beom's eyes could pose.
Let's test them
to see how dangerous they could be.
He's saying he's confident.
Try it.
I'm giving you a chance, so you'll have to deliver results.
Yes, sir.
Good luck.
You got this chance,
so do a wicked job.
All right.
Are you asleep?
-Jeez. -I was just teasing you.
I was doing some thinking.
About what?
I was thinking, "We can buy fish at grocery stores.
Why bother doing all this just catch fish?"
Is this your first time?
I actually have years of experience.
I loved to go fishing,
but I was never able to as a cop.
It would've been nice if it were for fun,
but I came here to get an earful.
-To be scolded? -Yes.
I was a bit of a troublemaker as a boy, you see.
It's why my father would often take me fishing.
I couldn't focus and was all over the place,
so it was his way of calming me down.
But I was too young to know that.
I thought he was trying to get rid of me instead,
so I obeyed him from there on out.
Kids are meant to cause trouble though.
There was no need to say it in such a serious manner.
Hold on. Is this lake appropriate for scuba-diving?
Of course not. You can barely see an inch ahead.
-I'm going to check it out. -What?
But...
Wait for me!
SNACKS, FISHING SUPPLIES
Hello?
It doesn't seem occupied.
Is anybody here?
What's this?
It seems like an illegally erected structure.
Are you going to enter?
Well, we might get a lead.
Step aside.
You can unlock this door?
And here I thought you had no talents.
Head inside.
What is all this?
Shit.
It seems like the owner is out making a deal.
The valuables don't seem like they belong to one person though.
How do you think he collected them all?
From dead bodies.
What?
Were the bodies dumped underwater?
Hold on. What are these?
How frugal of him.
He's breathing in liquid nicotine to save money on cigarettes.
Unbelievable.
KO YONG-DEOK, FORMER CHAIRMAN OF ARGOS
What is it?
What the...
So you're saying
that kind of technology can't exist?
More accurately,
cameras like that can be made,
but to make one
at the size of a ping pong ball and have it replace an eye is impossible.
I've tried multiple times but--
Then how do you explain what I saw?
It could've been a coincidence
or maybe you just saw wrong.
You still won't admit your incompetency.
I only speak the truth.
Look here, doctor.
Did you work alone
when trying to transplant an artificial eye into a human?
There was someone else on my team,
but could he have...
Finally, you have a job to do.
By the way, doctor,
he seems too weak for my taste.
Stop yapping about field experience
and do something.
Yes, sir.
What do you think the chief trusts more?
Gi-beom or his eyes?
Aren't they the same thing?
Focus.
It does seem that way to me too,
but then he sometimes treats Gi-beom like a disowned son.
One decent lead
and I'll go after them with full force.
-Like this? -That hurts!
Gwang-cheol,
training sessions aren't a joke.
Don't think that real fights only happen in the field.
It's why I always do my best
and think I'm out on the field
when sparring with Tae-woong.
So Gwang-cheol,
stop fooling around and try your best too.
I've never fooled around.
Bring it on.
Old man.
Why? Does it belong to Ko Yong-deok?
I think so.
It's gone dead.
Can you bring it back to life?
Let me see.
Are you done?
It might die at any second,
so use your time wisely, okay?
Would a dead man's phone still be in service?
If his family didn't cancel it, then yes.
HWANG DEUK-GU
Please don't.
Don't kill us.
Please.
Are they our voices?
Yes, sir.
None of them have records
and there's more where they came from.
Blame
everything
on
Chairman Hyeon.
That's all you have to do.
If you get caught in any way,
say you were following Chairman Hyeon's orders.
Don't care about whether it's true or not,
or why you're saying his name.
Just make sure Chairman Hyeon gets word of it.
Constantly, continuously,
and repeatedly.
Sir, could this actually pressure him though?
Chairman Hyeon's power is driven by his network.
We just have to isolate him.
How?
By making others avoid him like the plague.
Have them each wear these.
A visual impact is one
that sure leaves a mark.
CHAIRMAN KO YONG-DEOK
MEET ME BY THE RESERVOIR
What the fuck?
TO THE EXECUTION SITE
Hwang Deuk-gu.
-Was it you? -No.
Us.
Say hello
to your former boss
and now my colleague who will kill you.
Anyway, we don't have much time to enjoy this,
so let's get this over with.
Sure, let's party.
Just so you know, Many of your friends are down there.
Yong-deok,
is that really you?
He looks awful, doesn't he?
His death must've come as a shock
because his mind and body are both a wreck.
Even I regretted my actions slightly.
Instead of killing you,
I should've kept you alive and made you see me
slowly stealing your money, woman,
and even your organization.
That's what I should've done.
Maybe I should start believing in God
considering how he answered my prayer.
Mr. Ko,
did you hear that fucker talk?
I guess we should make our move too.
What are you planning to do with a corpse?
Get ready,
and shoot.
What the fuck is this?
A gift.
We prepared what you might like.
Will this even work?
Yes, the pressurized air will do the trick.
As if you could be trusted.
And...
And this.
Would that kill a person?
It's deadly.
Revenge is sweeter when they get a taste of their own medicine.
You think
you can kill me?
Yes.
However,
you don't have the right to die peacefully.
I'm glad you like it.
I knew you were a fun one.
I'm glad I kept you alive.
This sure was a surprise.
Well, I didn't expect that.
So what now?
Kang Gi-beom, where are you?
Where did you hide?
Get back here!
Where the fuck did you go?
I will destroy you from the inside.
Soon I will throw a party with all the middle bosses.
-Hwang Deuk-gu will be there, too. -We have to move up the plan.
We might need Ko Yong-deok.
I'm going to follow them after luring them and bring him back.
I'm not after you. I'm after the person who is crazy about blood.
Am I not the target?
Do you think he will live a decent life if he leaves this place?
It's a lot more like hell outside.
Subtitle translation by Liya Choi