RUGAL
ALL CHARACTERS, PLACES,
ORGANIZATIONS, RELIGION AND INCIDENTS
PORTRAYED IN THIS DRAMA ARE FICTITIOUS
-Hurry!
-Quick!
I WAS KILLED BY
THE SICK MURDERER KANG GI-BEOM
-Gwang-cheol, Mi-na.
-My goodness.
EPISODE 9
We'll lie low for the time being.
And we'll move separately.
-Got it.
-Gi-beom, get some rest.
Okay.
Okay, I caught you.
-What's going on?
-67H 2661.
They're shoving a body bag into this van.
We have to catch these punks.
Maybe they'll hang it somewhere else.
-What's the location?
-2661...
I'll track them and let you know.
Let's go.
We just got here and have to go back out.
Wait, hold on.
There are a bunch of them.
According to the movements...
One, two. No, there are three.
It looks like something's going on
at the park too.
We'll split up and track them down.
Once you find it, move on to the next.
And just return when we're done, right?
Mi-na, you should stay.
Why?
Gi-beom must be confused.
Stay and look after him.
Okay.
I WAS KILLED BY
THE SICK MURDERER KANG GI-BEOM
Enough.
How many times do I have to see it?
All the data from the scenes
of important cases must be
played repeatedly and saved.
Fine. Do whatever you want.
Data saved.
All of us are still shaken up
by the recent attack at the park,
and another gruesome incident
took place this morning.
A sign with the name of the perpetrator
was found at the scene,
which is very unusual.
However, the person is deceased,
so the police investigation
is back to square one.
Mr. Kang died last November
while trying to escape the prison
after being sentenced to death
for killing his wife.
The police think that this was
a deliberate act
to take advantage of the chaos
to weaken governmental authority
and plan to get to the bottom of it
immediately.
DEAD BODY, COP
"Kang Gi-beom"?
DEAD BODY, COP KANG GI-BEOM
THIS PAGE CANNOT BE ACCESSED
He's dead?
DELETING NETWORK DATA
Hold on. I keep erasing stuff,
but it's never-ending.
Shall we just message them
and ask them to delete these?
Do you think they'll do it?
Just erase them and delete the accounts.
Are people not interested in Argos
anymore?
Everyone is talking about Gi-beom.
It'll only get worse because of the news.
How long will it take
to delete everything?
Let's focus.
Yes, ma'am. Focus.
Cleared.
No.
It's not true.
Why are you asking to speak
to a dead person?
Yes, we will find out who did this.
Detective Yang. This person saw a man
who looks like Kang Gi-beom.
Just say okay and hang up!
All right.
Take it easy.
A man died, and we have to catch a ghost?
Does it make sense to you?
What a crazy conspiracy theory.
We're surrounded by reporters right now.
Reporters? Why are they here?
You and Kang Gi-beom were friends.
Be careful.
Damn it!
This is the Violent Crimes Unit.
HWANG DEUK-GU
Oh, my goodness.
Mr. Vice Chairman, it's nice to hear
your voice first thing in the morning.
By the way, is it really okay
to cause big trouble like this?
What are you talking about?
We haven't even begun yet.
I'll take responsibility for everything.
Just enjoy the ride and rake in money.
If I could actually do that,
I'd be very grateful.
Just make sure you get us
the things we need.
We have plenty of dead bodies,
so don't you worry.
By the way, you acted as if
you'd never even talk to me again.
Why did you change your mind?
Work is work.
We should put personal feelings aside.
I'll remember that.
All right.
I hope all goes well. Talk later.
Nothing's going his way,
so he's desperate.
All right. Keep on sinking, Hwang Deuk-gu.
Hwang Deuk-gu didn't send him, though.
Will this be okay?
Have you seen a dead man talk?
Beat him up to a pulp and hang him.
Jeez, you moron.
You should've paid back the money on time.
It's not like we want to do this.
The economy is bad, so I'm struggling too.
If my wife and kids find out,
they'll be shocked.
Please make sure
they can never find my corpse.
If we deduct the labor costs,
we won't break even
with what we can make off your body.
Please spare my family.
-Right?
-Yes.
-It'd be too cruel to kill all of you.
This isn't the Peach Garden Oath.
Don't worry too much.
We should spare the lives of those
who will pay us back.
Thank you. Thank you so much.
All right, no problem.
Okay, let's see.
"Kang Gi-beom is a murderer."
"Kang Gi-beom is alive."
Oh, I like this one.
"Kang Gi-beom is hiding amongst us."
What do you think?
By the way,
how did Kang Gi-beom get involved in this?
I have no idea.
I have no interest in learning about those
who have anything to do with Deuk-gu.
We should just do what we were told to do
and get paid for the job, okay?
Hang it around his neck and take him.
Okay.
What? What's going on?
What the hell?
Hey!
Who the hell are you? Identify yourself!
Usually, I just beat up bastards like you
without killing them and hand them over.
Who the fuck are you?
But today is an exception.
Fuck!
Hey, come here.
Don't come near me.
Stay away. You'd better stay put.
If you don't, I'll stab this guy! Okay?
POLICE LINE, DO NOT CROSS
What if we get caught?
Let's just leave, okay?
Hey, can't you hear
the subscriber count going up?
If I upload this,
the subscriber count will skyrocket.
Some of the hanged bodies were scorched.
I think this is where everything began.
-Hey, let's go in.
-What?
Gosh.
Hey, stand there and record a video of me.
So that man, Kang Gi-beom, was here?
Hey, how could he have been here
when he's dead?
Are you ready?
Oh, my.
That's so dangerous.
A COP ASSAULTS THE CHAIRMAN OF ARGOS
How can I
kill people who don't die
even if I kill them?
I'll just make them want to die.
Those who think they're just
can't bear getting their hands dirty.
That's why you're still alive.
You don't need to be ashamed.
It's okay to get your hands
a little dirty. Your survival comes first.
Min-jun.
Answer me, Seol Min-jun.
Yes, sir.
I like that you don't think.
You just do what you're told to do.
You said
I wouldn't be spared otherwise.
Just keep this up,
and you won't get whacked.
But from time to time,
I miss the old you.
You had a knack for blindsiding people.
About an ex-cop being pegged
as the perpetrator...
We made sure it'll be seen as a rumor.
People don't want to talk about it openly,
but most of them
believe that Argos was behind
the recent incidents.
If we manage to use the media wisely,
people will blame Argos
-instead of the police--
-All of that sounds nice,
but it's not realistic.
I didn't say it'd be easy.
It's not about that.
PARK ATTACK VICTIMS
This contains the park attack victims'
DNA test results.
They're all ordinary people.
What's crazier is that they're the victims
of missing-person
and abduction cases,
which the police failed to solve.
So the assailants were
ordinary people who were abducted?
Do you know how upset I am right now?
Kang Gi-beom or whatever his name is...
I wish he were alive.
I wish he were the real killer
so that I could put him behind bars.
I'll find a way to make sure
the police don't suffer any damage.
Chief Choi,
you're no exception.
You know that, right?
She's not an easy target.
Gi-beom, can you hear me?
Hey, Gwang-cheol. What's going on?
-The police--
-They've figured out
that we're Rugal and that you're alive.
It's all over the Internet now.
-What?
-Run away.
If you get caught, you'll be screwed.
Gwang-cheol.
What's going on?
MURDERER KANG GI-BEOM
CONFIRMED TO BE ALIVE, NOW ON THE RUN
Wake up, Kang Gi-beom.
Gosh.
You scared me.
-What happened?
-What's wrong?
-Did someone chase you in your dream?
-"Dream"?
How long was I out for?
About ten minutes?
What is this?
Why am I here?
You were dizzy and hallucinating,
so I was doing some checkups.
I tied you down because you kept moving.
Those eyes are sensitive,
so you can't move during a checkup.
How are the eyes?
-They seem fine.
-They're fine?
Why? Is there something wrong?
Something is wrong
with either my eyes or my brain.
What do you mean?
I only read one line,
but my memories are shaky.
It's happened before,
but this feels totally different.
Those words are dictating
how I should think,
and I feel like they're controlling
my emotions too.
I've experienced something similar.
My ex-girlfriend sent me a wedding invite
to keep me in the loop.
But that moment,
the groom's name looked like my name.
I got all emotional.
I couldn't figure out what was real
and what was fake,
so I kept staring at it.
You see,
I loved her.
A lot.
Are you kidding me? This is serious.
What I'm saying is,
memory distortions are common.
So don't worry.
But just in case...
Okay. There.
I'll reset it.
I'm going to make some coffee.
Removing the cause
of your cognitive dissonance.
What? What is the cause?
Hey, what are you doing?
What's wrong?
Thanks, Tae-woong.
Well, I suddenly got a weird feeling.
You and Gwang-cheol went after those guys.
What happened?
We caught them.
Tell me the details.
A few broken ribs
and a dislocated shoulder.
Abrasions and bruises all over.
They were handed over to the police
unconscious.
There's firm evidence, so they won't
be able to get out of it easily.
I'M THE CULPRIT
I'M THE MURDERER
Well done.
Don't tell anyone about
what happened today.
No.
I may be a rule-breaker,
but I can't sweep this under the rug.
You know nothing and I never came here.
Trouble with resetting
will incapacitate you during a blackout.
It's only until we find Dr. Oh.
I'll be careful.
Being careful won't cut it--
I don't want others to worry about me.
I'll tell you immediately
if anything is wrong,
so keep this a secret until then.
Got it?
My head...
Boss!
I have bad news.
Bong Man-cheol was arrested.
-Is that so?
-Yes.
He was going after a debtor
when he was caught at the scene.
If this gets traced back to you--
None of those I sent
were his clients though.
But the two of you--
All we do is conduct business together.
I provide him with the goods
while he makes money selling organs
or what-not.
His greed is what led to his arrest,
so how is that my problem?
I should've known that, boss.
Or are you saying
that I should clean up his ass?
I apologize, sir.
Know where your loyalty lies.
Yes, sir.
Fuck.
Ye-won,
one is supposed to find shelter
when it pours.
Why are you trying to solve this yourself?
Don't you remember what Chairman Ko said?
Even when we're at each other's throats,
we must unite to fight an outside enemy.
He isn't just a suspect.
He was caught red-handed.
There's no way out of it.
Nothing's impossible, Mi-joo.
All that matters is who our enemy is.
I get it and it's all good,
but why are you engaging
in the matter yourself
when it happened because
Hwang Deuk-gu was involved?
Because Argos is mine.
I don't want this to backfire on you,
that's all.
I'll just have to power through.
And let me say this since
we're on the subject.
Don't be outside of my circle.
Are you worrying about me
or threatening me?
Anyway, I have no intention
of taking the fall alone.
How dare you come in here.
That's not how you welcome
a guest that was invited.
And who the hell invited you?
Me.
What?
Can you give us the room?
You'd rather be with him alone
after what he did to you the last time?
Get out.
Fine.
You go ahead and keep doing this.
Shouldn't the vice-chairman
at least make a visit?
A visit?
Visit whom?
Bong Man-cheol? Me?
One makes the mess
while the other cleans up after him.
Thanks to you, I'm busy these days,
so I thought it's the least you could do.
Of course.
How can you not be busy when you're
communicating with a dead man?
He had a sob story to tell.
You've grown to be
way more considerate too.
It's why I'm the current chairman.
The job requires someone
with a generous heart.
Look at you lying through your teeth.
You're one to suck the blood out
of anyone that has anything useful.
Reassure Bong Man-cheol
so that he doesn't act out.
I'm meeting the Commissioner-General
this afternoon,
so be there as well.
It smells like Chairman Hyeon
had something to do with it.
This appointment didn't come easily,
so shut your trap until I say otherwise.
Then go alone why don't you?
This is my way of showing everyone
how far I'll willingly go
for the organization.
Why do you look upset?
You were only here for a few hours.
You have some nerve showing up here.
You think I betrayed you?
Shut up!
Shit.
Calling the cops
when we're doing business?
-You slimy coward.
-Man-cheol,
it wasn't the police or me
who put you in here.
What?
There's another force that's after us.
Here I am doing my best to catch them
even if that results in
getting stamped as a lunatic,
but the rest of you are too busy
only looking out for yourselves.
Let's be honest here.
Who else but me has come to see you?
So you're saying that it was them
who tricked us with the body
and fucked things up a few days ago?
In order to find out who they are,
we must upend things.
You can get me out of here, right?
How does tomorrow afternoon sound to you?
I'll hold you to your word.
Shit.
Bring it to my car.
One down,
one more to go.
Those in the political, financial,
and legal circles as well as the press
will lend a hand
in the rescuing of Bong Man-cheol.
Will that be possible
when it's an ironclad case?
They'll come up with
whatever reason they need.
How can they when the whole world saw it?
We can't let our guards down.
Argos finds it an embarrassment
to even have its ousted member imprisoned.
Not the oddball though.
He doesn't give a rat's ass
about the rules.
He could've used us
to get rid of Bong Man-cheol.
You think he used us?
That's not all.
He even mocked us by
dragging Gi-beom's name through the mud.
I wouldn't call it mocking.
Let's just say he made me a celebrity.
One wishes to get rid of Bong Man-cheol
while the other wants to save his ass?
Sounds like an internal turf war.
For now, we believe
Choi Ye-won is leading it.
In order to maintain her position,
she'll need Bong Man-cheol in his.
A few will try and take his position.
I agree.
Man-cheol's building
will be the battlefield.
Let's keep an eye out
for whom each of the players meet.
We'll tail them.
Sounds good.
Chief.
Wouldn't this be dangerous for Gi-beom?
His face was exposed.
When did we ever worry about such a thing?
Gi-beom, you'll be on standby.
Sure.
MOPIN CREDIT
For someone who doesn't even trust
money counting machines,
this seems too poorly guarded.
I'll forget that I saw anything,
so please step aside.
Is that so?
MOPIN CREDIT BANK
First Hwang Deuk-gu and now Choi Yong.
Keep your eyes on them
and see if they clash.
Maybe I should get
an artificial eye myself.
Then I could easily
send you photos of them.
Damn it.
Mismatch.
Two more failed retinal scans will result
-in the destruction of content.
-Is that it?
All I need are Ko Yong-deok's eyeballs?
What do you think you're doing here
without the owner's permission?
I guess one can't change his ways.
I didn't expect much from an asshole.
So you lock Bong Man-cheol up
and go after the safety deposit boxes
in his building.
It's odd how you seem
to care about Man-cheol
but you never once visited him in prison.
I thought I'd come here instead
to check up on a thief.
-What?
-You have two attempts left,
so let your eyes be scanned.
Go ahead.
If I were you, I'd manage my business
instead of chasing others around.
I hear you're in the red.
From The Red Ants to Argos,
I've served this organization
for 40 years.
I'm nothing like the thug who's only been
cleaning up trash.
Try looking in a mirror, Deuk-gu.
What you'll see is a swine
that doesn't know its place
and is wiping his shit
all over his own house.
You talk big for an old fox.
But that doesn't change the fact
that you're a geezer now.
We come into this world with nothing
and that is your life story too.
You came empty-handed,
so just sit tight for a second.
I'll make sure you leave with nothing too.
Anyway, have fun burning your eyeballs.
I'm off to see Man-cheol.
The online shopping mall notified you
of its product being in stock.
Don't pretend that
you're back to following my orders.
Mess with the files
in Yeo Jin's case again,
and I'll rip you out.
I was only following the analyzed result.
All you'll do is report.
The decision is mine to make.
Should I place an order on the product?
Yes!
Now, don't talk until I call for you.
Got it?
That's your punishment.
What the hell?
Turn yourself back on.
Will you only enable mute mode?
That's right. You happy now?
Jeez.
What a pain in the ass.
Don't touch anything.
So you knew?
You could've at least said hello.
All you do is fidget with gadgets.
Don't kill me!
-Was that fun enough?
-That's not fun.
I'm just bored out of my mind.
Wait, what are these?
SUBJECT F100H
Subject F100H. What's this?
It sounds like
one of Rugal's earlier projects.
I have no interest in out-dated technology
which is why it's been collecting dust.
Rugal's earlier project?
Will this give me an insight
into Rugal's earlier days?
You'll need Chief Choi's authorization
or access the data on his computer.
MOPIN CREDIT BANK
Choi Yong left earlier
and now Hwang Deuk-gu is on the move.
Surprisingly enough,
they're both in one piece.
Who should I tail?
Choi Yong's headed
to Yuyeon Police Station,
so tail Hwang Deuk-gu instead.
But Chief,
you sent Mi-na to shadow
the Commissioner-General.
Could it be...
He's not, right?
Not with Argos.
It's what we hope for.
Thank you.
How about this?
Sure.
This doesn't look like a disguise to me.
Where is this from?
Can I play this role next time?
You can if you want to
give me your artificial eyes.
That's one scary joke, Tae-woong.
Anyway, these seem to protect your eyes.
Yes, it's one of Bradley's inventions.
Exactly, so can't I play this role?
Just let it go.
Let it go?
You think I'm Elsa or something?
Jeez.
It was only a silly joke, you know.
What the hell?
You look beautiful.
I prefer to look cool.
This is what a disguise looks like.
No one would guess that this is Mi-na.
Seriously?
Tae-woong, did you just laugh?
No, I did no such thing.
Do you like the outfit I chose for you?
I guess I do.
I mean, it's not that bad.
Chief, why are the Commissioner-General
Choi Ye-won in the same place?
Let's not jump to conclusions,
but set up a camera just in case.
Got it.
I brought you some fruit.
How sweet of you.
My pleasure, ma'am.
Have you been waiting for long?
No.
Tae-woong, Hwang Deuk-gu is here as well.
He is?
I thought he and Ye-won
were out to get each other.
Did he recognize you?
No.
We did lock eyes,
but he didn't recognize me.
Lie low for now.
Got it.
Put your hand down.
Come on.
We're carrying out a mission here.
It needs to be perfect.
It's too heavy.
This wig is already too heavy for me.
Thanks for what you did back there.
I didn't know I'd meet him so up-close.
Do you know what shocked me?
He actually took us for a couple.
How's that possible?
Are you having fun
with your snide remarks?
You need some beating, don't you?
Mi-na, you've heard of this phrase, right?
"Fool yourself before fooling others."
We are like...
How should I put it?
An unfinished work.
What do you think we need to do
to complete this?
Shopping? Going for a drive?
If not,
how about a lovey-dovey time
over some steak?
Shall we go for a swim?
That sounds awesome.
-Over there.
-Over...
Over there?
Yes. Do you like it?
Stop joking around.
Did you just hit me?
No, no.
-Come here.
-No, no.
Let Bong Man-cheol go.
Ma'am, don't you know
the basic principles of negotiation?
You need to ask for something
that's attainable.
Can you prove
that he was at the crime scene?
Of course. A courageous civilian
caught him and handed him over to--
That's just what the police are claiming.
I can find out who that civilian was
or if they existed at all.
If I want to play dirty,
there's nothing stopping me.
What she's trying to say
is that she wants us to be
more considerate toward each other.
Let's just say
that you were carrying out
a targeted investigation.
Say that he wasn't even
at the crime scene.
Make him out to be a lunatic
who can neither give out orders
nor understand anything.
Are you telling me to make a fool
out of ourselves
just to spare some thug?
Sir.
You should mind your manners a bit more.
I'm just asking you to think
from my perspective.
I'm the Commissioner-General,
yet you want me to humiliate my own men.
I think it's a bit--
I think someone else came in.
It's a pity we don't have a camera.
Do you remember why
the former Commissioner-General resigned?
There were too many cold cases,
and the crime rate didn't go down either.
I promise to make you look competent.
-Sorry?
-I'm sure you'll
turn the page and become involved
in a new field in the future.
It's your choice.
Start anew, join us,
and live a long, prosperous life.
Or remain in the police force
where our loyalty doesn't lie in.
You sure know how to negotiate.
Why are you there?
I'm sorry, but who are you?
Let's just say
that I'm worth being in this room.
Do you want to say something?
I just have one question.
You brought up a dead police officer
and made the civilians lose trust
in the police force.
How do you feel about that?
Please don't tell me
that you believe we were behind that.
If that really happened,
I'll find out who did it
and teach them a lesson.
So you can trust me
and conclude our negotiation.
Come out.
I said come out, you geezer.
COMPRESSOR ROOM
Follow me.
Hello, sir.
Monitor the power well.
I don't want to see another blackout.
Yes, sir.
ELECTRICAL ROOM
Blue...
Why? Is something wrong?
There was a blackout. But something's odd.
This level of power cannot be reached
unless someone intended.
Chief.
I've been monitoring
power usages constantly,
and an odd place had a blackout.
-Where is that?
-One second.
Here.
It might be Dr. Oh's distress signal.
You mean he used the blackout
to send us a signal?
Shouldn't we go check it out?
Yes.
Yes, sir.
I'm on my way.
They've located Dr. Oh.
-How?
-Susan found him.
Gi-beom will meet us there,
so let's hurry.
All right.
I'll drop her home, so you may leave.
-What are you--
-Go!
I'll drive you home today.
Don't be ridiculous.
I should find out whom to punish.
I wonder who sent this message.
MEET ME BY THE RESERVOIR
Don't play jokes with me.
Aren't you curious?
Is this about Kang Gi-beom?
Open this right now.
You asked if I liked you.
If I said yes,
would you accept me?
Hey, fix that!
Hurry up!
If you don't clean up properly,
I'll kill you all.
If you don't want to lick the floor clean,
do a good job.
Sir, I don't think
we can fix this ourselves.
We should call a technician.
Hey, do you think we have money to waste?
Hurry up and fix this!
I was away for half the day,
but man, am I glad to see you.
Did you rest up well?
I guess.
But I'll work twice as hard,
so don't worry.
Are you sure Dr. Oh is in there?
I think so.
Anything else to tell us?
It's going to be a mess in there
due to the blackout.
We'll destroy them from the inside out.
-I've been waiting for this moment.
-I hope it's worth it.
I've been cleaning up all day.
Yes, that's a good expression.
Let's clean them all up.
Let's go.
Let's go this way.
They restored the power.
Gwang-cheol, turn the lights on.
Subtitle translation by Liya Choi
Why did I do that?
Did I mistake him for a test subject?
What happens if the artificial eyes
take control of me?
You will lose yourself
and live by its orders.
He risked his own life and walked into it.
Then we should play along with him.
We might be played by Hwang Deuk-gu.
Change the D-day to today.
Get started.
He will come out and reveal all the truth.
What if he refuses?
I am who Hwang Deuk-gu wants.