(All characters, organizations, places, and events are fictional.)
Yes.
Did you come to my house...
and see your dad there...
as well?
That night,
I had something to talk about with your mom.
There is a lot of stuff she needs to wrap up...
and prepare before she leaves.
Do you think I don't know anything?
How long do you think you can fool me?
Can you guys stop using me as an excuse?
You guys drive me crazy every time you do.
So just stop it already!
What should we do?
Just find Joon Young and take him home.
Sun Woo.
Do what you can to console him.
Make sure this doesn't end up hurting him even more.
That's all I want.
What's the problem?
I fixed the situation.
I don't want to discuss it. Send him to Sun Woo.
Send him to his mom.
You can't handle him!
He's Tae Oh's son.
I won't send him to that woman.
I brought him here, so he's my responsibility.
You did all you could.
That's more than enough!
I heard he's violent.
What if he hurts Jenny?
He got angry and made a mistake.
He'll be fine if we're thoughtful of him.
I can take care of him.
What's wrong with her?
What about Da Kyung? Is something wrong?
I didn't raise her to raise someone else's son!
I'm so upset, I can't stand it!
(Lee Joon Young)
Joon Young.
Lee Joon Young.
It's not complicated.
Mom's leaving.
Did you go somewhere?
Honey, I'm going to talk to Joon Young for a few minutes.
Do you remember what I said when you first moved in?
That I hoped you'll be comfortable here.
That you need to be happy for your dad to be happy.
You were hurt because of what the adults did,
and I'm responsible for half of it.
So I fixed it this time,
but if something like this happens again,
I can't just protect you unconditionally.
Don't do it again.
It'll make it hard for all of us.
Do it for yourself.
Can you promise me?
Okay.
Thanks.
From now on, get my permission before you go anywhere.
Aren't you going to answer me?
Okay.
What did you talk about?
I told him to get permission before going out.
Honey. Do you know Joon Young's friends?
Not really.
I think we should keep tabs on what he does and with whom...
and control whom he hangs out with.
Okay. I'll talk to him.
(Acetaminophen)
(Episode 14)
(Recent calls)
He wouldn't leave me alone.
But he doesn't even call today of all days.
He was useless,
but I wish he were here.
Ye Rim.
Are you very sick? Have you eaten?
What... You sound like you came because you knew.
Myung Sook told me you went to the hospital,
and that you got a bunch of painkillers.
She's such a big mouth.
You should've told me.
Must I have someone else tell me that you're sick?
I'll be sick and grow old alone for the rest of my life.
I should get used to it.
What is this?
This?
It's tiramisu.
I remembered you used to eat this whenever you were sick.
To be honest,
it didn't come to me right away.
I got confused whether it was chocolate...
or tiramisu.
Have some.
Aren't you tired of this?
No. I'm happy.
From the moment I started to wonder how I can help since you're sick...
and the entire time while I was coming here with this,
I was happy.
I was glad that there was something I could do for you.
Good morning.
- Hello. - Hello.
Is Dr. Ji in?
No, she isn't here yet.
Okay. See you.
Help!
Please help!
My child is sick.
- What's her name? - Park Hye Jin.
She was seen by Dr. Ji Sun Woo.
She has appointments this morning.
She'll have to wait a little.
She got sick after taking the drugs she prescribed.
Can't she see her first?
It's still before office hours...
Hold on.
What about Dr. Kim from Internal Medicine?
He has appointments too.
Hye Jin!
Do something! She's in pain!
- Send her to me. - Okay.
- You two, take her in. - Okay.
Come this way.
- What's going on? - She's Dr. Ji's patient.
Her stomachache suddenly got worse.
Darn it.
"Irritable bowel syndrome"?
Yes.
Gosh.
Goodness.
Dr. Ji.
I'm sorry I'm a little late.
Go see Dr. Sul right away.
A patient of yours was carried into her room.
It's Ms. Park Hye Jin who came to see you yesterday.
She says her abdominal pain suddenly got worse.
Please excuse me, sir.
This is a pain reliever. Please relax.
Since when did you feel this pain?
Around dawn. My stomach started to hurt around dawn.
There seems to be bleeding according to the ultrasound.
Let's have you take a CT scan.
- Nurse Joo. - Yes?
- Prepare for a CT scan. - Yes, ma'am.
- Nurse. - Yes?
- Can you prepare a wheelchair? - Okay.
What happened to you?
Why didn't you send her for an ultrasound?
Is it serious?
Just stay quiet and don't get involved.
I'll try to resolve it.
Hey, you said she had irritable bowel syndrome!
Your misdiagnosis put her in danger!
What are you going to do about it?
Sir, please calm down.
She's not even married.
What if she becomes infertile?
What will you do?
How will you take responsibility?
- Close the door. - Yes, ma'am.
The pain worsened because a cyst flared.
We should keep a watch on her,
but at this moment, there are no problems with her ovaries.
One can't get infertile from this.
Anyway, it's true she gave us a misdiagnosis.
Am I wrong?
I'm sorry.
It's irrational to say it's a misdiagnosis!
If this isn't a misdiagnosis, what is it?
You said a cyst popped and now she's bleeding.
It says on the chart that she was recommended to see...
an OBGYN.
Didn't your daughter say that?
No.
I haven't heard.
Go and check with her.
Gosh.
I was so startled in the middle of the night.
If she needs surgery, I won't let you get away with this.
I prescribed her some painkillers and antibiotics,
so she can go home once you've calmed down.
I'll book her in for an appointment three days from now.
If she feels any pain or gets dizzy before then,
come to the hospital right away.
My daughter better be fine.
I'll sue that doctor and the hospital.
Understand?
Don't apologize so hastily.
The moment you say that, it proves you did wrong.
Anyway, it was my mistake for not checking her ultrasound.
They won't care if you missed doing an ultrasound...
or made a misdiagnosis.
Don't take all the blame after apologizing,
and just sit still.
I'll take care of everything else.
Dr. Ji, what's with you these days?
I understand you had to take some time off for your son.
But you can't miss something so basic on her first checkup.
How is this possible?
You used to find out the causes of underlying diseases too.
You were the face of our hospital for a reason.
You were never late before, but now you're leaving early...
and making medical mistakes too.
What's going on with you?
Don't you think you have a problem?
I'm sorry.
It was due to my negligence.
I'll resign.
Come on, I'm the hospital director. Don't I have the right to say this?
Whenever I say something, you want to quit.
I don't dare open my mouth now.
I'm sorry.
All right. How long do you need?
2 days? 3 days?
Fine. A week.
Can you get yourself organized in a week?
I'm sorry.
(Letter of Resignation)
(Family Love Hospital)
(Korean Medical Association)
(Award for Respected Medical Worker)
(Family Medicine Doctor Ji Sun Woo)
(Mom, Lee Joon Young)
(Doctor Ji Sun Woo)
(Letter of Resignation)
Why didn't you talk to me directly?
Tae Oh tends to be upright,
so he hates being a nuisance even to his family.
I'll speak to my dad for you.
Gosh, will you? I'd be so thankful.
You're okay with it, right?
Of course.
You know very well your dad listens to you.
While we're on that, we should invite Councilman Cha...
and Hae Kang to our house too.
We can talk about becoming Councilman Cha's sponsor.
It'd be good to help Hae Kang...
and Joon Young make up properly.
That's a great idea.
It must be a lot of work for you to take care of...
the child of your husband and his ex-wife.
When I saw her embracing Joon Young,
I started to have second thoughts about Da Kyung.
You're really amazing.
She's too naive and nice.
She says the boy is innocent...
and made more work for herself.
If he's Tae Oh's son, he's my son too.
No parent would give up on their child...
just because they made a single mistake.
Raising a child...
is like creating a world.
You shouldn't think of him like an extra part of your husband,
or it won't be easy on you.
How much of that kid's life...
are you willing to be responsible for?
I'll give my best.
As much as I do for Jenny.
I can't cut out his future for him,
but at least...
I'm confident enough to shut the mouths...
of the people who are biased about kids under divorced parents.
Good.
It's the woman who keeps a household together.
You're a bigger person than I thought.
I didn't realize it until now.
Sorry for being so late.
- Welcome. - Hello.
Sit here.
Shall we go eat?
I heard something huge on my way over.
Dr. Ji handed in her resignation.
On top of that, I heard she might even leave Gosan.
Da Kyung, isn't this good news for you?
It's also good news for both you and your husband.
It's not exactly something we've been hoping for.
But I guess it's not bad news.
What did you do today?
I stayed home all day.
- What about your academy? - She told me to get a tutor...
instead of going outside.
I'm pretty much confined, aren't I?
Okay.
I'll talk to her.
Hey, you're home.
We talked for longer than expected. Where is Joon Young?
- He went upstairs after he ate. - I see.
It's school break right now, so why don't we go on a family trip?
The four of us can go somewhere nearby.
That sounds great.
By the way,
- about Joon Young going outside... - Oh, right.
I found a counselor for Joon Young and made a reservation.
- "A counselor"? - Yes.
She's an expert in counseling teenage kids.
She's famous for fixing problematic behaviors.
It wasn't easy to make a reservation.
Does he really need to get counseling?
He needs to get treated for kleptomania.
- We can't just leave it... - Are you calling him a thief?
I'm saying we need to be very careful about it.
Can't you...
just give him some time?
Let him breathe a little.
Why can't you just trust him and wait?
What's so wrong about getting professional help?
I tried my best to find a way so I could help Joon Young.
- Yes, I know. But... - If you know, then cooperate.
Don't tell me what you want or what you think.
Right now, we should do what's best for Joon Young.
Okay?
I'm sorry.
And thank you.
Do you want me to take Joon Young to his counseling sessions?
If Jenny grows up and causes trouble as well,
I'd do the same thing.
Things are slowly going back to where they belong.
From now on, we'll be perfect.
(A World of Married Couple)
I think this one will do.
- How was the meeting? - Well...
Can I trust you?
- Remember what we discussed? - Yes.
Your brother's leaving.
Say "Bye".
Gosh, you say goodbye so well.
Joon Young, how was your week?
Did you ever feel angry or sad?
Yes.
Can you tell me what made you felt that way?
Come in.
Hey, you're here.
- Myung Sook. - Hey.
(Ji Sun Woo)
- You're here. - What's this on your coat?
- Shall we go? - Yes, let's go.
Thank you.
I'm starting to feel better now that I'm eating something spicy.
Where do you think she went? She won't even answer my calls.
Maybe she went to get some fresh air.
Do you think she feels uneasy about having quit her job?
Why would she feel uneasy?
You told me she was already planning to leave.
But I bet he feels uneasy about it.
Who?
- Tae Oh? - Yes.
At least, that's how he looks.
Why would he feel uneasy? They're over now.
You only say that because you don't know men.
Even when a guy is with someone, he has eyes for other women.
And guys think about their exes quite often as well.
That's how guys are.
But not me.
I'm not like that at all. I was talking about Tae Oh.
Gosh, that jerk.
Did you ever get a call from your mom?
No.
Are you sure you didn't just ignore her calls?
Hello.
You wouldn't call even after I told you there were openings,
then you show up out of the blue.
I wanted some fresh air.
I left the hospital.
Are you going to Busan?
Was it finalized?
No.
I want to take a break.
Why did you come all the way here to see me?
You have a good psychiatrist close by.
It's time for my rounds. What do you want to do?
Go ahead. I'm not leaving anytime soon.
Okay. Let's finish talking later.
But don't say let's go for a drink.
- Did you really quit? - Of course.
- Go ahead. - Okay.
You must be psychic.
How did you know she'd come here?
I'm glad.
How is she?
She looks terrible, naturally.
I think she wants to clear her head.
Just come here if you're so worried.
She probably wants to be alone.
I'm in no position to intrude.
Fine. I'll call you if anything happens.
Sorry?
Me? The associate director?
There's no reason to keep it vacant any longer.
That's what the chairperson and I decided.
Don't you think you can handle it?
Tell me now. I'll take it back.
Of course, I can.
I know I can be better than anyone.
Thank you for having faith in me.
I persuaded the chairperson myself.
If by chance you cause trouble,
my neck is on the line too. Remember that.
I'll do my best to make sure that does not happen.
Also,
what will you do about Dr. Ji?
What can I do? She's the one who left.
But she's the face of our hospital.
We can't just let her go.
The chairperson is troubled too...
and says we'll never find someone as good.
Why don't we wait a few days?
The phone is turned off. Your call is being forwarded...
(Sun Woo)
Father.
What brings you here?
I was passing by, so I thought I'd drop in.
About Family Love Hospital.
I'm signing a sponsorship agreement.
Meet with Dr. Kong when you have time...
and finish it up.
Yes, sir.
I thought it would take a while,
but it was resolved quickly.
Good work.
No, no. Don't see me out. Go back to work.
Sun Woo?
She resigned a few days ago.
Then...
where is she now?
I don't know either.
Why do you ask?
Hello?
What are you doing?
Is Sun Woo...
not home?
- Why? - Do you know where she went?
You both did enough.
You harassed her enough.
You even took Joon Young.
What more do you want?
Please...
let her go.
Tae Oh.
Did you hear me?
What?
I said we're having dinner with Councilman Cha's family tomorrow.
With my parents too.
That's right. You did.
My dad usually hates sponsoring politicians,
but he's doing it for you and Joon Young,
so talk it out with Councilman Cha.
I should.
I'm going to shower.
Okay.
(23 missed calls from Lee Tae Oh)
(Power off)
Why do I ruin everything I try to excel in?
My family,
my husband, and my son. Everything.
I lost everything...
I wanted to protect.
What does it mean to you "to protect"?
Obsession is poisonous.
It's poisonous for a parent and a child too.
I already gave up wanting to keep him by my side.
I've accepted the fact that he wants to live with his dad.
What I can't stand...
is that my child hates me.
I wish I could change him around.
If I could, I think I can do anything.
It's not possible, is it?
You can't expect him to understand after hurting him.
That would be too greedy.
Whether it's hatred or resentment,
you should respect Joon Young's feelings.
Once you do that,
time will take care of it.
Did time take care of everything for you?
Pain is still painful even after time passes.
You know that too.
Life can't be sweet all the time.
You just somehow hang in there, that's all.
Then you'll find some days to be sunny.
That's how time will pass.
I'm too tired to hang on.
It'll be easier for everyone...
if I disappear.
For me, Joon Young,
and Tae Oh too.
Wasn't my apology enough?
Why do I have to make friends with him?
I'm so annoyed.
We're not asking you to force yourself to be friends.
You still have to see each other at school for another year.
It'd be better to be on good terms with him.
Please just go with the flow for today.
Da Kyung prepared today's gathering just for you.
I referred to previous agreements we've had.
We wrote a draft agreement.
(Donation Agreement)
At first, I thought your demands were out of the line.
But it looks like you had a foresight.
Dr. Ji caused a lot of problems lately.
If she was still the associate director,
it would have made things really difficult for the hospital.
What are your plans for the agreement ceremony?
- You must have an idea already. - I'm not sure.
I don't have one yet.
We're a small regional hospital,
but TO Pictures is known all around the nation.
You should pay attention to how you publish your articles.
We should make a video and have it air on a local channel.
It would hugely benefit both parties.
I'll have our PR teams work closely together.
You must be busy. I'll get going.
You should go if you're busy.
(Doctor Ji Sun Woo)
Sun Woo, where are you right now?
Are you all right?
The female customer from yesterday?
She said she'll stay for a few days and paid in advance,
but I saw her leaving at dawn.
Dawn?
- What time? - I don't know.
Maybe around 6am.
She must have gone out to see the sunrise.
Why do you ask?
Is there a problem?
No. Thank you.
The person you have reached is not available.
I'm too tired to hang on.
It'll be easier for everyone...
if I disappear.
Is Sun Woo well?
Why do I feel like your tone sounds strange?
What is it? Do you feel upset now that she's gone?
Do you know where she is right now?
I have an idea.
- Why? Do you want to know? - No.
It's fine as long as she's well.
What's between you two?
She was shocked after Joon Young's incident.
She said she was going to leave,
but she suddenly quit and disappeared.
That worries me.
I'm wondering...
if something happened to her.
I'm sure she's fine.
Dr. Ji disappeared?
I hope I'm just overly worried,
but I can't ignore what's happening since I saw some signs.
I think she might do something.
I feel anxious.
What should I do?
Please cancel the rest of my appointments for today.
- I'm sorry? - It's an emergency.
Please ask the patients for their understanding.
Tell them I'll call them personally later.
What is it, Dr. Kim?
Dr. Ma just called, and Dr. Ji...
Did something happen to Sun Woo?
Where is she right now?
Where is she?
- Tae Oh. - I said, where's Sun Woo right now?
(Dr. Ma)
She's not here.
But I don't know if that's a good thing or not.
I can't seem to feel at ease.
I'll also keep looking for her.
Dr. Ji!
Sun Woo!
Gosh, how could they leave their daughter behind like this?
What a terrible accident.
How is that little girl going to cope with this?
I can't believe this happened to her.
Don't you know the story? Her mother got shocked...
after she found out about her husband's affair.
I don't think it was an accident. I think she committed suicide.
She committed suicide just because her husband cheated on her?
I get how upset she must've been, but that's so wrong.
She probably caused the car accident so they could die together.
What an unbelievable woman.
So she just abandoned her daughter?
How could a mother leave her daughter behind like this?
Sun Woo.
Sun Woo! Wake up!
Sun Woo!
Please wake up!
Sun Woo! Are you okay?
Okay, good. You're okay.
Are you okay?
Go ahead and cry. Just cry all you want.
Cry all you want.
Tae Oh's son started receiving therapy.
I don't know if therapy will help though.
Da Kyung is trying hard.
We should hope for the best.
We should. I know.
I wondered why she was trying so hard for him,
but seeing how Sun Woo backed off on her own,
I feel like Da Kyung did the right thing.
But seeing her struggling to take care of the ex-wife's son...
makes my blood boil.
I don't know what's good...
or bad anymore.
We'll be late.
Let's go if you're ready.
- Is everything ready? - Yes, it is.
You scared me. I thought you were going to be late.
I have time, right?
I'm going to wash up.
I put out your clothes.
You can put them on.
Are you ready?
Grandma and Grandpa are good people,
so don't be too nervous.
Be polite to the adults, okay?
Joon Young.
We're really a family now.
You understand what I mean, right?
- Please enjoy. - Thank you.
Da Kyung, you must have worked so hard.
Not at all.
Joon Young. Hae Kang.
You know how they say kids fight as they grow?
That's a lie.
You need to fight and make up.
That's how you grow tall like your dads.
You're totally right.
Boys only grow closer if they've thrown a few punches.
Thank you for your wise words.
Thank you for inviting us to this precious dinner...
- and the precious food. - Thank you, sir.
Let's toast to their friendship.
- What do you think? - Sounds good.
Here's to Lee Joon Young and Cha Hae Kang's friendship.
- Cheers. - Cheers.
The wine is delicious.
Isn't it?
Speaking of wines, a new wine bar opened...
in the shopping district.
It's nice.
I have a friend, Sang Hyun,
who opened a wine bar.
I'll take you sometime.
I don't know if I got lucky with a good friend...
or with a good son,
but it's an honor to have the best sponsor in Gosan, sir.
Let's say you got lucky with both a good friend and a good son.
Since I'm sponsoring you anyway, I hope you win, Councilman Cha.
Thank you.
I'll do my best.
Is everything going well for the groundbreaking ceremony?
Of course.
The laborers are the ones who prepare for construction.
When is the next movie coming out?
You need to make another blockbuster.
I'm working on it.
That's odd. The housekeeper should be with her.
Excuse me.
Are you okay?
What did you do?
I'm sorry.
- I stepped away for a minute. - Take her.
Did you do something to Jenny?
I didn't do anything.
- She was alone, so... - Did you hit her?
I did everything for you.
You have everything now.
You should be adjusted by now!
Couldn't you behave for just one day?
What's the problem?
What did I do wrong?
- Joon Young, stop it. - I didn't do anything.
She fell while she was alone. What do you want from me?
Why are you taking it out on me?
We have guests downstairs. Stop it.
How patient must I be with you?
How much must I take?
Cry all you wanWhen did I ask you for your patience?
Honey.
Do what you can...
to console him.
Make sure this doesn't end up...
hurting him even more.
That's all...
I want.
You jerk.
Get your act together.
How many people must suffer because of you?
How much harder must it get for us?
What happened?
Please finish...
your dinner.
Tae Oh.
Mom.
(Mom)
Joon Young.
It's Mom.
Are you listening?
Did something happen?
Mom.
I'm really sorry,
but can you come and pick me up?
Dr. Ji.
What did I tell you?
I told you not to take in someone else's child.
Why are you wasting your energy?
Da Kyung.
What's making you...
so anxious?
Madam.
Gosh.
Is she out of her mind? How dare she come here?
Gosh. Didn't she leave Gosan?
No. Don't deal with her. Just make her leave.
(Call)
What is it?
I came to get Joon Young.
Why all of a sudden?
I didn't hear anything from Tae Oh.
Joon Young, hurry up and come out.
Joon Young.
Stop right there, Lee Joon Young!
Go back to your room right now.
I said, go back to your room!
Da Kyung, stop it.
- Move. - Just let him go!
Dad, stop him from leaving.
I have to make that crazy woman go away.
- Just let him go! - Let go of me!
Do you know how hard I tried?
I put in so much effort.
- You know it, don't you? - I do.
I'm almost there.
I can't let that woman ruin it.
Yeo Da Kyung!
I'm sorry...
I came so late.
Let's hurry and leave, Mom.
Okay, let's go.
I said, stop right there!
Wait in the car.
What's the problem?
It'll be easier for you if Joon Young stays with me.
Does Tae Oh know about this?
We already agreed that I'd take Joon Young back...
whenever he wanted.
Your obsession...
is ruining Joon Young. Don't you know that?
How much more will you confuse him?
He was stabilizing.
Instead of being with his unstable and obsessive mom,
it's better for him to grow up in a normal family.
You should think rationally.
Why are you obsessed with Joon Young?
Because this is what's best for him.
You two keep on fighting with Joon Young in the middle.
It even tires me out.
It must be tougher on Joon Young.
Also,
you're not normal.
Are you sure you can raise him properly?
I was the one who stopped the School Violence Committee.
Am I wrong?
Let's be honest.
You're not doing this for Joon Young.
It's your marriage and family you want to protect.
You're nervous because...
you can see Tae Oh's temptation.
I understand how much you wanted to protect it.
I was the same.
But do you know this?
Such earnest desperation...
is meaningless.
A marriage and a couple...
can get shook up,
flipped around, or break apart over nothing.
As for me...
My marriage is different.
You should know it better than I do...
since you did it too.
What are you talking about?
Tae Oh and I...
slept together.
(A World of Married Couple)
Can we just leave...
to a place where no one knows us?
Tae Oh will have a hard time getting over Sun Woo.
What makes you say that?
Think carefully.
This might be your last chance...
to escape from it all.
You said we should keep it a secret!
Do you still have feelings for me?
Think of all the things you've done before trying to blame others.
All I ever wanted from you...
was to make sure my daughter lived a happy life.
We promised to make an effort. You can't do this all of a sudden.
She wasn't the one who was delusional.
It was me.
I know everything now.