(All characters, organizations, places, and events are fictional.)
The most expensive house in the complex got sold last week.
I don't know who's moving in.
But they've been sending in foreign-made furniture for days now.
Really?
The location and surroundings are obviously great,
and everything in the house was made with luxury materials.
There aren't that many houses left.
Dr. Ji, why don't you make a down payment?
Give me until this weekend to think about it.
- Here you go. - Thank you.
I hope to hear from you.
Hello.
(Episode 7)
- Hello. - Hello.
- I'm not late, am I? - You got here in the nick of time.
- Where did you go? - Just out.
Go on. I'll clean up once we're done.
Are you sure you can handle it by yourself?
What?
Please try one.
- Okay. Thanks. - Sure.
- Hello. - Hello.
It's all thanks to the people of Gosan.
Okay. Later.
Hey. I got that yesterday.
Joon Young, did you watch "Good Life"?
It's really good.
No.
Why not? Your dad made it.
- Stop lying. - I am not.
Joon Young's dad is the producer.
- My dad's friends with his. - Awesome.
Hey, maybe you can get free tickets from your dad for us.
Hey. You know he doesn't live with his dad.
Yes, but they must keep in touch.
Pay for your own ticket. Are you a beggar?
He's such a snob.
Forget it! I don't want it!
Joon Young.
Hey, it's your dad.
- Who's that? - Joon Young's dad.
He produced "Good Life".
- For real? - Yes.
- Did you know? - Of course not.
Get in.
You must be so happy.
I hear your son-in-law's movie is really good.
I watched it too. It's really good.
That's why it had more than 10 million viewers.
That's right.
My husband sings his praises, saying had we known...
Jenny's dad was so talented,
we would've backed him sooner.
I'm sure.
That's right. He's super talented.
I assume you'll all be there.
- Of course. - Yes.
Excuse me.
Madam Chairperson! Excuse me. Madam Chairperson!
Hello.
Weren't you close to Dr. Ji?
Our husbands were close.
We have no reason to see each other after she got divorced.
It was too awkward for me.
Of course, it's awkward. I would feel the same.
Hey, did you see this?
What is it?
She must have spent a pretty sum.
What is she doing?
- Is she inviting her? - No way.
Hello.
Did you watch my movie?
Not yet.
Did you know it was my movie?
Why are you the producer and not the director?
Because the producer is in charge of everything.
Hae Kang says it's good.
Didn't you miss me?
I...
missed you a lot.
You never called or texted once.
Do you actually expect me to believe that?
I know...
you saw me do some horrible things.
And I disappointed you.
I wanted to change...
and become a cool dad...
and come back as a proud dad.
So you wouldn't be embarrassed because of me.
That took some time.
I hope you understand.
It's a gift. Open it.
You still play baseball, right?
I quit the team years ago.
I guess Mom made you quit to make you focus on school.
Since I'm in middle school now.
Remember Kang Dong Hoon?
You were his fan.
I'll let you meet him.
- Really? - Yes.
He'll be at my house that day.
"That day"?
Didn't you get the invitation that I sent you?
(To Lee Joon Young)
(You are invited to Jenny's house party)
(Gosan Premium Luxury Town Houses)
(24 First Ave, Pyeonghwa-ro Nam-gu, Gosan City)
(24 First Ave A-1, Pyeonghwa-ro Nam-gu, Gosan City)
Hello?
Hello, sir.
Joon Young didn't go to the academy?
No.
He didn't tell me.
See you.
It's been a while.
(A World of Married Couple)
You've been well, right?
It's not like either of us cares how the other is doing.
I wondered now and then how you were doing...
- and if you were seeing anyone. - What are you trying to pull?
Why are you back?
Let's not do this. It's been so long.
I'm not here to fight.
- Then? - I just...
want to do my best as a dad.
Just let me see Joon Young.
Now? Out of the blue?
Think about how confusing it must be for him!
Why would he be confused about seeing his dad?
Not seeing me all this time is what was strange. Am I wrong?
From now on,
don't even think about seeing Joon Young without my consent.
You look good.
You've still got it.
Here.
Is this a new client?
It's more important to keep preexisting clients these days.
Did the bazaar go well?
Yes.
I heard...
Tae Oh produced "Good Life". Did you know?
I don't have time for movies.
How are you feeling these days?
When is our homework due?
Why are you changing the subject?
I don't want to talk about him.
The whole neighborhood is talking about Tae Oh's movie...
and his return.
Don't pay attention to them, and let's focus on us. Okay?
If it bothers you,
we can always move.
- Do we have the money? - No.
You know our appointment is tomorrow, right?
- Don't be late. - I left that time slot open.
As long as you get good marks on your performance assessment,
I guess this semester is over.
Dad said he sent me an invitation.
I got rid of it.
Are you upset?
No. I'm not going to go anyway.
Right. I noticed you haven't applied for baseball camp yet.
I can go with you this time.
I can take two days off.
It's okay. You don't know much about baseball anyway.
Are you sure you don't want to go?
Then what should we do during your break?
Do you want to go on a trip?
I'll just take some classes...
at Sunhaeng Academy, the one you mentioned last time.
Can you sign me up?
You sound as if you're doing me a favor.
I didn't ask you to attend Sunhaeng Academy for me.
I'm going to bed.
I'll sign you up for just English and math. Okay?
I'll register you online tonight.
Good night, honey.
Bring your bat when you visit my house.
I'll get Kang's autograph for you.
Hey, Joon Young.
You're visiting your dad's house.
You don't have to worry about what your mom thinks.
Have you heard?
Dr. Ji's ex-husband is coming back.
Good morning.
Yes, it's so crazy. The whole town is talking about it.
Of course, people are talking about it.
Her ex-husband who cheated is back with his new family right close by.
Good morning.
On top of that, he's returning in glory after succeeding.
I'd go crazy if I was her.
I'll put it in.
How can she be so indifferent?
She has a strong mentality.
Does she look like she's fine to you?
She's acting like she's okay since everyone's watching her.
I guess you're right.
She's been paying extra attention on her makeup and clothes.
Who?
We were just talking about...
a celebrity.
I have some time, right?
Yes. You don't have any appointments right now.
Did you see that? She has thick makeup today too.
I kind of feel sorry for her.
- You're all finished. - Okay.
Take care.
Come in.
You don't have any patients right now, do you?
Can you give me a cup of coffee?
Come on in.
I didn't know they were getting your consultation.
I heard he came back.
It must be entertaining for everyone.
Everyone's talking about him all morning.
Are you all right?
Do I look like I'm all right?
I'm not sure. You kind of look okay, but not really.
I guess I succeeded if you're confused.
How do you really feel aside from the way you look?
I'm swearing at him inside.
I don't understand why he wants to come back.
He says it's because of Joon Young,
but I don't think he cares about...
how difficult it'll be for Joon Young.
It could really be because of Joon Young.
Does he need another reason?
I better go. Thank you for the coffee.
Come by whenever it comes to mind.
Do you mean him?
No, coffee.
(Family Medicine Doctor Ji Sun Woo)
(TO Pictures)
("Movie 'Good Life' Released")
("Lee Tae Oh Successfully Transforms From a Director to a Producer")
(TO Pictures)
(Hello, I'm Lee Tae Oh, the president of TO Pictures.)
(We plan to build a large movie set near Gosan City.)
Thank you for congratulating me.
No, you don't need to bring any gifts.
I'm just glad you're coming.
Oh, really?
I really want you to be there.
You should come even if you're late. I'll be waiting for you.
Okay, bye.
She never visits her in-laws.
Stop calling people.
People who don't want to come won't come no matter what.
Hello, ma'am. It's me.
Your husband will be there, right?
Yes, of course.
He should come. All the big shots of Gosan will be there.
Okay, see you later.
Okay, that's enough.
Most of the important people will be there.
Thank you.
- Thank you, ladies. - Goodbye.
Let's see.
You should wear this. Wear something flashy.
This is good enough for a house party.
I don't want to look like I tried too hard.
I hope the place won't be too empty.
What if not a lot of people attend the party?
It's okay. We already have enough guests coming from Seoul.
Why do think I put in so much effort to form an association?
I didn't do it so I could show off to people in Seoul.
They used to badmouth me saying I stole him from his wife.
I don't care if they don't show up.
You didn't steal him.
They broke up because they had a horrible marriage.
I still get furious every time I think about...
what she did to our family.
She totally humiliated us! My gosh, seriously!
No matter what people say,
you're his legal wife now.
Stay confident and show them who you are.
You're the true winner.
Honey, where are you?
Please check if we got the champagne and flowers.
Okay, got it.
We prepared our own wine glasses.
You can take them inside for now.
Hey, Ye Rim. It's me.
You're coming today, right?
I was going to come up with an excuse and not go.
But she's persistent.
You even got a call from her.
So I guess you'll have to go.
I guess they want to officially announce their marriage to everyone.
Everyone in the neighborhood knows that they started out with adultery.
Do they think they can start off with a clean slate or something?
I can already imagine how much money they would've spent on this party.
I think she's trying to make Da Kyung join the association.
- What should I do? - What can you do?
You're a pro when it comes to acting like nothing ever happened.
Is he crazy?
They should've gone somewhere far away and stayed there...
after all that humiliation.
Why would they bother to come back like this?
But they were brazen enough to invite almost everyone in Gosan.
You should go and have fun.
Why would I go there?
Everyone who got invited is dumbfounded about this.
People think they should know better for having committed adultery.
Most people who got invited probably won't attend the party.
Do you want to have dinner together?
Joon Young will be late...
because he went to a friend's house to work on a school project.
Gosh, I have an appointment with a friend today.
We promised to meet over a month ago,
so I can't just cancel last minute.
- I'm sorry. - Don't be sorry.
You should meet your friend.
Get going then.
If you want to eat with me, let me know a bit earlier.
- I'm busier than I look. - Okay, fine.
Dr. Ji, are you going home?
I'm seeing my school friends today.
- I see. - Yes.
I'm running late. I'll see you then.
- Sir. - Yes, get in.
(My son)
Hey, Mom. I'm at Hae Kang's house.
What time do you think you'll finish?
Should I go pick you up?
No, it's okay. I can go on my own.
My friends are calling me. I'll see you later.
Wait. Did you eat?
(Hae Kang's mother)
(Ji Sun Woo)
Thank you for letting my son go over to your place today.
The kids can come over to our place next time.
What is it?
No, it's nothing.
What's going on?
There's a line from here, sir.
Welcome.
Hello. I'd like one soup, please.
Okay.
Thank you.
(Sundae Soup, Hangover Soup)
- Here you go. - Thank you.
Goodbye.
Excuse me.
Can I have a bottle of soju?
Sure.
- Welcome. It's nice to meet you. - Hello.
- My goodness, hello. - Thank you for coming.
- Hello. - I'm glad you're here.
Hello.
- It's so nice to meet you. - Congratulations.
- Congratulations. - You must be so happy.
My gosh, you're amazing.
- Your movie got 10 million viewers. - Thank you.
Everyone in Gosan is proud of you.
Thank you for coming.
Hello. Congratulations.
Thank you. You should go inside.
- Hello. - Hey, you came.
- Thanks for the invitation. - Don't mention it.
Go on inside.
- You're here! - Hey, man!
Look at you!
You were kind enough to come even during your busy schedule.
- Congratulations. - Thank you.
This way.
- Thanks for coming. - My pleasure.
- Ma'am. - Come this way.
Welcome, Ye Rim. Give me a minute.
Da Kyung.
Da Kyung!
Congratulations.
Isn't Je Hyuk coming?
He's busy with work.
He asked me to congratulate you for him.
I'm so sad. I really wanted to see him.
How have you been?
We've been well. No problems whatsoever.
I'm glad.
I was worried.
Hello.
- Congratulations. - Thank you.
Hi, Jenny.
Hi there. Hello.
Long time no see. Thank you for coming.
Your daughter looks just like you.
No, she doesn't. Everyone says she's her dad's Mini-Me.
Peek-a-boo.
Da Kyung.
Hi. You made it.
- That way. - Yes, ma'am.
- Play with Auntie and Uncle. - Okay.
- Thanks. - Congrats.
- Congrats. - Thanks.
- You've gotten prettier. - Congrats.
Hey.
- It's been too long. - Congrats, man.
Thanks.
Hi you.
Ye Rim!
- Come here. - Okay.
- Welcome. - Hello.
- Welcome. - Have a seat.
You came early.
Here.
Here's to peace in Gosan.
- Here's to Grandpa. - Cheers.
- Hello. - Hello.
- One gukbap, please. - Okay.
What great timing. It's snowing out too.
I was craving a drink.
- A bottle of soju, please. - Okay.
Another shot glass too.
It's Friday. Don't you have a date?
I should be asking you that since you're drinking alone.
You're right.
I thought I did the best I could,
but I'm drinking alone on a day like this.
What's "a day like this"?
- Enjoy. - Thank you.
How long do you think...
two years is?
Isn't it too short...
to forgive someone?
I had hoped he'd at least feel guilty.
I can't understand how he could think of coming back.
Time is relative to each person.
He probably thinks the past is in the past.
Our marriage...
may have ended in the past,
but to me, our divorce...
is still in progress.
(Tae Oh)
Joon Young is fine and having fun.
(To Joon Young)
(Kang)
- Work hard. - Thank you.
You must be so happy.
You must be happy to have such a cool dad.
- Thanks so much. - It's nothing, bro.
What a nice house.
Congrats on your move, Mr. Lee.
Hey. I'll buy dinner sometime.
Call me.
Hey. Joon Young, come here.
Oh my gosh. You made it.
Congratulations.
I enjoyed the movie.
Where are you going?
I need to go get my son.
Is it that big a problem that he's at his dad's house?
Of course, it is. He's breaking the rules.
I made it clear that he can't see Joon Young...
without my permission.
But look. He took him without even asking.
Joon Young may have wanted to go.
I know my son.
He despises his dad.
What do you think? It's big enough, right?
It gets good sunlight too.
- Whose room is it? - Yours.
Isn't it only natural that a son has a room in his dad's house?
I'll set it up so that you can come whenever you want, okay?
We're family.
The bed will go here. The desk will go here.
What else do you need?
I'll get you a computer and install all the top games.
Tae Oh, can we talk?
Wait right here, son.
What do you mean, it's his room?
You didn't mention that to me.
It's empty anyway, so I thought it would be nice.
You should consult me first.
How could you tell him first?
Are you saying no?
We agreed I can see Joon Young when we decided...
to move back to Gosan.
That boy having his own room in my house is a different story.
I hope you won't decide on things without talking to me first.
Da Kyung!
(Mom)
The person you have reached is not available.
Please leave a message after the tone.
(Sorry, there are no taxis available)
You'll never get a cab in this weather. Get in.
I didn't drink. Get in.
Thank you.
I mean it.
- Really? - Yes.
All right, everyone.
- Ta-da. - Congratulations, Da Kyung.
Thank you.
- Take a seat. - My goodness.
You gave birth,
but you're still fit as if you're unmarried.
You must have had a difficult time, but your husband became successful.
You must be so proud.
You won't worry your mom anymore, right?
I had knew it from the start.
Both of my parents...
ended up respecting my decision.
If I was scared of what clueless people yapped about,
Jenny and the box office hit film...
wouldn't be a part of my life.
All right.
You'll accept Da Kyung as a member of Gosan Women's Association, right?
Well...
Of course.
We should raise our glasses to celebrate.
I would like that.
- Here's yours, Mom. - Thanks, dear.
Congratulations on becoming a member of the association.
- Thank you. - Cheers.
- Cheers. - Cheers.
Okay.
Please excuse us for a moment. You can carry on.
- See you later. - Let's go.
She became quite confident.
She's no longer the young girl who left Gosan in tears.
- She was rude from the start. - That's true.
She was always insolent.
That's how she stole a married man.
Gosh.
Seriously.
This is a lot of people for a party.
People who are influential in the region...
were all invited.
My goodness.
Sun Woo, what are you doing here?
Dr. Kim, you came too.
- Have you seen Joon Young? - Joon Young?
Did Joon Young come?
I might have seen him.
Where did he go anyway?
I can't seem to spot him.
What is it?
Couldn't you control your curiosity?
I thought you wanted to show me.
That's why you sent the picture.
Are you sure you're not using Joon Young as an excuse to come?
Sure, let's just say that.
Don't ruin our party and leave.
I'll take Joon Young home later.
I'm afraid I can't agree to that.
Da Kyung.
- We should go. - No.
I won't leave without Joon Young.
Are you really going to do this?
Hey.
Hello.
I knew you were really something,
but I didn't expect this.
How did you even think about coming here?
That's what I'd like to ask.
How could you...
even think about coming back?
We have the right to decide where we want to live.
You were the last thing on our minds when we made our choice.
So don't worry about that...
and please leave.
This is an invitation-only party.
I thought...
you sent this.
If not,
who could've sent it?
I didn't come here because I'm curious to know how you live.
I have zero interest in that, so please don't worry.
I'll just...
take my son and leave.
Joon Young.
Da Kyung, are you okay?
Go and kick that woman out first!
Right now.
Joon Young.
Please come this way.
I'm not sure if it's okay for us to look through the house.
Going on a tour is the fun part of any housewarming party.
Yes. Please come this way. This way.
All right.
It's so bright. It really says they're newlyweds.
There's no question the couple is deeply in love.
This is from Italy, isn't it?
My goodness. This must have cost a fortune.
It took six months for us to receive everything.
Once we made the order, they made it for us.
I bet.
That's why they say furniture from Italian masters...
isn't furniture but are works of art.
My goodness. Just look at this color.
If Dr. Ji saw this,
she'd be jealous.
I know they got a divorce because things didn't work out,
but it would still hurt to see them live so happily with each other.
I put in a lot of effort to decorate this room since they're newlyweds.
We took a look at the bedroom, so let's move on.
- Come this way. - Okay.
This leads right to their study.
My goodness, look at that.
Are you crazy?
What are you doing in our bedroom?
Why are you back?
I heard your business is doing well.
Why couldn't you just stay in Seoul?
Why did you have to come back?
My wife wanted to live near her parents.
You moved here because that's what they wanted?
They took me in when you kicked me out.
Her parents wanted us here, so it's natural that we came back.
Are you still not over me?
You must've been really lonely, Sun Woo.
This is nice.
Isn't this great?
I'm happily married to Da Kyung.
I don't even remember how we were together.
Do you really mean that?
Isn't it pretty obvious?
You mean nothing to me.
You're my past.
The only woman I love now...
is Da Kyung.
You used Joon Young as an excuse...
to come all the way to our house.
And not only did you send me an invitation,
but you also sent me that photo.
You obviously did all that to provoke me.
You did it because of me.
You just wanted to see me.
Am I wrong?
Yes.
You're wrong.
Will you please leave my house now?
Before you get even more humiliated.
Mr. Lee Tae Oh and his wife, the hosts of today's party,
will be giving us a short speech.
Let's give them a round of applause.
Nice.
I would've felt a bit upset if Councilman Cha didn't give us...
such a grand introduction.
He really loves getting attention.
Later on,
I might even make him sing.
Thank you so much for coming here...
to congratulate our new beginning.
I know we had to leave...
due to what happened in the past.
But we always missed our hometown.
We will...
never...
leave this place again.
Da Kyung stayed by my side when I was going through my worst.
And...
the same goes for Jenny, my one and only daughter...
and precious princess.
The three of us will live happily in Gosan for as long as we can.
Thank you.
Give Daddy a kiss.
She's so adorable.
- Good job. - She's so cute.
You're my past.
The only woman I love now...
is Da Kyung.
Will you please leave my house now?
Before you get even more humiliated.
Dr. Ji Sun Woo.
Thank you very much for coming today.
You're here to congratulate us and give us your blessing, right?
We'll run into each other often now.
Let's let bygones be bygones,
and wish each other happiness...
and get along.
You'll do that, won't you?
Okay! How about a toast?
Raise your glasses.
Let's toast to "Good Life".
Your dad must have made a lot of money.
Lucky you.
It's cold. Aren't we going back in?
Be honest.
You want to live here too, right?
It's much nicer than your mom's house.
Your step-mom is pretty too.
- Shut it. - What?
- You look like you'll hit me. - Hae Kang.
- What's your problem? - I'm fed up with you.
Stop it!
Joon Young!
Get over here now!
- Congratulations. - Congratulations.
Why are you getting mad at me? You're the one in the wrong!
Why did you have to come? It's humiliating!
Did you come with him?
Get in. Now.
Congratulations.
Stop that.
- It was all you. - No way.
Honey!
Come. Let's have a family toast.
- Here. - Here's to our family's happiness.
- Cheers. - Cheers.
- Good job. - Thank you.
Get out.
Don't scold him too much.
Mind your own business.
I embarrass you?
Aren't you?
Imagine what people must think.
Don't blame others. Tell me what you think!
Do I embarrass you?
If you had been honest with me, I would've let you go.
I wouldn't have gone there to look for you.
Stop lying. You wouldn't have let me go.
You said you didn't want to go.
That's what you told me.
What? You're preparing for your performance assessment?
Did you want to go so badly, that you lied to me?
Lee Joon Young. Answer me!
Yes, I wanted to go!
Dad knows what I like better than you do.
With my princess, my one and only daughter in the world,
Jenny,
the three of us will live happily in Gosan for as long as we can.
Thank you.
Give Daddy a kiss.
Thank you...
for marrying me.
I saw that woman...
walking out of our bedroom.
What happened?
To be honest, I didn't expect her to go that far.
I guess our return was very traumatizing.
I am her past that she never wants to see again.
Thanks to that, I realized more just how much I love you.
You are my present.
You are the only one...
that matters to me.
I'll give up...
Joon Young's room too, if it bothers you.
Crazy jerk.
What's the schedule for this month?
Here it is.
- Gosh, is it done already? - Yes.
Do you have the list of equipment we need for the ER?
We only need these ones.
Great.
Dr. Ji.
You can leave these with me. I'll let you know afterward.
Okay.
Do you have something to say?
It's about yesterday.
I really wasn't planning to go...
Right.
I saw the order request for the medicine you sent recently.
I noticed an error in the data from the previous quarter.
Really?
Can you double-check and resend the request?
Are you...
really mad at me?
- Nurse An. - Yes?
Can you give me an hour break from seeing outpatients?
I have a lot of documents to review.
- Yes, ma'am. - Thank you.
Are you stressed about something?
No, I'm not stressed.
I'm just tired.
How did you end up coming to that party together yesterday?
We had dinner together.
Dr. Ji said she'll go to the party,
and I was worried about her going there alone.
That's why I went along.
Are you saying...
you left after dropping her off?
No, I was waiting outside.
You waited for Sun Woo?
Yes. I was worried.
What is that about?
Are they together already?
Are you serious?
(Lee Tae Oh)
Hey, don't invite me next time.
I'm in a difficult place because of you.
- Hello. - Anyway,
I'm meeting your director tonight. You should join.
So what if you're meeting the director?
Why are you calling me?
It'll be good for you.
See you tonight.
(Text messages)
Joon Young.
Joon Young?
The foundation will make a donation?
I'm on board with it,
but my father-in-law is especially interested...
in contributing to regional development.
Everyone in Gosan knows Chairman Yeo...
is a respectable person.
It doesn't matter if it's used...
for seniors living alone or kids living under single parents.
We won't be picky about how it's used.
I'm sure you had a difficult time.
But you're thinking of the less privileged...
the moment of your success.
I'm in awe, Mr. Lee.
Before that,
there's one thing that bothers me.
My in-laws aren't the type to complain,
but as you know,
I'm ashamed in front of them.
I'm talking about Ji Sun Woo.
Do you have to have her as your associate director?
Are you saying that...
Are you saying...
Sun Woo should step down if we want the donation?
Yes.
Don't you think there's a reason why I came back to Gosan?
Joon Young.
If I owe anyone something,
I should pay them back.
Joon Young, are you okay?
(A World of Married Couple)
Isn't it strange?
Things keep on happening to them as soon as Tae Oh returned.
Call me if there's anything you need my help with.
It'd be dangerous to stay in a house with poor security.
It's not that I don't like Joon Young.
The housewarming party was enough.
I personally think this is too much.
This is between us women.
You don't need to know about this.
Are you sure you can take care of this?
If you disapprove, I'll just cancel everything.
Be careful. They're not easy to fight against.
You came unannounced and messed with my stuff.
Then you barged in and attacked me.
But did you think I'd get scared and run away?