This story begins
during King Sinmun's reign in the Silla Dynasty.
This is recorded in Memorabilia of the Three Kingdoms.
"In spring of the year 682,
King Sinmun received a bamboo flute
from the Dragon King of the East Sea.
When the flute is played,
enemies would retreat, diseases would be cured,
rain would fall during droughts, the rainy season would end,
the wind would stop,
and strong waves would subside."
Seeing its powers,
King Sinmun named the flute
"Manpasikjeok"
and designated it as a national treasure.
Although for people who do not believe the story,
it is merely a myth.
Name, Lee Lim.
Born in February 1951.
Currently aged 70
in the year 2020.
BIRTHDATE: FEBRUARY 27, 1951
Explain this.
For me, this is harder to believe.
I really am 70 this year.
I hardly aged
since the winter of 1994.
Since then, my time passed by slowly, unlike you guys.
Why did it pass by slowly?
You're just a guy born in 1951.
Because I finally got my hands on the Manpasikjeok.
I took it from my brother who had it, but did not believe in it.
So,
did you kill
your brother?
The Manpasikjeok was revealed only once every 20 years
to wish peace upon the world.
Just answer yes or no.
So
did you kill your brother?
Yes, I did.
He was allowed to see it every day.
My naive half-brother, who became King
just because he was born the legitimate son,
did not do anything
when he had the world in his hands.
He did not even know that the Manpasikjeok in his hands
would bring the world to him.
To be exact, two different worlds.
I did expect
that one day, my nephew
would face that legend too,
just like me.
FOUR TIGER SWORD
KINGDOM OF COREA, WINTER OF 1994
PRINCE IMPERIAL GEUM, LEE LIM LEE GON'S UNCLE
THE SKY AND THE GROUND HELP THE EARTH BALANCE
DEFEAT THE BAD AND MAKE THINGS JUST
The King is in Cheonjongo.
Let's go.
What I need is over there.
-You... -Yes.
They're helping me, Your Majesty.
Brother,
what are you doing?
Do you still not know
what I'm about to do?
Don't do this.
Put that sword down.
This is treason.
To you, it might be nothing but treason.
But I picked up this sword to gain something even bigger.
What is it that you're so willing to kill for?
Do you not fear the punishment of the skies?
The punishment of the skies?
I plan to become the very being who gives punishment from the skies.
Your Majesty.
Brother.
God never created humans.
It was the weak
who created God.
Father.
Father!
His Majesty has already...
This is too bad.
You're an orphan now, Your Highness.
Do you really think you can hurt me with that?
I will try!
This is treason.
I order the Royal Guards to arrest the traitor, Lee Lim.
I deprive Prince Imperial Geum of his royal status
and sentence him to the maximum penalty
in accordance with the national law.
You sound like the crown prince for the first time in your life.
I'm ready, sir.
I will do it myself.
I've waited all my life for this very moment.
I hid my desires, gathered people to assist me,
endured your foolish father and mine,
and quietly waited for this day my entire life.
So how dare you...
How dare a little kid like you...
You useless and powerless punk...
How dare you mess this up?
Your Highness!
Emergency alert. There's an emergency in Cheonjongo.
There's an emergency in Cheonjongo.
Your Highness, we've lost too much time. You need to get out of here.
It won't take long.
Sir, you won't be able to escape once the Royal Guards get here.
Let's go.
We're going to leave the palace right now!
Emergency alert.
All Royal Guards gear up and gather at Cheonjongo.
SEOUL METROPOLITAN POLICE AGENCY
Come back to us, Your Majesty.
Last night, Prince Imperial Geum murdered King Lee Ho and fled.
The spokesperson of the Royal Family announced that...
Prince Imperial Geum who is currently wanted for murder and treason
will be stripped of his position.
So Crown Prince Lee Gon, the first in line to the throne
of the Kingdom of Corea, will be crowned King.
Second in line is Prince Inpyeong's eldest son,
Prince Buyeong, Professor Lee Jong-in.
Salute.
At ease.
You're here, Prince Buyeong.
Is the Crown Prince awake yet?
I heard his neck was severely injured.
I am sorry to say this,
but asking about the Crown Prince's state in the current situation
could lead to misunderstandings.
Whether I mention him or not,
people will gossip about me.
What about Lee Lim's whereabouts?
The Royal Guards and the police are investigating together.
We're doing vehicle inspections. Please open your trunk.
They closed off all the roads right away,
If he is still in Busan, I'm sure they will find him.
I hope so too, but he seems to have thoroughly prepared for this.
I believe he would have thought of an escape plan first.
REPUBLIC OF KOREA, THE WINTER OF 1994
SEOUL ARTS CENTER
These sweet potatoes are sweeter than sugar.
Three for 1,000 won.
SALVATION ARMY CHARITY POT
NEWS OF THE HOUR 1. THE CAUSE OF SEONGSU BRIDGE COLLAPSE
THE 7TH REPUBLIC OF KOREA THEATER AWARDS, 1994
REPUBLIC OF KOREA HOPE MUSIC CONCERT FOR SEOUL CITIZENS, 1994
"Republic of Korea"?
PRESIDENT KIM YOUNG-SAM APPOINTS LEE HONG-GU AS THE NEW PRIME MINISTER
ANALYSIS ON THE FUTURE OF NORTH-SOUTH KOREAN RELATIONS
TWO MONTHS AFTER THE COLLAPSE OF SEONGSU BRIDGE
Shit.
You jerk, did you just hit me?
Hey.
"President"?
Hey!
Hey, what are you staring at? You jerk.
Lim!
Hey.
I know you.
Do you know me too?
What are you talking about?
What...
How did you...
Am I
your older half-brother?
When were you not?
How in the world are you walking around like this?
How can this happen?
I was right.
"Republic of Korea"?
So, where is your brother right now?
This is how you were living?
You're living such a lowly life.
Well, you and I do look alike.
But
we don't just look alike.
I am you.
You in a different world.
But I'm
very different from you.
I am much nobler
than you.
Uncle,
how are you...
standing?
Even in this world, you've seen something you shouldn't have.
And you're holding something you shouldn't be holding.
KINGDOM OF COREA CORONATION OF THE THIRD KING
The King is entering!
KING LEE GON THE THIRD KING OF THE KINGDOM OF COREA
Long live the King!
-Long live the King! -Long live the King!
Today is the 6th day of the former King's funeral.
After his coronation, King Lee Gon
began his first duty as King, mourning his father's death for 26 days
according to court laws.
The public is watching the young King's formality
-with a sad heart. -Father...
Father...
Is this your husband?
It seems he was in a hit-and-run accident while he was drunk.
I know you're startled, but we'd appreciate your cooperation.
Yes, he's my husband.
I was in the middle of work.
Can I go since I've confirmed it?
Oh, yes.
You may have his body transferred tomorrow afternoon.
I...
I heard that
the government will cremate the body for you
if you sign something.
Well, at least he had a meal before his death.
I guess there is a god.
My husband just died.
I prayed every day that he'd die.
I thought I would end up
either dying or killing him
before leaving this house.
But...
But someone killed him for me.
And the government will cremate his body for me.
Now...
I can leave this house with Ji-hun...
Father...
Hey.
Hey, eat this.
I'll give this to you.
Put that away.
Father...
He's not moving an inch.
Right.
He shouldn't talk to the King like that.
It's all part of a plan.
Just wait and see.
Hey, is it fun to study?
How are you getting into this place?
Get out.
Do you think this whole place is yours?
Yes, this place is all mine.
So get out.
You're lying.
Who's your father?
He's your father's friend!
The funeral process is finally over.
You've done well on performing your first duty, Your Majesty.
I miss my father.
Yes.
I know, Your Majesty.
I know.
Why are you crying?
Don't cry.
You should stop crying too.
Here.
From now on, you're the Unbreakable Sword.
The Unbreakable Board? What's that?
What's your name, though?
Jo Yeong. What about you?
I am Lee Gon, the King of the Kingdom of Corea.
Okay, I get it.
Anyway,
thank you for this.
My goodness.
There's someone over here!
Help! There's someone here!
Help! Someone help!
ROYAL HOSPITAL OF COREA
Oh, gosh.
Hello.
This can't be revealed to the public,
so I had to ask you to perform the autopsy yourself.
I have no idea what to do about this.
Calm down.
You made a wise choice.
I heard that the Royal Guards
think he committed suicide.
Yes, they say it seems like it.
He probably had nowhere to run.
They say all his bones were broken. Probably due to the waves.
Even so,
this can never be suicide.
This has to be
a shooting by the Royal Guards.
Your Highness.
I will have to make a false statement
for the young King and the Royal Court that is in chaos.
Do you understand?
Yes, Your Highness.
FORMER KING'S BASTARD LEE LIM MEETS TRAGIC END
Your Highness,
you were alive?
You believed I was, didn't you?
Yes, I did.
I believed you were alive.
But how...
How can you still look the same?
It has been over a decade since I last saw you.
How did you not age at all?
You've held out well.
Let me show you
a new world.
Yes, Your Highness.
KINGDOM OF KOREA, BUSAN MAIN PALACE THE FALL OF 2019
SUNGWOON GROUP LABOR RELATIONS BOARD
THEY WILL ONLY ADVISE GROUP ON LABOR UNIONS AND SUCCESSIONS
Yes, I'm caught today as well.
Prime Minister, please step up onto the platform.
I need to do an additional pat-down search.
Wireless bras don't support my breasts properly.
I'll begin the pat-down search.
I will do it myself.
-Are you new? -Yes, sir.
His Majesty does not like others touching his body.
This may be a mistake, but if it happens again, it's intentional.
Keep that in mind.
Yes, sir.
His Majesty is going to the VIP horse riding course.
I'm going to drop by my bedroom first.
All right.
1. PICTURE IN THE HALLWAY 2. VASE NEXT TO BED
We have to replace these every month,
so make sure to write down all the locations.
The first one is behind the painting,
and it goes counterclockwise.
And don't say a word to His Majesty.
Gosh,
I heard this talisman is the most effective for finding a lover.
What? Why aren't you answering?
I almost had a heart attack.
I heard the Prime Minister came early and is waiting right now.
What are you doing here?
These really seem to be effective.
I guess they have the power to pull people toward you.
Prime Minister Koo must be coming early every time because of these.
She might actually become the Queen.
Oh, that bitch...
I mean... My goodness.
She cannot become the Queen.
You said you don't believe in superstitions.
These don't have any powers--
I don't, but you believe in them.
What?
You believe that someone might actually answer your desperate prayers.
I have my reasons, you know.
The royal court is unstable more than ever.
So, you know, you should get married--
I do not want to.
It is the King's duty to produce an heir, and--
I am not interested.
How can you not be interested when you are so young and decent?
My goodness. This is unbelievable.
You are the very first woman to be so rude to me since I sat on the throne.
Goodness.
Oh, my.
-You shall be beheaded. -What?
Tell Prime Minister Koo we'll meet in two hours as planned.
My gosh. These are really expensive.
Let's put these clockwise this time.
Yeong, I found talismans again.
There were 8 today. That's 51 in total.
Really?
Why?
Is it not 51?
Did she hide more than that when you were keeping a lookout?
I didn't take an active part in it.
Well, I'm going to reprimand you actively, so just wait.
I know I'm here early, Your Majesty.
The weather was nice,
and I missed Maximus, so I hurried a bit.
Hi, Maximus.
It doesn't like women.
And it's spoiled, so it bites people too.
Me too.
I bite people often as well.
Can you wave your hand?
They're filming us 50 meters away.
The Royal Public Affairs Office thought a photo here would look great.
It'll be hard to walk together.
Just stand over here.
Your left face is pretty.
And next time, wear more comfortable shoes.
You're pretty considerate.
You shortened the state affairs report time down to half,
so I had no time to change my shoes.
Your reports last for an average of 18 minutes,
so I believe 30 minutes is enough.
Shall we begin then?
Should we shorten five more minutes since we're busy?
Like I said in my written report, the country is peaceful,
and the people are happy.
And they'll be happier when they see our photo.
It is all thanks to you.
I'm thinking of learning horse riding as well.
Do you think I'd do well, Your Majesty?
When you learn to ride, this is what you hear first.
"If you have trained honestly every time,
your horse will take you to the edge of the world."
Prime Minister, are you honest?
I received your report,
and we took enough photos, so shall we end it here?
I have to get washed up for my next schedule.
Oh, my gosh!
You nearly gave me a heart attack!
This is treason.
You should hurry. You might be late.
What will you do if I'm not late?
And how long have you been standing there?
Do you really want to know?
You're getting beheaded for sure.
This is when we say, "You reap what you sow."
You bolt like this all the time.
And I don't know if you've dug some kind of tunnel in your bathroom.
How can you say "bolt" to your King?
As you ordered, we got rid of the term "single-parent family."
And the banners.
Yes, good job.
But how can you talk like that to your King?
Everything here is mine.
Get it? It's all mine!
You know that now, don't you?
Hey, Unbreakable Sword. Aren't you going to answer me?
Do you get it now?
FAIRY TALES TOLD BY THE KING
"Alice didn't even think about how she would return
and jumped into the hole after the White Rabbit.
She fell down and down.
She was falling endlessly.
She said in a loud voice, 'How many miles
have I fallen?'"
This is my favorite book.
The author was a mathematician, too.
How is it? Is it interesting?
-No! -No!
It's boring.
I've never seen anyone talk so honestly to me since I became King.
Your Majesty, do you have a girlfriend?
This is what we really need to ask.
Oh, no.
So even this young girl is worried about the royal court.
All right.
I know who ordered you to ask that,
but I'll answer you.
I do not have a girlfriend yet.
Then you should follow the White Rabbit too, Your Majesty.
Should I?
All right, then I guess I should keep reading.
-"Alice..." -No!
It's boring. Please!
-Move! -Hey! Move it!
Find her! Where the hell did she go?
Long strides. Keep it firm.
Navy Academy.
-The 88th class! -The 88th class!
-Navy Academy. -The 88th class!
Navy Academy.
-The 88th class! -The 88th class!
THE 88TH CLASS WILL TAKE THE ROWING CUP AGAIN
Hey, men should wear little and move a lot!
Hey, some men look awesome even when they're all covered up.
This is so great.
He's moving to the finish line.
1. NAVY 88TH CLASS 2. UX CONSTRUCTION 3. ZENIST
Yes!
You'll need some water later.
Iced water for 1,000 won. I have iced water here.
Hey, my water!
That crazy bitch! Damn it!
I haven't even sold any today yet!
-We are! -Descendants of the Admiral Yi Sun-sin!
-If we fight, we win! Yes! -If we fight, we win! Yes!
That way. Run!
Where is she?
Damn it, move aside!
Move! Come on!
Damn it!
I'm really serious right now, okay?
If you don't want to die, move aside!
Boss, wait.
Don't move. Stay still.
-You idiot! -Stay still.
How can I get her if I stay still?
What's this red thing on you?
What is that?
Put your hands up!
-What? Why... -What's going on?
Soldiers? Why are soldiers here?
Why are they...
I'm sorry.
We should get away from here first.
Team One, take those jerks to the police.
Team Two, let's escort the VIP away from here.
Your Majesty.
-Over there! His Majesty went that way! -My gosh...
What?
Mom, His Majesty is really following the White Rabbit with the clock.
You have really good stamina.
You rowed 2,000 meters and you ran like that right after.
Why did you suddenly run like that?
I just saw the White Rabbit with the clock.
What do you mean?
Are you saying you saw a rabbit or a clock?
Weren't you listening when I was reading Alice in Wonderland?
I was busy organizing my team's schedules.
You really need some
fairy tales in your life.
And I think you need some shoes, Your Majesty.
These aren't my shoes.
You must wear this from now on.
You're going to protect me anyway.
Still, you must wear this.
Will you feel better if I do?
Then you can wear two for me.
I'm really going to get a warning if you don't listen.
You're the captain. Who would give you a warning?
My sense of duty.
You just made it really awkward.
We caught all the men who caused the scene at the competition.
And we're looking for the White Rabbit with the clock you saw.
I will check whether it is a rabbit or a clock once when we find it.
Are you having fun, Captain Jo?
Don't.
Don't do what?
Why do you want to catch the culprit yourself?
Do you want to get a Brave Citizen Award?
Why would I catch the culprit?
You should be catching the culprit as the captain of the Royal Guards.
I'm not catching anyone. I'm just trying to find
the face that only I can recognize.
Every time something like this happens,
it feels like that person is there.
When it happened 25 years ago,
and today as well.
It's been 25 years.
Your savior must have aged a lot.
Do you think you can recognize the face?
I'm not sure.
We might have already met unknowingly.
But
why hasn't my savior ever come to see me?
Because you've grown up well.
You don't need anyone's help now.
You're not mad at me anymore.
My dear Yeong.
How about a glass of beer?
No, thank you.
You can go home.
JEONG TAE-EUL NATIONAL POLICE AGENCY
I'm older than you now.
Lieutenant Jeong Tae-eul.
LIEUTENANT JEONG TAE-EUL DATE OF BIRTH: MAY 27TH, 1990
REPUBLIC OF KOREA, THE FALL OF 2019
Oh, my. She totally crashed into it.
I think that'll cost about 370,000 won.
She didn't have to hit it that hard.
My goodness.
Hello, this is the security office.
You live in Unit 405, right?
-There's some bad news. -Oh, no. What do I do?
Some woman just crashed her car into yours!
Oh, my gosh. What do I do?
I'm sorry.
What?
What? What's she doing?
Oh, gosh. She's insane.
Hey, that woman over there. Hey, stop right there!
-Hey! -It's illegal if you just leave. No, stop!
Hey, ma'am.
Did you see that?
You should come down. All right.
He won't come down.
Only delivery guys go up to his house.
-He hasn't come down for quite a while. -I'm telling you, he'll come down.
Bad guys are more sensitive when it comes to others breaking the law.
This is the most effective method.
Kim Bok-man and two others have left the house.
I'll block their escape route.
Right.
Oh, no. This is awful.
What happened?
Damn it!
Mister, where did this bitch go? Where?
The bitch who crashed into my car. Where is she?
Tae-eul, are you okay?
I'm fine. You know. I've done this many times.
I'm not hurt. Don't worry.
I mean, is your outfit really okay?
Your top and bottom really don't match right now.
What's wrong with my outfit?
It's all about being natural. It emphasizes the colors of these clothes.
I'm dressed as a chic, professional city girl.
I think I look pretty great.
You should've dressed up properly. Why only focus on the colors?
She has such a filthy temper.
Wait, there's a weird smell.
Come down.
So I'm saying, some woman just
crashed her car into yours and just drove off...
It's that car. The one driving backward like that.
You drove off naturally, but why are you coming...
Hey! Ma'am! What are you doing?
Hey! Damn it.
Hey! Damn it!
Damn it!
Ma'am...
What a crazy bitch.
Hey, do you have a death wish?
Oh, it hurts. My back!
Wait, I know this smell. Oh, no.
We found a body in the trunk.
We're changing this from an illegal gambling website case
to a murder case.
No!
I don't know that person!
I really don't know! I didn't kill him!
-Now give me your wrists. -Damn it!
The two others are heading that way.
-Damn it. -Hey.
One is going towards the playground.
You are mine.
Hey!
Shit.
Over here. That's it.
-Okay! -Damn it. What the...
Put on the handcuffs yourself.
Okay, let's go!
Hey, I really didn't kill that person. Stop! Wait! Don't go!
The Forensics team is going to arrive in 20 minutes.
Oh, why can't they come any faster?
You said it was just a plain illegal gambling website case.
Are we going to have to work overtime again?
I can't work overtime.
I'm serious.
I'm totally serious right now.
-I can't do it until we get a new member. -I can't do it either. Damn it.
When are we getting a new recruit?
I want to hire one too. I think about it every day.
But I have no choice. Nobody wants to join the Violent Crimes Division these days.
You don't get promoted easily, you don't get paid well,
you get hurt all the time, you get disciplined for everything...
Would you apply if it were you?
But we're doing this job.
That's right!
But what's with your outfit today?
What? What about it?
I'm a chic, city girl.
This is a natural style.
But did you call me "ma'am" a while ago?
Anyone would have called you that.
He's right.
Tell Captain Jo that I'm going to check
whether it's a clock or a rabbit first.
Team One and Two, put on the harnesses and stand by.
Where are you right now, Captain?
We got the identity of the body.
Lee Sang-do, age 45, a hardware store owner.
He was a member of Kim Bok-man's gambling website.
He took money worth a whole building from that site.
But he put the store up for sale and we can't get a hold of his wife.
I'll head back after investigating around here some more.
Okay, I'm getting the security footage. We'll discuss things at the station.
I want to check the security footage.
The VIP just passed Point 06. Over.
We're at Point 04.
Report at each point. Over.
What is it?
What's wrong, Maximus?
What was that?
Damn it. That startled me.
That's so scary.
I guess I'm really getting old.
How could I hallucinate like that?
Gosh, my heart hurts.
What the hell is that?
What a weirdo.
Hey, there's a horse.
It's huge.
What's a white horse doing on the road?
You, the man on the horse, stop right there.
Horse, horse-rider...
Excuse me, horse-rider.
Park your horse on the side road to the right.
-Do you see that? -What's that?
-He is so handsome. -Park your horse right now.
He's not listening at all.
Maybe it's for a film.
He's really handsome.
QUEEN YUNA THE BEGINNING OF A NEW LEGEND
Excuse me, sir! The man on the horse!
JEONG TAE-EUL NATIONAL POLICE AGENCY
You shouldn't disturb the traffic like this.
Get down.
Where did a civilian get a white horse like that?
You've violated the road traffic law.
And you'll be given a heavier penalty if that horse poops on the ground.
Why are you staring at me like that?
Oh, I see.
I'm a police officer. Get down from there.
And show me your identification card.
JEONG TAE-EUL NATIONAL POLICE AGENCY
What the hell
do you think you're doing right now?
I've
finally met you,
Lieutenant Jeong Tae-eul.
What are you doing? Are you out of your mind?
I am the King of the Kingdom of Corea.
I came to a conclusion that this is a parallel universe.
This is a parallel universe?
I heard Tae-eul got herself into a difficult situation with a handsome guy.
Kim Gae-ddong!
His Majesty was after whom? A woman?
Did you find the woman they were chasing?
-Yeong. Isn't that you, Yeong? -What's your problem?
I heard you're unidentified.
What exactly is the relationship between you and Lieutenant Jeong?
Container ship?
I can't stay here for long.
The reason why I have to stay in your world.
Could there be a reason?
I like being here with you like this.
But I don't know you. Why do you know me?
Lieutenant Jeong Tae-eul.
I take you...