(Episode 19)
Hong Jo, come here.
Where are you?
Hong Jo.
("No amount of time can erase the memory of a good cat,")
("and no amount of masking tape...")
("can ever totally remove his fur from your couch.")
(Quote by Leo Dworken)
Gosh, this is killing me.
You're just allergic.
I should've left you behind.
Leave the cat here...
and focus on your webtoon.
You never upload things on time.
You need to be steady in order to gain lots of viewers.
Then what about you? Did you write a lot of poems?
You told me you were going to write poems again.
Do you want to read them?
No, it's okay. They're boring.
I liked the drawing you drew a few days ago.
I could tell that you've come to deeply care for the cat.
Do you think you'll be okay?
Such a relationship isn't easy...
for a person or a cat.
You can sometimes visit to see the cat.
Who says I'm going to leave him behind?
I'll take care of him for you.
Then you'll visit me every now and then to see the cat.
But...
why are you here?
Because Sol Ah...
needs some time.
And I have nowhere else to go...
other than here.
I should've thrown your collar into the sea.
Let me stay for the time being.
Come down and eat.
Again?
It's the weekend, but I can't even go on a date...
because I need to work part-time.
So I was hoping you'd come down and eat with me.
Come down, okay? See you.
Welcome.
Didn't you say the part-timer here is really handsome?
Let's go somewhere else.
- Come on. - You guys.
I'm not a part-timer. I'm the owner's son.
I kind of understand them.
He should've just taken after me.
Ji Eun.
Hey, Sol Ah.
What are you doing here?
Well...
You must be here to eat.
- Well... - Let's go.
Hello.
There you are. You're here, too?
- We have customers. - What?
My goodness.
Look who's here. Sol Ah, it's you.
- You look beautiful. - Thank you.
Honey! Sol Ah's here!
Sol Ah?
My goodness, you're right! Sol Ah, it's been so long!
It's so nice to see you. Sit down.
- Have you been well? - Yes.
- Of course. - Ji Eun's here, too.
Welcome.
I always told you to drop by for a meal.
Why didn't you come for so long? I missed you so much.
I missed you, too.
I heard your father went to the countryside. Is he well?
Yes, he's doing well.
I visited him for his birthday.
And he asked me to give you this.
- My goodness. - Gosh.
- He didn't need to give us this. - You could've...
- come empty-handed. - You didn't have to bring anything.
- What's this? - What's this?
This is...
It's bracken!
- Why did he send us so much? - My goodness.
Did he start a bracken farm?
- No. - Ji Eun's nickname is Bracken too.
Really? Why?
I don't know. That's what people say when someone has small hands.
They're small, aren't they? It's cute. They look like bracken.
Did you give her that nickname?
No, my mom did.
Right, Mom?
My goodness, when did you hear that?
You must be hungry.
Honey, hurry up and grill some mackerel...
- so the kids can eat. - Yes, of course.
- I'll take this inside. - Just wait a little bit.
Okay.
How was the trip? What about Bang Guk Bong?
What?
Oh, well...
By the way, is Ji Eun a regular here?
You even got yourself a cute nickname.
We're going out.
What?
Are... Are you serious?
My gosh! Congratulations, you guys. You must be really happy.
Thanks.
Did something good happen?
What?
- I can't tell you. - What is it?
Oh, well...
It's about someone else.
Okay, you should go home.
Okay.
Can I go inside?
Well...
I didn't get to clean the place.
I came to give you this.
It's stir-fried bracken.
My mom made them just now.
The smell of perilla oil is amazing, isn't it?
I wanted to eat it with you and hold your cute, small hands.
That's not what she meant when she called me that.
What?
She was talking about brackens...
that turned too mushy because they were boiled too much.
That's what she thinks of me.
Gosh, that's nonsense. Do you want me to ask my mom?
No, don't tell her anything.
Don't say anything to her.
If she finds out we're dating, she'll be disappointed.
That's nonsense.
You can come next time after I clean my house.
But...
- Ji Eun. - See you.
Hey, wait.
I owe you guys an apology.
I think I expected too much from you guys...
when you are young and inexperienced.
Ji Eun, you wasted so much time.
The same goes for Sol Ah and Doo Sik.
This won't meet up to our company's reputation.
The clients keep asking us for revisions.
You guys are off the project. Hand over the materials to Mr. Cha.
Do you understand?
Okay.
I'm sorry for the sudden notice, but do me a favor.
Yes, of course.
- That's all for today's meeting. - Wait. But...
What just happened?
- Did we just lose our project? - You didn't lose it.
We're a family. We should fill up for each other when it's necessary.
Let's go.
That was a huge punch in the face.
Why didn't you say anything?
You shouldn't have just said okay to that.
It's true that the clients kept asking for revisions.
You know what? Let me go talk to her.
What do you need?
I don't think it's fair to take our projects away from us like that.
How so?
The three of us did our best...
You did your best?
You were busy doing other stuff, and you call that your best?
I draw webtoons after work.
There aren't any rules saying I'm not allowed to have two jobs.
Sol Ah.
You think your job is boring, don't you?
You think it's boring and meaningless.
What?
No, I don't...
"It's boring because you always ask me to do boring stuff."
Is that what you wanted to say?
Why do you think I ask Ji Eun to work on the important stuff...
and ask you to work on all the boring projects?
Because she did me a personal favor?
No.
It's because she enjoys everything she does.
Whether it's a project from a big corporation...
or simply designing a wedding invitation.
You're not desperate enough, Sol Ah.
What does it mean to be desperate?
Do you expect me to endure everything you ask me to do...
and stay quiet even though I lose my projects?
Is giving up everything the only way to be desperate and sincere?
I always worked with sincerity.
I always tried to finish the work that was given to me...
regardless of whether or not it was fun.
And the same goes for this project...
Do you think you're in charge of the project?
You're not qualified to be in charge.
Now, please leave.
She won't even listen to me.
I think you should try talking to her yourself.
Me?
(Wedding Invitation)
What... What are you doing?
Why are you...
I figured I should finish what I started.
This is why she treats you like a pushover.
What's going on? Are you guys fighting?
No, it's just that she's working on the wedding...
Sorry.
We all deal with things differently.
I know we're just working on a small project.
But she's not doing anything even though she's our leader.
Why would you assume that she's not doing anything?
This might be her way of trying to solve the problem.
Don't just jump to conclusions.
I'm just saying...
she should be more responsible.
How would you feel if we called you irresponsible...
for giving up your cat?
I saw your cat at Sonamu.
- Is it the cat that was locked up? - Yes.
All the other cats were adopted.
This is the only cat left.
- Why didn't anyone adopt this cat? - I think it's because...
the cat is too old.
I guess there's not much time left for this cat.
A lot less than what you think.
There's not much time left until the cat gets euthanized.
Can't you adopt it?
I guess not.
I'm trying to find someone who will adopt this cat.
But it's hard.
Hong Jo doesn't live here anymore.
It feels like someone's watching me.
I cooked some beef radish soup.
You didn't need to.
This is just an excuse to see if you're okay.
I'm sorry.
Why don't you just thank me instead?
You should have some while it's still hot.
I'll see you.
Hello, I'm Cha Sang Kwon from Nalsaem Design.
Yes.
I'm in charge of the project now. You know that, right?
Yes. I'm aware that you've had some communication problems.
But from now on, I'll make sure everything goes well.
Yes.
Sol Ah, do you want to eat lunch together?
(Sol Ah, do you want to eat lunch together?)
It's Hong Jo's cell phone.
The three of us should have lunch together.
I'm not feeling so well.
You guys can eat without me.
Let's eat.
It's on the house.
Thank you.
You seem to be a nice person.
May I ask you something?
What?
Would you like to adopt a cat?
Don't you have any friends who are willing to adopt a cat?
How have you lived your life?
You also have nowhere else to go other than here.
Normally, you ask this kind of stuff to your close friends.
Don't you have any friends who can help you?
Someone you can ask for difficult favors.
Not a single person?
Don't you even have a family?
No, I don't.
("J Lab Soft's Stock Price Falls After Chairman Lee's Retirement")
Yes, you do. You have a family.
Your parents.
(Chairman Lee Gu Yeong will be resigning from his position...)
I sent you to study abroad so you could go to law school.
But you even learned how to work with leather?
I'm sorry for disappointing you.
Look at how polite you are.
Where did you learn to be like that?
Even if I tell you not to do something,
you're the type of guy...
who would politely apologize and do it anyway.
From now on,
I won't ask for your help.
- I'll fend for... - If you fend for yourself,
can you do whatever you want?
Are you telling me to not touch you...
since you won't touch my money?
I didn't want to cause you a nuisance.
A nuisance?
I see.
Until now,
you were a guest in our house, not a member of it.
I understand, young sir.
Then stop being a nuisance...
and go on your way. The guest is leaving.
Father.
Don't you dare regret this and come back asking for a hand!
I will never give you anything!
Instead, I will just break your wrist!
Is this it?
I shouldn't have come here.
Are you running away again?
No.
Eun Ji Eun.
I want to apologize to you.
Do you not want to talk to me?
I thought you didn't want to talk to me.
I texted you.
But you...
I left my phone at home.
I saw you...
with a phone.
Oh, this one?
This isn't mine.
I had no idea.
I'm sorry.
For not doing anything.
I said I wanted to apologize.
If Doo Sik were to see this,
he'd make a fuss thinking I made you cry.
You don't know why...
I had Doo Sik's eraser, do you?
Hey, lend me your eraser.
Sure. Here.
- Hey. - What?
- Your eraser. - Goodness.
Here, keep it.
Hey, could you at least try to be more imaginative?
- What is that? - What's what?
- I found... - You're too far off.
Draw something.
You dropped this.
You call that a drawing? What's that?
- An apple or a persimmon? - Don't you even have an eraser?
You have one.
Your eraser is mine also.
Find it quick.
Did anyone see my eraser?
Have one of your own.
Thanks.
Do you know what's worst about keeping quiet?
Things keep piling on you before you let it out.
To be honest,
I had a lot of things against Ms. Park.
I just pretended to be nice,
but on the inside,
I was full of hatred and resentment.
I did nothing about it,
but I got jealous without anyone noticing.
And I hated people.
In the end,
I hated myself the most.
I hate myself so much.
You won't know.
Because you sparkle and shine.
You don't know how I feel inside either.
I pretend to be righteous and responsible on the outside.
Do you know who this belongs to?
It belongs to the person I cowardly pushed away.
No.
The cat.
I guess he needs a while longer to get ready.
Shall I bring you more tea?
No. We'll just get going.
Where are you going?
We can't wait here forever.
What happened?
Did something happen?
Nothing happened at all.
I'm fine. I walk and run just fine.
I sit in a wheelchair to give them one less thing to nag about.
How come...
Why didn't you tell me?
Did you ever even call me?
Oh. You did call to brag to me once...
that you're opening a leather workshop.
Was this why...
you couldn't come that day?
Were you upset with me until now because I didn't show up?
When you never came by once?
Because you threw me out.
Why are you here?
Do you want to read my will?
Because you found out my condition?
That's not why.
Who's he?
I came to ask you to take in a cat.
A cat?
It was abandoned.
It's old, like me.
You suddenly show up after years away to say...
you want me to adopt a cat?
One that's already old...
and doesn't have much time left?
You came to ask me such a difficult favor?
You?
It was wrong for me to come here.
I just thought...
Jae Seon.
Thank you.
It's the first time...
you asked me to do you a favor.
You thought you were so great,
you never...
asked for anything, which was so upsetting.
But thank you for coming to me.
Thank you for asking me for something.
Thank you.
Father.
Yes. I waited for this.
I'm sorry. I...
I thought...
It's okay.
(Episode 20 will air shortly.)
You said...
he sat here and cried.
Yes.
I think I know...
why he was crying.
I'm not...
Bang Guk Bong.
He was pretending to be someone else.
What do you mean?
Did he lie to you?
I was mistaken.
I just saw what I wanted to.
Now that I think about it,
when we first met at home,
he told me he wasn't Bang Guk Bong.
Then who was he?
Hong Jo.
Hong Jo?
Your cat?
Hong Jo...
was a person.
That can't be.
You lived in the same house until now?
Not now.
I kicked him out.
Who are you talking about?
The cat? Or...
Both.
What should I do?
Could I really...
love a cat?
Can I love a cat?
Welcome back.
Hey.
The cafe was closed early.
Jae Seon's at his parents' house.
His home? How come?
To give an abandoned cat a home.
They both found one.
The cat...
and Jae Seon.
Did you...
take Jae Seon home?
How did you do that? Even I couldn't manage.
Thanks.
Do you not eat well?
You don't look too good.
Did something happen at work?
Are you sick?
I'm... I'm just a bit tired.
What are you taking photos of?
Why did you photograph that?
We sat here before.
I first saw you somewhere around here.
It was Hong Jo.
He was...
next to me that night.
Even when...
(Jae Seon)
I didn't know.
He was always next to me.
She doesn't have a fever.
It's cold.
It's still cold.
Her hands were so hot all night last time.
The day it rained?
Did you...
secretly change into a human back then too?
I'm sorry.
How long were you secretly a human?
You spied on me these last few days, right?
My room, my bed...
For how long, and how much...
have you've been spying on me?
Tell me.
For as long as you were alone.
You always took care of others on your own...
and forgot your own stuff.
Don't drink too much.
I might be working late, so don't make a mess.
You were sick too,
but didn't even say anything.
My cat. He keeps shivering.
Don't get sick. Please.
I wanted...
to be next to you at least.
Are you...
really human only when you're next to me?
Why?
Why is it only when you're with me?
I don't know either.
Maybe it's because...
a cat cannot hug you.
I have to be human...
to hug you.
What are you doing then?
You're human now.
You have arms...
and hands.
By the way,
there was a drink inside this bottle.
Did you throw it away?
I'm sorry.
I had a hot massage pack in the drawer.
I guess you didn't see that when you spied on me.
You must've been cleaning.
Do you want me to come in?
Wait...
So this is what your place looks like.
(Doo Sik and Ji Eun)
Sticky notes.
You already finished it.
You talked so sadly about bracken.
It tasted good.
What else do you want? Just say it.
It's okay. I shouldn't just return an empty container.
Give it to me.
No need to be so polite. You're like family.
Just give me it.
You can...
have this.
Everything that belongs to me is yours now.
My eraser...
and my heart.
This is as far as I'll go tonight.
This is probably your first time doing stuff like this...
so I'll take it slow for you.
It's not my first time.
You've done this?
Well, if "stuff like this" means dating.
But...
you said...
you had my eraser for 10 years.
I had the eraser, but dating is a different story.
Oh, right.
Of course, we're all grown-ups.
- How many times? - Aren't you going?
I'll go. I'm going.
For how long?
What's the longest time you've dated a guy?
Good night.
- Go. Come on. - But...
- You should go. - Well, okay.
Good... Good night.
Bye.
You're drinking coffee again?
Since you'll turn into a cat if you fall asleep?
Oh.
I learned this.
Watch carefully.
Guess what this is.
- A spoon? - No, watch carefully.
See?
- I got it. - You do?
A mushroom.
It's a cat.
Thank you.
Then did you...
see me picking my nose and stuff?
Sometimes when I eat,
I even unbuckle my belt. Did you see that too?
I even danced at night when I was feeling full.
You saw that too?
- You call that dancing? - Hey!
Gosh, I can't believe it. You know everything about me.
Is there anything else? Something I don't know?
There's one more thing you don't know yet.
There's nothing to fear anymore. What is it?
I'm a cat.
I know that.
So...
I will die before you do.
A cat's time goes faster than a human's.
Are you saying you only live...
for the lifespan of a cat?
Even so,
you turn human, so...
You remember me from last winter.
I grew this much in a year.
How do you think I'll look in a few years?
Then...
One day,
I'll disappear first.
No.
Even if that's so,
that's in the far future. Why talk about parting already?
I'll stay by your side.
Even if the end is decided, I'm going to go down this road.
Because nothing is sure about how this road is going to turn out.
If there's anything I can do for you,
I'll do it until the end.
That's my choice.
Your choice...
is up to you.
You're saying to me...
what I said to you.
Hey, hey.
Did you scald your hand?
I'm fine.
What did you do all night to be so out of it?
I told Sol Ah that...
I'll disappear first.
I think...
I'll need to stay with you again.
I'm out of antihistamines.
Don't drink so much coffee.
And get some sleep.
I'm fine.
Good morning.
Sol Ah.
We got the pet food project back.
What? How?
The client wanted you back on board.
Oh, really?
Isn't it great?
Who can complain if the client wants us?
Don't overreact.
It's all for the better.
I only took it on because Ms. Park told me to.
You three. Come see me.
Do you think you won?
No.
That's right. You didn't.
It wasn't because you're good.
It's because the client thought you were easier to push around.
They were used to you. That's it.
But...
that isn't how I felt.
I'll say this just in case you misunderstood.
I really did like you, Ji Eun.
I also felt sorry for how she seemed so alone, like a lone island.
Favors have a way of bringing people closer.
Personal favors make a relationship personal.
We sometimes ate and had tea together.
I thought we were friends.
I guess it was one-sided on my part.
How sad.
Wait.
Here you go.
What is it?
I wanted to finish it for you.
My goodness.
I'm a great judge of character.
Do you want something sweet to drink?
No.
Shall I order some cake?
Not that.
Shall we go out and eat?
Pay me.
Not tea and not food.
I want you...
to pay me for my work.
What?
I thought...
we were close enough to say this.
See?
I got you right.
It's no fun if you're just obedient.
Okay. Business is business.
How much do you want?
Will this do?
I checked the going rate.
Hey, give me a discount. We're close.
Who is it for?
Your father?
Yes.
I'm visiting him.
Watch the cafe for me.
You have a visitor.
You can take coffee orders.
This one's here for you.
Where's Sergei?
- Why? - I want him back.
Why now?
Your in-laws don't want him.
My friend runs a cat cafe.
He's my gift.
I can't go.
What?
He belongs to someone else now.
He was mine.
Give him back.
Where is he now? Where is he?
Who has him?
Where is Sergei?
Sergei?
Sergei.
Sergei, it's me.
Where are you hiding?
Sergei? Sergei.
What? He was here all along.
He's only here for a while for a few reasons.
Did the person give him up?
Sergei.
Come here. It's me. Come here.
You're old already?
You were small and cute as a kitten.
I feel bad for giving him away.
- Who would want him? - Me.
It's my cat.
And it's Hong Jo, not Sergei.
What a weird name.
Thank you for abandoning Hong Jo.
He might have been smaller and cuter then,
but other than that short period that was less than a year,
thanks for letting him spend the rest of his time with me.
That time is so precious that...
I'll cherish every second of it.
I'll stay with Hong Jo and he will stay with me.
That's what we chose to do.
So don't feel bad.
Did what she say make you that sad?
Should I get jealous about a previous owner, not a girlfriend?
How funny.
She has Sergei?
Isn't that her excuse to check on you?
I'm checking on her.
You are? Why?
Because she'll need me.
Even more so now.
You said you became human to hug me.
I think this is the perfect time for that.
Are you embarrassed that I'm looking?
Shall I not look?
Hong Jo.
Why won't you change?
Is it because...
you can't change?
(Meow, the Secret Boy)
I think I borrowed too much time.
It's not easy, staying with her like a human being.
I have you. That's enough.
I keep wanting more. To be with her more.
They saw my webtoon.
A human has human affairs.
It's sad how I can't be part of that happiness.
Why are you out here?
I told you to wait at home.
Why are you like this?
Can't you look at me, even for just a while?