(Episode 21)
He looks fine.
That can't be.
Can you take a closer look?
Did he show any particular symptoms?
Like vomiting, diarrhea,
or loss of appetite.
Then why are you here?
He won't change.
(Cats have nine lives.
Three lives to have fun,)
(3 lives to wander around,
and 3 lives to stay)
Get some rest.
I'll get you some warm milk.
Hey.
You startled me.
What happened?
Why didn't you change?
I was sleepy.
What?
Gosh, I was worried.
Are you okay now?
I slept well last night,
so I'm okay.
Are you really okay? Let me see.
Are you sure you're not sick?
I'm really okay.
Let's go outside.
The weather is nice.
No.
Let's just rest today.
You said time is precious.
Do you want me to just sleep?
I thought you were going to make
every second count.
Where should we go?
There's...
actually a place I want to go
with you.
Don't look yet.
Why not? What is it?
Here.
Okay, ready? 1, 2,
three.
Where are we?
The sea.
But it doesn't look like a peach.
It's warm, isn't it?
Hey, is that human a fish?
Is he like me?
No, he's wearing an oxygen tank.
That's how he's able
to swim underwater?
To me, my oxygen tank is...
Me?
- Coffee?
- Hey.
Do you like it?
Yes.
But we came here because of me.
What about you?
I'm with you.
That's all that matters.
But still, don't you
want to go anywhere?
There actually is a place.
This is...
- Let's go inside.
- What?
Gosh, they're so pretty.
What do you think about this one?
It's okay.
I know, right?
It's not too bad. Here.
Okay.
It suits you well.
I don't own anything.
That's why I want to get it for you
as a gift.
Nothing is yours. You always
borrow things from others.
This is yours now.
And this one is mine.
Let's get one as a couple.
It's fun.
- No.
- What?
Eat this.
Hey, scoot over.
- Why?
- Come on. Scoot over.
No.
Hey!
What? What do you mean?
Me too.
It's not too bad, right?
This isn't alcohol.
It tastes like cream.
- Do you want another glass?
- Yes.
Wait. Let's drink
once the others get here.
What? Who's coming?
I invited them. Hey, guys.
Mom. Dad.
Yes?
- Hello.
- Hey, Jae Seon.
My goodness, Bang Guk Bong.
Hey, you traitor.
I heard you quit working here
and got a job at Jae Seon's cafe.
He blackmailed me,
so I didn't have a choice.
- What are you saying?
- Okay, everyone.
If you're done saying hi,
let's all sit down.
I have an important
announcement to make.
Gosh, this isn't enough food.
- What are you talking about?
- Today, I'm sitting with...
the woman I like.
- What?
- What did you say?
Are you serious?
Yes.
And she is...
Sol Ah, is it you?
What?
It must be Sol Ah.
- No...
- Listen.
Did you guys think this through?
You need to be careful...
before you start a relationship
if you don't want to mess it up.
- What are you talking about?
- Let me talk.
Can you guys believe this?
Can you? I mean, come on.
We're talking about
Ko Doo Sik and Kim Sol Ah.
- Seriously.
- I know.
You guys make such a great couple.
- Right?
- My goodness, you're unbelievable.
Dad, that's not what I meant to say.
You didn't need to make
such a big fuss about this.
Sol Ah, thank you.
Thank you.
No, you got it all wrong.
Mom, listen to me.
You've known each other for ages,
but cheers to a new start.
- Here.
- Cheers.
It's Eun Ji Eun.
What?
Ji Eun is the woman...
I have feelings for.
Oh, it's not... It's not Sol Ah?
No, I'm seeing someone else.
You have a boyfriend?
Who? Who is that punk?
Why are you guys focused on her?
You should be focused on Ji Eun.
Don't you want to know
more about her?
She has so many good traits.
She shoots guns really well,
and she makes the best
soju and beer cocktail.
She shoots well and makes the best
soju and beer cocktail?
And she's very sincere
with her work.
She cares about all her drawings...
even if they're on a leaflet.
And...
she's pretty.
She's pretty.
Yes, she's pretty.
- She really is.
- Yes, I agree with that one.
Hello?
Yes, I'm Kim Sol Ah.
It's not easy, is it?
What's not easy?
Pardon?
To stay beside her
like a normal person.
There are things that humans do.
We introduce the people we date
to our friends and family,
seek their acknowledgement,
and also get married.
It's a very natural process
for humans.
But Sol Ah won't
be able to do that.
Because of me.
I'm not saying this to hurt you.
It's not like
you didn't know any of this.
What should I do?
What's going on?
I have no idea.
She saw my webtoon.
Who?
The person who manages
the portal webtoon page.
She asked if I'd like to add some
stuff to my story and drawings...
and that they might publish
my webtoon online officially.
That's great.
I can't believe this.
Do you think I'll do well?
What if I don't do a good job?
You'll do great.
I know you'll do a good job.
This is all thanks to you.
You made this happen.
You're the one who drew them.
I'm so proud of you.
Thanks.
Hong Jo, I'll see you later.
Sol Ah, take your coffee.
She left.
- My coffee!
- Here.
Thanks. I'll see you.
- Bye.
My bag!
- Your bag? Where is it?
- My bag.
- Over there. Hurry.
- Okay, your bag.
Here.
- Did you forget anything else?
- No, I'm all set.
- I'll see you. Bye.
- See you.
- My lips!
- Chapstick?
- My lips.
- Didn't you apply it?
Why aren't you
wearing the bag I got you?
We got it as a couple.
- I'll wear the bag.
- I'll be off now.
That bag looks new.
I got matching bags.
Don't you need a girlfriend
to get matching bags?
Where is your girlfriend?
She took her bag and went to work.
What about you?
Don't you have anywhere to go?
No.
The bag is empty.
I don't own anything.
My grandma also got me a bag...
because I'll be
going to school soon.
But it's really heavy.
I carry around a notice book,
journal, and pencil case.
And inside my pencil case,
there's an eraser...
and three pencils.
I envy you.
You have a lot of stuff in your bag.
And you have
somewhere to go every day.
I envy you.
You have nothing in your bag.
And you get to go wherever you want.
I want to stay.
I want to be so heavy
so I won't be able to go anywhere.
Dae Sung, can you
run an errand for me?
Okay, Grandma.
Yes, I'm going to stay by her side.
I told her everything.
But she still accepted me.
What?
What do you mean?
Are you serious?
- Hey, it's a cat.
- Can you hold this for me?
Hello? Yes, I'll be right there.
Okay, bye.
- Where is the cat?
- Over there sitting on the bench.
That's weird.
I'm sure it was a cat.
She was right.
He's really a cat.
I'd say he's as cute as a cat.
The cute guy is walking toward us.
Can I have one?
What?
Can I have a cup of coffee?
Here. We got more than enough.
Thank you.
Would you like this as well?
Hey.
What? Do you have something to say?
What is it? What is it about?
No, not you.
Then is it for me?
What?
Well...
Oh, right.
Can you take this to Ms. Park
and ask her if it's okay?
- This?
- Yes.
- I saw it happening.
- What did you see?
I saw him turn into a cat.
When?
Wait.
- He's still outside.
- The guy who asked us for coffee?
The guy who asked you for coffee?
Some guy used his handsome face...
to ask us for coffee.
His eyes were sparkling...
as he asked us for a cup of coffee.
Are you sure he wasn't a weirdo?
Did you give him one?
You should've seen his eyes.
I couldn't ignore him.
Why is he still there?
- I wonder if he's a beggar.
- Sol Ah.
Do you know him?
- Yes.
- Really? Who is it?
Well...
I'll be right back.
Hong Jo.
Sol Ah.
What are you doing here?
I came to see you.
- You should've waited at home.
- I wanted to see you faster...
so we could be together for longer.
You're unbelievable.
Sol Ah, you see...
I can't believe
you asked a stranger for coffee.
They were my seniors at work.
Sorry.
Wait for me at home.
I still have a lot of work left.
Okay, I know humans have jobs.
Okay, don't worry.
I also have something to do.
What are you doing here?
Today's my day off.
I need to work on something.
I need to ask you for a favor.
Will you give me some space?
Teach me how.
Hey.
Wait.
I told you not to hold it like this.
Give me that.
You need to hold it with
these two fingers and keep it fixed.
"Puss in Boots"
taught the wrong thing to cats.
Hey.
Do you think you can get
anything you want...
if you just look at me
with those sparkly eyes?
Why do you want to learn this
all of a sudden?
Teach me how to engrave
Sol Ah's name on wood.
Do you want to spend time
with Sol Ah and the guys again?
(Not really.)
Not really.
(It was fun.)
It was fun. Let's invite
the others to dinner.
You're so tactless.
(You said...)
Darn it.
You said you liked me
because I'm tactless.
Yes, that's how it is.
The reason you fell in love
becomes the reason you break up.
But already?
Doo Sik.
You're talking about love
during work hours?
You really are so tactless.
Ji Eun.
Will you think about others too?
What did I do?
- Forget it.
- What?
That I told my parents about you?
Should I have deceived them?
Is that not tactless?
You didn't warn me in advance.
I even asked you not to tell anyone.
What can I do when
I want to brag to everyone?
Think about the others too.
Did you have to do that
in front of him and Sol Ah?
Who?
Bang Guk Bong? What about him?
Whatever.
I know about them too.
That it's a tough relationship.
You knew as well?
So I invited them on purpose.
So they wouldn't have to hide.
It's not a crime.
They aren't related by blood
and it's legally okay as well.
Do you think I don't think at all?
Before telling Mom and Dad about us,
I thought about it long and hard.
However hard I thought,
there was only one conclusion.
That Mom and Dad would like you.
Why should you
feel bad about liking me?
If you knew how much
I like you, you'd get so arrogant.
How can I show you how I feel?
Should I kiss you?
No?
Is it not that kind of mood?
Am I being tactless...
You're tall.
You acted cute to make me teach you,
and you're bored already?
It looked fascinating,
but it's not fun.
Like you.
Human business
isn't as easy as it seems.
Is Sol Ah working late again?
- This is nice.
- This one.
- That too.
- Which one?
What do you think?
There are many kinds of cats.
- Won't this work?
- This and this?
Put that higher.
(Gosh...)
Hong Jo, I'm off to work!
Just a moment.
I'll walk you.
What for? It's cold out.
Stay indoors where it's warm.
(Why would I eat alone?
You're so mean.)
Do you want some coffee?
You were right.
Caffeine really does
bring your time forward.
I rarely say what isn't
right or true.
I think I sped up my time too much.
What do you mean?
I'm just saying you were right.
That it wouldn't be easy
being around Sol Ah as a human.
That was right too.
The man who collected cats.
I don't want to become like him,
but I keep wanting more.
I want to be with her.
I want Sol Ah to do well,
and I thought I'd be happy
if she were happy.
I feel sad that I don't think
I'm part of her happiness.
That's what
being with someone is like.
You shut each other in or out,
and sometimes become alone.
Is this what you feared?
I get it now that it happened to me.
It must've been hard being a human.
But I guess...
you managed pretty well, Jae Seon.
Stop being cheeky
and finish what you're doing.
I won't see you for a while now.
I'll spend some time at home.
Is your father not doing well?
It's only for a few days.
Don't get too excited that
no one will be watching you.
(Nalsaem Design)
The cat from last time.
Look, there's a cat on the bench.
I wasn't mistaken.
Why do you keep talking about a cat?
Hey. The coffee beggar is back.
Wow, that's really weird.
There was definitely a cat there.
Last time too.
Are you okay?
What do you mean?
Are you sick?
What if like last time...
It's not like that.
The sun was nice and warm.
You dressed up today.
You wore something pretty.
Are you sitting here
to seduce someone?
I have something for you.
It won't take long.
Drink your coffee and wait.
I get off work early today.
Okay.
- Ms. Park, I...
- Any evening plans?
- I was...
- If you do, cancel it.
The client asked for
an emergency meeting.
The project's almost done,
so don't mess up at the last minute.
All three of you must be there.
- But I...
- Okay.
Okay.
- Hello?
- Hey, Hong Jo.
I'm sorry. Something urgent came up.
You should wait for me at home.
I'll be there as soon as I'm done.
Okay, don't worry about me
and get back to work.
Bye.
We did some market research
about your target customers.
Here are some materials
you can look at for reference.
(Hong Jo)
Instead of using
expensive packaging,
we should keep it simple
and comfortable to look at.
And I think it'll be better
to let people see the origin.
I'm working.
We switched the design and color
to a much simpler one...
just like what you asked us to do
over the phone.
And like we told you earlier,
we tried to make it brighter.
- Well done.
- Thank you.
Welcome back.
Why are you here?
It's dark out and it's raining.
Hey, you...
You're so cold.
How long were you in the rain?
Sol Ah, I have...
I told you to wait at home.
Why are you like this?
I was thinking of you.
You come to my workplace
and get rained on.
How is that thinking of me?
Aren't you acting out
to get noticed?
I just...
Yes.
Even then, if that's what it takes,
can't you focus on me?
Yes, I know I haven't been
the same these days.
I'm sorry. But later on...
Later when?
I don't have the time.
Yes.
A cat only lives for the day.
That's how we spent time together.
Like a cat.
Focusing just on that very day.
I'm not doing this for my sake.
It's about us. I drew us.
More people will read it
if it becomes a regular webtoon.
I want more people to see it,
and I don't want them to
ridicule me.
I want to make them smile.
Like you made me smile.
But I don't want...
people to think
I put work second to my webtoon.
I didn't mean to disturb you.
You're...
It's too hard for me
if you're always waiting for me.
You said you have
something to do as well.
Give me a little time.
So, what I mean is...
Don't wait for me.
Are you serious?
The time I can spend as a human...
is predestined?
Waiting is what a cat does.
And you don't want me to
do that too?
You're getting wet.
I'll use my own umbrella.
What I could do for you.
What I couldn't do for you.
I wanted to do it all.
You're doing fine right now.
It's more than enough.
You'll catch a cold.
Let's hurry home.
Dad. Are you all right?
I'm fine.
I'm just dying.
You may be...
the owner of a small cafe
and workshop,
but you're a mess.
Do you want money to buy clothes?
No, it's fine.
Dad.
Here.
Take it.
I even took in that old cat for you.
Is there anywhere you want to go?
No.
Anything you want to eat then?
There's nowhere I haven't been...
and nothing I haven't eaten.
Everything I wanted, I had or did.
The one thing
I thought I didn't have...
came to me at the last minute.
But...
even I...
can't control or keep time.
This thing called time.
It never waits for you.
Hong Jo.
I'm sorry.
Give me a little time.
- Great job!
- Well done, guys.
You know what? I'm talking here.
Seeing you three work together...
- made me so anxious.
- Ms. Park.
- Thanks.
- But then,
you pulled it off and I'm glad.
The three of them
get along pretty well.
- Right?
- Yes.
- Well done.
- It's all because...
- you're a great leader, Ms. Park!
- Yes.
That's right.
- Thank you.
- Eat all you want.
- Let's eat.
- Well done.
- Okay.
- Thank you.
How's your other project going?
- I have a lot of experience.
- See, dating...
Have you heard from
the webtoon person?
No.
- I thought they'd call this week.
- By the way...
I guess it's not happening.
(Sonamu)
Hey. It's me.
Hong Jo.
Hey. Hong Jo.
Guess what?
Cats don't show they're sick
even when they are.
- For fear of abandonment.
- Really?
My wife doesn't tell me
if she's sick too.
When I'm busy, I pretend
not to notice even though I do.
Can't she get sick on my schedule?
- You're so mean.
- That's wrong.
- You're nasty.
- That's terrible.
What happened?
A broken mirror's a bad omen.
- Are you okay?
- Yes.
- No, I'll do it.
- It's okay.
- Answer your phone.
- What?
Oh, okay.
Hello?
Hong Jo!
I...
I... I made it.
- They'll run your webtoon?
- Yes!
Sol Ah!
Congratulations. I'm so happy!
What did I say?
I said they'd like it!
You said yes yesterday.
- Come on, Dad.
- Darn it.
Okay, fine.
Hide it before your mom comes home.
- Drive safely.
- I will.
This is so heavy.
What's this?
Rice cakes. Take it with you.
Sol Ah will officially debut
as a webtoon artist.
We should congratulate her.
Gosh, my back hurts.
I need to see a Chinese doctor.
Give me a ride.
What?
- What now?
- I don't know.
- Shoot.
- What's this?
What's going on that made you
swivel your eyeballs so fast?
Well...
- Be careful.
- My gosh.
This is really heavy.
I told you to be careful.
Don't you think
you need the car to take this?
- Yes, I do.
- I carried it back from the market.
He can walk.
You should've taken a taxi.
What are you saying?
- Hello.
- Hi there.
- I'm...
- Hey!
Take the rice cakes
and the car, quick.
- Come on out.
- Yes, we must go.
Hey.
Bye.
- Thanks, Mom, Dad.
- Sure.
- See you.
- Bye.
- Congratulate Sol Ah for me.
- Okay.
- Go on.
- Go.
I'm so worried for them.
Don't worry about our son.
Who said I'm worried about him?
She seems to be a sensitive soul.
I'm worried that...
the thick-skulled fool
will hurt her.
Good for you. You are the best.
You're so thoughtful.
And what? You make me
look like a small-minded witch?
Am I someone who shoots daggers
at every girlfriend of my son?
Why do you keep me out?
Why do you keep me out of things?
My goodness.
Who would call you old-fashioned?
You're so sophisticated.
Where are you hurting? Here?
Don't you touch me.
I'll go to an acupuncturist.
Yes, acupuncture's good.
Here, was it?
- I'll give you a massage.
- My gosh.
- Look. Why is he coming back?
- What's wrong?
Did he forget something?
- What is it?
- Well...
This is for you.
(Devoted Mr. Gogalbi)
What's this?
I heard that you wanted to
change your sign.
I gave it a go.
You drew this yourself?
- My goodness!
- What?
I like the current sign
that Doo Sik drew...
I still am not used to
the current sign.
It gives me the chills
whenever I look at it.
- It's all bones.
- Right?
It looks terrifying!
Look at this.
The eyes look so fresh and lively.
- Gosh.
- They glisten.
This mackerel could
jump off the page.
Thank you.
I'm glad you like it.
What I like the most...
is well-boiled bracken, you see.
When you cook bracken with mackerel,
it becomes so soft and tender.
It's just delicious.
- It's delicious.
- Yes, it is.
Bracken and mackerel are
a match made in paradise.
- Right. A perfect match.
- Yes.
That's right. They suit each other.
Lovely.
Hey, let's just have a few beers.
We don't have to throw a party.
You are too extreme.
We don't need balloons.
Ji Eun. I think all the red balloons
are grouped together.
- These?
- Yes. Spread them out.
Move them this way.
Yes, that's it. Great.
We really don't need balloons, guys.
You're too crazy.
Breathe this in.
Guys.
Me too.
I want some coffee.
(Sonamu)
Come out. I know you're there.
What do you want?
Where's the cat?
I've been watching.
I haven't seen the cat.
It's none of your business.
I want to check something.
I think...
I saw something.
Does that girl know that...
I saw?
Shall I go and ask her?
Don't touch Sol Ah.
Her occupation.
Did you say she was a designer?
Darn.
Watch out, here.
- Congratulations.
- Congratulations!
- Thank you.
Shouldn't you give us an autograph?
You didn't have to do this for me.
Thank you all for coming
such a long way.
Also, thanks to you two for always
drawing with me all this time.
And I'm always thankful to you too.
But...
where is the person
I'm most thankful to?
Oh. Please excuse me.
Doo Sik, you spattered it
all over my face.
Why don't we sit down and eat?
What are you doing here?
You look like a dog
protecting a house.
Why did you come outside? Everyone
is here to congratulate you.
Aren't you going to congratulate me?
That hug you gave me last time,
was that all?
You didn't even bring a flower?
All you can do with your hands
is hug me?
Congratulations.
What is...
I was just joking.
Did you make this yourself?
You can put your phone in there.
Since you forget it all the time.
It was okay since
you always took care of me.
If I can't use my hands anymore...
What?
I just meant your clumsiness
is getting way out of hand.
Gosh.
Oh, you said you had something
to give me last time.
This is what it was.
You said you had something to do.
You were thinking about me
all the time.
I told you waiting
is what a cat does.
Go on inside.
I'll be waiting here.
Come with me.
Last time when I drank
with Jae Seon...
Ji Eun, this tastes great.
Hey, where were you?
Wait, it's the coffee beggar.
- Beggar?
- I don't know.
Hold on, what is going on
between you two?
- Is he your boyfriend?
- I have something to ask.
Did you see a cat on the bench
near our company?
Stop saying that.
I'm certain I saw a white cat
sleeping on the bench.
But when I looked again,
it was you. It happened twice.
By any chance, are you a cat?
He does kind of look like a cat.
Wait, Sol Ah looks like a dog.
Gosh, you two
don't look good together.
Sol Ah, it must be tough for you
to go out with a cat.
I have to make money for my kid's
diapers and dry milk,
but you have to make money
for cat litter and food.
He turns into a human,
so he'll probably be able to make
money for his litter and food.
What is your job?
I don't have a job.
Oh, I know why.
That's understandable
since he looks young.
How old are you?
One.
So you really are a cat.
Right.
What's with this mood?
Bang Guk Bong is a bit strange.
That's his charm.
What did you just say?
His name is...
Did you just say "Bang Guk Bong"?
I didn't hear wrong, did I?
What a unique name.
You must've been teased a lot
when you were young.
"Bang Guk Bong, Bang Guk Bong."
He's not Bang Guk Bong.
He's Hong Jo.
Hong Jo?
Why are you calling him Hong Jo?
Hong Jo is...
Wait.
Who was it?
I heard that name a lot somewhere.
Did you change your name?
Let me introduce him.
He was the first to recognize
my drawings.
He liked them...
and helped me to continue to draw.
He's the one I feel
the most thankful to.
And he's the person I love.
How romantic.
- Shall we say cheers?
- Yes.
Let's get up.
Sol Ah, congratulations!
- Thank you!
- Congratulations!
You two look so good together.
I envy you.
Why aren't you drinking?
I have to drive later.
Your webtoon is so fun.
Really? Thank you.
I'm really enjoying it.
I still have a long way to go.
How long have you been going out?
We've been...
- I envy you. I'm so jealous.
- Me too.
Oh, the cake. Hong Jo.
There's a cake inside.
Can you go bring it?
Oh, okay.
He's charming.
I agree with you.
Shall I go with you?
No need, it's just a cake.
Okay.
How's your father doing?
He's feeling much better.
The doctors at the hospital
are even surprised.
I'm glad.
I guess he feels better
since you're beside him now.
Thanks to him.
Are you going somewhere?
We're going to the East Sea
to see the sunrise.
Jeongdongjin?
There's a place in front of
a bed and breakfast in Jeongdongjin.
- It's the perfect spot.
- Really?
But if you go now, it will be hard
for you to find a spot.
You have to hurry
since there are so many people.
How do I go?
Oh, I know.
- You do?
- Yes.
- We better get going.
- What?
We're going to the East Sea
to see the sunrise.
You should stay a bit more.
We can't see it if we don't go now.
- Let's go.
- Hey.
- See you.
- Be careful.
- Congratulations.
- Thanks.
Drive carefully.
- Goodness.
- He's in such a hurry.
- I envy them.
- Me too.
Hong Jo.
What happened?
Everyone's waiting.
Don't tell me...
you can't turn back into a human.
Why isn't he coming out?
I told you, he's a cat.
He likes to hide in a corner
when there are strangers around.
I'm sorry, but something urgent
came up.
Sol Ah, is that...
Don't come out. Just stay with them.
I'm sorry. You can continue
with the party without me.
- But...
- Okay, bye.
What are you doing here?
Is that...
a cat?
Move.
Wait.
Can you show me for a second?
Hong Jo is sick.
He needs to go to the vet. Move.
I...
lost all my cats...
because of you people.
Mister.
You're not in your right mind
right now.
That's what everyone says.
All I did was love my cats,
but they say my love...
is an illness.
I...
really saw that cat turn into
a person. I'm sure I saw it.
But no one believes me.
They all think I'm mad.
That's why...
I will prove it.
That I'm not crazy.
Transform.
- Transform.
- No!
- Stop, Mister!
- Transform.
Transform.
- Turn into a human.
- Mister!
Transform. Transform.
Will you change now?
Transform!
(Welcome)
- I wanted to hug you.
- You don't have to be human.
Do you want me to stay a cat?
Is turning into a human
making him sick?
Sol Ah has to live like a human,
but she sleeps all day like a cat.
Can you not change?
The time I can spend as a human
is getting shorter and shorter.
Stay close to me.
Is it too late?
He's mostly a cat these days.
This will be the last time.
You said you'd be human around me.
I'll stay with you.