(Episode 15)
Hong Jo, it was you, wasn't it?
I told you...
that I wanted...
to get more intimate with Bang Guk Bong.
But the thing is,
Bang Guk Bong actually...
kissed me...
all of a sudden.
What am I going to do now?
It was you, wasn't it? You told him, didn't you?
What are we going to do?
Gosh, I'm in so much trouble.
Do you know what's even worse?
I want to...
I want to do it again.
I should tell her.
Wait. Am I being jealous right now?
It's for Sol Ah.
I'm pathetic.
I can't believe I'm jealous.
But I still need to tell her.
Why are you coming out?
It's a bit early to come unannounced like this.
Sol Ah and I are close enough to do that.
But you can't just wake her up...
I've done that a lot of times.
We used to eat sweet red bean porridge and go to school together.
Sol Ah doesn't like porridge.
She apparently doesn't like the texture.
She eats sweet red bean porridge.
She likes the small rice cakes that are inside them.
Not anymore.
She once got sick because of those small rice cakes.
Oh, right.
Sol Ah tends to get an upset stomach when she eats rice cakes.
She was fine after she ate the tteokbokki I got for her.
I bet you don't know where her favorite park is...
and what her favorite bench is.
I bet you don't know her sleeping habits.
Do you know which side she sleeps on?
Her left side?
She lies on her back.
You can come back later.
What's the use of knowing all that?
Sol Ah doesn't know who you are.
You just hide...
and watch her from behind.
So you can't exactly say you really know her.
What's going on?
Sol Ah.
Do you really...
Do you really sleep with Hong Jo?
He always snuggles underneath the sheets.
You have no idea how much he moves around at night.
But why do you ask?
It's nothing.
I was wondering when you're going to neuter him.
I'm not sure.
He does need to get neutered.
But...
did you come here to ask me that?
Yes, there's an animal hospital nearby...
Let's go inside.
- Get lost! - You should do it right away.
Hey, calm down.
Let's go.
("Cats exist so they could teach us this one thing about life.")
("If we can completely immerse ourselves to a moment,")
("it can turn into an eternity .")
(Quote by Jeffrey Moussaieff Masson)
Sol Ah, eat breakfast before you go.
I also made coffee.
No, it's okay.
- Don't you feel well? - I'm fine.
Then what is it?
Why do you keep...
Why won't you look at me?
I'm too embarrassed to look at you.
I mean...
Forget about what other people might think.
But we still need to think about our parents.
They only just started living together.
Listen to what I have to say.
- I should go. - Wait.
I need to tell you something. It's important.
I'm... I'm late!
Then I'll wait for you. Let's talk once you're done.
I'm going to tell her...
who I really am.
I want to show her my true identity.
Will that be okay?
That way, we'll truly be able to like each other.
No way. Is it really you?
A long time ago,
I also fell in love just like you.
That's him.
Baek Gu.
I liked this song too.
I see.
Thank you.
What happened?
I grew old first.
At one time, we loved each other so much that...
we only had eyes for each other.
Now I have grown old and wrinkly,
and he doesn't even recognize me.
What?
A cat's time goes by much quicker than a human's.
What do you mean?
You will grow old first.
And in the end, you will die first.
Leaving that person alone.
Sol Ah...
will be left alone?
So don't let her find out what you really are.
Just stay by her side...
as a silent, wordless cat.
If you want to...
at least stay close to your loved one like me,
you must never tell her, okay?
A cat's time is fleeting.
Love, even more so.
Isn't it nice?
Sing it.
- I like this part. - Me too.
- What? - Tada.
What's this?
A cat that can't do anything without Sol Ah.
I feel helpless about that fact already.
But there's one more.
A cat's most dreadful limit.
Our lives are shorter than a human's.
What should I do?
I wanted to tell Sol Ah everything.
Don't tell her.
Don't say anything...
and leave.
Leave?
You will die first anyway,
and Sol Ah will be left alone.
The end has been decided.
I know how it feels...
to be left alone.
It feels like you're sinking...
into a bottomless pool.
Do you want Sol Ah to feel that?
Is leaving her now...
the best I can do for her?
You won't want her to see you...
grow old.
It'll be a burden to her.
Is this how it's meant to be?
I'll be leaving her without a word too.
Just like you did.
Not again.
Welcome home.
Why are you up there?
Will you come up?
You said you wanted to talk. Shall we talk up there?
That place is a bit...
It's a bit weird.
Okay. Give me a few minutes.
I guess...
it's nice and quiet, perfect for a chat.
Shall we sit?
My gosh!
Why is your heart beating so fast?
Is it?
Does my time go faster...
because my heart beats faster?
What do you mean?
Did you drink too much coffee?
Does your heart beat slower than mine?
What?
What are you doing?
Forget it.
Is this why you wanted me to join you up here?
Just tell me what you wanted to say.
What did you...
want to say?
Just one more day.
What?
Let's stay together just one more day.
That means...
I'll stay only until today.
What about after today?
What happens tomorrow?
I have to go on a trip.
Where to?
Bolivia.
The Uyuni salt flats.
Really?
I'm sorry.
It's for real.
You're leaving.
The Uyuni salt flats.
Why does it have to be there?
Because it's furthest away from me?
How did we end up being family?
Yes.
Family does come first.
But...
do you have to go halfway around the world?
And do you have to leave tomorrow?
That's why...
I want to be with you...
today.
Okay.
Today is almost over though.
We aren't that high up,
but I see things I couldn't before.
So this is what Hong Jo saw.
What are you drawing?
Today.
What are you looking at?
The cat...
Is it me?
Who says it's you?
It's my muse, Hong Jo.
What happens after this?
Why didn't you keep drawing?
I don't know.
I'm suddenly out of ideas.
But...
I'm never going to draw the two of them kissing.
A kiss was powerful enough to bring Snow White back to life...
and turn a frog into a prince. But whenever I kiss,
I suddenly become all alone.
It's funny, isn't it?
You're going to...
continue drawing, right?
I'm going to miss it.
I'm going to miss you too.
Goodbye.
Would you like a drink?
Thanks.
I told her I'm going to leave.
I thought I'd be able to be with her forever...
as long as I drank coffee.
If you drink coffee to stay awake,
you eventually become really exhausted.
Drinking caffeine...
is like borrowing time from your future.
Do you get it?
The more time I borrow now, the less future I'll have later on.
Living without Sol Ah...
will be meaningless anyway.
What if I stay here...
for a bit longer?
Do you want some more coffee?
Why don't we go out and get something to eat?
- Sol Ah. - Yes?
You'll tire yourself out if you keep overworking like this.
Let's just call it a day.
You guys can go home without me.
Will you be okay by yourself?
There are two possible reasons why she's acting like this.
She either really enjoys her work or she doesn't want to go home.
Whenever we got our report card, you stayed in the art room...
and drew until really late.
Good luck.
Why is she so obsessed with work?
I personally think it's boring.
And who named the company "Nalsaem"?
It's no wonder why we always work until late.
Don't you agree?
Can you at least respond?
"To stay up all night" isn't the only meaning "Nalsaem" has.
It also means "To soar up into the sky".
That's what our company's name means.
Well, when is that going to happen?
Every day is the same. It's so repetitive.
That's what I actually like about this company.
I always have something to draw...
every single day.
Do you like every drawing you've done at the company?
Don't you want to draw your own drawings?
Well, some people are passionate to do something big.
But some people prefer to do things...
little by little every single day.
I'm more like the latter.
You speak very eloquently.
You make me feel embarrassed for complaining.
Can you walk faster?
I know you find me uncomfortable, so I'll just stay behind you.
That makes me feel even more uncomfortable.
I prefer it here.
Since I got you talking, why don't you talk a bit more?
What's your relationship with Ms. Park?
Does she have something on you or something?
He's probably gone by now.
(Uyuni Salt Flat)
What are you doing?
Sol Ah isn't home yet.
I'm worried if she's okay.
Wait inside. I'll call her.
What are you doing here?
I was worried you might not come home.
I had a lot of work to do.
Are you sure it's not because you're scared the house might be empty?
I also heard...
that he's leaving.
I bet he wouldn't feel comfortable about leaving either.
This is awkward.
I can't believe I'm talking about this with you.
What's awkward is the relationship you have with him.
You guys will only end up hurting each other.
I know.
So go home and let him leave in peace.
That way, he won't have to leave with any regrets.
What do you mean?
He hasn't left yet?
Don't be so happy about it. Don't forget you're talking to me.
This is really awkward.
- See you. - Okay, bye.
Guk Bong.
You're home.
What are you doing here?
And why did you drink so much coffee?
I've been waiting for you.
For how long?
I waited all day.
You're freezing.
Let's go. You must be cold.
Thanks.
Why are you still here?
Because I wanted to see your drawings.
The webtoon?
You can see it wherever as long as you have the internet.
I can't wait to see what happens next.
I want to be the first one to see it.
I guess I have the talent...
of making people wonder what happens next.
Draw your webtoon. I'll leave once I see it.
Okay.
But I'm too tired today.
I just came back from work.
Can I get some rest...
and just be with you until the day ends?
There's not much time left anyway.
Okay.
Just until today, okay?
(Episode 16)
Is he gone?
I couldn't draw because I had no ideas.
So let's stay together just one more day.
What?
I mean,
inspiration doesn't come suddenly.
You have to go out and meet people.
There must be input for there to be output.
Also, I feel bad for making you wait yesterday.
We only spent a little time together in the morning and evening.
That's not enough to say we were together for a day.
What's your point?
Just...
one more day.
Come somewhere with me.
Will you see this model?
Okay.
Hey. Take a look.
I'm not...
Whether you take it with you or not is up to you.
And it's up to me to give you a present.
I'll take this.
The phone's owner needs to fill this in.
Fill in all the parts I marked.
Okay.
- Go on. - Okay.
(Phone contract)
(Name)
Go on. Fill it in.
(Hong)
(Hong Jo)
Hey, are you kidding?
Actually, I...
The truth is, I'm...
Are you...actually...
So that's why.
That's why you couldn't say...
Are you...
a credit delinquent?
Me?
It's okay, you don't have to say. I'll put it in my name.
No, I'm...
It's fine. Don't thank me.
I'm only lending you my name.
Work part-time and pay the bill, okay?
Do you feel more inspired now?
No. Let's walk a little more.
I heard that walking helps.
Now, do you have an idea?
Walking like this with you...
made me hungry.
What?
Tteokbokki's the best when you need inspiration.
Then shall we...
head back and draw?
Hey. You're such a bother today.
Will you stop talking about drawing?
I was about to get inspired until you said that.
Eat more tteokbokki.
Okay.
Here.
It's tasty.
What are you taking photos of?
Why did you photograph that?
We sat here before.
How do you know that? Did you see me here before?
I didn't see it.
It's my story.
You have a fond memory at this bench too.
You would, since you lived nearby.
I first saw you somewhere around here.
Wasn't it when I fell from the roof?
I was watching you before then.
You've been watching me? Since when?
From the start.
How did I look?
It was like a dream.
What?
In the short moment when I lost track of you,
I kept having that dream.
But then...
it wasn't a dream.
It wasn't a dream.
That's called a dog's dream. Because I'm a dog-like person.
Hurry up.
Sol Ah, today...
I know.
I slept and now it's today.
What?
We agreed to spend today together.
This is another today.
If you keep putting it off like this,
Isn't it strange?
I thought tomorrow would come yesterday,
but I opened my eyes, and it's today again!
- Shall we get rid of that? - This is...
Hold on.
(Bang Guk Bong)
Today's fortune.
I think I won.
Today's coffee.
(Bang Guk Bong)
Are you still here?
If you can't leave, why don't I help you?
I could make you leave instantly.
I'll leave. I will.
- Excuse me. - Yes?
Let's go for lunch.
- I brought... - Let's go.
I already told everyone you're going.
I have some urgent work to do.
I'm sorry, next time.
Okay, don't skip your lunch.
I told you she wouldn't come.
I bet she's going to say we bullied her later.
Let's go, I'm hungry.
You know you need to revise...
the wedding invitation by this afternoon, right?
Yes, ma'am.
Okay, keep up the good work.
- Why aren't you going? - Let's go.
Is someone getting married?
My nephew.
You have a nephew who's already getting married?
My nephew's parents...
His parents are getting married again?
- Did Ms. Park make you do this? - No.
I saw everything.
I'm right, aren't I? She asked you to do it.
And it's not the first time.
No, she really didn't.
Are you finished with the wedding invitation?
Why don't we go and talk?
She's talking with me right now.
About what?
She never talks to me.
When she's our project team leader.
You shouldn't keep talking...
to someone who's silently doing her job.
Let's go talk.
She doing something that isn't even part of her job.
I mean,
her boss kept asking for personal favors,
and she kept doing it without saying a word.
She didn't even know how to refuse.
She kept being summoned during working hours,
and couldn't even eat lunch...
because she was busy writing what floor the buffet was at...
on a wedding invitation for someone she doesn't even know.
Why can't you say anything?
That's why you're being treated as a pushover.
Because you won't say anything anyway...
even if that boss asks for personal favors.
You keep quiet even when everyone bullies you...
and thinks you don't deserve to work here.
- Mr. Ko. - "No, I can't!"
"I won't!"
Just say it.
I mean, if you said no, she would've asked me to do it.
It's been my lifelong dream to design a wedding invitation.
I can even sing for free too.
Doo... Doo Sik.
- Stop following me. - Where are you going?
I don't know.
I lost my temper and just realized what I did.
I'm sorry.
You should feel sorry for yourself.
You said you liked drawing so much.
Will you call that your drawing too?
Why do you keep following me from behind?
Do you secretly stare at my butt or something?
I guess you found out.
Do you need another part-timer?
Let me work at your cafe.
Ask for your own cup.
I might get fired.
Even if I want to continue my parents' business,
you took away our part-timer.
Our sales have plummeted since then.
You can take him back. I can't stand the sight of him.
Why? What do you mean?
Because he's with Sol Ah all the time.
You can't do anything about that.
It's not like they're living together because they want to.
Sol Ah...
only looks at him.
She smiles next to him...
and chats with him...
and even falls asleep with him.
That's because they spend more time since they're living together.
Kim Sol Ah? She finally got over you?
You seem a bit excited.
Hey, honestly, it does feel satisfying.
If I think about how much Sol Ah suffered because of you.
But the guy she chose after you is Bang Guk Bong?
Are you sure? What will you do?
I'll make her stop.
Stop what? How will you do that?
No matter how weird that guy is, Sol Ah chose him.
You don't want her for yourself but don't want to give her up either?
How selfish.
It's not that.
Do you have feelings for Sol Ah?
Hey...
Hey. Is it true?
After all this time?
It's not for me, but for Sol Ah's sake.
What are you talking about?
"I will like you for your sake?"
- How pathetic. - I'll become pathetic.
Even if I become pathetic, I'll protect Sol Ah.
In this situation,
I'm the only one who can protect her.
I told you to ask for your own glass.
You ask then.
Why should I when this is my glass?
I want to drink with this glass.
Whatever.
- You can't even drink. - I will protect Sol Ah.
- Get that? - Whatever, do what you want.
What's wrong with you?
It's dark. Let's go inside.
You asked me to draw.
Aren't you cold?
I'm okay.
You asked me to draw.
Are you hurt?
- It's nothing. - Let me see.
This scar looks pretty deep.
How did this happen? When?
Come to think of it, Hong Jo hurt his front leg too.
His left leg like you.
There's something that I imagine from time to time.
I know it will sound funny,
but I think you're Hong Jo sometimes.
I mean, if I think about it,
I've never seen you holding Hong Jo.
Strangely, every time you're around,
Hong Jo never comes out and is nowhere to be seen.
Right, I thought your eyes seemed strangely similar.
And you even act like a cat.
I always felt lonely liking guys like cats,
so I wanted to meet someone who was like a dog.
But I somehow ended up falling for...
a cat-like guy again.
I'm sorry...
for being a cat.
Thank you.
For being a cat.
You said we should spend just today together.
To me, it felt like Hong Jo was saying that.
Think about tomorrow when tomorrow comes.
And just focus on today, today.
Cats are like that.
I tried living like a cat,
and every day was a great today.
Me too.
I hoped today would never end.
Then can't we...
just go on living like cats?
Waking up to a brand-new today is so fun and exciting.
Can't we just...
live for...
today?
Kim Sol Ah!
Let's talk.
What's the matter?
Kim Sol Ah.
Why did you come with her?
You shouldn't be here. Why are you still here?
You... You can go.
- Hey, wait. - Get out.
Right now.
Did you have a drink?
Get out of here.
- I'll get some water. - Okay.
Kim Sol Ah. You don't know anything.
That idiot...
can't be with you because...
is a ca...
- A ca... - Who did you drink with?
- Ko Doo Sik? - Ko Doo Sik!
That idiot is Ko Doo Sik.
What?
Why are you calling Bang Guk Bong, Ko Doo Sik?
No. I mean...
That guy isn't Bang Guk Bong.
No.
He's not even human.
You don't have to be so mean.
No, listen to me.
Okay, fine. Give me a moment.
Hello, Ms. Bang.
Yes, I can talk.
Your father's birthday is coming up.
Can you come by this weekend?
What?
I wish Guk Bong could come with you.
With Bang Guk Bong?
The truth is, we got a marriage license.
We won't have a wedding,
but I thought we should eat together as a family.
If you're not up for it, you don't have to come.
No. I should come.
Yes. I'll be there.
Bye.
What was that about?
That sounded like a parent.
Bang Guk Bong's...
mother.
Yes.
She wants us to visit together.
This is it.
Don't go any further.
Stop right here.
Before the truth comes out.
Are you going today?
To your parents?
I bought your ticket too.
I have to drop by work. Let's meet at the train station.
I can't go.
I know how it'll all end.
Because I'm me.
I'll just cause you a heartache.
Bang Guk Bong.
It looks like...
I won't get to see your drawing.
Do you have to leave?
It might not seem so now, but later as time goes by,
it'll only get worse for you.
Who knows?
Giving up now might cause more heartache later.
I might still miss you, feel bad, and have regrets about today...
no matter how much time passes by.
Every day is today,
but a today that has passed never comes back.
Sol Ah.
Didn't you say you're going to your father's?
- I am. - Take care.
Is Bang Guk Bong going too?
I don't know...
if he'll come or not.
I have to leave early today.
- Okay. - Take care.
Bye.
See you.
(KTX platform)
Hi, Sol Ah.
Hey, Jae Seon.
I'm at the train station.
I'm sorry, but can you do me a favor?
Sure.
Hong Jo will be alone at home. Can you check on him?
What about Bang Guk Bong?
I'm going with him.
You're going together?
Or maybe not.
Are you waiting for him?
Anyway, take care of Hong Jo for me.
Bang Guk Bong.
No. Hong Jo.
Are you here?
He left.
Kim Sol Ah.
Jae Seon.
Stop waiting.
He left.
I'll be with you.
What?
I put you through too much for too long.
So I don't have the right to do this,
but don't go elsewhere for comfort for what I did to you.
I'll comfort you.
- Jae Seon. - I won't leave you alone again.
I'll be there for you.
Bang Guk Bong.
- Don't mention a guy that left. - He hasn't left.
I thought about it all night.
The end is too obvious.
Should I go down that obvious path or not?
Did you finish the drawing?
The result may be obvious,
but there might be something for me on that path.
(Meow, the Secret Boy)
This cat.
It's you.
I...
like you.
I just don't think it's me to run away and hide.
I must like whoever I like.
Enough to let the whole world know.
Because I'm a helpless puppy.
It's up to you now.
What are you thinking?
This is my choice.
- I'll tell her everything. - Hey, you...
Yes, Ms. Bang. I'm at the train...
What?
Bang Guk Bong?
Attention, please.
- The 11:20 train... - I can't hear you right now.
- is pulling in. - What?
- If you have a ticket, - Bang Guk Bong...
please go to Platform 5 and wait for the train.
He's there right now?
The 11:20 train...
headed for Sancheon is pulling in.
- If you have a ticket... - That can't be.
No way.
He's right before me.
(Meow, the Secret Boy)
You're here, so it's fine, whoever you are.
You felt it too. That I'm Hong Jo.
Why doesn't she trust you?
I don't want to run away.
This is as far as you go.
- What happened? - Sol Ah, listen to me.
Since when have you known?
I shouldn't have just watched.
I can't believe that he's Hong Jo.
Love is like a miracle.
I didn't know it would be you.
I really like you.
Will you give me some time?
I want to turn it back now if I can.
What are you doing?
I should've acted instead of just thinking.