Yes, Ms. Bang.
What? Bang Guk Bong...
He's there right now?
That can't be.
No way.
He's right before me.
Where are you right now, Sol Ah?
I'm at the train station.
- But...
- I guess you're about to depart.
I'll see you later.
What?
Bang Guk Bong...
is already there.
I'm not Bang Guk Bong.
Then who are you?
The 11:20 train...
- headed for Sancheon...
- We'll miss the train at this rate.
- Will be departing soon.
- Let's get on first.
Please board the train.
- Where are you going?
- The 11:20 train...
- headed for Sancheon...
- I'm going to tell her everything.
Will be departing soon.
Please board the train.
("Poets generally love cats
because poets have no delusions...")
("about their own superiority."
Quote by Marion Garretty)
Did I not hear her correctly
because of the train?
I should call her again.
Don't.
Your mother said something weird...
The real Bang Guk Bong is
someone else.
Then who are you?
Hong Jo.
Stop joking around.
I'm not joking around.
Think about it carefully.
You felt it too. That I'm Hong Jo.
Jae Seon.
Jae Seon, how did you
get on the train?
I bought a ticket using an app.
But why...
- Where are you going?
- I was worried about you.
Why?
There's no need to be worried.
Wait. Then what about Hong Jo?
- He's home alone.
- I'm right here.
Why do you keep talking nonsense?
- Excuse me, sir.
- Okay.
Sol Ah, I'm...
You're Hong Jo?
Then I want you to turn into a cat.
Here?
Why don't you just tell me
that you can teleport?
That makes more sense.
You're here with me,
but you're also with your mom.
And you always come and go.
- Sol Ah.
- I must've misheard your mom.
You're here, so it's fine.
I don't care who you are.
Hello.
- Don't be so bothered by...
- This is nice.
Did you read the new webtoon
that Sol Ah uploaded?
What? I thought you were...
Did something happen?
Sol Ah must be
really determined this time.
She must be really focused.
Let me see.
Let me see it, too.
Sol Ah did a good job.
It's a bit different this time.
You're right. I thought she quit...
because we said we didn't like
her work last time.
You guys should take a look.
It's a lot better.
I gave her some tips
so her drawings could improve.
It looks like
she took my advice to heart.
("Welcome", Sol Ah)
Not bad.
(It's pretty.
It looks like a big peach.)
(I don't need this!)
I personally think you should write
about something else.
You've been writing about
Beodul Love for too long.
You're capable of coming up
with a different story.
Why did I say that to her?
You've traveled a lot,
so I bet this is nothing to you.
I've never seen anything like this.
It's so pretty.
I guess you haven't been
to a lot of places in Korea.
The place we're going
is near the sea.
- "The sea"?
- Yes.
I love watching the sunset
by the sea.
It reminds me of a peach.
- Do you want to go with me?
- Sure. Sounds nice.
How far are you going to go?
She won't believe me.
I want you to get off with me
at the next station.
You want me to send her there
on her own?
You promised to leave.
I don't want to run away
just because I know it'll end.
That's exactly what
you've been doing until now.
- What?
- I don't want to run away.
What if Sol Ah runs away?
Why do you think
she can't believe you?
Maybe it's because she doesn't
want to believe you.
If I get abandoned, then so be it.
I have no control over that.
But...
I won't abandon her first...
just so I could avoid
being abandoned.
I won't be like you.
Look at that.
Oh, that one?
- That's so pretty.
- What?
That will look good on you.
- Really?
- Yes.
I want to see it up close.
It's pretty.
- This looks pretty, too.
- Yes, it does.
- What are you doing?
- We're getting a birthday gift.
You're even going to meet
her parents?
Sol Ah's father has a weak heart.
I know.
Don't make things worse.
- You can't go there.
- I know.
Guk Bong, what about this?
This looks warm, doesn't it?
- I'll take this one.
- Okay.
Wait.
I also want to get him a gift.
Really?
Give me some money.
- What?
- I worked part-time. I want my pay.
- Ma'am, here you go.
- Thank you.
Jae Seon, are you sure about this?
Wouldn't it be uncomfortable?
Why? Can't I go?
You're shy around people.
I also want to celebrate
your dad's birthday.
It's been a while,
so let me say hello to your dad.
My dad is also shy around people.
I'd like some premium Korean beef.
I can't go empty-handed.
(Bus Stop)
She told me it's near the bus stop.
I wonder where it is.
Hello, can I ask you something?
You can't go any further than this.
I know.
They recently moved here from Seoul.
Oh, the married couple who are
madly in love with each other?
Do you know where they live?
Yes, I know where they live.
Keep going up this way.
Then turn right.
Then keep walking straight.
Then go...
Hey, don't ask her stuff.
- She's senile.
- My goodness.
I'm not senile.
You're the one who's senile.
My goodness.
You came just in time.
Oh, hello.
By the way,
I brought someone with me.
Who?
That handsome young man?
You brought your boyfriend.
Where's Bang Guk Bong?
Guk Bong?
Guk Bong left to take photos.
Oh, did he?
Why did he leave
without a word to me?
We should go. Get in.
Okay.
Hey, did you just see that?
A person turned into a cat.
I told you.
You are senile.
Hang on. Am I really?
You really are out of your mind.
I don't know what to do with you.
Thank you.
You're so polite.
You run a cafe?
Yes.
Drink your tea.
Do you come by often
if you live opposite?
Pardon? No, sir.
Why not?
You should look in on my daughter.
Oh. I will.
Do you still give her a hard time?
Pardon?
I didn't say anything.
This is what he's like.
He sees but pretends not to.
He knows but pretends not to.
You should date someone
who makes you feel comfortable.
Mr. Kim.
Daughters fall for a man
who is just like her father.
Jae Seon may seem cold
on the outside,
but I'm sure he has
a warm heart on the inside.
Right, Sol Ah?
I guess.
But...
not anymore.
What?
You're trying to flag down
a bus that already left.
I'll explain when
Bang Guk Bong comes back.
The long-haired guy.
It's my personal preference.
Come and sit down.
Sol Ah.
You said you'd explain
when Guk Bong's here.
You wanted to talk to me?
What?
- But...
- What's going on?
My goodness.
Why are you acting like
you saw a ghost?
No, it's... It's just...
I'm... I'm sorry, excuse me.
What...
I'm sorry. Excuse me.
Sol Ah.
Kim Sol Ah.
What's going on?
Why is he Bang Guk Bong?
He's not. You know he's not.
The person you think
is Bang Guk Bong...
actually isn't.
Then what? Who is he?
Hong Jo.
What... Why are you
acting weird too?
Sol Ah. Hear me out.
My head's about to split in two.
I need to think on my own.
(Bus Stop)
Where's Sol Ah?
She met the real Bang Guk Bong...
and freaked out.
Where is she now?
She left to be alone.
So you just let her go?
Didn't you come here
to be at her side?
Where are you going?
To be at her side.
My mom told me to check on you.
Sol Ah!
- Sol Ah.
- Sol Ah!
Darn it.
Sol Ah!
Kim Sol Ah.
Sol Ah...
Is that the sea?
You've never seen it before?
Not in person.
I promised to see it with Sol Ah.
It's my fault.
I shouldn't have just watched.
Like you said.
Instead of just thinking,
I should've taken action.
Should I have done this sooner?
What are you doing?
Are you...
the real Bang Guk Bong?
What?
Yes.
I see.
You're the real Bang Guk Bong.
Then...
who do you think he was?
Who do you mean?
I don't know...
who he is.
Until now,
we lived in the same house...
and we ate together.
We talked together.
We even...
If I throw this down there,
what will happen?
After that,
I could just leave you here.
Then you'll never
get to see Sol Ah again.
You'll live like an ordinary cat.
I had this perfect option.
When one abandons a pet,
I heard they take it as far away
from home as possible.
So they can't come back.
Do it.
I met Sol Ah and got to
spend time with her.
I owe that to you.
If you hadn't taken me in,
I might be dead already.
Toss it.
You deserve to.
Don't just stand there. Toss it.
Shall I?
If I throw it away,
can I turn things back?
Will Sol Ah...
come back to me?
If she does,
don't run away this time.
And don't fear abandonment.
Aren't you afraid?
You should fear being abandoned.
You could die.
Will you throw that or not?
Take it back.
Here. Take it back.
Are you kidding me?
Are you done crying?
We're almost out of tissue paper.
Can I just have one more?
Do you still need to cry a bit more?
No.
I need to wipe my nose.
Thank you.
I don't know what's going on.
But...
is it because of Hong Jo?
Do you know Hong Jo?
I met him
when I went home last time.
Well...
Which one?
Human?
Or...
a cat?
What do you mean?
Hong Jo...
is the name of my cat.
The Hong Jo I met was a guy.
And he told me his name is Hong Jo.
I've been...
calling him by a different name.
But...
it turns out that wasn't his name.
I mean,
that's already absurd as it is.
But...
it even turns out...
that he's actually a cat.
Do you think that makes sense?
Why aren't you startled?
You don't believe me, do you?
I do.
When you travel around the world,
you see and hear so many things.
I've heard...
of something similar.
This also happened to someone else?
A cat fell in love and...
Did it turn into a person?
It fell in love with a mouse.
"A mouse"?
Yes, a cat and a mouse.
It's nonsense, isn't it?
What does that have
anything to do with this?
Love is...
a miracle.
It's not here. We can't find it.
Let's just go.
What's with that look?
Don't give me those eyes.
I'm not the one who threw it here.
You just failed to catch it.
Just take something else.
Does it have to be that ring?
Then why don't you
help me look for it?
I told you not to give me that look.
I found it. Hey, are we good now?
What?
Sol Ah.
I've been looking for you.
How long have you known?
I was closer to him than you.
Maybe you were too close.
I must've seemed pathetic.
I knew nothing.
No.
I still don't get it.
I get that he isn't Bang Guk Bong.
But I can't believe...
he's Hong Jo.
I just can't believe it.
Here.
That's Hong Jo's collar.
How is this here?
Because Hong Jo came here, too.
He normally keeps it
underneath his shirt.
I was going to throw it
far away but..
You were going to throw it?
- Why?
- No.
I didn't throw it.
I mean, I did throw it.
- But I didn't mean to.
- What are you saying?
Anyway, he's a cat right now.
He's probably lost somewhere.
But he's able to turn into a person.
He can't do that anymore.
He doesn't have this.
What about that?
Is it a magic ring or something?
It's not the ring. It's you.
It's because this is yours.
He needs you...
in order to turn into a person.
Why does he need me?
No one knows why.
Maybe it's magic or fate.
Or something similar.
Love is...
a miracle.
Anyway, we need to find him.
It'll turn dark soon.
I think I know...
where he is.
I see it now.
Hong Jo, he has your eyes.
I'm not Bang Guk Bong.
- Then who are you?
- Hong Jo.
It's colder than I expected.
I thought it'd be warm
like the color of a peach.
How can there be any fishes
in the water when it's so cold?
They must be freezing.
I didn't know you'd come.
I thought I should at least
see it on my own.
I wanted to see the sunset
by the sea.
You really changed into a person...
because I came here?
So it's true.
You're...
You're really Hong Jo.
(Episode 18)
(Seolleung Station)
What are you doing?
I was...
The bus is here.
Two, please.
Thank you.
Sit over...
You love to stare at my back.
Will this do?
Just because we go in
the same direction...
doesn't mean we must go together.
I never said...
we should go together.
Do you want to?
I don't want to bother you.
Did Ms. Park say anything?
It's dangerous.
You should face the front.
Okay.
Why did you sit behind me?
All this turning around
is giving me motion sickness.
I feel nauseous.
That's why you should
face the front.
I didn't eat anything
and I feel nauseous.
Just face the front.
Shall we eat dinner?
Mister. Two meals, please.
Hello.
Yes, hello.
Honey!
Doo Sik brought someone with him!
Who is it?
Who should I say this is?
Should I say you're Doo Sik's
high school art club friend?
Or workplace senior?
A neighborhood friend
sounds much better, doesn't it?
Why don't you just let them...
The wilting girl.
Hello.
My gosh.
Why is she the wilting girl?
I have a wilting plant.
- What's wrong with it?
- Go on inside.
- Go inside.
- Come inside.
Don't stare at her
while she's eating.
We're just checking to make sure
she doesn't need anything.
Where are your parents?
Why do you live alone?
They live in the country.
- Oh, I see.
- I see.
You can't ask things like that.
He's right. Young people
these days hate things like that.
Sensitivity is key when
communicating with youngsters.
So, when did you move out?
Oh, after graduating from
high school.
Until then, I lived with my mom.
- And your father?
- Yes.
He's not at home.
Darn it.
I told you not to ask.
What's wrong?
What's the matter? It's fine.
Single-parent families are common.
It's not an issue.
Yes. Who cares?
Oh, that's not what I meant.
He works on a ship.
Oh, he works on a ship.
That's nice. He's a captain.
It's not his ship.
Who cares if it's not his ship?
It's cool to be a sailor.
He must have bronze skin.
I always dreamed of
marrying a strong man.
Yes.
He doesn't work right now.
His health deteriorated.
Oh, dear.
Oh, dear, he must be terribly sick.
The sailing took its toll.
He's an alcoholic.
Alcohol...
It was a joke.
My goodness.
That was funny.
Your friend is quite witty.
How is that funny?
My goodness. Alcoholism...
Did I not get it?
Yes, so, she told a joke.
That was funny.
My gosh.
Are you worried for your daughter?
Guk Bong said he talked to her.
I'm not waiting.
I'm getting some fresh air.
It's cold. Go inside.
Okay.
Where did you two go...
A cat?
Isn't that your cat, Sol Ah?
What happened?
I didn't see it earlier.
It was looking at the sea.
It likes to walk about on its own.
You went to look for the cat?
Yes, kind of.
Let him sleep.
You said he turns human
when he's near me.
He's a cat if he falls asleep.
And he can turn into a human again
once he sleeps.
I guess you can say
his time is limited.
He said he had
something like narcolepsy.
So that's what he meant.
My head is so jumbled up right now.
Like all the pieces of a puzzle
are scattered about.
Can we talk?
Do you know...
when it is you first met Hong Jo?
What?
It was...
when your ex-girlfriend brought him
when you opened your cafe.
Come to think of it...
You weren't aware of it,
but the kitten you abandoned...
was Hong Jo.
You must've seen wrong.
I wrapped this scarf
around a little boy.
I first saw you
somewhere around here.
Why aren't you saying anything?
Will you make a sound
if I press a button? Beep.
Why aren't you saying anything?
Will you make a sound
if I press a button?
That boy was...
Hong Jo?
Yes.
I looked everywhere for him.
That's why I misunderstood you.
How could something like this
happen?
I know it's late,
but I want to turn things back.
This way.
- Good night.
- Thank you for the meal.
- Bye.
- Good night.
- Let's go inside.
- You can go in first.
- What about you?
What? You'll walk her up
to her home upstairs?
Mind your own business.
- But...
- Just go inside!
Are you going to follow her
upstairs?
- But he's...
- I'm sorry.
They think asking questions
is a way of being friendly.
I know.
They're nice people,
but I was too shy.
Do you have an upset stomach?
I know a very effective
digestive medicine.
We weren't going to the pharmacy?
Don't you know coin karaoke
is the best when you feel sick?
It's way better than
poking your finger with a needle.
I just want to go home...
All right. Instead of singing...
How about that?
- I just have to kill that thing.
- Really?
Why don't you shout out loud
for a change?
(Bodyguards are up front.
We are outnumbered.)
(Stage 1 Score)
I just wanted to...
break the wall between us
and become friends.
I heard that often.
"Break the wall."
"Come out of your shell."
I was scolded all the time.
Someone asked me if I had
a bad childhood memory or something.
I don't have a particular trauma.
I'm just always like this.
This is who I am.
That was inconsiderate of me.
It's just because you barely spoke,
so I wanted to make you
talk to me.
I just did it to hear your voice
at least.
If you want to talk,
let's talk.
Someplace quiet.
I know you wanted to talk,
but how could you bring me
to a library?
There are a lot of other
quiet places.
Who's stupid enough
to make noise at a library?
You don't want to talk with me?
- No...
- Why?
Are you disappointed
now that we've talked?
Because we have different tastes
and I talk too much?
I'm right.
I catch on easily, you know.
That's not true.
There...
Ji Eun. I'm usually quick-witted,
but I was so frustrated and
was just venting.
Ji Eun.
I mean it.
I'm really a quick-witted guy.
Doo Sik, you're slow-witted.
No matter how much I stared at you,
you didn't know.
That's...
That's why I like you.
You're slow-witted...
and it makes you seem more sincere.
Hey, what is...
What's wrong with this?
What's wrong? Is your coin stuck?
Hey.
Spit it out. Come on!
I got one for free.
Thank... Thank you.
You don't remember, do you?
You probably didn't even know
who I was.
You didn't have to be nice to me,
but you were.
So I felt more thankful.
It wasn't because you were
thinking of my feelings,
but because you truly meant it.
So...
just keep being slow-witted.
There's something I didn't tell you.
What is it?
Are you a cat too or something?
I was...
abandoned like a cat too.
(I'm sorry.)
This was the only thing
that was left.
Just like when people
abandon their pets,
I was abandoned somewhere
far away...
at an unfamiliar place...
so I would never find them.
I wanted to find out
who my parents were...
but it was impossible to find them.
They shouldn't have done that
if they were really sorry.
They should've given me...
a chance to do something at least.
Whether it's to resent or forgive.
What I really can't forgive...
is that I wasn't given a chance to.
You're giving me
that sad look already?
That was the 1st of 4 stories
of how I was abandoned.
My current parents are
my fourth adoptive parents.
I was abandoned once,
and it kept happening.
People must think...
because it happened once,
it's okay to do it again.
On a snowy day,
the kitten I found
on a heap of trash...
remained me of myself.
I was afraid...
you would abandon me like that.
I had no idea.
I said it was
your excuse to run away.
I spoke too rashly.
You were right.
I was ashamed to tell you this.
You shouldn't have been.
You were just a child.
Hong Jo...
was just a kitten.
He made me feel even worse.
We were both abandoned,
but he chose to stay with you,
and I ran away.
Now I look back...
and see that...
our warm memories outnumber
my sad ones of being abandoned.
That cat...
stayed with me all night.
That's how I survived.
What a sweet thing.
You were the same.
Now...
I'll stay by your side.
I'm not asking you to accept me.
I just...
want you to know that...
I'm by your side.
If that makes you feel
just a little warmer,
that's enough for me.
(Media)
Did I ask you to keep looking at me?
You're around me
at work and at home.
If someone keeps looking at me,
of course I'd feel bothered.
Okay. I get your point.
I get it. I'll...
(So now I'll look at you as well.)
So now I'll look at you as well.
What... What do you mean?
I'm not checking things out.
I'll look because I want to.
What?
Why?
I just want to.
I want to see you
chew your mackerel.
And I want to see you
shoot in the gaming arcade.
You look like a pill bug
when you slouch on your desk.
It's cute.
No way.
A library is a nice place
to talk in.
Your voice echoes.
Let's go outside.
We don't need to do this.
Come on.
It would've been nice
if Guk Bong were here too.
Did he go somewhere?
He left again like the wind.
He seems to love
the Uyuni salt flats.
He's going back there again.
He really is going there.
He left a huge birthday gift.
Did you see the computer
in your room?
Yes.
So your father can see
your webtoon on a large monitor.
My webtoon?
Oh, dear.
He told me not to mention it.
Dad. Did you read my webtoon?
How did you find out?
It was...
the guy with the smiley eyes.
- Ko Doo Sik?
- Yes.
When did he get your number?
Don't read it. I get so many...
negative comments.
He leaves a lot of comments himself.
"Fun", "great fun", "the best fun".
When did I do that?
What?
I thought it was a pre-teen kid
and considered him my only fan.
That pre-teen kid was you, Dad?
It wasn't me.
Oh, come on.
Did you have to write something
that sounded so childish?
Seriously. My gosh.
Was that funny?
No, sir.
Why are you sitting there
if it's not funny?
Will you stop it, Mr. Kim?
Jae Seon bought us
Grade A Korean beef.
Is it time for my medication?
I have high cholesterol levels.
Oh, high cholesterol levels...
Then I shouldn't have bought beef.
I apologize. I didn't know.
- Oh, dear.
- Next time,
I'll get something else.
He looks like he's about to cry.
Don't cry.
- Was he kidding?
- Yes. My goodness.
- Happy birthday to you
- Happy birthday, dear Mr. Kim
- Happy birthday, dear Dad
- Happy birthday to you
Make a wish.
What were you doing?
I just listened.
To the laughter and the singing.
It sounded nice.
Did you hide like this all along?
I found it strange you knew me well.
You were watching me all along.
The day we first met.
You said that day felt like a dream.
I remember that day clearly.
I brought a lost kid home,
but he suddenly disappeared
and I looked for him.
"What happened to that little boy?"
I thought about him
every now and then...
and got worried.
But...
he was right next to me.
And a grown adult too.
I'm sorry.
I just don't know...
how to accept you.
My cat Hong Jo...
and the guy I liked.
They both suddenly feel
so unfamiliar.
Can you give me some time?
Sol Ah.
Dad.
Who were you talking to?
I was on the phone.
Why are you out here?
I felt hot and needed some air.
It's cold.
My gosh.
Thanks.
That wasn't from me.
From whom, then?
A cat.
What?
Dad.
Will you listen to my story?
What is it?
A cat...
You don't need to tell me.
You want me to keep it?
Why did you adopt
an animal you can't handle?
Are you bored of it already?
No, it's not like that.
I like it.
I really like it.
Leave it here.
You can't keep a pet...
when you live alone
and work all day.
And you can't travel freely either.
I'm sure this place is
much better for the cat too.
Don't let something like a cat
tie you down.
Leave it here and
get on with your life.
(Welcome)
I was next to you
even when I didn't know it.
Such a relationship isn't easy
for a person or a cat.
Sol Ah needs some time.
You said he sat here and cried.
Are you sick?
- What is it?
- I want to apologize to you.
I'll stay next to you.
Even if our fate is sealed, I'll go.
It's my choice to do
everything for you before I leave.