- Transform. - No!
- Stop, Mister! - Transform.
Transform.
- Turn into a human. - Mister!
Transform. Transform.
Trans...
Hong Jo.
Will you change now?
Transform.
Transform!
Transform. Transform!
Darn it.
Hong Jo.
Sol Ah.
Sol Ah!
What... What are you doing? Why did you get in?
Where are you going?
I can't believe this!
Fasten your seatbelt.
Last time, you only paid a fine, but this time, it'll be different.
Sol Ah!
Sol Ah! Sol Ah!
I'm at the entrance of the cafe street.
Please hurry up.
I have nothing to lose. All my cats died because of you.
None of them died. They all found great owners.
Great owners, my foot.
You treated my house like a prison, but you think your place is great?
Fasten your seatbelt!
Why would I? I'm going to get out! Stop the car!
- You're just going to keep them... - Stop the car!
in the house just like I did. How are you different from me?
Fasten your seatbelt!
Stop the car!
- Fasten your seatbelt. - What are you doing?
- Fasten your seatbelt. - Let me go! What are you doing?
No, just stop the car!
- What's going on? - What?
Darn it.
Don't...
- Let me go. - Let me go.
- Let me go. Let go of me. - You let go.
I... I don't want to fight.
Do you think I do? You know what? Let's just fight.
- Let me go. - I'll teach you a lesson.
- I told you to let go. - My hair.
- My hair. - What about your hair?
Should I pull on it harder?
- My hair will fall out. - Get off me.
I don't care...
- if your hair falls out or not. - Stop.
Why did the car stop?
What's wrong?
- What the... - My goodness.
There's a car waiting behind us.
Sorry! Just a second!
- Hurry. - Okay.
Step on the pedal.
- Let me go. - You let go first.
- How about we let go together? - Okay.
- 1, 2... - 2...
Three.
What do you think you're doing? Stop it!
Hey!
I told you to let go!
Okay, fine. I let go.
- How can I trust you? - Let me go.
My hands. My hands are up here.
You want me to let go? Okay.
My gosh.
Sorry.
Sol Ah.
What happened? Are you okay?
Sol Ah!
Are you okay?
- Yes. - Did you get hurt?
You...
I... I was right.
No, you're wrong.
I'm not locked up.
Waiting for her is the most important thing in my life,
and it makes me happy.
But the cats that were with you...
never waited for you to come home.
So your love is an illness.
I told you it'll be different this time.
Sol Ah, are you okay?
Sol Ah.
Who is this guy?
What did you do to her?
Did you get hurt?
I'm okay.
But Hong Jo... He's not well.
("The cat is nature's masterpiece." Quote by Leonardo da Vinci)
I just got the test results.
Does your cat exercise a lot?
I'm sure you don't abuse him.
What? What do you mean?
He shows a high inflammation level and lack of liver function.
But I don't know why.
It could be due to stress.
Is there anything wrong with his heart?
His heart beats really fast.
Their heartbeat is normally faster than ours.
Then what can we do to treat him?
We don't know exactly what it is that's causing him to be like this.
You should first make sure he gets good rest...
and eats well.
If he doesn't eat well, that could harm the liver.
And if it gets worse, it will be very dangerous.
Hey, don't you have any instant noodles?
Sol Ah, here you go.
Weren't you supposed to go to the East Sea to see the sunrise?
Exactly.
If it weren't for you, we'd already be there...
eating a warm bowl of udon noodles.
So let's eat instant noodles instead.
You must've been startled.
We'll stay with you tonight.
You guys can go. I'll stay with her.
You too?
How many bags of noodles do we need to cook?
By the way, where is Bang Guk Bong?
He's not Bang Guk Bong.
Oh, right. Was it Hong Jo?
But I have to say, the name sounds so familiar.
Hong Jo. Hong Jo.
Hey, are you okay?
Let me see.
- I'm okay. - Did you see that? The cat...
Hong Jo, are you okay?
Yes, I remember. That's the name of her cat.
What's with this reaction?
Didn't you guys see what happened?
Am I the only one who saw that? The cat turned into a human being.
You don't believe me, do you?
Oh, I remember!
The day you moved here, Jae Seon and I came over.
There was a guy upstairs, but then a cat suddenly appeared.
Gosh, I knew it!
You were the first one to see it but the last one to realize it?
You all knew?
Then why didn't you tell me?
Bang Guk...
I mean, Hong...
Hey, brother. How could you do this to me?
I think you should go somewhere and help him calm down.
Yes, you're right.
Yes, go ahead. Jae Seon, you should go too.
Your dad will be worried.
Will you be okay?
Thank you guys for everything tonight.
This doesn't make sense.
I'd get it if he were a dog, but he's a cat.
He's definitely a dog type.
We'll be off now.
Call me if something comes up.
Wait. Let me see him one more...
No.
Let's go. We're late.
We'll be off now.
- See you. - Bye.
My gosh.
You're not alone.
I was worried you might be all alone if I wasn't around.
But I was worried for nothing.
Why would you say that?
Why wouldn't you be around?
I wasn't able to be there for you this time too.
Especially when...
you needed me the most.
What are you talking about?
You were always there for me.
You don't need to be human.
So don't force yourself to change.
Sol Ah.
If I fail to change again...
It's because you're tired.
The doctor told me you're okay.
He said you'll be okay once you get some rest.
So...
just stay as a cat for a while.
Okay?
It's been a long time...
since we sat like this.
Aren't you going to say anything?
You've become really talkative.
In the past,
you would sit like this and stay silent for an entire hour.
You're right.
I barely got myself to talk.
But it's too late, isn't it?
I couldn't say anything when I should've talked to you.
But I'm finally...
ready to talk.
There's so much I want to share.
But no one's here to listen.
You're not late.
You gave your dad his last gift.
I tried so hard to run away...
not knowing that there's always an end to everything.
If I had come back earlier,
it would've been a better ending.
My dad...
has been waiting for me all along.
But...
I made him wait for too long.
We spent such little time together.
You're really talkative now.
Go ahead...
and say what you want to say.
There are plenty of people who are willing to listen to you.
How is Hong Jo?
Tell me.
You used to tell me to be quiet...
every time I tried to chat before.
Did he not change that day...
because he couldn't?
Yes.
Do you think it hurts him...
every time he turns human?
Like when a cat that gets abused?
He told me...
that he used up too much of his time.
Maybe that's why he can't change any more.
No way.
That can't be.
This is too short.
I also thought I'd have more time...
with my dad...
and you.
I can't believe this.
Then...
Then are you saying he spent all that time...
waiting for me?
Welcome home.
It's too hard for me if you're always waiting for me.
Don't wait for me.
I'm all he has.
All he ever did was wait for me.
But do you know what I said to him?
I told him to stop waiting.
I told him I can't focus on work when I know he's waiting for me.
I said that after I promised to make every second worth it with him.
I can't believe I said that to him.
I'm sorry.
I should be the one consoling you.
Just like how you silently gave me a hug,
I should be doing the same for you.
I'm sorry.
I'm so sorry.
(Nalsaem Design)
Are you serious?
Don't you think you're being too rash?
I was going to put you in charge for the next project.
Something important came up.
Do you want to negotiate your salary?
It's not about the money. What I need is time.
You should give us time as well.
This is way too sudden.
I'm sorry.
About when the client asked me to put you back on the team.
The truth is, it was because they liked your design.
I wasn't going to tell you this,
but it's a parting gift.
I got you something as well.
It's not chocolate, is it?
I'm trying to lose weight.
It's mine.
Good luck with your webtoon.
If you do a poor job after quitting on me like this,
I'll leave a nasty comment online.
Thank you.
I'm sorry to escape on my own.
You joined the company because I did.
I did not.
I joined to see Ji Eun.
It was destiny.
It was.
Hey. Is he really a cat?
Can he jump from really high places...
and see well in the dark?
See you.
Hey. What about the toilet?
Does he use a urinal? Or a litter box?
You quit your job?
- Yes. - Why?
I think I'll become a really successful webtoonist.
Didn't you read the comments?
Was it for me?
No. I'm making my dream come true.
There were so many things I wanted to do when I quit my job.
I'll read all the books I wanted to, research various topics,
exercise at home to get my figure back,
and starting today, I'll eat healthily too.
Oh, and I'll quit caffeine too.
We don't drink coffee anymore.
What should I start with? There's so much I want to do.
Sol Ah.
- Sol Ah. - Yes? What?
The sun's already up.
I'm already up too.
Then why won't you get up? You had a lot you wanted to do.
This is one of them.
Sleeping in.
It's no longer morning...
Sol Ah.
You're sleeping again?
I'm reading.
I'm sleepy.
I'm going to bed.
You did nothing but lie around all day.
What did you do?
Why is my bed so cold?
Hey. You're a cat.
You should've warmed my bed for me.
Get in here.
Sol Ah.
Sit up.
Is that coffee?
You can't drink that.
It's for you so you can wake up.
I threw out all the coffee.
Sonamu.
You went on your own?
It's dangerous.
Why won't you go out?
You've been indoors, sleeping for days.
Well...
I need to sleep...
to make you sleep.
Come here.
Your heart's beating so fast.
Is that why your time passes by quicker?
Beat a little slower.
Don't beat too quickly.
You got a call.
What? I don't see my phone.
It's under the comic book.
Never mind. If I move to get that,
it'll stop ringing.
Hang on.
It's the webtoon manager. Don't take it.
Put it right back down over there.
(Lee Jin Woo)
Darn you.
Hello, Mr. Lee.
Yes, how are you?
Yes, of course.
I'm working hard day and night.
What?
I don't think I can do that.
Not an interview.
My webtoon's still ongoing.
Could you do what you can to cancel it?
Yes. I apologize.
Why did you turn down an interview?
Who would want to know about me?
The people who like your drawings.
Call to say you'll do it.
No.
Did you give up on being human because of me?
Is that what I did to you?
You did not.
If not, then call him back right now.
Okay.
Hello again.
About that interview.
Can I have another latte?
Sure. Just a moment.
I'll make it.
- Where's Sol Ah? - She finally went out...
to see the webtoon manager.
She told me not to make you work.
This is for me.
And to not give you any coffee.
Coffee doesn't work now anyway.
The time I can spend as a human...
is getting shorter and shorter.
Sol Ah has to live as a human.
But she quit her job for me,
and she can't focus on her webtoon.
She sleeps endlessly like a cat around me.
This isn't why I wanted to stay with her.
I just wanted to hold her.
I'm slowly losing my hands to hold her with.
See? I'm always getting hugged.
Tell me if there's something I can do to help.
Anything.
Do you feel sorry for me?
People give money when they feel sorry for people. Donations, was it?
Oh, right.
People also get money when they quit their jobs. A severance pay.
Are you kidding me?
Hey, get off me.
I shouldn't have agreed to do the interview.
You got changed again?
I liked what you wore just before this one.
That was a bit too much.
And that one's too dull.
Should I just call and cancel?
I think what you're wearing right now is the best one.
No, my neck feels so empty.
I don't want to do it. Who was I kidding?
Here.
Smile.
Your smile is the best accessory you could wear.
I want to stay at home.
The last episode of my favorite drama airs today.
- I love that show. - Right?
Let's just buy tteokbokki and fish-shaped buns...
- and stay at home. - The show got canceled today.
Don't lie to me.
You look nice. What do you think?
Why do you want me to become so famous?
I know you want to show off...
your beautiful girlfriend to the entire world.
But do I really need to doll myself up...
to satisfy your desire to show me off?
Are you worried about leaving me here all alone?
- Do you want to come with me? - Can I stay next to you?
No, you can't.
You need to be glued to me like this.
Let's hurry up and get ready.
Do you feel okay?
I should be the one asking you that.
Don't worry about me. I'm a pro.
- Did you get the questionnaire? - Yes.
Where did it go?
Here.
Thanks.
Let's take the photos first.
- Come this way once you're ready. - Okay.
My neck feels so empty.
- I'll see you. - Okay.
Be careful.
We'll start with the photoshoot.
You just need to look at me and smile naturally.
The photographer will take care of everything else.
Don't look into the camera.
Gosh, this is awkward.
Well, then...
Don't look somewhere else.
- Please don't look to the side. - Okay.
Don't let your eyes wander.
Hi.
What does this mean?
It says "Mignon".
It's a French word that means "cute","charming",
and "adorable".
I'll take this one.
- That's it. - Okay.
Don't mind the camera. Just be natural.
- Just look at me. - I'm sorry.
Just a second. Give her something to wipe off her sweat.
Sorry.
Thanks.
Have you guys seen a cat by any chance?
A cat?
Never mind.
Thank you.
Ease up.
Okay.
Okay, just a few more.
Let's take a few from here.
I'm sorry. I don't think I can do this.
If you feel too uncomfortable, let's just do the interview first.
I need to find my cat.
I'm sorry. I'm really sorry.
Sol Ah, what are you doing outside?
Where were you?
Here.
I told you to stay by my side.
I just wanted to help you.
It's over now.
I told you to sleep.
Why are you still human?
Don't stay behind me like that.
Who told you to come in front of me?
You spent too much time as a human being today.
Do you want me to be a cat?
No.
I just don't want you to be sick.
You're right. I should sleep.
This time, I might be asleep for a really long time.
So please take this.
You didn't have to get me this.
You gave me a collar too.
So I also want to put this on for you.
I want this to show that I chose you...
as my owner.
You won't ever lose your way home as long as you wear this necklace.
So you're safe to go outside whenever you want.
No matter how far we may be apart,
you'll always be my owner.
This is the mark that proves it.
I want you...
to show everyone what you're capable of.
You totally deserve that.
It's what you need to do.
That way, I'll be able to show you off.
My gosh.
But...
what does it say?
"Mignon".
Is it a sound that a cat makes?
Like "Meow"? "Mignon".
It means "cute","charming", and "adorable".
Look in the mirror. You'll see it's true.
It's pretty.
Thank you.
(The last episode will air shortly.)
(Final Episode)
Hong Jo. Let's talk.
I can't concentrate.
Shall we go out and get some fish-shaped buns?
Let's go out and walk hand-in-hand.
I touched your toe beans, so this time I want your hand.
Human Hong Jo, show up.
Tada!
Why are you all here?
We bought this.
Come on in.
Hey. You look...
You're glowing.
You've been staying indoors eating, sleeping well, and it shows.
You never leave home even when I call,
and only let us see you if we come over.
Fish-shaped buns.
I was craving some.
Where's Hong Jo?
He's in the room.
Hey, bro. How are you? Why don't you come out?
He stays mostly as a cat these days.
Why? Then he can't talk.
Isn't that frustrating?
It's nice that you're here.
Thank you.
It feels like we haven't met in ages.
How strange.
Oh.
Thank you.
What?
Hong Jo gave me the courage...
to tell you that I like you.
He was in a box.
I thought he was a stray cat,
but he had a ring on his collar.
I like you.
It was you, wasn't it?
How strange.
Your webtoon's almost done, right?
How is it coming along?
Not well.
I'm a bit stuck.
How are you stuck? We can brainstorm with you.
Well...
I don't know how to end it.
I can't picture the end of a cat's life.
Maybe you'll get the answer by going back to the beginning.
What did it mean to you...
when you met the cat?
Sol Ah.
Hong Jo.
It's really you.
Let's go somewhere.
Where?
Hurry.
There's not much time.
You kept me warm.
Don't look at me like that.
This is what you do when you say your final goodbye.
This is where I first thought...
I should stay with you.
Why do you keep looking back?
I'd rather think about what to do tomorrow.
Shall we go to the seaside?
The day after, let's draw on the rooftop.
And the day after...
This will be the last time...
to see me as human.
How do you know that?
I feel it.
I'm barely managing right now.
No.
If we have some coffee...
Let's have coffee.
I can be human only for a certain amount of time.
I used all that up.
You said you can be human around me.
I'm right beside you.
Why won't it work when I'm so close to you?
Won't this work?
I'll stay with you.
I'll stick right beside you.
Won't this...
help at all?
Thank you.
For being the person to make me human.
Is it really the end?
Already?
You said you'd leave first,
but you never said it would be so soon.
I didn't know either.
If I'd known it would end like this,
I wouldn't have disappeared when we first met.
I shouldn't have let you follow me from behind.
I should've held your hand and kept you close.
I should've...
let you walk next to me.
Hong Jo. Are you all right?
I think it's time.
Don't go.
You said you'd stay with me.
If you leave like this...
I won't leave.
What do you mean?
I just won't be human.
But I'll be with you.
As a cat.
You're disappearing yet you're saying you're not leaving?
You'll be there, but I won't be able to see you.
I won't be able to touch you like this.
I won't be able to hear your voice.
What kind of goodbye is this?
I'm sorry.
I can't hug you anymore.
If you don't turn into a human,
will you not be in pain anymore?
I'm sorry...
for not being human.
You don't have to be a human.
Just don't get sick.
Just...
Just stay beside me.
I'll wait for you.
Since waiting is...
what a cat does.
I'll wait too.
Since tomorrow might come to us again.
So tomorrow, let's go see the ocean.
Let's do that.
And the next day,
let's draw together at home.
Let's do that.
(2 years later, Sonamu)
Water, water, water!
Here.
My phone, phone, phone!
Why are you looking at me so anxiously?
See? I have everything.
I'll be off then.
My bag, bag, bag!
I'm really going now. Bye!
I'm really, really going. Bye!
- Today's the big day. - Yes, it is.
You must be nervous.
See you.
Next, the main color is...
The main color should be a comfortable and warm color...
in a beige tone.
The logo... The logo should be...
And we should include picture icons so children can easily...
Did you also stay up all night because you were so nervous?
I slept really well.
- But why are you yawning? - To help you calm down.
I heard nervous cats feel soothed...
when they see their owner yawn.
Aren't you talking about dogs?
Whether it's a dog or a cat, I'm just saying.
Tell me honestly.
You become an animal when you sleep too, right?
Me?
You're so adorable when you sleep.
How could a human be so adorable?
We selected white as the main color, for a neat look.
And to emphasize certain points, we used a beige color...
that can conjure up a comfortable and warm image.
For the logo, according to our concept of maternal love,
we made an image where it seems like...
a large silhouette is hugging another small silhouette.
Also...
We added picture icons for each menu...
so young children who can't read...
can easily and conveniently place orders.
The concept is based on a cute drawing board...
- that children will love. - What a surprise.
Was she always this good?
Thank you.
Impressive.
("Welcome")
(Kim Sol Ah's Autograph Event for "Welcome")
Hello, I'm Kim Sol Ah.
Let's begin.
- Hello. - Hello.
- Thank you, enjoy the book. - Thank you.
Hello.
- Here you go. Thank you. - Thank you.
("Welcome")
Hello, thank you for coming.
- Here you go, thank you. - Thank you.
- Ta-da! - How did you guys come?
- Ta-da! - Ta-da!
- Hello. - Da Som, hi!
We thought no one would be here, but it's crowded.
Thank you for coming.
My kids love your book, so I came for an autograph.
Ms. Park.
I guess it's perfect for children's tastes.
You haven't changed a bit.
Why don't we take a picture?
1, 2, 3.
Thank you. Have a good day.
It took two years to publish this into a book.
The autograph event is over.
I came right now on purpose.
Let's go get dinner.
You know I can't. Hong Jo is waiting for me.
- Then give me an autograph. - I told you it's over.
Come on, how could you treat a fan like this?
Take this at least then.
Hong Jo's not the only one waiting for you.
You know that.
You have two options.
Do you want to take these flowers or eat dinner?
When I look at Hong Jo lately, he seems so comfortable.
I guess he's really happy being a cat.
Then what about you?
I'm the same.
Him being a cat makes me happy.
Hong Jo...
hugs me even when he doesn't have hands.
Hong Jo, what do you think?
Do you like it?
Just like how you waited for me,
I'm waiting too.
Hong Jo, I'm off to work.
One,
two,
three.
I checked...
every day...
just in case you might've turned into a human.
Even if it's just once,
I want to see you again.
Are you still waiting?
However long it may take,
it's okay even if you come back as a wrinkly old man.
I...
will still...
recognize you right away.
Welcome.
(Thank you for watching "Meow, the Secret Boy".)
He became my priority.
The whole house changed.
The pleasure of seeing a puppy is beyond words.
A friend. A friend I live with.
I don't know if he understands, but when I speak,
he seems to relax.
It's as if they are my caretakers.
It's like they sense their owner's pain.
He gives me a lot of comfort.
I'd like to think that I became a better person.
I learned how to appreciate and love something.
I think I gained the ability...
to be more considerate toward others.
Maybe this much more.
(Choi Nakta's "Blooming" is now released.)