(Episode 11)
Who...
are you?
Bang Guk Bong.
Can you get me some water?
I feel like throwing up.
Let's go to the bathroom.
What are you doing here?
- Water.
- I need to check...
if you're really Bang Guk Bong.
I met a guy earlier, and he told me
his name was Bang Guk Bong.
And he didn't seem to have
a reason to lie.
Show me your ID.
I knew it. No wonder you seemed
quite unusual from the start.
You lied and pretended to be
someone else.
What is it that you want?
Hey.
Tell me who you are.
Let me call the police first.
Hong...
What?
Hong Jo.
Water.
Give me some water.
Water...
Can I have some water?
Water.
("A cat is a puzzle
for which there is no solution.")
(Quote by Hazel Nicholson)
He must've left through the window.
Yes, that must be it.
I sneezed every time I was near him.
Oh, gosh! Jae Seon?
What are you doing here?
I was worried.
About what?
- Me?
- It looked like you drank a lot.
I didn't want to leave you here
all by yourself.
Then you were here since last night?
Do you want some coffee?
You stayed here all night?
Where's Guk Bong?
I wonder if he left already.
I'm not sure.
Did you cook this?
Eat up.
What about you?
I'm fine with just coffee.
The rice tastes delicious.
Guk Bong likes rice too.
I guess he left
without eating breakfast again.
Did you happen...
to notice anything weird about him?
He's really weird.
But that's why
he's so fun to be with.
Are you guys close already?
Yes, he understands me very well.
It's kind of weird.
Make sure you keep your door closed
when you sleep.
Don't forget to lock the door.
There's no need to worry about that.
I know him well enough.
Just keep a distance.
I think he's going to leave
on a trip again.
Now that he's about to leave,
I feel like I'm going to miss him.
I guess he kind of grew on me.
- Sol Ah.
- My gosh, I even started...
to like his name.
- But he even changed his name...
- You should be more suspicious.
What?
He might not be the guy
you think he is.
- What are you talking about?
- Come see me after work.
Don't be with him.
- Why all of a sudden?
- Just do as I say.
I also have something important
to tell you.
- I can't tell you what it is yet.
- "Something important"?
I'll look after the cat
while you're at work.
Why? Just leave him here.
I need to check something.
Ji Eun.
Is that not her?
Hey, it's you.
I'm sorry.
I said a bunch of nonsense yesterday
because I was too drunk.
I want to talk to you
about something. Is that okay?
He stayed up all night
in front of your room?
Yes.
And he even cooked for you?
Then he even offered
to look after the cat.
Just like how couples
take care of each other's cat?
- Isn't that weird?
- It's a good thing.
Now that the misunderstanding
is gone,
he's trying to take the next step.
It's charming.
Why does it feel so weird though?
Maybe it just feels unreal
since it took him so long.
Yes, it's been a long time.
I liked him for a long time
and suffered a lot.
And it took me so long
to get over him.
I don't want to start
liking him again.
But still, it took so long
to finally work.
I know I'm being a little weird.
But it's just strange.
It's best that we stay friends.
How can you be friends
with someone you used to like?
Is that even possible?
Well...
Maybe time will make it possible.
I don't think
I'll ever be able to do that...
no matter how much time passes by.
What are you guys doing?
Why are you guys suddenly so quiet?
I'm quick-witted, you know.
I can tell what's going on.
You guys suddenly stopped talking
as soon as I came.
I should go now.
What's going on?
I heard you guys drank without me.
What did you guys talk about?
Please don't tell Doo Sik.
Don't try to give him ideas...
or make things awkward
by trying to help me date him.
I'll quit.
No.
I'll just die.
Okay, I won't tell him.
I won't.
- Will you please tell me?
- My gosh.
- Hello.
There's definitely
something going on.
I'm so curious. I'm so curious.
Nothing's going on.
(Do you think he knows
what's going on?)
(Don't worry. He's slow-witted.)
You told her that I'm slow-witted,
didn't you?
I'm quick-witted, aren't I?
It was about work.
We were talking about the project.
Aren't I part of the project?
Ji Eun, do you want me
out of the group?
I left a note over there.
(Color tone: Healthy-looking green)
Sol Ah.
Yes?
Are you and Ji Eun friends now?
How did you manage to do that?
We talked and there's a connection.
- What connection?
- There's no connection.
Sol Ah's trying hard to
keep the project afloat.
Covering for the employee
who was served a job.
It was a misunderstanding that
she was given the job.
I asked her about it.
How is that credible?
Of course she'd deny
she was given the job.
She would, right?
Where did you hear that
she got the job as a favor?
- Me?
- Yes.
If you tell me, I'll check.
I heard it from...
Hye Yeon, of course.
Why look at me?
I heard about it from Da Som.
That's weird.
I definitely heard about it
from Sang Kwon.
That means...
Bang Guk Bong.
Hey. Look at you staring back at me.
Are you a human?
Can I help you?
Oh, hello.
Do you live here?
I don't, but...
Do you know if I could meet...
the person who lives here?
What business do you have
with that person?
I'm not a strange person.
- I mean good...
- Who are you?
I'll come back another time.
No, wait.
What was that?
I was sure I closed the door.
Hey.
Why did you come from that side?
Hey, wait.
Hey! Why... Why are you
running away?
What... Do I have to run?
Hey!
Stop where you are!
There are cars around here!
Why... Gosh, I'm sorry.
Hey, stop.
I just want to talk. Hey!
Why are you running? Stop!
Jeez.
You must be
out of breath too, so stop.
Let's just talk, okay?
I'm sorry.
Time-out.
Hey, you. Hey!
That's a dead end.
Jeez. Seriously?
What?
He jumped over this?
Something this high?
I can't believe
I got to experience this.
I was chosen by a cat
to be its carer.
Okay. You'll need time to settle in.
You can relax.
I won't hurt you. It's okay.
Lee Jae Seon.
Jae Seon. Where were you?
The cat disappeared.
Hong Jo?
I totally get you.
I also find it hard
to befriend people.
I want them to understand me,
but I'm afraid
they'll see through me.
(Seowon High art genius Ko Doo Sik)
Can you believe
I kept his eraser because...
I couldn't even return it?
10 years...
is a very long time.
(Seowon High art genius Ko Doo Sik)
You want to be my friend already?
It's been 10 years
and I still haven't managed.
I didn't know it could be
this simple.
I should pluck up some courage
like you.
First...
I'll start with eating with him.
How's that?
You have a caregiver?
I was sure I closed the door.
It doesn't make any sense
that a cat opened it.
He must've gotten out again.
What should we do?
Did you search thoroughly?
What about my house?
Hear me out first.
- That cat...
- Hang on.
Hello?
It was your cat.
I thought someone had abandoned it.
No.
I noticed something move
on my way home,
and the cat was in a box.
There was a ring on its collar.
Yes. Oh, no, I'll come over.
See you.
I'm sorry. I had no idea.
It's okay. Thank you.
You found him for me.
You sit down.
Do you want coffee?
Oh... That's okay.
I'll leave you two together.
There's no need.
I should go.
She left already?
Yes.
Do you want it?
Can I have it then?
What's that?
I'm going to try and build
a cat tower.
- Is it for Hong Jo?
- It's for you.
Do you think I like climbing stuff?
By the way,
didn't you say you had something
important to tell me?
Yes.
I wrapped this scarf around a boy.
You wrapped the scarf...
around a boy?
Hong Jo was found with this scarf?
The reason why things never
worked out between the two of us...
Isn't that already in the past?
Listen to me.
This might sound a bit stupid.
- Sorry. Let me get some water.
- Okay.
The day I misunderstood you...
You told me that you gave your scarf
to a little boy.
But I think...
that might've been...
I think...
that boy might've changed into...
Sol Ah!
Guk Bong.
Are you okay?
Oh, gosh.
Are you okay? Let me see.
- I'm sorry.
- It's okay.
That necklace...
Hey, where are you going?
I'll come back for Hong Jo later.
I don't think that's necessary.
How did you
suddenly show up like that?
You also showed up out of nowhere
the first time we met.
You saved me again.
You're like a cat.
You disappear all of a sudden
and show up again.
Are you also going to leave
without even saying anything?
Like a cat?
You told me not to leave.
You asked me to be Bang Guk Bong.
I was drunk when I said that.
So you're not going to leave
or change your name?
If you give me permission.
Your opinion matters more than mine.
- It's your life.
- I'm going to stay.
Really?
It might seem like
I'm gone sometimes.
But I'll still be here.
You just probably won't notice.
What are you talking about?
You even talk like a cat.
Anyway, if you feel like
it's time to leave,
at least give me a heads up.
Don't just disappear
out of the blue.
Okay.
I was right. I made this.
Are you really a cat?
It's Sol Ah's ring.
The cat I picked up was actually
a human being?
What are you doing?
I can't believe what I'm seeing.
How can a human change into a cat?
It's the other way around.
That still doesn't make sense.
How long have you been like this?
What about your parents?
Are they cats or humans?
Or did you escape from a secret
research institute or something?
All I know...
is that Sol Ah...
makes me turn human.
What do you mean?
I'm able to turn human
when I'm with her.
But she's not here right now.
Her belongings.
That's absurd.
But Sol Ah...
has no idea that she has the ability
to turn a cat into a human?
Please don't tell Sol Ah about this.
Why not?
Because I won't
get to stay with her.
You want me to leave you
with Sol Ah?
Even after I found out who you are?
I mean,
you might be human,
a cat, or a monster.
I don't even know
what to think of you.
I have no idea either,
but I won't do anything bad.
Why Sol Ah?
Is it because you want to be human?
I wasn't the one...
who wanted to be human.
Sol Ah was the one
who made me turn into a human.
So maybe she needed me.
What?
She was alone...
because of you.
I'll do what you say.
If you tell me not to turn human,
I'll just stay as a cat.
Just let me be with Sol Ah.
Jae Seon.
I'm here to pick up Hong Jo.
- You were in there?
- Yes.
Are you okay?
Didn't you get injured?
I'm okay.
Where is Hong Jo?
By the way, I never got to hear
what you wanted to tell me.
You were telling me
something important.
Oh, that.
Just forget it.
Don't let it bother you.
Okay.
Let's stop talking about the past.
Things wouldn't have worked out
even if it weren't for that.
I would've wanted to find out
more about you,
talk to you a lot,
and expect you to do the same.
But you would've looked for excuses
to push me away.
This time, it's not an excuse.
I have my reasons.
Of course it's something
you can't tell me, right?
I can't say what I was going to say,
but instead,
I'll say something else.
I'm sorry.
I got the wrong idea about you.
I didn't say anything
or hear your side of it.
I just left you alone
so I could be alone.
I'm sorry about that.
Why would you say that now?
We're friends.
To be honest,
I was never a friend to you.
I know.
You know that and so do I.
But even if we knew how we felt,
it still didn't work out.
Doesn't that mean it never will?
Then...
do you think we can be friends?
I don't think I can do that.
But I still...
If you fall in love
with someone else,
then I'll be a real friend
to you then.
(Episode 12)
It suits you.
This is animal abuse.
You said you'd do as I say.
I'll even pay you hourly wages.
You're not even human
and I'll pay you.
I can't work full-time.
You talk like you're human.
I can't stay human for too long.
There's a limit to my stamina.
Is that true?
What happens when you're tired?
I fall asleep as a cat.
Are there any more?
Weaknesses, I mean.
There is.
What are you doing?
Finding a weakness.
Oh. Is that not my weakness?
Don't ever get out of my sight.
Is this what you wanted to do?
Monitor me?
He went overboard.
This isn't the right green.
What is this?
Ji Eun.
Wow. You look like
you stepped on a turd.
Can you stop hating me?
You have a lot in your bag today.
What's all this?
Give it back.
Gosh, I really hate it.
That feeling when someone hates you.
It was okay when she hated us both.
Why is it just me now?
Da Som. Do you like me?
I do like you. You're cute.
What about you? Do you like me?
You do have a messy desk,
but I kind of like you.
What about you? Do you like me?
We're both guys. Why ask?
Do you like me or not?
Okay, fine. I like you loads.
See? They all like me.
It's no joke, but you're
the first person to not like me.
I'll make you like me.
Do you still dislike me?
The toner...
You like one of these, don't you?
I have a tumbler.
Thank you.
Sure.
Will you like me now?
- Why...
- Thank you.
It's so hard.
Do you want...
to have lunch with me?
Me too?
Did you eat this well on your own?
It wasn't because
I didn't want to eat with you.
I'm a slow eater
and I thought I'd be a nuisance.
If I try to eat faster, I get sick.
Oh. I see.
I didn't know about that.
I need to go to the restroom.
You're a slow mover as well.
Give me that.
Will you like me now?
Is that all?
Oh? Something just fell out.
- What is it?
- Nothing.
You're hiding it
and it makes me more curious.
What is it? Let me see.
You'll show it to Sol Ah, won't you?
Why won't you show it to me?
You can't see it.
Will you just like me too?
Will they even talk to each other?
Can we just forget about it?
I will if you like me.
I like you.
What?
My eraser?
It's from when I was in high school.
Why?
I love it here.
He's so handsome.
Wash the mugs.
Darn it.
You do the cool stuff
while I wash the mugs?
It's not cool.
I became a liar...
just to keep your secret.
Sorry about that.
Why did you run off last winter
using me as an excuse?
You eavesdrop?
Yes.
It was an excuse, but...
It wasn't just an excuse.
Then what?
I felt ashamed.
About what?
Jae Seon.
Hong Jo's not at home. Is he here?
Right here.
Hey.
Bang Guk Bong?
- Oh, Hong Jo?
- In there.
- At home.
What?
At home.
He left. Check again.
That's right. He'll be somewhere.
What's going on?
You two seem oddly friendly.
Do you work here?
Yes. I was just about to
get off work.
- You need to do the dishes.
- You do it.
Let's go home.
Wait.
You're here again.
Shall I call the police?
I didn't do anything wrong.
We met last time...
Do you know him?
I thought you were a nice person...
who looked after stray cats.
Oh, I wasn't planning on doing
anything bad.
I just missed her a bit.
You know, the one who lives here...
with nice legs and a pretty face...
Why?
She seemed a bit lonely...
and it seemed dangerous too.
I think someone should
care for her.
Of course it's dangerous if
a suspicious guy lurks around.
But may I ask who you are?
Someone who cares for her.
She has someone who cares for her,
so stop lurking around a house
where a girl lives alone.
She doesn't live alone.
I live with her.
Sol Ah, come here. Let's go inside.
Wait.
There seems to be
a misunderstanding.
I was talking about the cat.
I didn't mean her. The cat.
What?
The cat that lives here
seemed to be neglected.
I saw it walking around the street
alone dangerously...
a few times.
- It's my cat.
- I know.
I saw you a few times at the vet.
What did it eat this time
to get sick?
Well...
I think it ate garlic.
Last time it was milk,
and this time it's garlic?
I'm just hoping...
you have
some sense of responsibility.
I'm sorry.
I tend to be a bit clumsy.
Don't worry.
That cat is more than happy.
People believe
what they want to believe.
Well, then.
Someone who cares for her.
She doesn't live alone.
I live with her.
What is this feeling?
How strange.
Hong Jo. Are you having trouble
sleeping too?
Do you want a snack?
All right.
Let's see.
Guess which hand it's in.
Right hand? Left hand?
It's right here.
I better drink some milk.
(Dad)
To what do I owe the honor?
Where are you?
Are you alone?
In bed.
The two of us.
With my cat.
- You know, tomorrow...
- I know it's tomorrow.
She said she wants to
set the table...
for your mom's
ancestral rites ceremony.
Ms. Bang?
I'm grateful.
I'm sorry to leave you alone.
I told you I'm not alone.
Good night.
I was thinking of drinking milk.
How did you know?
- What are you doing?
- What?
Aren't you going to sleep?
I keep seeing things
that I have to clean up.
Aren't you just looking for things
to clean?
Is that all? Anything else?
There's one more place
that's been on my mind.
What on earth?
Why is it so clean in here?
Do you even sleep?
Do you go out every night
or something?
It doesn't seem like
anyone lives here.
Are you done looking?
Let's go downstairs.
I found it.
I think that's enough.
Is something wrong?
There is.
Tell me.
Why aren't you saying anything?
Will you say something
if I press a button?
Why aren't you saying anything?
Will you say something
if I press a button?
How do you know that?
That's a secret between
me and my mom.
I heard it when I was young.
My mom said it to me
when I was young too.
- What about you?
- The first person I remember.
You mean your mom, right?
You say the same thing
in such a cool way.
Tomorrow is my mom's
death anniversary.
The day she died.
We used to hold a simple
ancestral rites ceremony at home.
But my dad said he'll do it
starting this year.
And your mom will help him.
So there's nothing for me to do.
But why are you cleaning
in the middle of the night?
I was always busy doing something.
I cooked and cleaned
since middle school...
and took care of my dad.
My mom's death anniversary
passed by...
just like any other hectic day,
but this time, something felt empty
inside me.
So it felt like
I had to do something.
How about going somewhere
you both remember?
The home Mom raised me in
now belongs to someone else.
Shall I go to the riverside
we used to visit?
It's cold this year too.
My mom used to love peaches.
She passed away in the winter,
so I can't give her peaches.
I should go back downstairs.
Let's go together tomorrow.
The riverside.
I'll be with you.
You're doing something
I didn't tell you to.
I'm leaving after this is done.
A part-timer's taking time off?
Who said that cats return favors?
I have important plans.
If it's important to you...
I'm the person you should
consider most important.
I found you half frozen to death
and bathed and fed you.
I saved you.
I don't remember that.
Look at these scars.
Why did you take me in?
You should've left me there.
You looked like me.
I did?
I was abandoned too.
People get abandoned like cats?
Four times.
First, my birth parents left me.
Then I was adopted
and returned three times.
You were afraid...
of being abandoned again.
Why didn't you tell Sol Ah that?
I told you. I felt ashamed.
"The abandoned kitten
I saw looked like me."
It sounds like a playboy's excuse
to avoid a serious relationship.
How could I say that?
To Sol Ah?
Sol Ah would've given you a hug.
Forget it. Why am I
telling you this?
What are you doing?
If I were you,
I'd have stayed with Sol Ah.
You?
Even if it means being abandoned.
Being with someone
isn't as easy as it sounds.
Not to mention that...
you're a cat.
- Come on in.
- Welcome.
Is there room for us
to sit together?
Yes. We'll put
a few tables together.
Thank you.
Give us a moment.
Oh, dear. You sound very sick.
Okay. Get some rest.
What made the hard-working
Ji Eun take a sick day?
She was fine yesterday.
Give her a call.
Why me?
Sol Ah, you're Ji Eun's best friend.
Shouldn't you
check on her or something?
Yes. You visit her.
Oh... Well,
you see...
It's my mom's death anniversary.
Oh, right. It's around
this time of the year.
Will you spend it alone?
Will you order?
An americano and an orange juice.
Oh, no.
Can I go now?
Will you be okay? You must be tired.
If you fall asleep outside
and turn into a cat...
Do you know where they sell peaches?
Hi, Jae Seon.
I'm sorry, but...
is Bang Guk Bong there?
He left. It's been a while.
Oh, really? Then why...
Did he get lost?
His important plans were with you.
If he comes back, give me a call.
Sorry.
He doesn't have a phone
and it's inconvenient.
Where are you meeting him?
(Yugwasu Supermarket)
Do you have peaches?
Not in this market.
Not here. Try the large
supermarket over there.
Lee Jae Seon.
What are you doing here?
Can't I be here?
Why did you bring flowers?
It's for your mother.
You remembered?
Thanks.
No. I must hang in there.
Where's Bang Guk Bong?
He's not coming.
Did something happen to him?
Is there a reason he must come?
Not really.
Then why are you waiting?
I don't know.
Why am I waiting for him?
Jae Seon's right next to me.
For some strange reason,
I'm not at all pleased or excited.
Someone who cares for her.
What he said bothered me because...
I live with her.
The person I'm waiting for is...
Let's get going.
I think I can manage.
- Manage what?
- Being friends.
I think...
I can manage...
to be friends with you.
I have to get there.
(Sliced peaches)
Sorry for misunderstanding...
I apologize.
No. It happens.
Thank you.
Is that guy a cat too?
He keeps making me sneeze.
- He smells like a cat.
- He does?
Then is he, like you...
It's not just one.
(Welcome)
Sorry for not keeping my promise.
- Did something happen?
- I wanted to come to you.
Does he make you that nervous?
He promised to be with me.
He must feel uncomfortable.
He was crying.
- I'll watch on my own.
- What do you mean?
I think someone took him.
I'm nothing without Sol Ah,
and I said I'd be with her.
Guess what my nightmare is.
I ask questions
but no one answers them.
Then they all disappear.