(Episode 13)
Let's get going.
I think I can manage.
Manage what?
Being friends.
I think...
I can manage...
to be friends with you.
Bang Guk Bong.
I'm going to wait for him
a bit more.
You can go without me.
Why?
Because I think
he's going to show up.
He's not coming.
You've waited enough.
He promised...
that he'll be there for me.
Do you really mean that?
Yes.
This is where I live.
("Having someone wonder
where you are...")
("when you don't come home at night
is what humans need.")
(Quote by Margaret Mead)
(Sliced peaches)
Do you know where they sell peaches?
Without this,
he won't be able to change.
Hong Jo.
Why did you come back?
Isn't that Hong Jo's collar?
- How do you have this?
- I found it outside.
What do you mean?
Where? How?
You should check if Hong Jo's home.
Do you think he's okay?
Check if he's home first.
I'll search the neighborhood.
Okay.
Hong Jo.
Did you find Hong Jo?
No. Wasn't he home?
No.
Isn't it weird?
How did this come off?
And what was he doing so far away?
It couldn't have come off
on its own.
I think someone took it off
on purpose.
You mean someone did it
to steal Hong Jo?
- Or do you think...
- Let's look for him again tomorrow.
No, we should look for him now.
We won't be able to find him...
if someone took him away on purpose.
- And it's really late.
- My gosh.
I can't believe this happened again.
I... I seriously lost him
this time, didn't I?
This time...
This time,
I'll help you find him.
We'll be able to find him.
He's not a normal cat.
Can you take a look at this?
Thank you.
We're looking for a cat.
Please read...
- We're looking for a cat.
- Please have a read.
Thank you.
(We're looking for a missing cat!)
Can you please read this
and call us if you see anything?
I'm sorry.
Are you okay?
Yes, I'm okay.
Bang Guk Bong didn't
come home last night either.
I wonder if something also
came up with him.
Can you please take a look at this?
Thank you.
Please have a read. Thank you.
Hey, let's eat lunch.
I'm going to eat lunch at home.
Again?
Are you hiding a pot of gold
at your house or something?
- You guys can eat without me.
- Okay.
(We're looking for a missing cat!)
There are so many people
who have lost their cats.
You're right.
(We're looking for a missing cat.)
It's kind of weird.
It's like someone's kidnapping them.
Hello. Can I ask you something?
Sure.
Have you ever seen
anyone suspicious around here?
I'm not sure. Why?
I lost my cat.
And I was wondering
if you might know anything.
Oh, dear.
There's a man who comes here
to feed the cats.
But he's a kind person.
Have you ever noticed
anything strange about him?
For example,
did he ever take them home?
I've seen him
taking them a few times.
My goodness.
He takes them to the hospital.
He treats the wounded cats
and neuters them.
He neuters them?
Why doesn't he ask
the borough office to do that?
He does a whole lot of things
for stray cats.
All I do is feed them dry kibble.
But he even gets them canned food.
By any chance,
do you know his number?
I brought a new friend.
He's going to wake up soon,
so you guys should say hello.
From what I know, he works
at the nearby garage.
The youngest in our team?
He goes around feeding stray cats.
But he went home today.
Can you tell us his address
or phone number?
I can't tell you his personal
information without his permission.
(Don't leave your car
with just enyone.)
Thank you.
What is it?
It should be "anyone", not "enyone".
I can't stand typos.
It's part of my job.
If you lost your cat,
don't waste your time here.
Instead, go to your parking lot
and tap on the car hoods.
Cats tend to hide there
when the weather gets cold...
because the engine remains warm
even after you turn it off.
- Thank you.
- I hope you find your cat.
Okay.
Are you here?
Or are you here?
There you are.
We should go home now.
I'll visit the garage again
tomorrow.
Wait.
We meet again.
What brings you here?
(We're looking for a missing cat!)
Did you lose him?
See? I told you...
to take good care of him.
She didn't lose him.
It looks like someone stole him.
He's probably
with a better owner now.
Just mind your own business.
May I take a look?
What are you doing?
Are you trying to imply
that I stole the cat?
You're the one
who left your cat outside.
And now, you're suspecting me?
I'm sorry, but this is just trash.
You're lying.
It's a cat.
Stop right there!
Stop!
- Hey!
- Stop right there!
Hong Jo!
Be quiet.
Wait.
Please be quiet. Be quiet
for a little while. I'm sorry.
Be quiet. Stay quiet.
What is it?
Look.
"Enyone".
(Don't leave your car
with just enyone.)
It should be "anyone", not "enyone".
It's a typo.
(Don't leave your car
with just enyone.)
Are you home?
Mister! My goodness.
What do you want?
Your cats meow and cry
day and night.
The kid upstairs
cries day and night too.
What? The other tenants
complain about the noise...
- and smell.
- They're not as noisy as humans.
Humans smell more too, like you.
What did you say?
You're out of your mind.
Hey!
Open the door! He's just mad.
What...
You...
How did you...
get in?
Why do you do this?
I...
I... I...
I saved them all.
You locked them up.
And display them like objects.
They'd all be dead
if they were left outdoors.
They get hit by a car or freeze.
Or get stuck in a car's hood.
Cats...
die if they get abandoned.
Not all those here were abandoned.
You stole some.
Don't... I couldn't stand people
who don't deserve to have a cat.
People exactly like you.
You get one because it's cute,
then leave it on the street.
When it gets old and sick,
you'll just let it go.
No?
Then what right do you have...
to collect cats?
I like them.
I like cats and
I want to be with them.
Open the door!
- You...
- Excuse us.
- My gosh.
- Hey. Open the door.
- Hong Jo!
- Why are you here?
I think he took our cat.
Hong Jo!
- Get out.
- Hong Jo!
- Let them go.
- Get out!
Let them go.
Every one of them.
- Open the door!
- Hong Jo!
Let us in!
They're my cats.
Without them, I can't live either.
Don't do this.
Let go!
I told you to leave them alone.
Darn you.
Step aside. I'm glad
I have an excuse.
I need to see just what kind of
mess he made inside.
What's wrong?
Hong Jo!
Are you okay? Were you hurt?
I'm sorry. I'm so sorry.
Oh, no...
Are you okay?
An animal hoarder?
What on earth is this mess?
How many cats are there?
This is disgusting!
A person...
turned into a cat.
I'm sorry.
Hong Jo.
Not only was he hurt,
but he's also dehydrated.
I'll keep him here for the night.
I wanted to be with him.
If you leave something
with your smell, he'll calm down.
Oh. Okay.
- Here you go.
- Okay.
Oh, and...
I'm home.
I just got my cat back.
Did he go traveling?
Cats are like that.
They're not around when you want...
You...
I'm sorry I couldn't
keep my promise.
Well, I was a bit
out of sorts myself.
Something happened to Hong Jo.
I'm sorry that you had to...
go through that too.
Did Jae Seon tell you?
I wanted to come to you too.
I wanted to be there for you.
Did something come up?
Where were you?
What?
You can't say?
I couldn't tell you.
There was...
nothing I could do.
Even if I wanted to come to you,
without you,
I couldn't be with you.
You're talking gibberish again.
I'm sorry. It was your mother's
death anniversary.
It's fine.
I'm used to it.
Everyone around me is like a cat.
So was my mom.
She had cancer and she didn't
tell me until right before she died.
Everyone has their own nightmare.
Do you know what mine is?
I ask a question and no one answers.
And then they all disappear.
I forgot for a while...
that you're a cat like them all.
Why did you have to be a cat?
Where on earth did he go?
I don't get him at all.
Still, he didn't go on a trip.
What am I saying?
Why did I have to fall for
a guy like a cat?
Yes.
I don't know how he got out,
but he came home overnight.
He seems fine,
so I'll keep him at home.
I'll wire you the hospital fee.
Bye.
You should've stayed at the clinic.
Did you have to break out?
You're such a nuisance
to take care of.
Why did it have to be me?
"Why"?
That's what Sol Ah said.
"Why did you have to be a cat?"
What do you mean?
I disappeared without a word.
I made a promise,
but she had to wait all by herself.
I did exactly what you did to her.
What I did reminded her of you.
That's what
she meant by that, right?
That's not quite what I meant.
I happened to find out your secret.
So I was the only person
who could save you.
But...
unfortunately,
you're just an ungrateful cat...
who doesn't even know
how to thank me.
I don't want to say this.
But thank you.
Why didn't you want to say that?
Because you were there for Sol Ah
when I couldn't be there.
That's not exactly
the right thing to say.
It's natural for me...
to be there for Sol Ah.
"To be there for Sol Ah"?
I guess I also thought
it was natural.
I guess I got used to talking,
picking things up,
and opening doors
like a human being.
I felt so frustrated and pathetic...
because I couldn't do anything.
But that's what I normally am.
I'm actually nothing without Sol Ah.
But I promised to be there
for her...
without knowing that my existence
could end up harming her.
Just like the guy who locked me up.
I can't believe this.
Are you consulting me
about your feelings for Sol Ah?
Seriously? You're talking to me
about Sol Ah?
You didn't hurt Sol Ah.
You're not
that important to her yet.
What happened to the other cats?
They're still locked inside a cage.
I'm going to upload their photos
and help them find their owners.
And I'll help the homeless ones
find new homes.
What if you can't find anyone?
How long are you
going to keep them locked up?
A month at most.
What about after that?
Will they be set free?
We'll have to put them to sleep.
But we should still try our best.
I guess that guy...
wasn't entirely wrong.
They'd all be dead
if they were left outdoors.
They get hit by a car or freeze.
Cats die if they get abandoned.
I'm sorry for coming so late.
Thank you.
I can't believe the cat
was actually stolen.
My goodness, what a horrible person.
She must've been scared.
No.
She had fun because she got to see
the other cats in the neighborhood.
That's a relief.
- Are you waiting for a call?
- What?
No, I'm not.
Then do you want to call someone?
Just call that person instead of
fidgeting with your phone.
No.
I guess she still hasn't
recovered from her cold.
- Did you call her?
- Me?
Why would I call her?
Come on. She went to school with us.
Oh, okay. I'll call her later.
- Why...
- Why are you following me?
- I didn't follow you.
I was thinking about something.
Okay.
- Why...
Why me?
Why did I have to fall for
a guy like a cat?
- Hey, Sol Ah.
- Hey.
- Well...
- What is it?
Is someone with you right now?
The part-timer.
He's there?
Is it because you don't want anyone
to hear what you're about to say?
No, it's nothing. Bye.
Sol Ah?
- What is it this time?
- Are you alone?
I'm with the part-timer.
I see.
Is everything okay?
Yes, everything's okay.
- But why...
- I'll hang up then.
- Are you looking for Bang Guk Bong?
- What?
- No.
- Should I put him on the phone?
No.
I can't put him on the phone
even if you want to talk to him.
He's not here.
- Where did he go?
- I don't know.
Maybe he went to
the Uyuni Salt Flat in Bolivia.
What?
He's really not here.
- You got off work early.
- Yes.
Have a seat. Do you want coffee?
No, I just dropped by.
By the way,
where's Bang Guk Bong?
Did he really go on a trip?
Does he make you that nervous?
What? Me?
- What are you talking about?
- You're nervous...
that he might disappear again.
Just like me.
What's that?
He searched all over the place
to buy peaches.
Peaches?
(Sliced peaches)
My mom used to love peaches.
She passed away in the winter,
so I can't give her peaches.
He got this because of what I said?
He couldn't show up because
he was trying to buy peaches?
Of all the people, how could you...
Why does it have to be him?
I told you I'll be your friend
if you ever find someone new.
But not him. I don't approve of him.
I'm only giving this to you
because I can't stand...
seeing you so nervous
because of another guy.
(Sliced peaches)
Welcome home.
You didn't...
disappear.
(Episode 14)
I guess not all cats are the same.
You should've said you couldn't come
because you looked for peaches.
You can't get peaches in the winter.
Why not just come if all you had
were canned peaches?
I fell asleep.
You slept? Where?
You didn't come home either.
In the street.
Before I knew it.
Do you have something
like narcolepsy?
Can you not control
when you fall asleep?
It's something like that.
Oh, I see.
Thank you.
My mom will be pleased.
They're just canned peaches.
But they're tasty.
Hong Jo.
What?
I should go to the animal clinic
and get Hong Jo.
Oh, no.
He's at home.
I brought him home.
Hong Jo.
Is he upstairs?
Let's have a snack.
Here you go.
There.
Did it hurt a lot?
You're okay now. Eat all you want.
Hello, Ms. Bang.
Yes, I'm fine.
Thanks to you, my mom's...
It's only right that I take over.
My son left, didn't he?
No, not yet.
He's still there?
He usually leaves right after
he unpacks... No.
He just takes the same backpack
and sets off again.
He must like it.
What? Me?
That's impossible.
Not that.
You seem to get along well
with my son.
What's wrong?
Do you feel uncomfortable?
No, it's not really like that.
How strange.
Will my son finally settle down?
The truth is,
your father has changed a bit too.
He started writing poems again.
Did he really?
Thank you, Sol Ah.
For being my family.
"Family"?
Bang Guk Bong and I are family?
It's not like I'm going to
marry him.
We're not related by blood
or anything.
He started writing poems again.
No.
Dad is finally happy again.
Welcome home.
It's just like having someone
at home waiting for me.
Isn't that okay?
Oh, I don't know.
Why do cats sleep for so long?
I don't know.
I want to play with them.
I don't want to sleep either.
If I had a choice.
Adults drink coffee.
Coffee?
My grandma can't sleep
a wink at night...
if she has just one cup of coffee.
Is that true?
How long has Ji Eun
been away from work?
Is she so sick that she can't eat?
Welcome.
- I'll serve you right away.
- Thanks.
You can sit over there.
One meal, right?
Is she the girl who lives upstairs?
Yes.
Is she sick?
She always looked sick.
She does look
a bit more withered than usual.
It's just a grilled mackerel...
and she keeps sticking
her chopsticks in it.
- I can't stand it.
- She'll hear you.
That's how frustrated I am.
Mom, I'm hungry.
- Sure.
- I was out and came for lunch.
Sit down.
You're eating?
You're... You're eating.
You're eating.
Why are you eating?
What I mean is...
Why are you eating here?
This is my restaurant.
Your restaurant?
Doo Sik, do you know
the sickly girl...
Do you know the girl from upstairs?
What are you talking about?
The girl from upstairs?
They're his parents.
- Hey. Why is she running away?
- Wait.
You fool. What did you do?
I did nothing!
Oh, my goodness.
That was so humiliating.
Oh, no. I didn't pay.
Hey. Who is she?
It's a long story.
Tell us. Who is she?
My high school art club friend.
A friend?
But I don't remember her.
It was the awkwardness.
That's why she ran away.
She's my senior at work.
What? She's your senior?
Then why did she run away?
You should've stopped her!
I should've given her
some free food.
Don't you know how to
brown-nose your seniors?
- You idiot.
- I'm not done explaining.
- There's more?
- What's more?
The eraser.
A really heavy
and cumbersome eraser.
(Nalsaem Design)
You know how much
I hate heavy things.
I'm scared of them.
Oh, so Eun Ji Eun confessed.
She actually has guts.
Hey.
You should've told me if you knew.
What if I did?
Then I wouldn't have charmed her.
I'd have cautiously held back.
Do you dislike her that much?
It's too burdensome.
She kept my eraser for 10 years.
Do you think...
she moved in upstairs on purpose?
She did. And she
got this job on purpose too.
Hey.
If she knew it was
your parents' restaurant,
do you think she'd have
sat there to eat?
And you started working here
after she did.
I guess so.
Anyway, I don't think
I can face her again.
Welcome home.
Hey. Why do you look so happy?
I found a way.
What do you mean?
This.
As long as I have this,
I won't fall asleep.
Coffee?
You'll cure your narcolepsy
with coffee?
I won't leave you alone
from now on.
I'll always be by your side
when you need me.
There's no need for that.
I won't sleep at all
and stay with you all night.
If you want.
- Are you okay?
- Take this.
Did I do something wrong?
I'm sleeping over
at a friend's house tonight.
Where are you going?
(Devoted Mr. Gogalbi)
Sorry, my house is a bit cramped.
Sorry for suddenly asking
if I could sleep over.
What's wrong with your face?
I brought tteok-bokki.
Coffee?
Cats can't drink coffee.
It was okay to eat human food
when I was a human.
I can stay with Sol Ah as long as
I want now, as a human.
I said you can't.
I wonder why Sol Ah suddenly left.
She was probably
uncomfortable being with you.
Why? Why would she be uncomfortable?
I won't tell you.
It wasn't Jae Seon?
And he's...
He's...
connected to you like that?
You're better off than me...
who's living with a step-brother.
Yes, he's... He's...
connected to me like that.
You met him before.
Do you remember the bench near work?
The bench near work...
Oh, yes.
Did you say you gave him food
because he was hungry?
Yes.
But he was crying back then.
He was crying?
He cried so sorrowfully,
and it made me cry too.
It seemed like he understood
how I felt.
You're right.
He is like that.
I envy you.
Since he's that kind of guy.
There's nothing to envy.
I shouldn't like him.
Anyway, thanks for listening to me.
Actually,
you came to listen to me, right?
Did you hear about the eraser?
What do you mean...
I know...
you even brought tteok-bokki
to make me feel better.
This is so spicy.
This tteok-bokki is so spicy,
isn't it?
It's really spicy.
It's so spicy.
Don't cry.
It's just so spicy.
There's no need for me
to make this, is there?
I already have
a gigantic cat tower here.
- Morning.
- Sol Ah.
Hello.
Ji Eun came too?
- Hello.
- Good morning.
Ji Eun, you're back.
You have a lot of work to do.
Get feedback from the client
and make changes.
Yes, ma'am.
Aren't you going to work?
Hey, aren't you going to work?
I am working.
- It's a cat.
- How cute.
Look at that cat.
It's so cute.
It's adorable.
- Hello.
- Let's take a picture.
How pretty. How old are you?
It's so cute.
- Are you satisfied?
- You're doing a good job.
- How old are you?
- How cute.
- What's your name?
- It's adorable.
- It looks like a doll.
- It's so pretty.
Can I touch you?
- It's so cute.
- Hello.
Oh, my goodness!
Ji Eun, I'll send you
the final version.
I sent it. Check it.
- I got it.
- Okay.
I sent it.
We're finished.
We just sent you the revised draft.
Yes, that's why I'm calling.
It looks really nice.
She likes it.
By the way, can you change
the letters to a lighter color?
Sure.
And make the top drawing
a bit larger.
Oh, that's...
And I liked the font
from the previous version better.
I see.
Okay, I understand.
Then when can you send me
the revised version?
We'll do it as quickly as possible.
Give it to me. I'll talk to her.
She hung up.
You should know how to say no
at times.
If you do everything she wants,
you'll just waste your time...
and she will eventually say
she likes the first version better.
Right.
- Okay.
- Stop just saying okay like that.
Okay.
I need to get some fresh air.
We've met again.
I'm here to see Sol Ah.
She's working.
Shall I call her for you?
I just want to see her alone.
(Taekwondo Program)
Please sign up for our program.
Please take this.
Thank you.
I'm sorry, but could you move
your foot?
Over there.
Don't throw that away!
Give it to me.
Why are you collecting these?
Still, this is my drawing.
Why is this your drawing?
All you did was draw
what others asked you...
and revise it as they wanted.
It's still my drawing.
I even thought of working
somewhere else.
Since I make you uncomfortable.
But...
Still...
It's still my drawing.
I want to draw.
So I'll keep drawing.
Because I still like it.
I'll keep liking it.
Drawing...
or...
You're really burdensome.
Leave it. I'll...
Hey.
Page 14.
Revise it.
I can't do that now.
Where are you going?
To wash my face. I need to wake up.
Oh, I saw him outside earlier.
That... That...
That guy.
Bang Guk Bong?
Yes. He said he came to see you.
Oh, did he?
When was that?
He sat here and cried?
Why did he cry?
You're there doing that again.
Come on.
Stand in front of me.
That way I can ask you to
sit next to me.
I thought you'd feel uncomfortable.
You can sleep at home tonight.
I'll move if you feel uncomfortable.
Are you going somewhere?
A place I like.
That sounds like a nice place.
With whom?
Someone I like.
What?
Oh... Oh, I see.
Did you...
come here to say that?
Hey.
What was that about?
He likes someone?
He's really not home.
I'll give you something tasty.
Give me a moment.
Why does he have to be
Bang Guk Bong?
Why is that?
Not that again.
Hong Jo. This is a secret.
A secret you really
can't tell anyone.
You know,
I wish Bang Guk Bong
wasn't Bang Guk Bong.
She said she wanted me
to be Bang Guk Bong.
If he weren't Bang Guk Bong,
he could be anyone else
and that would be okay.
Even a cat?
I'd rather he were a cat.
I can't like Bang Guk Bong.
If Bang Guk Bong
weren't Bang Guk Bong,
even if he likes someone else,
I'd still tell him I like him.
I'd ask him to stay with me
and not leave.
I'd say that to him.
If Bang Guk Bong...
weren't Bang Guk Bong...
I would do this to him.
This.
Hey. Hey.
Where are you going, Hong Jo?
That bratty cat.
Hong Jo.
Where did he get to?
Hong Jo. My gosh!
Hey. What are you doing up there?
Do you want to join me?
What?
You said you were going
somewhere nice.
This is it.
Who is the person...
you like?
Hey.
Bang Guk Bong.
I'm not Bang Guk Bong.
Then who are you?
Why am I blushing?
Hong Jo.
(Welcome)
Sol Ah has eyes only for him.
I want to be with you.
Come somewhere with me.
I first saw you somewhere near here.
Why is your heart beating so fast?
So what if you know?
Sol Ah doesn't know who you are.
I'll tell her everything.
Don't you ever tell her.
Sol Ah will be left alone?
That's how it ends.
Without saying a word, just leave.
I want to see her.
- You're so cold.
- I waited for you.
There's not much time left.
Can't I stay a little longer?
Let's stay together
just one more day.