Do you know when it was?
I know how long it lasted.
(When My Love Blooms)
I don't think superstitions are always bad.
They're not, but it doesn't taste nice.
I'm sick of beans and tofu.
I apologize.
Where are all the people who wept when I went in?
Why are you alone?
They're all in the unexpected executive meeting.
They wouldn't be happy to see me after four years.
I'm not the Olympic Games.
You must really be careful. The atmosphere is really bad.
All your people were fired,
and the company's always frigid.
Frigid?
It suddenly turned freezing cold.
It'll get even worse.
Why? Is something wrong again?
A typhoon's moving in.
Why come all the way here when the weather's bad?
I don't like chain supermarkets.
Why is that?
Their goods are much cheaper.
That's why I hate them. That's why I got fired.
You even have a university degree.
Why work at a supermarket?
- Because I have a record. - A record?
- What kind? - The criminal kind.
It's quite something.
Ma'am. You should expect a special visitor.
What? A ghost?
Not a ghost. A special visitor.
A morning spider means a special visitor.
Evening spiders mean robbers.
Why did that thing come out here...
and spin another web up there?
Get lost.
(Hyung Sung Supermarket hiring university graduates)
Ji Su!
Yoon Ji Su!
(April 1993, Sinchon)
You brat. I yelled your name so many times.
Sorry. I was watching them.
We live and fight
They're protesting again. I'm so sick of it.
Our comrades live on in our hearts
Don't you think they have a cause?
I don't care about that.
Students should study.
Why are they always out here protesting in a time like this?
They do seem like they're from another world.
They look scary and furious.
Just think of them as aliens.
Aliens that will soon disappear.
Oh, that's not what's important.
I'm taking that professor's lecture.
For real? That's really...
It's raunchy. The assignment is to write a raunchy story.
Kids like you can never take that lecture.
I'm late. I have to run.
Bye!
With guns we fight on
Attack!
Attack! Attack!
Attack! Attack! Attack!
Run!
Copy me. Breathe deeply.
Don't you know what that means?
Inhale deeply.
Breathe out. Breathe in.
Breathe out.
Did a tear gas canister do this?
No, a Molotov cocktail.
Did they have to throw a vase?
Don't touch it.
Don't rub it. Press down on it.
Can you manage on your own?
Yes.
I didn't even ask for his name.
(March 5, 1993)
Is there a protest today?
What they did yesterday morning.
What happened yesterday?
When's the next protest scheduled for?
Without love, without honour
Without even leaving a name
We agreed to fight forever
- Is it any fun? - It's so much fun.
I was so surprised.
Hey. It's what you like.
You go ahead.
Next up is the keynote speech from Han Jae Hyun,
who majors in law.
(Stop making us sad.)
(The 13th Anniversary of Gwangju Uprising)
(Memorial for Democratic Martyrs and Opening Ceremony)
Hello, fellow students!
I'm Han Jae Hyun, class of 1995, studying law.
I fight for democracy...
and labour laws,
and greet you all today!
(Memorial for Democratic Martyrs and Opening Ceremony)
Today, to fight for a better tomorrow,
we take to the streets again.
Times have changed,
and some might ask why we still do this.
But listen!
There are still places and people who need us!
In Gwangju in 1980,
people fought for democracy...
and were cut down and shot by soldiers.
Without an investigation into...
who gave the order,
they were written off as communists and violent mobs.
In the name of redevelopment,
people are thrown out of homes they lived in for 30 years.
Under the excuse that they must prepare for a difficult future,
husbands and fathers are being let off with a short goodbye.
Our society swings too much to the right.
I'm not asking for the minimum respect and consideration.
I'm talking about the desperation of survival!
I found him. Han Jae Hyun.
(Books for Today)
(Music Records)
Take one.
Okay.
(Department of Law)
(Law Department Student Society)
Are you looking for someone?
What? Oh, class of 1995...
Who in that year?
There are so many.
- Han... - Jae Hyun?
Jae Hyun.
Someone's here for you.
She's really pretty. A class queen.
(Law Department Student Society)
Four years these days...
is enough time to remodel a whole landscape.
I'll be honest. The sentence was too tough.
Why do you think so?
The stock price manipulation and embezzling.
It was all the chairman's doing.
I'm sorry. Are you okay?
Is this what suddenly turning frigid means?
I apologize.
(No jaywalking)
Lady!
You can't jump out like that.
Sorry. My plastic bag tore.
Get out of the way.
I'm trying to do just that.
What are you...
- What are you... - It's my life's blood.
Lady!
I apologize. There was a weird lady.
What's that?
She took the bottle of water...
but left this behind.
That's a man's handkerchief.
She didn't look like the type to care.
You know women...
who don't mind wearing their husband's shorts or socks.
- Jun Woo. - Yes?
- Let's go to the company. - Okay.
What? You won't go home?
I must see the chairman first.
Dismissal is death! Cancel the dismissal!
- Cancel! Cancel! - Cancel! Cancel!
Mayflies only live for one day.
- Have some water. - We last two years.
That's how long our contracts last.
Anyone who works for over two years becomes a regular employee.
So the company fires us after two years.
We cry and beg...
and fight, but we keep getting fired.
That's how we spend those two years.
In fear.
Cancel the unfair dismissal!
- Cancel! Cancel! - Cancel! Cancel!
- Cancel! - Cancel!
What an eventful welcome ceremony.
Even if it were sewage and not an egg,
I'd have laughed like a lunatic.
It's my first day back in society.
Spending time behind bars is no easy feat.
- You did well. - Not at all.
Do you want to return to work?
I've been away for so long that I am a bit anxious.
Then go to the supermarket.
I put Seo Kyung in charge,
but I'm not sure she'll manage.
Four years will pass in no time.
Take the fall and hang in there for four years.
Then I'll make you my successor.
The women protesting down there.
I want them out of my sight.
You're the best at getting rid of people.
Why do you think they call you Scissorhands?
Yes, sir.
Jae Hyun.
Just because the hound brought back the hare,
did you ever see a hunter let the hound keep it?
A hound must eat what a hound eats.
If it wants the hare,
wouldn't the hunter get angry?
Yes.
You don't have to work right away.
You need to play some.
You always worked,
so did you forget how to play?
I'm not sure what to do, but I'll give it a go.
I'm a pretty quick learner.
Let's try living like a rock
Even if the wind and rain pound
We will not fall for any trick or lure
Let's try living like a rock
Hey, Young Min.
Shall I bring something tasty this weekend?
(Murderous Company)
Young Min, sorry. I'll call you back.
Thank you.
Not at all.
I'll stick this together and bring it back.
Don't bother. I should do that. This is about my son.
I have a son too.
So I want to help you.
They're such bad people.
What do the youth do to play?
They play games or drink alcohol.
Guys go and play billiards.
You say the landscape gets remodelled in four years,
so why hasn't that changed?
I don't know. How about a movie?
Some nice ones are out.
I don't like that.
Things like movies.
(Murderous Company)
(Hye Jung)
Call someone. Like the security guy.
I may be a mom with no femininity left in me,
but I don't want to advertise that I live alone.
How do you live alone when you're that timid?
It's fine.
I don't do much at night anyway.
I'll watch some TV then sleep early.
I can see just fine with some candles.
You sound like a madam from the Joseon era.
Why don't you just catch fireflies?
It's nice and cozy, like a cinema.
While others went to clubs,
you went to cinemas to watch movies.
Now you don't go near one.
Movie tickets are a waste of money.
They show it all on TV after a while.
I'm sick of your stories, so stop.
Hang in there for a few days and I'll fix it for you.
Will you?
(Karl Marx)
("The End of That Summer", Poems by Lee Seong Bok)
(From Ji Su to Jae Hyun again)
The resentment...
(Movie Special, "Love Letter")
They're showing "Love Letter".
(May 1993)
Do you have "Love Letter"?
Tomorrow at 3pm.
Come to Hendrix, 3rd floor of Nakwon Musical Instrument Arcade.
(Hendrix, Guitars, Amplifiers)
How will I recognise you, Dampopo?
I'll be in a white hoodie.
- Excuse me. - Excuse me.
Do you want "Love Letter" too?
You placed an order first.
Why are you just leaving?
You can have it.
You ordered it because you want to watch.
I'd feel bad to keep it for myself.
- Then what? - Let's watch together.
Dampopo said that...
the video will be too grainy if he makes another copy.
- Or if you watch it too much. - Forget it.
I won't tell anyone.
No one would believe me anyway.
Who'd believe that...
a hardcore protester watches sad Japanese movies?
Don't you speak Korean? I said forget it.
I want to watch "Love Letter" with you.
("Love Letter")
What are you doing?
It's a habit. I tend to exercise my fingers when I can.
It's distracting.
Okay.
That's dirty.
I always have a runny nose when you're around.
You saw me crying my eyes out twice.
That means you saw me at my worst.
- So you must take responsibility... - It's over. Leave.
Okay.
Wasn't the soundtrack of the movie good?
I can play pieces like that too.
There's this favourite piece I've been playing a lot lately.
Do you want to listen to it?
No.
That's a shame.
My fourth period on Wednesday is free,
so I always practice it in Room 301 at the Music Hall.
Forget it. Thanks for the movie.
When can I see you again?
What do you mean?
- When will we meet? - Why must we?
Because I want to see you.
Just go.
Why don't we date?
I'm busy.
Exactly. Why do you join the protests when you're a student?
Other people just stick to one thing.
Is that something I should be criticized for?
Let me join you too.
With my studies or the campaign?
The campaign.
I like doing campaigns too.
Right. When I was young, I used to compete in horse racing.
I'm running this campaign to get rid of bourgeois like you.
Your parents taught you horse riding and invested a lot to raise you.
If they find out you're joining the campaign,
your parents must be thrilled.
They didn't do that.
Which bus are you taking?
Bus 12.
It's here.
(Gaepo-dong to the entrance to Yonsei University)
I won't give up.
So you should give up instead!
I'll date you even if it means death!
Is it "Love Letter" again?
How could you watch a movie as soon as you come out?
That didn't mean you should turn it off.
Anyway, welcome back.
It must've been tough.
It must've been tough all by yourself too.
I'm sorry I couldn't pick you up in the afternoon.
It's okay. It's not like I came back with a gold medal.
And you must be busy now that you're the CEO.
That reminds me.
I'm going to Hawaii tomorrow.
- Hawaii? - It's not a personal trip.
It's a business trip.
To Hawaii?
I'm going there to research the industry if our supermarket...
can launch there.
Okay. Have a safe trip.
I'm really not going there for pleasure.
Okay. I got it.
Oh, right. I need to ask you to do something.
It's about Jun Seo.
Can you pay more attention to him?
Don't you feel bad that he was away from his father for four years?
It doesn't matter how much I'm there for him,
but you said boys always need their fathers.
I'll do my best, but...
I'll be busy too.
But you said you wouldn't come back to work right away.
I'm going to have fun...
to the fullest.
He made you stay in the slammer for four years.
Now, he's giving you the finger.
Unbelievable.
He said he'd make you the vice chairman of the headquarters.
How could you be the vice chairman of a supermarket?
It's the opposite. I'm grateful...
because he's doing exactly what I expected of him.
In the end, it's Hyung Sung Supermarket.
That's the last of the succession process.
It's the biggest in the corporate governance structure.
And did you do what I asked you?
I delivered the materials...
to the inspection agency of the media agencies.
I did what I asked,
but what's our ammunition?
Shares or real bullets. We don't have anything.
Pandora's box or the Trojan horse.
Can you put it in layman's terms?
Whether Pandora's box opens...
or the enemies spill out from the Trojan horse,
can they just sit back and watch?
Causing a scene and forcing the enemies...
to make their next move...
is our ammunition and weapon.
Do you understand that now?
I see.
By the way, I took a photo of your wife.
- A photo? - Yes.
Sir.
I'm sorry.
- Where were we? - Are you all right?
Hold on.
My son, what did you have for dinner?
Rice.
What about the side dishes?
Frogs?
Mom, I need to do my homework.
Fine. You never show me your affection.
You can hang up.
My gosh. My hands slipped.
I'm sorry, Smart Pauper.
I should go get my lunch again.
Now, we're mothers of the same international middle school.
Let's support our children...
and fix any problems together should they arise at school.
Sure. Don't worry.
There won't be any problems at school.
- Everyone comes from a good family. - Yes.
School violence is always done by kids from poor families.
- That's right. - Yes.
By the way,
I heard Young Min got first place for the finals again.
He always got first place ever since he started school.
I heard you studied piano in college.
What does his father do?
Actually...
He's a lawyer in Gangnam.
- Lawyer? - No wonder.
I don't know about other stuff, but intelligence runs in the family.
- Right. - Right?
Sometimes, rich people can be more frugal.
You're giving us cookies to celebrate your son's grades?
You must have your work cut out for you too.
Thanks to your son, the top student,
you have to chair the parents' committee.
I don't think she's the type to chat like we do.
- Don't make us sound so crude. - My gosh.
No, you can't. What are you doing?
I just heard Hwa Jin is dead.
- My comrade has vanished - My comrade has vanished
- Only the flag flaps in the wind - Only the flag flaps in the wind
- Until the new era emerges - Until the new era emerges
- Let's not be weak - Let's not be weak
- Time may pass by - Time may pass by
- The universe will know - The universe will know
- After waking up, we will scream - After waking up, we will scream
- At the top of our lungs - At the top of our lungs
It's been a while.
You look great.
Is it because you married a rich girl?
You still look better than ever even after staying in prison.
I just feel bad for the one who passed.
Everyone seems to have a great life.
Hey, Kyung Ho.
I get how you must feel.
You weren't going to follow through.
Why did you get her involved?
She would've gotten the scholarship for four years in college...
and been a great officer of the law if you didn't get her involved.
My foolish wife had...
a hard time leading the labour movement.
Couldn't you have asked her why at least?
It had been 20 years...
since she saw her old crush.
If you thought about the feeling she had to ask for money...
even for a minute, you wouldn't have done that.
So are you saying that Hwa Jin died...
- because of me? - That's right, you jerk.
I saw your interview in a magazine.
Even I was proud of you.
Is that why you came to see me?
Well,
no.
Then, what is it?
Can you lend me some money, Jae Hyun?
Kyung Ho and I...
have bad credit scores, so we can't take out a loan.
And we can't take out private loans anymore.
Can you accept money from me?
It looks like your civic group reported me and the company...
I work for to the Ministry of Labour.
Actually, all of my money...
is from the company.
I see.
I came to the wrong person.
I'm sorry. Things have been messy for me too.
- How much do you need? - Forget it.
I don't need it.
No, you're right.
I cannot take...
that dirty money from you.
(Mutual Aid Society Office)
(Wujeong Funeral Hall)
(LP Music Café)
Ji Su.
It was cancer.
She didn't have money,
so she couldn't get the surgery in time.
Didn't...
she have a child?
Yes.
She had an eight-year-old son.
She...
must have been in a lot of pain.
The pain must've been unbearable.
I'm regretting for the first time...
that I cut my ties with them and left.
If I didn't,
I could have been able to spend more time with her.
Back then,
you had no choice.
In 1, 2, 3.
Even when we take photos, we get three seconds to get ready.
But this kind of farewell doesn't give us any time.
And there's no warning...
or hint.
We're helpless.
When I left,
is this how other people must have felt?
This isn't the same thing.
Stop beating yourself for it.
I'm sure she went to a nice place.
She did a lot of good deeds.
Around my age, there are no happy occasions.
There are only bad occasions.
So you should get your medical checkups diligently.
Isn't that the only report card we'll get now?
It shows us the kind of life we have been leading so far.
And we can sort of see what kind of future we'll have.
I'm not scared of such report cards.
Then, what are you scared of?
Let's say that we miraculously meet again.
But I'm scared...
it might be at her funeral.
Are you talking about Yoon Ji Su?
Hey, don't you know she's young? It's too early for her funeral.
Hwa Jin was too young to die as well.
And besides,
I looked everywhere, but I couldn't find her.
Are you in the NIS? CIA?
How can you find everyone you want?
I'm sure she's hiding somewhere.
Is that so?
Hey, don't you know that she was clever?
People think she's delicate because she looks weak.
When she was in college, she was a total warrior.
She was like Black Widow. The one who roams around in tights.
My gosh, she scares me.
Engineer majors are the best!
I didn't learn to switch lights in college.
Is this how you utilize this top-level labour force?
I'll cook you something delicious.
The protest pays nothing. When will you keep that up?
You're so consistent. You never liked protests.
It's because I'm a pacifist.
I don't think I can do it this year.
Nice. I'm glad to hear that.
But why all of a sudden?
My father's caretaker wants me to raise her pay.
Didn't you say she was the only one who could handle him?
You should be grateful for her,
but isn't she taking advantage of that?
Hye Jung.
Yes?
I think I'm going to throw up.
I sit with the protesters and share a bottle of water some days...
and others, I hang around with mothers who buy clothes...
that are a month's worth of living for the protesters,
eating brunch at a hotel and chatting.
I feel so queasy.
That's why you need to stick to one thing.
That way you won't get confused.
I can't give up on the protesters,
and when I think of Young Min,
I can't say no to the mothers, either.
That's why I have to put on a mask and play the piano.
Whoever said you get focused when you reach 40...
should be given a beating.
We're all going crazy.
Who the heck is focused?
When I reach 40,
I thought I would be sitting elegantly in a massage chair,
looking at travel brochures,
rubbing oil all over my body...
in a heavenly beach,
and getting a tan.
Gosh, life.
I do visit heaven often.
Part-time Job Heaven and Gimbap Heaven.
(Gimbap Heaven)
I heard you're quitting.
Yes, I'm sorry.
Your son attends an international middle school, right?
Gosh, that must cost a fortune.
Isn't that a bit out of your league?
- Haven't you heard? - What?
He won several times...
at international Olympiads,
so the school gave him a full scholarship.
- They even pay for the expenses. - Goodness.
Is that so?
Then you should go and look after him...
instead of sitting around like this.
- Goodness. - I felt really bad.
I'll be coming out this week.
- Gosh. - You don't have to.
- Go on, already. - Yes.
Forget it.
That crazy punk.
Call the police.
No, the ambulance!
I'm dying here! Hurry!
(Homeroom Teacher)
(Jang Seo Kyung)
- Yes? - Who do you think you are?
I told you to look after Jun Seo, didn't I?
What are you talking about?
Jun Seo got hurt!
What?
Young Min...
threw a chair at his classmate.
But he won't say why.
Dad?
Why are you here? Where's Mom?
And Grandpa?
It's been four years, and that's all you have to say?
Oh, right.
I forgot.
Welcome back.
You've only gotten bigger in size.
What happened? Where did you get hurt?
Did you get hurt anywhere else?
- No. - Then tell me.
What happened?
There's this poor kid,
and he suddenly went crazy...
and threw a chair at me.
"Suddenly"?
Without a reason?
Yes. I didn't do anything.
You didn't have a fight?
But should I...
go to the hospital?
Jun Seo.
I'm really hurting.
I know something similar happened...
when you were in the sixth grade.
Are you sure you didn't do anything like that time?
No! That punk is the crazy one!
He's the annoying loser!
(Hwabon Station)
Like so, the defendant, Lee Se Hun,
is clearly responsible for the failure of this marriage,
but the plaintiff, Yoon Ji Su,
denies any monetary compensation,
including alimony and child support,
and only desires custody of Lee Young Min,
so the verdict shall be as follows.
Order.
The custody for Lee Young Min...
will be awarded to the plaintiff, Yoon Ji Su.
The duty of alimony...
and child support of the defendant...
shall be exempted as the plaintiff has requested.
Is your father in a critical condition?
Unless you're expecting any life insurance money,
what are you relying on?
I have no intention of raising Young Min...
with you or your mother's money.
I get what you're aiming at, but do you think it's possible?
If something happens to Young Min,
I'm going to file for custody.
I'm not giving up on you, either.
As long as we have Young Min,
you can never get too far.
I really don't know what to say.
This is a first since the school was established.
Why don't you bring him out, first?
I think this should be between the adults.
Yes, of course.
Yes, sir. Young Min, let's go.
He doesn't seem to be a bully.
Come on in, Ms. Yoon.
I'm sorry.
I apologize with all my heart.
If you show us mercy this once,
I will never let this happen again.
I know this is unforgivable,
- but he is still a young student. - Ma'am,
this isn't that simple of a matter.
The victim's father is here, so...
Gosh, he must be so outraged.
I'm sorry. Should I go after him?
Stay here.
Let's not set up the School Violence Committee.
But you just left, so I thought you were outraged.
I left because I didn't think I needed an apology.
But this is still school violence,
and for discipline, we should...
I'm here after seeing Jun Seo.
It's nothing to worry about so please end it here.
Young Min, you can tell me.
There's no way you could have done this without a reason.
You wouldn't even hurt a fly,
let alone a person.
Tell me. Did something happen?
But am I getting kicked out?
No.
They're letting it slide.
You don't have to worry.
So you really have to tell me what happened, Young Min.
Mom, I have homework to do.
Yes, I'll be there at about midnight.
Yes.
Then drive safely, sir.
No, actually, I won't be going.
Yes, it's snowing too hard.
I'll be leaving the car here, so come and pick it up.
All right.
(Last train to Hwabon, 9:30pm)
I think that's mine.
There you are.
Yoon Ji Su.
It's a winter wonderland here, isn't it?
With all this happening,
I guess I won't be getting home tonight.
Don't worry too much about the school.
Boys get into fights all the time...
at school.
There you are.
Yoon Ji Su.
(Those who fade away heartbreakingly...)
(leave a scar-like light in the hearts...)
(of those who knew them.)
(From "The Gray Snowman", by Choe Yun)
(When My Love Blooms)
I guess it happened...
because it snowed. A lot.
I wish more snow would fall. So we can't get anywhere.
You came to me every day and I didn't even have to try.
(I can go on because of you. Sorry and thank you.)
That's why I could go on with life.
- What do you think you're doing? - Let's play it by the law.
I'm not trying to teach you a lesson.
We just have different ways of protecting our love.