I beg of you, ma'am.
Please reconsider it.
If the reason you're trying to hold...
the committee is because it's your son...
Please take it out on me.
It's my fault for raising him poorly.
You can take it out on me...
however you like.
Then let's see what you can do...
to relieve my anger.
Please, ma'am.
Forgive him...
just this once.
Please get up.
What do you think you're doing?
Get up, Yoon Ji Su!
Explain what's going on.
What's going on?
- Ms. Jang. - Take Ms. Yoon...
and excuse us.
Sure.
I told you not to make this an issue.
You talked about a young boy's future...
and acted as if you were so righteous.
Was it about a woman?
Why did you call her name...
and act so besotted?
She's a university friend.
Your first love?
Like the film "Love Letter"?
I didn't want to turn the kids' problem into ours,
but you just won't listen.
What do you mean?
If you don't cancel the committee,
that Se Hwi.
The guy called Se Hwi will never get to model again.
He has nothing to do with this.
He has something to do with you.
You'll ruin someone's bright future over something like this?
I'd like to say...
the exact same thing to your face.
Do you know how much they donated to us?
If Jun Seo transfers to another school,
we'll have to stop working on the new gymnasium.
And we'll have to fire 4 or 5 teachers too.
- Did it have to be Jun Seo... - I apologize.
But I feel that...
my Young Min must've felt lonely.
This school's in the middle of nowhere,
so everyone feels lonely and wants to go home.
Do all lonely kids resort to violence?
What about your wife?
The School Violence Committee will not meet.
Did your wife agree...
If you go against me again, my son will change schools.
I'll drop you off on the way.
No, thanks.
We gave you a tough time.
You did.
It hurts.
My wrist hurts, and so do my knees.
Get in. A car ride is better when your joints hurt.
No, it's not my joints that hurt.
I'm not that frail yet.
I know.
My gosh.
Drop me off at the station. I can manage from there.
I'll drop you off at Seoul Station.
No. At the train station here.
You can't buy shoes here.
I can walk.
I wouldn't care if I hadn't seen,
but I did and I can't let you walk in that state.
You're not a starving kid.
What grown-up wears boots with a broken heel?
Are you okay?
- About what? - Your wife.
You bowed deeply twice,
and today you even went on your knees.
I can do that a hundred or a thousand times.
If only to stop my son from crying.
To me, that is love.
Not making someone cry.
So I understand your wife too.
We protect our love in different ways.
I'll say this just in case.
I didn't cancel the committee just for you.
He still denies it,
but I think my son bullied yours.
In elementary school, he was a ringleader...
and got into trouble for bullying other kids.
His mom's indifferent,
and his grandfather's always on his side,
so he didn't fear anything.
I'm ashamed to say this,
but I'll talk to Jun Seo.
You should talk to Young Min.
(When My Love Blooms)
I'll take you home. Your boots...
It's a minute if I run.
I might have shoes in the trunk. Wait.
It's really okay.
I'll take these.
These are for men, so they'll be big.
Still, they'll be better than that.
It's really okay. It's a hassle to return them.
You don't have to return them.
Wear them when you take out the trash.
They weren't at all expensive, so no pressure.
- Okay? - The pressure...
(December 1993)
Are you a huge rock star? Why are you the last to show?
My dad wouldn't let me come.
I had to sneak out.
You always trip up and you still want to protest?
Don't lose me.
Don't look anywhere else.
Follow my footsteps.
Are you all right?
What do you want?
Wow. Your face looks like it'll explode.
Everyone thinks you can drink a lot.
You can dupe others but not me.
I'm always looking at you.
Are you...
like "Misery"?
How did you know?
My gosh.
I thought you were like "Love Letter".
You're "Misery".
That's what people think,
but I'm more like the horror, thriller, psycho genre.
That doesn't mean I don't like "Love Letter".
It's such a nice story.
And the final scene is so moving.
The snow field scene is so sad.
You have...
beautiful eyebrows.
Sleep well, Han Jae Hyun.
I'm freezing.
(Jae Hyun, Ji Su)
Let's hear your love story.
I love melodramatic movies too.
So tell me.
I went to Jun Seo's school...
and found out her son was the other kid.
His grades are superb,
but his family's poor,
so she's been working hard to support him.
I thought if something were to happen to the kid,
things would get worse for her.
- That's it? - How about teaching Jun Seo morals?
He's doing what he did in elementary school.
Are you saying Jun Seo made him do what he did?
It's quite likely.
This is why I told you to...
pay more attention to him.
I'm not the kind of person...
who can teach or change someone.
I will pay more attention.
And if possible, I'll pick him up on Saturdays.
You should've done that before.
But honey.
Why won't you ask me about...
my relations with the model?
Do you not care?
It's not something to applaud you for,
but I feel partially responsible.
I was in prison for four years...
and was busy with work before then.
Is that it? Aren't you even angry?
It looks like you want to say something.
So I'll ask.
Why did you see another man?
When I happened to be...
away in the dark?
Because I was lonely.
I don't have friends or siblings.
All I have...
is Dad and you.
Neither of you were with me then.
So...
don't make me lonely.
I can't stand being lonely.
Liking someone who doesn't like me back.
I hate things like that.
Mr. Han looks great in a suit,
so even a basic design like this would work too.
Everyone knows he looks good in a suit.
But he has too many with the basic look.
I want something with a unique texture or design.
Okay. I'll ask our team leader when she arrives.
Did the gloves he bought you fit?
What do you mean?
When Mr. Han was last here...
Jin Young.
What is she talking about?
Did Jae Hyun buy something...
when he was here?
Was it a woman's item?
Well...
Bring it to me.
Let's see my husband's taste.
She's a university friend.
Get up, Yoon Ji Su!
Send in Secretary Kim.
What's the matter?
Number one.
You found Ji Su but didn't tell me.
Number two.
You liked Ji Su. Which is it?
Don't talk nonsense.
You met the real Yoon Ji Su?
Is she doing okay? No problems?
Her son goes to the same school as my son.
Wow, then she married into a rich family.
I was so anxious that...
she'd end up...
a divorcee who had left a violent husband.
So, is she still pretty?
It was number two then.
Number three.
What's that?
I think that...
Ji Su had a huge crush on me.
Didn't she mention me?
No.
Give me a moment.
Take your time. You can't pee if you rush.
Yes, ma'am.
Yu Ri's not free today?
That's too bad.
It's okay.
Thank you.
Hello, ma'am.
You said that Ha Young's sister wanted to learn the piano.
Really?
That can't be helped. Give me a call next time.
Thank you.
Ji Su!
It's been a while.
How long has it been?
About four days.
Really?
Wait.
My car's coming. Wait a little bit.
I'm fine.
I know you are. I want to lend you my umbrella.
It's really okay.
- I'll just... - You can run,
but it's cold.
Wait just a little. It'll be here soon.
Oh, and I'm not here for some nasty business.
I'm running away from a friend after we had a drink.
I didn't ask.
Right. You didn't ask.
I thought you asked.
Pop the trunk for me.
I'm really okay.
It'll be a hassle to return.
You can keep this too. I have a lot of umbrellas.
Then...
Thank you.
Goodbye.
Yoon Ji Su.
What about your bar?
- I closed early. - Why?
Because it's raining.
I want someone to pour me a drink.
Jae Hyun?
Where? How?
His son goes to Young Min's school.
It's an amazing school if Hyung Sung's heir goes there.
You knew who he had married?
Yes. I read about it. In a magazine interview.
Oh, that?
I read that too.
Did you meet Jae Hyun too?
Yes.
And?
Is he still cool?
Not at all.
He changed.
I thought he'd stay cool even with age.
Like a Hollywood star.
He does look a bit like George Clooney.
No way. How does he look like George Clooney?
His eyes. They wrinkle when he smiles.
Whose eyes don't wrinkle at that age when they smile?
They aren't just wrinkles. They have a certain depth.
They're deep because he's old.
No.
There's something sexy and dignified about them.
You're still head over heels in love with him.
(December 1993)
Oh, come on!
Okay, my bad.
Isn't he just so good-looking?
This is insane. What exactly is good-looking about him?
He's so thin, he looks like a withering bean sprout.
Look at how he moves.
Whenever he gets the ball, foot volleyball turns into ballet.
That's why he's so useless. Because he's dancing, not kicking.
- Here you go. - It's mine.
What was that? Was that ballet?
Will you kick properly?
- You said it's your ball. - When did I say that?
It wasn't even in my direction.
Nice one.
Jae Hyun finally looks like a real university student now.
Jae Hyun, Jae Hyun.
Are you a flatfish? With eyes just for one man?
I wish he'd play sports instead of protest.
Wake up. As if a dog can quit eating poop.
No dog can be that handsome.
You're not just head over heels in love. You have a disease.
Kick properly.
Go on home.
Shall I come along when you get Young Min?
It's a long train ride.
Forget it.
My feelings for you are a disease.
A terminal disease.
- Hey, Dong Jin. - Where are you?
You're still there?
I thought you were pooping.
Did you leave to avoid paying the bill?
Hey. Are you really short on cash these days?
You asked how much lawyers make.
Why are you acting out of character?
Hey, Dong Jin.
How about your kids learn to play the piano?
My kids? Sure, why not?
One is a year old and the other is three.
It's time they learn the piano, and they're both boys too.
Yes, it's time.
What do you mean it's time?
- Dong Jin. - What do you want now?
- When will it next rain? - Are you barking mad?
Ask that to the weather forecaster. You jerk.
(Class rank: 11, Overall class rank: 50)
(Dad)
Son, didn't you get your report card?
Hey, Jun Seo. I'm here. Come down now.
Okay.
Aren't you Young Min?
Do you remember me?
I'm Jun Seo's father.
Hello.
Hi.
Do you not like me?
Because I might be on his side?
Not all dads are on their sons' sides.
I'm on the losing side.
I wanted to tell you this.
I'm sorry.
But I was the one who messed up.
It's not about just winning, losing, or making mistakes.
Given what happened, I'm sure my son is responsible for this too.
How do you know that?
I just do.
Some things become obvious at my age.
Which brings me to my question.
It looks like you're troubled.
Does Jun Seo still bully you?
I see.
That's not the only reason.
My grades went down a lot.
Young Min.
It took me all night yesterday to follow the recipes from...
Mr. Baek and Kim Soo Mi.
Try it.
I'm not hungry.
Come on. You should eat some though.
The school can give you all the food you want,
but it's not good.
Hold on.
Aunt Hye Jung bought this...
for you because you're still growing.
Isn't it good?
Jun Seo's dad...
is very different from Jun Seo.
Is that so?
How did he seem?
He's kind...
and warmhearted.
He looked kind of cold to me.
I was never envious...
of his rich family.
But I'm kind of envious that he's Jun Seo's dad.
But you have an awesome mom.
Young Min,
I want you...
to worry as much as a kid around your age.
What do you mean?
"What will happen if I do this?"
"I shouldn't do that, right?"
"Yes. Let's just put it up with a bit longer."
Stop thinking about others.
If you're hurt, tell me that you are.
"Why is everyone bothering me?"
Get upset like this too.
Just like you threw a chair at Jun Seo,
I'm sure he must have given you a hard time too.
And you're dealing with it on your own.
And all the adults are talking about how awful throwing a chair is.
Young Min.
You're not an adult.
Why are you putting up with this by yourself?
That's cheating. And it's illegal too.
But you're alone.
You have to make money by yourself...
and raise me by yourself.
And my grandparents can't help you either.
You must do everything by yourself.
And if something happens to me,
you have to stop everything and come to me.
That's why you should tell me everything.
We only have each other.
That's right.
I'm the only one you have,
but if I kicked out of school,
Dad might take me from you.
Young Min.
No one can take you from me.
Actually, you don't know about this,
but I'm like...
Black Widow or Captain Marvel, the characters you like.
I'm as strong as those superheroes.
Get that. My gosh.
Are you okay? Does it hurt?
I'm not crying because it hurts.
I heard you've been working. But nothing has changed.
I told you to get rid of those women.
Are you rebelling against me?
No.
Why are you making him do such dirty works?
He has other people for that.
He's the best at getting rid of people.
Do you not want to work?
No.
Then, get rid of them within a week.
I can't let our company get messy with those lowlives.
The foreign buyers are visiting us.
Yes, sir.
Instead of removing those women,
why were you meeting up with the head of Seoul Bank?
Do you need money?
I don't think he's tailing me yet.
From assemblymen...
to Madam Jung in Cheongdam-dong.
I heard the old geezer has a lot of connections.
I guess it was all true.
It's not a surprise at all.
That's how he grew his company.
The surveillance cameras from the police will be watching you.
I can't be caught on those surveillance cameras.
So we need to make a move without letting them know.
- Can you do it? - Yes. I must be invisible.
Right. Get me the list of workers who got fired.
I need to look into someone.
(Application: Name, Yoon Ji Su)
What's her angle?
Doesn't this look like she approached him on purpose?
She was hired when the vice-president was imprisoned.
It's a bit tricky to say.
Does Jae Hyun know?
Unless she told him about her situation,
he wouldn't have found out.
There are over 1,000 workers...
who were terminated.
He cannot know.
If he finds out about her divorce, her job, and this termination,
his heart would break, given his character.
If he has an affair with her,
it will hurt my pride.
It's like their love is real.
Okay.
Raise your son well. And stay healthy.
I'm sorry.
Good job, Ji Su.
Gosh, you don't have to say it. We all know how you feel.
Just don't forget about us.
I won't.
I will never forget you.
The management of Hyung Sung Supermarket must wake up!
- Wake up! - Wake up!
Termination is murder! Cancel the unfair dismissal!
- Cancel! Cancel! - Cancel! Cancel!
The management of Hyung Sung Supermarket must wake up!
It's going to rain tomorrow. Can I see you tomorrow?
I need that umbrella back.
And I need to talk to you too.
The management of Hyung Sung Supermarket must wake up!
How strange. I definitely heard it was going to rain today.
Thank you for the umbrella.
Do you want something to eat?
I already ate.
By the way,
what did you need to talk about?
Is it about school?
- No. - Then, what is it about?
I'm not sure if you know,
but I'm the vice-president of Hyung Sung Supermarket.
And I found out that you used to work there...
as a temporary worker and were fired recently.
You don't have to explain what happened,
but I just...
don't want you to join the protest in front of the building.
Why shouldn't I join them?
I was unfairly fired too.
We will take legal actions.
From what I have learned, we didn't violate any law.
I don't want you to get hurt from this.
I can help you look for another job.
Are you asking me to leave them?
No.
I believe raising your son...
should take priority over anything.
You know everything.
Did you have someone look into my past?
You sound like a different person.
You're not the guy I used to know.
Yes.
I'm a completely different man.
I am incredibly selfish and materialistic.
The temporary workers who are protesting right now...
will be removed for causing illegal labor disputes,
occupying the property without permission,
and obstructing business.
So...
it's better if you stay out of it.
No.
Is it some kind of loyalty for your colleagues?
Or is it a sense of justice?
You won't make money off it anyway.
Why?
I learned it from you.
You taught me the losing side...
is our side.
(January 1994)
- Ji Su. - What happened?
Jae Hyun and other members are in Hyeonjeo-dong...
to the PV campaign.
They called us to say they need us.
- PV campaign? - It's like the farming campaign.
It's a campaign to help poor villages.
I didn't know you did that.
We do all sorts of campaigns.
- I don't have much time. Bye. - Okay.
Hey, give back my ddakji!
Come on, give back my ddakji.
- Hey! - Let's go!
Just take them down!
Hey!
Go!
- What is this? - Come on!
Leave!
- Hey, you jerk! - Take them down.
Goodness.
Didn't Young Woo tell you?
What?
What the campaign was for.
Your outfit today...
I didn't know. I'm sorry.
Your good clothes must've gotten ruined.
Good job.
Jae Hyun, why do you protest...
Why do you participate in this campaign?
You don't have time to study or have fun like other students.
You're always chased and get hurt.
How could you participate in campaigns every day?
I want the losing side to be my side.
Everyone says the winning side is their side.
And the losing side is always lonely and sad.
I'm on the side of those people who always end up losing.
That's what I want.
You taught me that I should side with the people...
who always end up losing.
That's what you taught me.
Should you be taking sides right now?
If you do, you might end up losing.
It doesn't matter.
I don't have much experience in winning anyway.
I haven't won a lot in my life,
but I'm not ashamed of my life.
And I don't want to change that for you of all people.
It's somewhere around here.
Where, sir?
Hyeonjeo-dong.
It's the last place where I still had a conscience.
Sir, the micro-dust level today is pretty high.
When it comes to toxicity, I can beat micro-dust, hands down.
Why would you say such a thing?
Right.
The micro-dust must feel offended.
They don't mess up with other people's lives.
Did something happen today?
I'll be on your side.
You're on the losing side.
So you must be lonely too.
So I'll take your side.
Teaming up with me will be hard. You can't handle it.
Being in Hyeonjeo-dong today...
felt strange and was heartbreaking.
After listening to you,
my heart keeps pounding.
And I feel overwhelmed with a surge of emotion.
I told you not to come.
This kind of activity doesn't suit you.
I have a lot of people on my side.
You should go back to your place.
I have a meeting to get to. Take the bus and go home.
It's Ji Su.
I'm in front of your house.
I don't think I can just go home today.
There's something I'm dying to tell you.
And I want an answer from you too.
I'll wait for you. I won't leave until you get here.
(Sinchon Station)
You're a pianist. You should put on some gloves.
They are cold as ice.
Whether it's the organization or assemblies, don't come.
The era we live in doesn't require people to risk their lives.
You're not desperate for a change or believe in the cause.
To me,
you are my belief and my world.
So I will do everything you believe in.
And I'll be on the same side with you...
and live in the world you live in.
I won't change my mind, so quit trying to change it.
Meet me at Room 310.
It's the club I founded.
Is that about philosophy too?
No, movies.
And...
we're dating as of today.
Jae Hyun used to be on my side,
my belief,
and my world.
Your belief...
doesn't exist anymore.
We told them we'd negotiate,
so I'm sure all the leaders will be present.
And a lot of people will be present to show them their support.
But there's nothing we can use as bait.
I'm sure they just want to be reinstated back to their positions.
But we can't allow that.
It's a formality and an act.
We're just building a history.
The negotiation will end within 30 minutes.
Then, I'll insert the police as soon as it's over.
Sure.
I'm neither educated...
nor went to college.
I'm not sure if I can do this.
Don't worry.
You know better than anyone...
what the people want.
My gosh. Should I take some relaxing pills?
They suddenly want to talk now.
I'm nervous.
I heard that the new vice-president was...
one nasty man.
But I heard he's not a bad person.
He's smart and reasonable.
Hey, I'm worried because he's smart.
I don't know what he has up his sleeve.
Besides, he's the son-in-law of the chairman.
So he'll side with the company.
But still, it's huge progress.
No one from the company was willing to meet with us before.
I'm sure it will go well. The world has changed a lot.
Right?
Yes. Then, let's go and have just one drink.
I won't be able to sleep without a drink.
You'll negotiate with them?
Who told you could do that?
You didn't even talk to me first.
Didn't you tell me to take care of it?
Is your four-year imprisonment causing this?
You're not acting like yourself.
It's a formality.
The result won't be different.
Make sure to report everything about the negotiation.
Sure. I'm going out for some fresh air.
Ji Su.
Yes?
You know,
I don't think we'll win.
But still, we won't go down without a fight.
Whether you lose or win,
I'll be on your side to the end.
(Three-way Supermarket)
("The End of That Summer")
(From Ji Su to Jae Hyun again)
(Application: Name, Yoon Ji Su)
(Name, Yoon Ji Su)
Yes, Seo Kyung. What is it at this late hour?
Cancel bringing in the police today.
- Pardon? - I already talked to the chief.
I'll try to negotiate with them first.
I'll decide afterward.
May I ask why all of a sudden?
Just proceed as I asked.
Okay.
- No temptation can waver us - No temptation can waver us
- Let us live a life of a rock - Let us live a life of a rock
- Only the reeds with weak stems - Only the reeds with weak stems
- Will be swayed by the wind - Will be swayed by the wind
- The rock rooted in the field - The rock rooted in the field
(Police)
It's the chairman's order.
Stay out of it.
Let go of me!
Is it some kind of loyalty for your colleagues?
Or is it a sense of justice?
You won't make money off it anyway.
I learned it from you.
You taught me the losing side is our side.
(Police)
(When My Love Blooms)
I am my own guardian.
Whenever you act strangely, that woman is involved.
I still don't understand why you left the way you did.
I should put her in her place.
I want to be happy.
I'll make a choice different from the ones I did so far.