There you are.
Yoon Ji Su.
I should have found you sooner.
I'm so late.
You didn't find me.
We ended it.
How could I not look for you?
Why did you go into hiding?
I kind of understand,
and I also resented it.
Before I could do anything,
we parted helplessly.
It was as if I had a fishbone lodged in my throat.
I'm sorry but...
I don't remember the past much.
To be honest,
I don't have many memories of you.
Thank you for dropping it.
And I'm sorry your son was hurt.
His name is Young Min?
He seemed sweet and cute.
I don't yet know why the two fought.
There's nothing to be sorry about...
or grateful.
Anyway,
thank you. I should go.
(When My Love Blooms)
(Episode 2)
(Hwabon Station)
Even a senior you don't have many memories of...
will be a useful guide.
I helped at many rural communities.
I know my way around countrysides like this.
- Who's there? - My gosh!
I won't ask you to hold my hand.
Just stay close.
It's okay.
Okay then.
Don't lose me. Follow my footsteps.
Don't lose me.
Don't look anywhere else.
Follow my footsteps.
C sharp minor. 9. 9, 9.
B7 and 13. Teen, teen.
Teen.
What, is this math or music?
Today, all of us
Gathered around together
We bless
Your future
Tomorrow, Civil Law
The day after, Criminal Law
One by one, my exams are approaching
Tomorrow is Labor Day
The day after is the Opening Ceremony
Day by day, we fight and fight
Love and dating
I'd love to give that a try
The only person I can page is Lee Dong Jin
- I'm ruined - Why are you still here?
My gosh.
Why are your eyes closed?
You're such a joke, you are.
(GMAT Special Lecture by Kim Gi Hwan)
I think that's mine.
There you are.
Yoon Ji Su.
You know my name?
It was in huge letters on your sheet music.
Oh. You remembered.
That handkerchief was expensive.
It doesn't look too expensive.
My mother's gift when I started university.
Oh, I'm sorry.
I meant to return it.
No, you keep it.
Why?
Your snot and hair grease. It's dirty.
I didn't tie my hair with it. You called before I could.
And I can't keep your mother's gift.
I have five more. It was a set.
So stop hanging around my society...
and study.
No one studies.
- What? - The seniors protest...
and freshmen get drunk.
No one studies.
You learned all the bad things.
We study really hard.
We read and debate every day.
If I study hard, will you date me?
No... No.
Your cassette tape.
You dropped it on the grass.
I didn't listen to it.
Hand it over.
If the chord's too hard, can't you just change the note?
Forget it.
I memorized it.
Still, forget it.
I don't want to.
The song's nice,
and you're even nicer.
I realize that you're just another person,
and unlike when you protest,
you're quite cute.
You...
Don't show that you know me.
As if she doesn't remember.
She kept my handkerchief for over 20 years.
As if I don't remember.
I even remember the song.
Love
And dating
I'd love to give that a try
The only person
I can page
is Lee Dong Jin
(Bed and Breakfast)
She still sweeps with her foot.
Young lady, take this.
It's your breakfast.
I put some rice water on the boil.
Take this.
The rice water tastes really nice today.
Are you two just dating?
If you're married, you wouldn't take separate rooms.
Even more so if this is an affair.
It's neither. We're just friends.
What a joke.
Men and women can't be friends.
Why not? Friendship can cross genders.
How do you know so much?
Those special terms.
I watch a drama every day before I watch the 9pm news.
That's all they talk about.
People slap each other over affairs,
and sometimes they even fling kimchi.
Gosh, it's such a sight.
I hope it snows some more.
So we get stuck here.
Can I take a look?
Let me see.
Hold this.
It won't come out.
- It's fine now. - I'm almost done.
It came out.
Isn't your family worried?
They said it's fine. To take my time.
Good.
From what I saw of your kid, his dad must be a nice man.
Can I ask what he does?
He's a lawyer.
Is he?
Then he must've studied law like me.
Was he from our university?
Jae Hyun.
These conversations make me uncomfortable.
Thank you for yesterday and today,
and if I owe you, I'll pay you.
That's all.
I want to deal with it as parents of two classmates.
I feel uncomfortable listening to...
old stories I barely remember.
Okay. I understand.
The sun's up now, so let's each go our own way.
Welcome back, sir.
I'll take you home,
then go back for your car.
- Hey, Jae Hyun. - Hey.
How much do lawyers make?
- Do you want to become one? - No.
Is it tough to make a living?
It depends on the lawyer.
A civil-rights lawyer or a public defender...
could struggle financially, right?
Hey, are you getting fired? Does the old man want you gone?
I gave you some detailed advice...
to put away some cash.
You jerk. Thanks anyway.
- Jun Woo. - Yes?
The person who dropped this handkerchief.
You had that.
I was going to throw it away.
What did it look like the woman did?
I don't know.
She had a bag full of 500ml water bottles.
Does she sell them?
Anyway, you know the typical middle-aged woman.
Relentless and thick-faced.
She was pretty though.
I bet she was popular back in the day.
- Find out about her. - Pardon?
Come on, sir.
Because she's pretty?
You almost hit her in the street...
and you want to ignore that?
What human does that?
- Is that how I taught you? - No, sir.
I know nothing about her.
- I do. - Pardon?
Her child goes to Jun Seo's school.
What? Really?
(Convalescent Ward)
(Homeroom Teacher)
I keep asking Young Min,
but he won't say what happened.
Young Min won't say.
The meek and sweet little boy...
threw a chair at a kid.
And I completely forgot about that.
From last night until now.
I'm a bad mom, aren't I?
It snowed.
It snowed a lot. Maybe that's why.
This season thing really gets to me.
I wish there were only one season,
but there are four.
Each one of them is pretty and heart-fluttering.
They come hand-in-hand with him.
On some days, he comes with the wind.
On some days, he comes with the flowers.
On some days, he comes with the rain.
When I close my eyes not to see him, I can remember him more vividly.
When I drink because I feel so miserable,
he shows up in my dream without a warning.
He shows up every single day even when I don't do anything,
so I couldn't live my life.
No.
Actually,
I could live because of his memories.
I imagined us meeting again over hundreds of times.
But what happened yesterday...
wasn't in any of the scenarios I thought of.
Why did we have to meet again...
when I was the most pathetic and miserable?
They are my wife...
and my daughter.
Aren't they beautiful?
But it was nice seeing Jae Hyun again.
That's why I can understand...
how much pain you must be in, Dad.
Sir, your wife is home.
Can we talk?
Do you run a charity?
I thought you already donated enough of your money.
What's your point?
Who told you we would let this incident slide?
Who said you could let that kid off the hook?
Should I have put him in prison or something?
Of course. He attacked our son.
It's nothing serious.
And he's still a kid.
It's worse because he's only a kid.
He's already violent toward other kids at that age.
What if his aim was better and the chair hit our son?
Didn't you think about that?
Check on Jun Seo first.
See if he made any mistakes.
Even if he did, that doesn't matter!
I'm already annoyed...
that he's going to school with my son for free.
We'll settle this? We won't press charges?
That will never happen!
If you do this, you'll only ruin our son.
I heard a few things about the incident,
so don't dismiss my decision.
Can we talk?
I don't like beating around the bush. I'll cut to the chase.
I want you to resign your position as the chairperson of our committee.
It won't be pretty if we object.
I want you to tell the school that you'll resign.
I didn't take the position because I wanted to,
so I can tell the school I'll resign,
but may I ask you why?
I heard about Young Min.
Well, it's not just about him.
The problem is you.
You lied to us more than I can count.
You're divorced.
I guess you don't need to disclose that since it's your personal life.
But you're working at a supermarket.
That's a bit appalling, you know.
Another parent saw you doing a protest in front...
of the supermarket headquarters.
Was she wrong?
Must I disclose my personal life...
to you?
You shouldn't have deceived us at least.
I'm sorry if you felt I deceived you.
I didn't want to tell you because I didn't want you...
to judge my son based on my decision.
Let's be honest. Weren't you embarrassed to tell us?
You already knew that you wouldn't...
be able to socialize with us.
That part is true.
Dealing with school stuff and eating brunch at the hotel was too much.
This all worked out. I'll tell the school.
Unbelievable. How could you be so brazen?
Aren't you going to apologize?
You must have forgotten already.
I already did 30 seconds again.
(Lee Se Hun)
What is it?
Tell me what you couldn't tell me on the phone.
This is rude. You didn't even knock.
I keep my manners only to humans.
Did something happen to Young Min?
No.
Really?
- Nothing happened. - That's odd.
Why is his cell phone turned off then?
It's been off for two days.
Didn't you call him?
He called me with his friend's phone.
He said his phone was broken.
I see. Is that so?
If this is it, you should tell me on the phone.
I can't see your eyes on the phone.
Our eyes can't lie.
I will never come to your office again.
You should try to find a way to tell if I'm lying or not...
through my voice.
If you settle, your charge can get acquitted.
I won't settle.
If the court accepts you did this on purpose, you'll serve time...
when you shouldn't serve time.
It was neither an accident nor done in the heat of the moment.
He mocked the accident...
and ridiculed my bereaved family.
He didn't show any signs of remorse or repentance.
I...
intended to do it.
I'm going to tell the world...
what he did.
The phone is turned off. You'll be directed to the voicemail box.
(Homeroom Teacher)
The receiver cannot be reached.
Termination is murder! Cancel the unfair dismissal!
- Cancel! Cancel! - Cancel! Cancel!
Cancel the unfair dismissal!
The management must wake up!
- Wake up! - Wake up!
Hey.
It's about the woman you wanted me to look into.
Yes. What did you find out about her?
She's divorced.
She's divorced?
Yes, three years ago.
That can't be right.
As of now, it's just her and her son on her family register.
Does it mean she's raising her son alone?
Yes, it seems like it.
Then, what about her ex-husband?
Is he paying her alimony?
He's a lawyer at a law firm.
They had a divorce lawsuit.
In exchange for getting the custody of their son,
she gave up on receiving alimony and child support.
How does she get by?
Does she have a job?
No, not really.
It looks like she has a few part-time jobs.
(Make sure to turn on your headlights.)
Yes, hello.
Ms. Yoon. You called me earlier.
Yes. Young Min's cell phone is turned off.
I was worried if something happened to him.
No, nothing happened. He was in all of his classes.
Really?
I'll tell Young Min to call you.
Okay. Please tell him to call him.
And...
there's one more favor I wanted to ask you.
Sure, go ahead.
If his father calls,
could you not tell him about the incident?
I don't want him to worry.
Okay. Thank you.
What is it? Did I annoy you?
I must have lost my mind when I hurt my head.
It's because of you, so I hope you understand.
- When the dawn breaks - When the dawn breaks
- The red sun soars high - The red sun soars high
- Our bloody heart turns into a rage - Our bloody heart turns into a rage
- And becomes a massive wave - And becomes a massive wave
- Even when people are out to get us - Even when people are out to get us
- We will defeat them and become one - We will defeat them and become one
And you must quickly decide what you plan to do...
with the temporary employees who have been protesting...
for over a month now.
What do you think I should do, Mr. Park?
We didn't violate the contract.
But they are arguing that the contract itself was unfair.
- I want us to stick to the law. - Put yourself in their shoes.
Most of them are housewives in their 40s and 50s.
If we just terminate them at this day and age, they will...
start petitioning and cause quite a mess.
Then, what do you suggest that we do?
Just let them be.
It looked like they were having fun. It's like they're on a picnic.
Do you think they'll break down the door and barge in here?
Right.
Talk to the legal team...
and bring me a plan.
Don't ask me questions like you're giving me a quiz.
Okay.
We'll pretend to negotiate the terms and stall time.
And they'll be forced to disband.
Illegal labor disputes, occupying our building without permission,
obstruction of business, and so on.
Gather all the evidence that could forcefully remove them.
Yes, sir.
By the way, why aren't you getting married?
Wait, did you already get married once?
I can't believe no one made a move on such a handsome man like you.
- No way. - I'm sure he had a girlfriend.
You couldn't choose because you had too many, right?
I liked a girl,
but she didn't know for 25 years...
because she's like a horse at the racecourse.
Well, it's not that bad.
She won't...
at least tell me she wants to break up.
Hey.
Let's go.
You should sit here.
- Pardon? - We finished our drinks.
- But you didn't. - Have a good day.
- Let's go. - Good luck.
Good luck.
What do they mean by that?
They want me to have a busy night.
Is it obvious that I drink a lot?
A bit.
I think I smell alcohol from you too.
Really?
(Law Department Student Society)
(May of 1993)
Hey, isn't that you?
Yes, it's you. The pretty girl who came to look for Jae Hyun.
Are you here to see him again?
Yes, I need to give something to him.
Give me that. I'll give it to him.
No, I don't want to.
There's a way you can meet Jae Hyun every day.
Join our club.
What kind of club is it?
Solidarity of Philosophy. It's a philosophy club.
What a name.
The name is a bit pretentious,
but we just study philosophy there.
I don't know much about philosophy.
We don't know much either.
That's why we meet up and study.
This club isn't strictly for law majors. It's a college club.
You can join if you want.
Jae Hyun is the principal assistant administrator,
so he attends the seminar every week.
He's actually in the club room more than the room for law majors.
Really?
(Books for Today)
We write down where we'll meet on this board.
That's Jae Hyun's.
Jae Hyun drinks at the bar often.
I'll know where he is once I look at this board.
Some people write in code not to give away where they are.
But usually, everyone is welcomed.
It's more like, "Come if you want to drink."
"Let's drink until we drop."
And Jae Hyun practically lives at this bookstore.
(Books for Today)
(Hyun Yi, meet me at Manmiru by 4pm.)
(Jun Seok, 12pm at our hideout.)
(Books for Today)
By the way, did a tall and handsome student come here?
Most of my customers here are tall and handsome.
But he must stand out among them.
He's a junior law major. His name is Han Jae Hyun.
- I see. Jae Hyun. - When will he come?
I don't know.
Then, what kind of book does he buy?
What a coincidence.
Do you come here often too?
- Move. - What?
You're blocking my way.
I see.
("Even Birds Leave the World")
Thank you.
See you.
- Miss. - Yes?
Jae Hyun told me to give you this.
("The End of That Summer", Poems by Lee Seong Bok)
("Closer to You 2")
I keep standing on my toes
Yet I still do not see you
At times when the waiting grows longer
I can not help but resent you
Cirrus clouds float through the dark skies
What song shall I have to sing
In order for it to reach your ears?
We never met, so we shall never part
Yet we can not hold hands, though we never parted
So as the waiting grows longer
I can not help but resent you more
(I can not help but resent you more)
Is something wrong?
What is it?
I'm trying to decide...
what to tell you first.
I've decided.
Hurry up.
Young Min will be back in two days,
and I still haven't gone grocery shopping.
Come on, you...
I should go before they close.
She hasn't changed a bit.
Why isn't she wearing any gloves?
And her jacket is too thin.
(3 Ice creams for 1 dollar, Soda for 1.5 dollars)
Goodness.
Who is this for?
It's for me.
Gosh, why?
Why would a lady need to drink that much?
Then what am I supposed to do?
Do what?
I already have a hard time falling asleep,
and now it's going to get worse.
Why?
I shouldn't be acting like this.
I need to get a grip, but it keeps coming back to me.
It's driving me crazy!
Where are you?
Did you fall in a well or something?
Why aren't you back? Why?
Hurry up, already!
Thank you.
Here. Oh, gosh.
I'll help you take this to the door.
No, it's all right.
This is heavy.
Oh, thank you.
No problem.
Have we met before?
I have a common-looking face, so I'm used to that.
You don't look so common.
Oh, really?
I wonder why everyone says so. That's odd.
Goodbye, then.
- Good job. - No problem, sir.
She went inside. Should we go?
- Yes, let's go. - All right.
May I ask how you know her?
No, you may not.
Yes, sir.
- Hey, Jun Woo. - Yes, sir?
Could you come straight here in the morning...
for a few days?
- Sorry? - See where she's headed...
and what she's doing.
Yes, sir.
It's not stalking, and it's not a crime.
Just think of it as good will.
All right, sir.
I know her from college.
She was a nice, smart kid.
(To Jae Hyun)
(Thanks to those moments that were as pretty as flowers,)
(I think I can go on. Sorry and thank you. Jae Hyun.)
These are the gloves you were looking for, sir.
They are all new this season.
Okay.
Are they for your wife?
No.
Oh... All right, sir.
You don't have to tell her, either.
Of course, sir.
I'll take these.
Yes, sir.
Yes?
Mr. Han.
Are you doing your job?
I am, but...
Ms. Yoon is...
Is what?
She's at the office, sir.
What?
(Cancel the unfair dismissal!)
Young Min, how long are you going to keep ignoring my messages?
This is foul play.
(Cancel the unfair dismissal! Murderous Company, Hyung Sung Group)
Should we keep watch?
Forget it.
Yes, sir.
Good will, my foot. This is stalking.
I'm sorry for asking you to do this.
It's nothing, sir.
Should I cancel the meeting you had today?
- What meeting? - With the head of Seoul Bank.
- I still have to work. - Yes, sir.
You're right.
"Three handsome sons-in-law..."
"of conglomerate families everyone wants to date..."
Whatever.
He has a great figure. He could be an actor.
He's still young, and he's already a vice-president.
- Haven't you heard? - What?
He's Jang Seo Kyung's husband.
- Jang Seo Kyung. - You're right!
The chairman was against the marriage,
but Jang Seo Kyung caused a fit...
and managed to make it work.
He went to jail for the chairman and recently got discharged.
- Really? - Let me see.
- It says so here. - Give it!
- Where? - Let go!
- Gosh, what's wrong with you? - That hurt!
- I couldn't see. - Goodness!
- You could've waited your turn! - Gosh!
(Three handsome sons-in-law of conglomerate families...)
(everyone wants to date, Han Jae Hyun of Hyung Sung Group)
(The marriage between the chairman's daughter and a mere employee)
I will never agree on a settlement.
Set up the School Violence Committee.
But...
Mr. Han said to never allow...
And you should have stopped him.
Even if it were Jun Seo's grandfather who came,
- you should've stopped it. - I'm sorry, ma'am.
I did tell him that we can't do that,
but he insisted, saying he's a young boy.
I don't want you to misunderstand me.
Even if my son wasn't the victim,
I would've wanted you to go by the rules.
If we just let this pass,
it will only humiliate the school.
This school should be special, don't you think?
Isn't that why parents...
want to send their kids here at all costs?
And it's also why I make such large donations here.
(Han Jae Hyun of Hyung Sung Group)
(The marriage between the chairman's daughter and a mere employee)
Yes?
I don't know what to tell you.
Is something wrong?
I think the School Violence Committee will be set up.
Why, all of a sudden?
Jun Seo's mother came to see us.
She told us not to give you...
her number.
I don't think she wants to agree on a settlement.
I see.
What about...
his father's number?
- He said he would give... - I'm sorry.
We can't give you that, either.
- I'm really sorry. - Then...
when will it be held?
This will be a great opportunity for Seoul Bank as well.
All right. Let's get it started.
Thank you, sir.
Go ahead. Take it.
Excuse me.
Yes? What is it?
Dad, are you with Mom?
No, why?
I wanted to ask Mom what she said.
What do you mean?
They're going to hold the School Violence Committee...
because of Mom.
Yes. The head of Seoul Bank?
All right.
What is he up to?
Excuse me. May I see Ms. Jang?
Do you have an appointment?
- Not really... - Then no, ma'am.
You need to make an appointment.
Is she in, though?
I can't tell you, ma'am.
Then...
- What about Mr. Han? - It will be the same, ma'am.
You cannot see them unless you have an appointment.
Hey!
What is it?
What's wrong?
You can't do this here.
No, I'm not here because of the protest.
Please let me call them, at least.
You can't do this here. Please step outside.
- No, I... - Please leave.
- I... - Come, ma'am.
What do you think you're doing?
I told you not to change the decision.
Why shouldn't I?
It wasn't serious enough to ruin someone's life.
You fire employees...
and sue them for interfering...
with your business so easily.
Why are you worried about his life?
He's a young boy.
He's just 14.
I'm sure you fired a truckload of people...
who have kids that are younger.
I'm saying we should play it by the rules.
I'm not trying to teach the kid...
who hit my baby a lesson.
Well, I guess I can't say it's 100 percent not that.
So, Young Min.
Please tell me why you did it.
I don't care if they hold the committee.
Of course, you do.
You said you liked school.
You liked your teachers and said the class was fun.
Young Min.
I really don't believe you did anything wrong.
I was just annoyed. At everything.
"Just"?
You did it without a reason?
I'm almost in the eighth grade.
I will be, soon.
They say kids get moody then.
Says who? That doesn't even make any sense!
Isn't Dad coming tomorrow? What do I do?
(Mom)
(Mom...)
(Building 2)
Where's Seo Kyung?
She just left for the school, sir.
Don't worry, ma'am.
We'll be careful not to let any rumors out.
Of course, you should.
It's just as embarrassing to be known as the victim.
Ms. Yoon.
I beg of you, ma'am.
Please reconsider it.
- The boy's future... - I'm doing this...
for the boy's future, ma'am.
Isn't it the adults' duty...
to tell them what's right and wrong?
It can't be good for his education...
if we let it slide without punishment...
when he committed a crime, don't you think?
And for the other students, as well.
If...
the reason you're trying to hold...
the committee is because it's your son...
What did you say?
Please take it out on me.
It's my fault...
for raising him poorly.
You can take it out on me...
however you like.
However I like?
Yes, ma'am. However.
Then let's see what you can do...
to relieve my anger.
Please, ma'am.
Forgive him...
just this once.
Please get up.
What do you think you're doing?
Get up, Yoon Ji Su!
(When My Love Blooms)
I can't help but think of the old days.
Ji Su!
It's been so long.
Good luck, Ji Su.
Just keep in mind that I'll be watching her.
Are you asking me to leave them?
I don't want you to suffer.
No.
I want to protect you.