Is it some kind of loyalty for your colleagues?
Or is it a sense of justice?
Why?
I learned it from you.
You taught me the losing side is our side.
(May 1994)
Let go of me!
Stop it! Stop!
What a relief.
Are you done watching?
I heard it was your idea to get the police involved.
I told you to get rid of them, didn't I?
I planned to negotiate with them, for show,
to leave a record that we followed procedures.
Whether it's for show or not,
why should we negotiate with them?
Why are you acting out of character?
Do they have something on you?
I made the decision with the media in mind.
You fear public sentiment?
Are you a celebrity?
I'm more famous than most celebrities, thanks to you.
Economic crimes, corruption,
illegal tax evasion.
I'm the scum of the earth that does all the worst things.
So now you want people to stop calling you that,
and become an elegant hunter, is that it?
If I were a hunter,
that's not how I'd corner the hare.
Most of them are women in their 40s and 50s.
If you disperse them with force, there will be a backlash.
That could be true.
Come back tomorrow morning.
You're here...
to ask me to help you save face.
I must consider something first.
Will you just admit to it?
Do you have a husband?
- No. - Parents?
None.
Don't you have a guardian?
I am my guardian.
That's what you think.
Basically, you don't have anyone to vouch for you?
Then you can't leave today.
Even if someone did vouch for you,
you'd have to stay the night.
- Investigate the Gwangju massacre! - Investigate the Gwangju massacre!
- Investigate the Gwangju massacre! - Gosh, how scary.
Investigate...
Let's go before we get drenched in tear gas.
I want to talk to Jae Hyun.
You can't. They'll shoot any minute.
This is a major event. It'll be fine.
Are you crazy?
Go on home.
Yoon Ji Su!
Darn it.
(No entry)
Investigate the Gwangju massacre!
- Look down! - Don't look up!
- Look down! - You.
Hey, you.
Look down!
- Watch it. - Don't look up.
Do you have a lighter?
- Down. - What?
- Do as you're told. - Hey!
Hide it if you do.
They'll arrest you for lighting Molotov cocktails.
Look down.
- Hey. - Move!
Look down!
Your father's name.
Yoon Hyung Gu.
This keeps getting stuck.
His workplace.
His workplace!
Seoul Central District Prosecutors' Office.
You're lying in great detail.
Why not say your dad's the president?
That is where he works.
What does he do there?
Is he a paralegal?
A chief prosecutor.
You're completely out of your...
(Trustworthy police)
I was going to escort your daughter home.
Forget it.
Pardon?
No, not right now.
Later.
(Cancel temporary worker system)
"Illegal protesting, obstruction,"
"obstruction of justice".
Wow, you have a flashy record.
Are you a professional protestor?
I got sued after I was wrongfully fired.
How is that related to today's protest?
If I got fired before,
should I stay silent if I got fired this time?
The illegal dismissal is the employer's fault.
Is it the worker's fault?
Come on now. We're both experts in our fields.
Some of you go undercover to get jobs...
and instigate others to protest.
Choi Sun Hee, you keep quiet.
This will take a while.
Ms. Yoon Ji Su's still inside.
Some left with their guardians,
but those with a record or those who seem suspicious...
will be detained.
You don't know why Ji Su's being kept?
No, I couldn't get that much.
I knew nothing...
about Ji Su.
What lectures she takes,
who her friends are. Nothing.
Yes, you idiot.
You really have a problem.
Protesting isn't a great title.
Why must those around you suffer?
Hello, Books for Today.
Yes, Mr. Kim.
I haven't checked the stock yet.
Yes. I'll call when I get them.
Yes. Goodbye.
Hey, go and page me.
- Something's not right. - Your pager is innocent.
You're the guilty one.
Give up on her.
Haven't you heard? Her dad is a chief prosecutor.
What if he sentences you to 10 years?
You saw how...
his wrist moved when he slapped her.
The full swing with zero hesitation.
He finally got the message.
What a relief.
Sleep well,
Ji Su.
Jae Hyun.
How could you just walk away?
Give me your shoes.
You have huge feet.
How do you know?
Your footprints.
In the snow.
You silly thing.
You're so high-maintenance.
You're so sweet.
Don't your feet hurt?
Let's swap shoes back.
Ji Su.
Yes?
I don't like war movies.
Of course, I hate wars even more.
Why would you suddenly say that?
Whether he's a general or an officer,
the lead always gives orders from the center.
At the front line,
nameless soldiers take all the fire.
Whoever manages to survive...
gets cut down by the bayonet.
No one there...
deserves to get shot or cut down like that.
Until they fall, they're all the lead in their own lives.
Even if it's just a movie,
considering humans just a means or a pawn...
is despicable.
Humans...
should never crush others for whatever reason.
That's another reason I protest.
Also, I don't have a religion, but I believe deities exist.
So...
I believe that all men are children of deities.
Ji Su.
To deities, every human...
is precious and meaningful.
Don't let anyone treat you badly.
Not even family.
You are...
a special and precious...
child of a deity.
Your feet really are huge.
Is that why you're so nice?
Shall I take another look?
- Let's go home. - Okay.
The reason you're doing things you didn't...
is her, isn't it?
Whenever you act strangely, that woman seems to be involved.
It could be because of her.
She brought back old memories.
Things that I used to believe were right.
They aren't an organized labor union,
and they're not using the protest to sway the company.
They're just someone's mother and grandmother.
They're people like you and our mothers.
Shoving them to the side isn't the only solution.
Exactly. Why did you turn so soft?
Why did you suddenly change? It's freaking me out.
I might change even more.
What does that mean?
I will make decisions different from the ones so far.
Why is that?
To be happy.
What does that mean?
Do you mean you weren't happy?
I'm talking about beliefs.
It's the same thing!
Why use difficult words to confuse me?
I don't care.
Just remember that I have an eye on that woman.
("Hyung Sung Group Chairman's Family Has Many Borrowed Name Accounts")
I'll let the women go.
I need you to deal with this.
("Hyung Sung Group Chairman's Family Has Many Borrowed Name Accounts")
Can you do it?
How do you want me to deal with it?
The statutes have expired.
I just have to pay the tax and get chewed out.
But there are outstanding charges with tax evasion...
and breaking the Securities and Exchange Act.
What?
Are you afraid this bite will hurt?
No. I'm pretty good at getting bitten now.
I'm sure...
you don't want me or Seo Kyung to end up in prison.
No.
The borrowed name accounts.
They're all mine,
but put them in your name for now.
When things quieten down, you can give them to Seo Kyung.
Don't worry about the tax you'll incur...
when the accounts are transferred.
I understand.
By the way,
who do you think leaked this?
I believe Director Hwang Hak Su...
manages the borrowed name accounts.
For a long time.
But it's not him.
That depends on...
who else has access.
I'll have Hak Su look into it.
You keep an eye on the shareholders and other directors.
Yes, sir.
Seo Kyung said that something is bothering her.
I told you to have some fun. Did you actually have fun?
The fool...
acts like she's cheating on you, but you are all she cares about.
Clean up your mess and look after her.
I won't stand by...
if my child cries.
(Gangnam Police Station)
Good job.
- Let's go. - Oh, dear.
Let's go and eat some tofu.
It was just lockup, but it's still a cell.
Tofu doesn't help.
Don't say that.
Don't brag about having a record.
I'm proud of it. No one takes me lightly.
How did you get out?
It can't have been easy with your record.
The company told the police to release us.
They want to negotiate.
Why did they have you detained then?
To scare you?
Yes. I'm a completely different man.
I am incredibly selfish and materialistic.
The temporary workers who are protesting right now...
will be removed.
It's strange.
What is?
Jae Hyun.
He said he'd have them removed.
Then he said he'd negotiate.
Yesterday, when we were detained, he seemed almost flustered.
Today, he let us go.
I'm not sure if you know,
but Jae Hyun has a bad reputation.
Our seniors...
all badmouth him and question if he was a true protestor.
80 percent of them are curses.
Part of that is jealousy because he married well.
But then,
the old Jae Hyun would've never married a rich woman.
I think it has something to do with when and how his father died.
I don't know the details.
A person changing...
is the equivalent to the Big Bang.
Still, you haven't changed.
Your world collapsed just like the Big Bang.
Sorry. I didn't mean to upset you.
I get angry when you mention Jae Hyun.
Ms. Yoon was released,
and so were the others.
(May 1994)
What will you do with Ji Su?
What are you talking about?
Do you really not know?
You know that she likes you.
You should tell her how you feel about her.
Why won't you just tell her how you feel?
Young Woo.
Actually, Ji Su and I are...
She's always chasing you around every single day.
Don't you even feel bad for her?
Then, why are you so invested in this?
What do you mean?
If I turn her down,
what will you do?
Well, you know...
But she won't even consider me.
She doesn't look around her.
She just keeps on looking ahead.
That girl...
is as determined as Joan of Arc.
Ji Su!
Hey, what are you...
What is this?
Is this like...
Pandora's box?
I hope the negotiation goes well.
What about you? Do you want your job back?
I already found a job.
Really? I'm so glad to hear that.
It's a permanent position, not a temporary one, right?
(Ocean Music Academy)
You were supposed to come yesterday.
How could you reschedule on the day of your interview?
I'm sorry. Something came up yesterday.
We can't allow that.
Our job isn't to handle the kids,
but their moms.
If you're late for a minute or teach them less,
they'll call me right away.
And they'll demand to change the class.
Okay. I'll be more careful.
And...
you cannot tell the mothers...
that you didn't finish college.
Okay.
You said you are willing to clean up...
on top of teaching. Is that right?
Yes. I'll do my best.
(List of applicants for reinstatement)
(Yoon Jin Seo, Yoon Ji Seong)
You didn't apply to get your job back.
I didn't.
Is it because of me?
I found another part-time job.
I think you need a more stable job.
Why would you choose that?
Didn't you protest...
to get a permanent position?
The others set it up.
I only brought them some water.
I can't benefit from their hard work.
The people who risked their lives...
from the start should get the benefit.
And I gave up in the middle...
with an excuse that I needed to make a living.
Then, instead of working at the supermarket,
are you interested in getting a desk job?
Did you make the same offer...
to other people?
No.
Isn't this employment corruption?
I'm hiring employees for my company.
That's not illegal.
It would be a problem if you hire someone who's not qualified.
What would someone who majored in piano do at your company?
Besides, I didn't even graduate,
so technically, I'm a high school graduate.
Jae Hyun.
I didn't have much...
and didn't achieve much.
Perhaps, that's probably why,
but I felt free.
I was busy trying to figure out about my future,
so I didn't even have the time...
or the need to reminisce about my past.
But ever since meeting you,
I feel trapped.
I keep looking back,
so I'm moving forward slowly.
I want our memories together to remain like beautiful flowers.
But I'm angry because...
you're stomping on those flowers now that you've changed.
Then, you shouldn't have left.
How could a farewell be beautiful?
I still...
can't understand why you left me like that.
When I share my pain,
it doesn't get halved. It doubles for me.
I have to see my loved one suffer in pain too.
Could anything be more painful...
than parting with your loved one?
Ji Su.
I don't reminisce about my past either...
because it has never become my past even for a moment.
It's a rock, dangling on my heart...
and a bone stuck in my throat. How can they be my memories?
Just let them be part of your past.
Remember only the good days.
I'll do the same.
Your silence
And my dry lips
As you turn around
I say goodbye to you
Even a music major can tell I'm pretty good, right?
I don't know much about guitars,
but you're pretty good.
Then, should I play it again?
What about Jae Hyun?
- Is that what you want to know? - Yes.
50 cents.
Okay.
Come on.
Didn't he tell you that he's preparing for an election?
An election?
Is he running for the school president?
No, not that. The chairperson of the Society Committee.
The chairperson of the Society Committee?
My gosh, I'm good at chairing meetings.
Ladies and gentlemen. Please welcome...
Ji Su Yoon.
Is that really for chairing events?
Yes.
People talk with the microphones during campaigns.
That's for leading the campaigns.
He chairs assemblies...
and is concerned about the society, hence, the title.
On top of all this, he has to fight for supplies.
Fight for supplies?
Do you work here? Okay.
- Come on in. - Fighting for supplies.
In other words, it's a part-time job.
He has to cover his transportation, food, and election campaign...
with the money he earns.
I doubt he'll have any money left.
That's "carrot".
"Carol"?
No, I said, carrot.
I see.
Gosh, people laugh so hard when they hear this pun.
By the way, if he gives private lessons, he'll make more.
It's obvious why he chose that job.
Wait, that girl...
She's unbeatable Hwa Jin.
She can defeat 100 members of White Skeleton all by herself.
Her hobby is taking their helmets.
I heard she uses the helmets as buckets at home...
or to scoop up rice. She's a legendary warrior.
He's working there because of her?
No.
Think. Why don't you think?
If he stays there,
he can meet up with the others...
and save time on going back and forth.
With one hit, he can double his catch.
What do you mean?
Kill 2 birds with 1 stone.
I see.
And that stubborn guy...
doesn't like giving private lessons...
because that's what capitalistic jerks do.
Goodness, he complicates his life all on his own.
Jae Hyun must be so tired.
(Park No Hae's Poetry Book, "The Dawn of Labor")
Does it feel nice to hog the fan?
What?
Earlier, it was broken.
I know who came by.
Who came by?
Why are you dozing off here?
Oh, that. It was hot.
Isn't it really hot?
It's the hottest day ever recorded.
You don't have to fan me. It's not cool at all.
Then, quit working at the main gate. It's so hot.
It's so hot, but it's not hard at all thanks to someone.
It's my birthday today.
Today is your birthday?
It's not my birthday, but I'm happy as if it is.
- When is your birthday? - June...
29.
It's coming up soon.
Yes.
(Convalescent Ward)
How dare you come here?
How dare you?
Get out of here now!
You caused it!
Had you not been there...
She wouldn't have died had you been never born.
Get out.
Get out of here! Get out!
Why is that my fault?
What did I do? What could I have done?
What was I supposed to do?
I know that you want to blame someone...
and you need to lash out on someone, but you need to stop this now!
She won't come back even if you do.
I know that too.
I should never have been born.
I should have never.
If I was never born...
My gosh, there you go again.
Goodness, sir. You're all right.
Don't cry. Okay? My gosh.
I brought some traditional cookies you like.
Please don't be so upset. Please?
You talked back to him today unlike other days.
You've been so good to him.
(Notice of Acceptance to School, Yeonhui University, Piano)
(January 1993)
So what?
Ji Su got into college.
Is this a real college?
You just press some keys on the piano.
Is this something to brag about?
This is humiliating. Don't make a fuss about going to college.
What...
must I do to be treated like your daughter here?
There isn't a thing you like about me.
Should I go back to Mom's womb?
Ji Su.
Keep going.
Ji Young said she'd study law in Seoul National University.
Isn't that what you want?
You won't be embarrassed to face your friends from school.
So can't you stop being mean to me?
Why can't you let me take a breather?
She hasn't gotten in yet.
Ji Young didn't enter college yet.
So don't even breathe...
until my Ji Young gets into Seoul National University.
I'll be there in 30 minutes. Get ready.
Young Min.
Open the door.
Go back home with Jun Seo.
I can't just leave him in the hospital all alone.
Okay.
Young Min.
It's the flu.
He's been sick but hasn't been eating well.
It looks like he was fatigued.
Okay.
But may I ask who you are?
My son is friends with Young Min. They are in the same class.
What's your son's name?
I know all of his friends.
Since you're here, I'll get going.
Bye.
Jerk.
(Hwabon)
(Emergency Medical Center)
How did you take care of him...
that he passed out from the flu?
If this keeps up, I'm going to have to take back custody.
Don't you dare. I'm going to bite you.
What great love you have for your son.
So why would you take his father away from him?
You can't take him today.
I'm going to take him home.
Too bad, but my mother's on her way.
Jun Seo.
Jun Seo, how were you?
Good.
Is that it?
You're just like your dad.
What about Dad?
Probably at school.
- Why? - That punk passed out.
"That punk"?
The kid who threw a chair at me.
(7021, Susaek, Seoul Station, Myeong-dong, Lotte)
- Please follow that bus. - Okay.
Good night, Ji Su.
It's my fault, isn't it?
The reason...
why you weren't happy.
It's because you chose me, right?
- Seo Kyung... - I...
always told my dad...
that you were the best choice...
I ever made.
I appreciate that.
That's why I'm trying my best.
It was my best choice,
but I guess...
it was your only choice.
- Seo Kyung... - Stop.
Your thanks was enough...
for me to understand.
She works at a hotel, ma'am.
Doing what?
She plays the piano in the lobby.
Doesn't my husband go there often?
- Yes, ma'am. - Was she...
after him from the beginning?
She started working last year,
which is when Mr. Han was still imprisoned.
Who knows? She could've gone to visit him.
But one thing peculiar...
is that she wears a mask when she's playing.
Does she?
So she doesn't want to be seen?
I should put her in her place.
Are you free this Friday evening?
Why?
There's a private party being held in the suite room,
and they requested a pianist.
Specifically you.
Me?
Yes. They specifically told us they wanted...
the pianist in the mask.
They like your performance.
- Who is it? - A VVIP guest.
You'll find out on that day.
The pay...
will be double.
They're holding a party for the brand as well,
so they requested that you wear it.
You can return it afterwards.
This is so expensive.
What if something goes wrong?
What could go wrong?
Are you coming?
No.
It's your boss's command.
It's not just any party,
but our brand showcase.
I know I don't have to go.
All the other top global brands...
post pictures on their social media with influencers.
What would they think if the president is there...
and the vice-president isn't?
Seo Kyung.
You can't even do that for me?
You spent a whole day with someone else's son in the ER,
and you can't spend two hours for your wife?
Is that what you call, "trying your best"?
I may not be smart, but I can take a good guess.
How can you thank me...
when I told you I love you?
Why don't you say sorry?
You can apologize to me all your life.
- Goodness, long time no see. - Hello.
- It's been so long. - Thank you for coming.
Where are you, Jae Hyun?
All right, hurry up.
You can have this, ma'am.
You can't leave this...
Oh, gosh!
Are you okay? Oh, no!
Are you okay?
Wait here.
Please continue playing.
We can't have the music stop.
The dress costs several times your pay,
so I'll give it to you.
But instead, I wish you would take off that mask.
It's red wine, of all things,
so it looks a bit grotesque.
(September 1994)
(5th Annual Student Music Concour)
Girl, you're so pretty!
Aren't I? Thank you.
- What about your parents? - I didn't invite them.
Why not?
It's nothing, anyways.
What do you mean?
You're playing because you won first place...
in that big competition.
They wouldn't have come, anyways.
No way.
Ji Young has her SATs coming up.
Gosh, I can't believe them.
And him?
- He'll be here after the rally. - "Rally"?
Is it so hard for him to skip one rally?
They need him at that rally.
Him and his rallies...
He can't even protect his girlfriend,
so what is he trying to protect?
I can't wait to see what a beautiful world he's trying to make.
Gosh, I'm so mad.
Stop smiling!
I'm sorry.
It's okay.
What about your family?
That again?
Ji Su.
I didn't invite them.
Why not?
Because I'm not going to see them anymore.
What do you mean?
What you taught me.
"Don't let anyone..."
"treat me badly."
"I am a special and precious..."
"child of a deity."
I won't be playing.
Why not? Because they saw your face?
It's like putting lipstick on a pig.
What?
I'm saying I don't want to waste my quality music...
on such a vulgar party made with money.
I'll be paying for the dress.
I'm not going to take it anymore.
My dad's beating.
Why...
did he beat you?
I got caught listening to pop music.
He said the piano is low enough, let alone pop music,
and threw the radio.
Jae Hyun.
I want to see the ocean.
How dare you come here?
How dare you?
You caused it!
Had you not been there...
She wouldn't have died had you been never born.
Get out.
Get out of here! Get out!
I'm sorry, Ji Su.
I'm sorry.
Jae Hyun.
Why did I have to be the one to survive?
Being alive itself is a sin and debt,
so I can't ever be happy...
nor complain.
I've kept myself so busy,
but I still can't pay...
for the sin nor the debt.
I really...
want a break now.
I want to let it all go.
It's so romantic.
- Is it your first time on a train? - Yes.
Aren't we going to have any eggs? Or soda?
They go around selling lunch boxes, right?
I believe...
there is a reason...
to why someone survives.
It's because there's something in this world only you can do.
That's why the reason you're alive...
may be a blessing to us.
So Ji Su,
you can do anything you want.
You can rest,
you can cry,
and if it's too much,
you don't have to try so hard to bear it.
I'll be by your side.
Why would you be by my side?
I'll be in my place,
and you'll be in yours.
Okay.
Anyone can see that this isn't right,
and even if it's your first love,
you can't justify something that's inappropriate.
But why can't I...
turn away from you?
Why can't I just keep you in my memories?
I kept thinking about it,
and the answer was in our past.
You told me...
that I am...
your belief and your world.
There's something I couldn't say back to you.
To me, you were my dream.
I'm facing the dream I had lost,
so I can't leave it...
nor run away from it.
Because that's my dream.
Because it's a dream,
we'll wake from it soon.
(As the night came,)
(snow started pouring in the valley.)
(I am sure my love...)
(will certainly cease somewhere, as well.)
("A Joyful Letter", by Hwang Dong Gyu)
(When My Love Blooms)
It's just a dream.
It's all just a dream.
But you know...
that I was also with another man.
Don't think of it so seriously.
They say there are people...
that end up with each other no matter what.
When did that black car start tailing us?
What I'm most afraid of...
is having him break down because of me.
That's why I decided to avoid what I fear the most.