(All characters, places, companies, )
(and incidents in this drama are fictitious.)
Excuse me. Did you see a young woman here?
Oh, she's sitting over there.
Thank you.
Hae Won.
I'm so scared.
I don't know what people are truly like anymore.
It feels as if I'm being deceived.
I can't trust anything.
What I see.
What I used to believe.
Do you want to go home?
No.
Then where do you want to go?
("The Maze of Sisterfield")
Eun Seop just called me.
He said he'd go and find Hae Won.
So don't worry and go to sleep.
("The Maze of Sisterfield")
(Shim Myeong Yeo)
Myeong Yeo.
Is this why you wrote this?
I know it's late, but I want to pay for what I did.
And it's something...
I had to tell Hae Won eventually.
So? Do you want to turn yourself in or what?
Then what does that make me?
I spent seven years behind bars.
What was that for?
You shouldn't have taken the fall for it.
How many times have I told you?
- Because it wasn't your fault.
- Myeong Ju.
Do you...
really think it was your fault?
Yes, of course.
Why do you think it was your fault?
I killed him.
You see,
had it not been for me,
you wouldn't have been there.
Had I never...
married an abusive man,
you wouldn't have done such a thing.
And...
had it not been for me,
you wouldn't have had to step on the gas pedal to begin with.
If you turn yourself in,
I'll feel like I have to go through all the punishment again.
Then what about me?
Should I...
just keep living like this?
- Is this hard for you?
- Yes.
It is hard.
I feel like I must tell everyone and be chastised to live.
If someone bashes me, I'll feel much better.
Then write a book about it...
- and tell people that it's fiction!
- No.
I got greedy while writing the book.
"Yes. Since this already happened, I should just turn myself in..."
- Shim Myeong Yeo!
- Myeong Ju.
Myeong Ju.
I...
I have dreams every night.
About what?
About Ju Hong.
What?
Did he show up in your dreams...
and blame you?
No.
He's always good to me.
Myeong Yeo, have some coffee.
You like coffee, don't you?
He's always so sweet to me.
And that...
That's what...
really drives me crazy.
(Episode 15: Until We Meet Again)
Out of the way!
Hey, stop!
- Hwi, stop right there!
- My gosh!
- I said, stop!
- Go away!
Don't follow me. Go away!
I'll teach you a lesson when I catch you.
- Hwi!
- Don't come anywhere near me!
- Go away!
- You'd better stop right there!
- Hello!
- Hey.
Did you have a meal with Eun Sil yesterday?
- No, I didn't.
- What?
We went to a place where no one could see us. How did he find out?
Jang Woo, I'm happy I ran into you.
- I'm going to file a complaint.
- A complaint?
Someone keeps leaving their garbage in front of my house.
- My gosh, garbage?
- Goodness.
It happens so often.
There's nothing I can do though.
Jang Woo. You know that Eun Sil is leaving today, right?
What? Who's leaving?
Her vacation is over, so she's going back to Gangneung.
I had a meal with her yesterday, and she never mentioned that to me.
She is leaving. I saw her mom packing up side dishes for her.
Oh, really?
But why are you telling me this?
You have a crush on her.
What? How on earth did you find out?
I know everything.
I even know that you've had a crush on her since high school.
I heard she was taking the bus.
What time was her bus?
She said it leaves at 3pm.
It leaves at 3pm.
Aren't you coming?
I'll head in first, then.
Gosh, I should put up a security camera or something.
Gosh.
Why there of all places?
- Do it.
- Do what?
Turn yourself in.
If it's tormenting you that much, just do it.
I was wrong.
I thought...
if I left like that...
(From Mok Hae Won)
"Mok Hae Won, Park Hin Dol".
You'd like to return these two to the senders?
- Yes.
- Oh, there's one more.
"Shim Myeong Yeo"? Would you like to return this too?
No.
(From Shim Myeong Yeo)
I thought you'd be happy here.
Hi, Myeong Ju. It's me. How are things with you?
Hae Won is doing well.
I'm doing pretty well too.
(I'm doing pretty well too.)
Actually,
I'm not doing well.
I can't.
I just can't.
I thought you'd forget everything...
and move on.
I'm doing pretty well too.
Hae Won is being mature about it and adjusting well,
and seeing that helps me feel at ease.
Everyone in the neighborhood is so good to us as well.
Yesterday, the next-door neighbor dropped off a box of tangerines.
We're doing well here. Myeong Ju,
you don't need to worry about me and Hae Won anymore.
Just take good care of yourself.
That's all I ask for.
I never thought...
you'd be this miserable.
I'm...
really sorry.
I used to live in this house.
The day of Dad's accident...
(Emergency Services)
That was the last day.
It's supposed to be deserted now.
Do you want to go in?
No one is here anyway.
I didn't know these were still here.
(Electricity Bill, Shim Myeong Ju)
Did you leave something behind?
You should've told me then.
I could've sent it to you and save you all the trouble.
Well, I don't even know your home address anyway.
(Electricity Bill)
Are you leaving?
I should.
What about Ju Hong?
You came here for his birthday, didn't you?
It's not like I could celebrate the anniversary of his death.
Take care.
Call me when you turn yourself in.
Okay.
By the way,
where do you live?
Where on earth do you live?
I live in my house in Paju.
What? Since when?
Ever since I was released from prison.
Well...
I have nowhere else to live anyway.
Bye.
I think Mom still lives here.
How could she do this?
Yet another thing they kept from me. How could they...
She probably thought...
it's best that you don't know.
If you found out,
you'd suffer too much.
She probably wanted to deal with it alone...
until she...
absolutely couldn't anymore.
But I'm her family.
Is it really fair that I've been left out of all this?
But you would have suffered.
She must have chosen to suffer alone...
until now...
so you didn't have to, Hae Won.
I'm sure of it.
My saddle.
Hey.
You're pretty good at riding a bike.
Hey, I'm sorry to say this,
but I'd like you to stop talking to me.
Deep down, I'm still not cool with you.
My scalp still hurts so much...
where you pulled out my hair.
See you tomorrow.
No thanks. I'm going on a date with Young Soo.
Hey, Young Soo is mine.
By the way, Lim Hwi,
I hear you're an outcast.
Yes. Do you have a problem with that?
I mean, I'm graduating soon,
but I could put in a good word for you with the kids in your year.
So don't worry.
Consider yourself lucky.
I'm only letting this go,
which is so kind of me,
because Young Soo asked me to.
Right.
Let's take a picture now that we made up. 1, 2...
That's a good one.
Don't worry, you don't have to thank me.
But I'm not thankful to you.
Seriously, not at all.
And I'm not scared of you.
Gosh, my pride is hurt.
My pride is hurt.
My pride is seriously hurt.
Hi, Eun Sil.
I found this on the street.
Idiot.
You're even prettier than these flowers.
Yes, that sounds better.
Yes.
Hi, Eun Sil. How are you?
Where are you going? Do you want a ride?
Where can you drop me off?
I can drive you all the way to Gangneung.
What are you talking about? You don't even have a car.
I do.
- It's my dad's.
- Really?
- Yes.
- It's my lucky day.
- Let's go.
- Okay.
- Where's the car?
- You have only one suitcase?
- Yes.
- All right. Here.
It's for you. On my way here...
What? Is something wrong?
You don't blush so much anymore.
- What are you talking about?
- I mean your face.
Before, whenever you saw me,
your face would automatically turn red.
But now...
You're blushing again.
All right. Let's go.
So where's your car?
What are you eating?
Rice cakes.
It's from the rice cake festival. They're so tasty.
You carry rice cakes in your pocket?
I couldn't tie them to my ankle, could I?
- Do you want some?
- No, thanks.
Is it okay if we stop at a rest area...
and get something to eat later?
I didn't have breakfast.
Mom kicked me out.
Sure, I'll buy you some food.
Thanks. Let's go. Where's your car?
Over there.
By the way, I heard...
you broke up with your boyfriend.
Yes.
How does everyone know? They all asked me that.
Did someone post on the internet that I broke up?
It feels like there's a sign up somewhere. Everyone knows.
Well, my mom wants me to get married early.
She wants to see a grandchild.
- Why are you telling me this?
- Tell you what?
What do you want to do?
I can go inside.
Then...
- Will you...
- I'll have to ask her.
I'll ask her.
I'll ask Auntie myself...
why she didn't tell me.
If I'm the only one she hid it from all this time.
If it's really because she didn't want me to get hurt.
And if...
what you said is really true,
I might...
be able to understand.
Okay.
I envy you so much.
Why?
Because you're this warm.
("All My Firsts" by Cha Yun Taek)
"Do you know what warmth is?"
"She asked me, and I answered."
"It's when my cold hand touches your cold hand..."
"and we both become warm."
"When loneliness meets loneliness and becomes coziness."
"When sadness meets sadness and becomes happiness."
"When a cool breeze collides against another cool breeze..."
"and becomes soft snow. That's what warmth is."
You were home.
We need to talk.
Did Mom leave?
Yes, she left.
Then I want you to explain...
how all this happened.
I killed your dad.
Is that it?
You must've read it in my writing.
I'm sorry.
I'm really sorry, Hae Won.
Why did you hide it from me?
Why only me?
It would've hurt you too much.
It would be okay...
if the only ones who knew...
were me and your parents.
But if you found out,
it would hurt you too much.
We couldn't bring ourselves to do that.
But why now?
- Why tell me now?
- Since I'll turn myself in now.
What?
I deserve to be punished for what I did.
I...
really didn't want to write novels.
But it was so hard to make a living.
Not for me, but for you.
I had to make some money at least...
for you to live comfortably.
That's why I decided to write one last novel, and that's when...
Cha Yun Taek told me to write something about my life.
So I thought this was my chance.
"Yes. I'll reveal everything and run away."
"I'm glad. There's no other story as shocking as mine."
"It will become a bestseller."
After making a bunch of money...
and being blamed by the public,
I wanted to turn myself in.
You'll really turn yourself in?
Your mom was really against it all this time,
but I won this time.
She said to do it if I want.
That's all I have to say.
Go to sleep now.
(Restaurant)
Welcome.
But why now?
- Why tell me now?
- Since I'll turn myself in now.
What?
I deserve to be punished for what I did.
Auntie.
Auntie! Auntie!
Auntie, wake up!
Did I ever ask you anything?
Where you live right now, who you live with,
whether you live alone, why you don't live with me.
Why...
Why did you always refuse to see me when I visited...
and never replied to my letters?
I never asked, did I?
That's why seeing you come here so unexpectedly like this...
makes me feel uncomfortable and awkward. So...
go back tomorrow.
Hae Won, the thing is...
Answer me right now!
No, she didn't...
- Let go!
- Hae Won.
Hey, Mok Hae Won!
Mok Hae Won!
Mok Hae Won! Gosh, that girl...
Hey! Mok Hae Won!
How...
Hey.
Why did you want to take your own life?
Don't die.
If you die, I'll die too.
So will your mom.
And my mom too.
It's just the way it is.
You may think we don't care,
but we do.
We'll all die.
("I Wish to Have a Beloved Poem Again")
You're up.
Eat up. Your stomach must be upset from the hangover.
I went to the noodle place with my colleagues...
because we had a team dinner and saw you passed out.
So I brought you to my place.
Why did you drink so much?
Did you and Eun Seop fight?
Bo Yeong.
I liked you too.
I did.
That's why I was hurt by what you did.
Because...
I trusted you and liked you as a friend.
However,
everything I had to endure back then...
was caused by you,
so it wasn't easy for me to forgive you.
I still don't think we can get our relationship...
back to the way it used to be.
It can't even have a single crack?
Even if a table has a crack, you can still use it.
It's only natural for things...
to get wear and tear with time.
There's no such thing as a perfect relationship.
What's wrong with a little crack?
And what's wrong with hurting each other's feelings a little?
No one is perfect.
That's why we do things that we have to apologize for,
say sorry,
and mend things.
That's how life goes.
I know...
I hurt you immensely,
but I really...
wanted a chance to fix things.
I'll wait if you're still not ready.
Who knows? Perhaps when more time passes,
it may become a little easier for you.
It's raining nonstop.
- Aren't you cold?
- No.
The taxi is taking forever.
Make sure the braids look nice.
Back when I was in school,
I always braided my hair into two long plaits.
I feel like I'm a school girl again.
Mom, it's done.
Look in the mirror. Doesn't it look so pretty?
Gosh, what is this?
What is this mess?
Am I an alien?
None of the boys...
- Hey.
- would like me with this hair.
- Come here.
- No, don't!
- Hae Won, get your mom.
- What?
- Mom!
- Myeong Ju?
- Attack!
- Myeong Ju!
- Go, Mom!
- Come here, I'll braid your hair.
- Gosh, stop it!
- Come here.
Myeong Ju.
Hae Won, hold your mom. Hold her down!
- Hey, let go!
- Stay still.
- Gosh!
- Get back here!
- Get her!
- No, Mom!
Get her! Bring her back!
Since...
I'll turn myself in now.
Auntie.
Excuse me, can we talk?
Sorry? About what?
It's not true, okay? Please let me explain.
- What are you talking about?
- It's... I mean...
You're mistaken, so let's...
- Goodness, gracious.
- Hurry! Move it!
- Get them in the car.
- Aren't you cold?
They can go in that car.
- Yes, sir.
- Gosh, that hurts.
Goodness. Where did the rest of them go, completely naked?
- Get in the car.
- I can't believe those punks.
Corporal Kim.
- Hello, ma'am.
- What's going on here?
There's been a report...
of a naked party at the guesthouse in the back.
And those punks ran that way.
What?
Excuse me, what were you saying before?
Nothing.
- At the guesthouse?
- Yes.
That explains all the noise.
- Did you talk to the owner?
- Yes.
- Make sure it never happens again.
- Okay.
- Thank you.
- See you.
Did you think I was already turning myself in...
and panic or something?
Why do you keep that picture there?
It wasn't there when I lived here.
It was definitely not there when Grandma was still alive.
You haven't been back here...
since Mom passed away.
I miss her.
Auntie.
Say it.
I kind of hate you.
I get that.
You didn't want me to suffer.
I thought hearing you say that would make me understand you,
but it didn't.
I still can't understand you.
Why not?
I believe...
families should share their pain with each other.
Let's share our pain.
Don't turn yourself in.
If you've hung in there for the past 10 years for Mom,
hang in there for the next 10 years for me.
- Hae Won.
- You once told me...
if I died, so would you,
Mom, and Grandma.
Back then, I was living in a nightmare too.
Even though the incident didn't involve me directly,
it was still a nightmare for me too.
If you turn yourself in now,
I'll be living in a nightmare again.
So just continue living the way you've been living.
But...
I don't think I can look at you the same way anymore.
I need some time...
to sort myself out.
I'll leave.
What?
I'll leave, Auntie.
Eun Seop.
Can we talk for a second?
Of course.
Do you want some coffee?
Are you okay?
Auntie wanted to turn herself in,
and I told her not to.
I see.
The thing is,
I can't look Auntie in the eye anymore.
So...
I think I should leave.
Spring is here.
Good luck with your bookstore.
I hope you'll always be the warm person you are.
And...
there has never been a moment...
when my heart has not been true.
You know that, right?
Well...
Take care, Eun Seop.
I'm home.
Tell me, Eun Seop.
About us.
Is this love?
Yes.
It is love.
I feel the same way.
"The bookstore will be closed for a few days."
Hae Won, think about it.
If Eun Seop is missing at this hour, where do you think he would be?
Hae Won.
I understand...
that you will leave this place one day.
I'm sorry, Eun Seop.
I'm bracing myself for anything that can happen.
However,
when you leave this place,
I hope you don't leave with a heavy heart.
I just hope you can leave smiling happily.
I hope...
I hope you're not hurt at all.
I'm sorry.
I'll sincerely hope so.
Eun Seop.
I'm going to leave now.
Are you disappointed I keep doing as I please?
No.
I still love you.
Goodbye,
Hae Won.
(Good Night Bookstore Private Blog Posting)
(As I continue to post my diary, )
(the weight of each day gets heavier.)
(Though the days piled up, )
(I wasn't gifted with anything different in particular.)
(But when she came to me this winter and we shared our love, )
(those days didn't pile up evenly like before.)
(The weight of today is different than before.)
(Next winter will probably be even more different.)
(The weight of the upcoming winter that I cannot fathom yet.)
(I put up a sign that the bookstore will be closed for a few days.)
(It feels like a bowstring that's been tightly pulled back.)
(I've decided to let things go and rest for a while.)
(When the Weather is Fine)
I believe you're doing well.
I'm doing well too.
When are you going?
A week later.
You're not coming back?
Wouldn't that be better for the both of us?
- Eun Sil.
- I like you now.
- What?
- I like you now, Jang Woo.
How did you know?
That I didn't really mean it...
when I said I liked you for a long time?
Because...
I know the eyes of someone who has liked me for a long time.