(All characters, places, companies,)
(and incidents in this drama are fictitious.)
Auntie.
Auntie, are you up...
Auntie!
Auntie, what's wrong?
Auntie! Auntie, open your eyes!
Auntie, what's wrong? Auntie!
Auntie, wake up!
Shall I tell you?
Auntie. Auntie!
What's wrong?
- Oh, my gosh. - What's going on?
Auntie. Auntie!
Auntie!
I always practice going back to that day.
If I go back to that day,
it feels as if I could turn everything back to normal.
Everything that has passed by in my life.
I'm going to do everything with you!
I'm going to do everything with you.
Like this.
Everything that I have lost.
Please let me go back to the person I was that day.
Please.
Please...
To the way I was that day.
(Episode 14: The Maze of Sisterfield)
This is called closed-angle glaucoma.
It is a type of glaucoma.
Your aunt's intraocular pressure suddenly went up...
and she fainted.
Then...
We'll have to do some more testing.
It seems like she has almost lost vision in one eye.
And...
But has the patient left her eye like this...
all this time without tending to it?
It must've been very painful.
By the way, has your aunt seen a doctor yet?
She gets severe headaches.
You have a headache?
It's seriously driving me crazy.
At this rate, she probably had severe headaches...
and pain in her eye as well.
She probably vomited from time to time too.
It would've been hard to handle.
It's her first time coming to the hospital, right?
Hello?
Who is this?
It's Hae Won.
Can't you even recognize my voice?
Auntie fainted.
Did you hear me? She fainted.
Okay.
- What? - I heard you.
Hello? Mom.
Hae Won.
Ms. Shim Myeong Yeo's guardian?
Yes?
- I'll be back. - Okay.
One short rib soup please.
One short rib soup for table three.
- Coming up. - Jang Woo, are you going later?
- To the village hall. - Yes, I'm going.
Go have a nice meal and help out the elders.
- Okay, I will. - By the way,
I heard that Ji Eun Sil girl broke up with her boyfriend.
What? Eun Sil? Say again?
You know, the girl who works at Gangneung City Hall.
Oh, the daughter of that side dish shop?
Yes. I heard she broke up with her boyfriend.
Too bad.
She had a boyfriend?
Yes.
He was a colleague of hers.
Why do you sound so surprised?
Oh, it's just because I found out something new.
- Really? - But how did you know...
something I wasn't even aware of?
- My wife told me. - I heard it from Eun Sil's mom.
You know Eun Sil's mom?
Yes. Their side dish shop is located in our apartment complex.
You know that alteration shop next to that place?
That family with three sons and a daughter?
Are you talking about Young Ran's family?
Oh, them? Why? Is something wrong?
No, I heard they gave birth to twins recently.
Oh, I heard. Ji Woo and Chae Yeon.
They're fraternal twins.
Right! You know Hyeon A who works at the supermarket?
She's getting married.
I already know. She's getting married to a math teacher.
Right.
I envy her.
Jang Woo, when are you getting married?
I'm not thinking of getting married yet.
Why not?
I don't know.
Hello, sir!
- Did you bring rice? - Yes.
Hey, I'm putting the rice here!
Okay.
So many people left their rice already.
Hello.
It's already time for the rice cake festival?
Yes.
(Hyecheon Rice Cake Festival)
Every February,
this town...
(Rice Cake Festival)
opens a festival to make rice cakes...
just like a scene from a movie.
Here.
Go on.
- Gosh. - My gosh, thank you.
- What is this? - This is...
- Look! - Let's check it out.
- Hello. - Hello.
- Hi. - Come on.
- What about this? - My gosh.
- Look! - Hello.
- Gosh! - Take turns!
That's when you can tell.
That winter is over,
and...
spring is coming.
Hey, what are you doing?
- Let me help. - Gosh, look at that.
- Is this better? - Yes, much better.
My, that looks great.
Hey, so?
- What? - Did she go to the hospital?
- Right, yes, in Ji Yeon's car. - I'm telling you.
Mom, the doctor said that her optic nerves are all damaged.
- My gosh. - Her eye looks green...
because of glaucoma.
The Hodu House family with the beautiful daughters, right?
- Yes. - Gosh.
Those girls were beautiful, but they totally wasted their looks.
One got pregnant and married a man in Seoul.
Then her husband died, and she went to jail for it.
I heard the other one was doing well for herself as a novelist,
but now she's stuck here looking like a complete mess.
The older one...
- murdered her husband, right? - Ma'am!
It was manslaughter, not murder.
Really? Is there a difference?
Yes, of course there is.
Anyway, their mother was utterly heartbroken because of them.
That's why she ended up with cancer in her final years.
I know. Before that, she was so healthy.
Gosh.
Oh, dear. I feel bad for her. What a sad life.
Hey, what on earth are you doing?
Goodness, you're doing a great job. So great.
- What? It looks good. - Look at this.
- Doesn't this look nice? - Yes, it does.
It looks very nice.
Right. The guy who works at City Hall, Jang Woo.
I heard he went on a blind date. I think things are going very well.
- What? He went on a blind date? - Yes.
I heard he might get married next month.
What? That's... He might get married?
My, that's great news.
We'll get to eat noodles and rice cakes.
We'll have a feast at the buffet. It's been a while.
Yes! I'd love that.
Eun Sil, are you having fun working at City Hall?
No, it's not fun at all.
- But about that blind date... - Gosh.
Just know that you're very lucky.
Be grateful that you have a job.
- That hurt! - And try to make this look nicer.
- Don't be so mean to your daughter. - Make it look better.
- I quit. - Don't whine like a kid.
- Let's scrape this off. - Gosh.
- Oh, boy. - Goodness.
- Are you all right? - Gosh.
- Boy, I'm exhausted. - Are you okay?
My, this delicious aroma.
- Gosh, are you all right? - Here you go.
- Oh, I think this is ready. - Yes, take this inside.
- Should I take this inside? - Yes, to the living room.
I'll take this. Hello, hello.
- Hello. - Hi, Jang Woo.
- Hello. - Hurry up.
- Come on. - You didn't get it yet?
- Hurry. - All right.
- Hey, over here! - Okay, I'm coming.
- Hello, hello. - Hi.
Hello, hello. I brought this.
- Hi, Jang Woo! - Hello.
Ladies, say hi. This is Jang Woo.
The one who went on a blind date recently.
A blind date?
- You know Jang Woo. - He's good-looking.
- Seoul National University? - Hello. I'm that guy, Jang Woo.
- Are you looking for something? - No, no.
I'm not. I came inside to drop this off and say hello.
This will be so delicious.
- Thanks for this. - Thank you.
- He's handsome. - He is.
My gosh. Hi, Eun Sil.
- Who are you looking for? - Me? You. I mean, hold on.
I need to use the bathroom so badly. I'll be back.
- He's very handsome. - Right?
Jang Woo went on a blind date?
Over there...
- Rock-paper-scissors. - Rock-paper-scissors.
1, 2, 3.
So? Is Seung Ho's grandpa all right?
Yes, of course. He's fine.
Thank goodness.
Hey, how did the coffee festival thing go?
It went well, thanks to you.
- Hey, give me that! - Not a chance!
- Hey. - Yes?
I heard you went on a blind date and that you're getting married.
Gosh, what are you talking about?
- So it's a groundless rumor? - Of course.
How much of it is not true?
- The "getting married" part. - Then what about the blind date?
I did go on a blind date.
My parents want me to get married soon,
so I went on one, but...
I guess you didn't really like her.
No.
Oh, well. It's not cold at all now, right?
No, it's still very cold.
No, look.
You can only see half of your breath,
compared to the middle of winter.
That might be because of your lung capacity.
- You think so? - Yes.
By the way,
your lips are purple now. It looks so lame.
Jang Woo, you always look lame.
- Really? - Yes.
What are you doing? You need to stay for a few more days.
You still need to get a few tests done.
I'm broke.
They'll move you to a six-person ward when a bed frees up.
- I heard it must've been painful. - Nonsense.
It wasn't so bad.
The doctor said it must've been extremely painful.
It was painful,
but I was too lazy to deal with it.
I heard it must've hurt enough for you to want to see a doctor.
My laziness outdid the pain.
Are we good now?
Auntie.
Auntie!
Mok Hae Won, aren't you going back to Seoul?
Those who must leave will leave.
You showing up and bossing me around like this...
exhausts me.
You should go back to Seoul now.
And those who must be left behind will do just that.
That season is coming.
- Hey, this one too. - This too? Okay.
- All good? - Yes, it's great.
- Over here! - She wants more soup.
- My gosh. - There it is.
Oh, okay. No problem.
- Hey! - All right, here it is.
- Try this. - Eat up.
- Can I have more of this? - Thank you.
- Oh, I'll do it. - Okay.
- Thank you! - Look at this.
Hey, go on.
All right. Here you go.
After making rice cakes with rice from last year,
we get ready to plant rice in the field. That's how it goes.
Yes, exactly.
We should...
close down the ice skating rink.
Time flies, doesn't it?
Gosh, you're still young.
- I'll take this. - Okay.
All right, enjoy.
Oh, okay. Sure.
Hello! Yes.
- My gosh! - Come on.
Gosh, you scared me.
Are you coming from the hospital?
What are you doing here?
Did Hae Won call you?
Yes.
I'm okay.
Hae Won overreacted.
Myeong Yeo.
Take off your sunglasses.
No.
This isn't what I...
I sent you here so you could live a full life.
So you could write books, date,
and live your life to the fullest...
How...
But how...
could I do that?
What?
How could I do that?
I killed a person.
Other people...
might have pitied you,
but I didn't.
I pitied myself.
Why would you pity yourself?
I have the right to pay for what I did,
but you took that away from me.
That's because...
you didn't do anything wrong.
I did.
I'm the one who stepped on the gas...
and killed him.
Myeong Ju, I even remember...
how the wind against my face...
had the smell of blood that day.
How could you say I didn't do anything wrong?
How could I possibly...
pretend nothing happened...
and go on with my life?
How could I?
Did you eat?
Did you try to persuade Myeong Yeo?
Try to persuade her.
With some medication and laser treatment,
they can at least save the other eye.
You and Auntie are close, aren't you?
Was I ever?
She finally started writing again,
and it seemed like she was seeing Yun Taek again too.
I thought she was changing little by little.
But I was wrong.
Auntie never wants to do anything.
- Myeong Ju. - Yes?
I want to do everything.
What do you mean?
I want to do everything in the world.
I'll do it all.
The weather is nice.
Myeong Ju.
I'm scared.
I'm so scared.
Myeong Ju, I'm scared.
I'm scared.
I'm so scared.
Myeong Ju.
- Hey, Lim Hwi. - Yes?
How dare you come to school on Young Soo's bike?
- Who are you? - Me?
I'm Young Soo's girlfriend,
Song Jae In.
I see. So that's who you are.
- What? - I'm glad you're here.
- Hey! - Hey!
- Let go! - Gosh.
Guys, this is unbelievable.
- Let go! - How dare you?
I said, let go!
Let go!
Hey!
Seriously.
Let go on the count of three.
- 1, 2, 3. - 1, 2, 3.
- Why are you not letting go? - Gosh!
Hey, Young Soo!
Song Jae In and Lim Hwi got into a huge fight because of you.
Aren't you coming?
What's with him?
(Good Night Bookstore)
Yes, Mother.
I'll be right there.
Okay.
Shame on you.
What are you talking about?
How could you fight with another girl over a guy?
I'm ashamed of you.
Mom.
Guys are everything to me.
Are you out of your mind?
Have you completely lost it?
It hurts! I'm not out of my mind. I'm perfectly fine.
After drinking that brain tonic, I'm more clear-headed than ever.
Why would you make a move on a guy who has a girlfriend?
Mom, it was just a deal.
A deal, like a business arrangement.
Hwi, I don't think that's...
That's not the point.
Hwi!
Seung Ho, what are you doing here?
You came here as my guardian? All right.
I hear you got in trouble.
Yes, how did you know that?
Did you tell him?
- Yes. - Gosh.
Come on. When you get in trouble,
your parents are called to your school.
I know that much.
Right?
Seung Ho, you're so smart.
Smart boy.
Should you be complimenting him for being smart?
Do you want everyone to find out I got in trouble?
My goodness.
If you're worried about that, why did you get in trouble?
I said it was just a deal.
Everyone already found out.
- Everyone knows. - Stop hitting me.
It hurts.
Grandpa!
Seung Ho!
Do you feel better? Are you okay now?
Yes, I am.
You're all grown up,
worrying about your grandpa.
Let's go home now.
Shall we?
I've been driving a lot today.
You really have.
Did you try to reach Seung Ho's dad?
Yes,
but I couldn't reach him.
Do you at least have the right phone number?
I'm not sure. I called him but couldn't get through.
I tried calling the travel agency he works at too,
but he apparently quit.
I see.
When did you say he was last here?
I think it was about five years ago?
I gave them my number for now.
What about you?
Everything's the same for me.
Auntie is stubbornly insisting she's okay...
and my mom seems like she doesn't even want to persuade her.
What is wrong with both of them?
What happened to Seung Ho's dad and Myeong Yeo.
Maybe...
it's something time will take care of.
Just like when spring comes after winter?
Yes.
It feels like spring will come soon.
Right.
(Hey. Who do you think is the one who killed my brother-in-law?)
Cha Yun Taek.
Yes,
you're right.
What everyone says is wrong...
and you're right.
To tell you the truth, I...
("The Maze of Sisterfield" by Shim Myeong Yeo)
(Cha Yun Taek. Yes, you're right.)
I never wanted to give up on myself for a single moment.
(Winners of Literary Contest)
You know what? I find this so amusing.
What do you mean?
I'm the best writer here anyway.
What?
I'm the best writer.
What use is it if I win a contest?
I'll beat everyone eventually.
Am I wrong?
I never thought that I was untalented...
or thought this was the end...
and that this was all that I had inside me.
I never thought I would crumble or fall ill...
or grow old and ugly. I have never...
thought of that in my entire life.
I never imagined spending the rest of my life...
alone in this empty place...
like someone waiting to die.
Have a good life.
Get married like you've always wanted,
have kids like you've always dreamed of,
and live happily ever after.
And the truth is,
Myeong Yeo.
Please be happy. Forget an idiot like me, okay?
I have never...
wanted to break up with you for a single moment.
Sir, can you turn the car around?
That's the truth,
Cha Yun Taek.
This way.
Why do you keep coming back to this town?
You told me about the train schedule.
Hey, Shim Myeong Yeo.
Let me hug you just once.
What?
No.
To be honest,
I never wanted to break up with you either...
for a single moment.
Are you sure you read what I did...
in the manuscript I sent you?
Article 4-3, "Confidentiality of contents".
"I will not ask what is the truth and what is a lie."
You don't even know...
what is the truth and what is a lie.
Look at yourself right now.
Is that wrong?
You are...
more tolerant than I thought, Cha Yun Taek.
Of course, I am.
That's why I loved you.
Hello.
- Hey. - You're all here.
- Hello. - Hyun Ji, don't carry that around.
Did someone smack you in the head with it?
- Hello. - Welcome.
- Jang Woo, you're here. - Hello, sir.
What's up?
- Hi, Eun Sil. - I'm glad you're here. Come inside.
Inside? Just the two of us in that small room?
Wait, let me put this down. Hang on.
- Why are you so late? - I dropped by my place.
- Eun Sil, what is it? - I'm glad you're here.
Taste this.
What do you think?
- What? - How does it taste?
I don't know.
Oh, no. What do I do?
Then...
What about this?
Oh, it tastes good.
- What? - What?
I bought this.
I bought this one from my mom's shop.
So are you saying this is the only thing that tastes good?
No, I didn't mean that.
Then... what about this?
What do you think? Is it too salty? Sweet?
- I really don't know. - Seriously!
Do you only lose your sense of taste for my food? Are you kidding me?
You little... Oh, gosh!
My gosh, your arm... Your arm is very strong.
Oh, I have strong legs too.
My gosh, it's so nice. I mean, good for you.
Hey, you two. What are you guys doing?
Oh. What?
- What do you mean? - Gosh.
- What's with that smirk? - Well, we were just...
- What's going on? - Nothing.
What?
All right, let's see.
My, what a nice blanket.
Right? It took me so long to make this.
- Isn't it so nice? - Yes, it is.
- Geun Sang. - Yes?
When you're done with that,
can you clean the mold too?
Sure, I was going to do that anyway.
Hey, here you go.
My gosh, Hyun Ji. How come you're so good at this?
Did you take classes or something?
I thought it'd be cool to include it in my hip-hop performance,
so I practiced it.
Goodness. And people call me a lunatic?
Gosh, unreal.
Young Soo. The more I think about it, the angrier I get.
I'm talking about Song Jae In.
The girl who's been telling everyone that she's your girlfriend.
What on earth did you say to her? She totally beat me up.
Hey, I've never been slapped in the face before.
I've been a total outcast for two years,
but no one ever slapped me in the face.
I heard you pulled her hair out too.
Well... She started it though.
Did you just scoff? Do you want to get involved in the fight?
- Hey. - What?
Song Jae In wants to go to school with us every morning.
What? Why?
No! I hate it!
Gosh, I really don't want to do that.
We're here. Let's go inside.
Let's go.
1, 2, 3.
- Welcome home! - Welcome home!
- How are you feeling? - I'm great.
Did you have dinner?
- No, he hasn't eaten yet. - My gosh.
- Oh, right. - Let's go in, Seung Ho.
The ones you made are no good.
- Why? - Gosh, go on in.
- Come on. - What?
You must be exhausted.
No, I'm good.
Go in and get some rest.
Okay.
Oh, right.
Bo Yeong said sorry.
She sincerely apologized to me.
But she also said that she hates me.
She hates me because she liked me.
And she said I probably disliked her.
Did you?
I'm not sure.
Did I never like her to begin with?
All I can think about is the way I feel about her now,
so I can't even recall how I used to feel about her when we were close.
But things can't go back to the way they used to be...
even if I remember how I used to feel about her.
Trust is like glass.
Once broken, the cracks will always be visible...
even if you glue the broken pieces back together.
That's true.
Don't think too much though.
Go on in.
Bye.
Drive safely.
Eun Seop, I sent you an e-mail.
Can you check?
("The Maze of Sisterfield")
(Shim Myeong Yeo)
I read your e-mail.
You wrote that it's up to me to decide...
whether or not I want to share what I read with Hae Won.
But perhaps, you sent me this writing because...
- you want her to know the truth. - Gunbam!
Gosh, you came to see me? Gunbam, my sweetie.
You look so glamorous and adorable.
I'll see you later, okay?
Like you said, hurting a family member...
is a crime. I can't refute that,
but I don't know exactly what happened.
That's why I don't think I can be the judge of this.
It'll be hard, but telling her in person would be...
the right thing to do.
But if you can't bring yourself to face her,
I'll pass this writing along to Hae Won...
and leave it at that.
Keeping this all to yourself...
must've been very painful.
But no matter what happens,
I trust that your love for Hae Won...
is real.
What is this?
Read it.
What is it?
A novel you wrote?
No.
Then what is it?
It's just...
All right.
But why are you telling me to go home?
I want to stay.
Well, I think reading this is more important.
I'll come to Hodu House after work.
Let's talk then.
Okay.
This, all of a sudden?
I'm home.
Auntie.
Auntie?
But why are you telling me to go home?
I want to stay.
Well, I think reading this is more important.
("The Maze of Sisterfield")
(Shim Myeong Yeo)
"The day before I broke up with you,"
"September 4, 2010."
"It started raining early in the morning."
"My sister texted me."
(Curry?)
(Myeong Ju)
Curry?
(Sure.)
(Sent)
It was a day like any other.
Myeong Ju.
Gosh.
How dare you?
How dare you...
look down on me?
Who do you think you are?
Answer me! Who do you think you are?
Hey!
Answer me!
You little...
Who do you think you are? Answer me!
Hey!
"Even my brother-in-law beating up my sister..."
"was the same as always."
"The only difference was..."
"that I..."
"ended up killing him."
("The Maze of Sisterfield")
- I'm home. - Mom.
Mom.
Well...
I mean...
Who killed Dad?
What?
Does this mean you're not the one who killed Dad?
It was Auntie, who looked after me?
So Auntie...
- Hae Won. - Tell me.
Did Auntie really kill Dad?
Well...
Hae Won, the thing is...
Answer me right now!
No, she didn't...
- Let go! - Hae Won.
So you two knew.
Hae Won.
I know why you hated Dad.
I didn't like Dad all the time either.
Still, he's my dad.
It wasn't you...
who killed Dad...
but Auntie?
Hae Won.
I'll be looking after you from now on.
She was the only person left that I could trust and rely on.
Hae Won.
You two are scary.
Don't follow me.
("The Maze of Sisterfield")
"So tell me."
"Do you think you can forgive me?"
(Bukhyeon Three-way Intersection)
Mom!
Hae Won.
I think your mom is in a bad mood today.
Why don't you play with me?
Okay?
Miss.
Are you okay?
(Books)
Excuse me. Did you see a young woman here?
Oh, she's sitting over there.
Thank you.
Hae Won.
(Good Night Bookstore Private Blog Posting)
(There was a time when I thought life...)
(was the process of finding one's place.)
(A place where it's okay for me to exist...)
(without bothering anyone, or being bothered either.)
(Finding a place where no one would refuse me.)
(That's what I thought life was.)
(But now, I've changed my mind.)
(Wherever it may be, the place where I am right now is my place.)
(As long as I live as my true self,)
(I believe it will be okay for me to exist in this place.)
(That's all I have to say today.)
(If I say more, I might want to quit everything.)
(When the Weather is Fine)
Do you think all of this was really something I didn't have to know?
Since you would've been hurt.
They probably wanted to shoulder everything instead.
You know Eun Sil is leaving today, right?
She's going back to Gangneung. Apparently, her vacation is over.
I'm so afraid.
I don't know what people are truly like anymore.
It feels as if I'm being deceived.
Are you saying you'll turn yourself in?
What does that make me?
Although it's late, I want to pay for my sins.
I'm going to leave.
Spring is here.