I believe...
there is a reason...
to why someone survives.
It's because there's something in this world only you can do.
That's why the reason you're alive...
may be a blessing to us.
So Ji Su, you can do anything you want.
You can rest, you can cry,
and if it's too much,
you don't have to try so hard to bear it.
I'll be by your side.
Why would you be by my side?
I'll be in my place,
and you'll be in yours.
Okay.
Anyone can see that this isn't right,
and even if it's your first love,
you can't justify something that's inappropriate.
But why can't I...
turn away from you?
Why can't I just keep you in my memories?
I kept thinking about it,
and the answer was in our past.
You told me...
that I am...
your belief and your world.
There's something I couldn't say back to you.
To me, you were my dream.
I'm facing the dream I had lost,
so I can't leave it...
nor run away from it.
Because that's my dream.
Because it's a dream,
we'll wake from it soon.
I should go now.
Jae Hyun.
Yes?
Sorry to ruin the mood,
but I'm so cold and hungry.
Yoon Ji Su.
Are you upset? Are you?
I thought you were all grown up,
but you're a baby.
Are you upset?
You're not, are you?
Whatever.
I'm sorry.
Hey. You'll catch a cold.
(Jungang Market)
That's the one.
This is...
clotted blood?
Yes.
When we have nosebleeds,
the blob we feel...
is this blood clot?
Humans are so cruel.
We even take the blood from cows?
You aren't eating? It's delicious.
What?
Do they sell this in Seoul too?
I'll buy you some.
It's amazing.
Jae Hyun.
Weren't we a little cute back then?
No.
We were very cute.
(When My Love Blooms)
(Some topics were exaggerated for dramatic effect.)
(Episode 5)
Go on home.
Ji Su.
I said yesterday that I'd be by your side.
I meant it.
It was a dream.
It's all a dream.
I woke up.
- So you should... - I'm not trying anything.
I just want to stop you...
from crying again.
Don't worry.
I cry in my dreams, but rarely in my real life.
Don't you cry.
If you do, I'll come for you.
That sounded like a line from a Christmas carol.
Get some rest.
Where's my wife?
Oh. She's not back yet.
Hi. Come in.
I have to leave soon. I'm shooting a movie.
At what time?
Around 3pm?
Can you not do that?
It bothers me that there are so many girls.
They are nothing to me.
I'll give you the money.
I don't work for money.
Then what for?
Self-realization?
You're not a teenager.
See you another time.
Wait.
- Buy what you need. - It's fine.
It's not fine.
That bag is terrible.
Throw it away.
Yes, sir.
Where are you?
At home.
Then come over.
Okay. I will.
Are you preparing for the parliamentary inspection?
Yes.
I heard they're trying to figure out...
whether to grill you or boil you.
It's fine.
Assemblymen live for the fun of yelling at others.
Bow a little when you need to,
and pretend you respect them...
with a few sweet phrases.
Do you understand?
Yes.
What's up with Seo Kyung now?
I told you to sort it out. Didn't you already?
You don't fear me, do you?
I fear myself.
I can't control myself...
when it comes to my own daughter.
If you make my girl cry,
you'll have to leave this house.
You'll have nothing but shorts on.
Will you be okay with that?
Hey.
- Sir? - Yes?
Someone is using your wife's credit card...
to spend thousands of dollars every few minutes.
Where?
At luxury label stores at the department store.
How dare you come here?
I thought you wanted me here.
Were you with her?
"I'm suffering. I'm pathetic."
"Don't worry. I'll look after you."
With a face full of pity,
did you shoot your melodrama?
You're drunk.
You know what?
I was with a man too.
We're even.
So don't be so serious.
This is nothing at all.
You and I both are way too stressed out.
We need a diversion.
It's nothing more,
and nothing less.
Right?
Hello.
I'm so sorry. I really loved your music.
It can't be helped.
I couldn't control my temper.
It was great to see. I loved it.
How much do you think I'll have to pay her back?
- What? - The dress.
I'll find out and get back to you.
Will you work at another hotel?
Tell me where so I can come along.
I really don't know...
where to go now.
Cheer up.
You work so hard.
Your day will come soon.
My good day hasn't come yet.
I thought it would soon.
Don't do it again.
When around me,
don't hold someone else's hand.
You know why I'm like this.
Even your fingernails are so weak.
So why are you so mean?
Do you think you're still fierce?
You can't leave home.
You told me to fight.
Running away isn't fighting.
I can't handle him.
I'll come with you.
You can't handle him either.
Then what? We never see each other again?
No. But I really think this isn't the right day.
If it's not today, it's not tomorrow either.
I want to ask you something.
Why are you so harsh to Ji Su?
Must I explain that to you?
To be honest, I don't think I can accept...
any explanation you give.
Even if she's hit with a flower, I don't think I can take that.
To be a warm-hearted prosecutor who helps the powerless outsiders.
To be a fair prosecutor who only pursues the truth.
To be a trustworthy prosecutor who wins trust and understanding.
To be an upright prosecutor who is stricter to himself.
You swore that oath,
and out of all the prosecutors who also did,
you reached the highest position.
I ask you to...
treat Ji Su with warmth.
You're studying law?
Yes.
Will you take the law exam?
I plan to.
Is it because you're cautious,
or because of your beliefs?
You seem to lack both caution and beliefs.
You should leave.
I don't want to hear from or see you again.
We're lucky that it ended at this.
It's me.
Find out about a kid for me.
Law major, class of 1995, Han Jae Hyun.
I think he's into protesting.
Find out about his finances.
Bye.
Don't worry.
I won't see him again.
The dress costs 3,000 dollars.
Did you practice a lot? Go on home then.
- Goodbye. - Bye.
Ma'am.
Yes, go ahead.
Well,
do you know students who want private lessons?
Ms. Yoon, don't you already teach a lot of private lessons?
I am...
in urgent need of money.
I can sympathize with you,
but it's not like I have a list of students for private lessons.
Anyway, I'll tell you as soon as I get a request.
Thank you. Thank you so much.
(Part-time Paradise, waitress wanted, kitchen assistant wanted)
(Looking for a part-timer at a pork rib restaurant)
(Special Exhibition on Leslie Cheung)
(Pork Ribs)
So Ji Su,
you can do anything you want.
You can rest,
you can cry,
and if it's too much,
you don't have to try so hard to bear it.
I'll be by your side.
Hey, Young Woo.
Where are you?
I'm home.
What are you doing?
I'm washing dishes.
Where are you? Send me the address.
If you don't, I'll report you missing to the police.
If you want a job, work at my bar.
Their hourly rate is high.
I'll pay you the same rate.
I know your bar is slow.
You don't want to play the piano anymore?
Can you do manual work with your hands?
Rubber gloves are pretty sturdy these days.
Why are you working at restaurants?
I was doing a part-time gig at the hotel.
And I ruined a brand designer's dress.
Find another hotel to work at.
- I don't want to. - Why not?
I can't think while doing this physical labor. It's nice.
Besides, it's pathetic that I'm trying to make money...
at working at a hotel like I'm classy or something.
I had to eat brunches with the other mothers at the hotel,
so I wore a mask.
My whole life had been appalling.
Now, I'll live without a mask.
Actually,
I never got to tell you,
but you look much better without a mask.
Do you mean it? Or is that sarcasm?
It's the truth.
That's heartbreaking. I tried to look my best.
Don't you have a mirror at home?
My gosh, that's why you're still single.
Hey, wait up.
You must be busy. I'm sorry to ask you to come back.
It's all right. What is this about?
Well...
We should settle up.
Yes.
"Since I'm rich, I don't want your money."
I don't do that.
I learned it since I was a kid...
that things must be clear when it comes to money.
I'll pay you in a week.
Do you think you only have to pay for the dress?
Why won't you compensate for trying to wreck my family?
I already know what you and Jae Hyun will tell me.
Since I cheated first, you think...
I don't deserve to say anything.
Then, you should've stopped where I stopped.
Have fun with him for a while and leave him,
so he doesn't have an ounce of sympathy...
and lingering attachment for you.
Then, I'll settle that you paid me...
everything you owe me.
For your information,
I'm not ethical at all.
Be it your hair or whatnot.
I'll grab everything I can put my hands on.
I'm very good at slapping people...
and splashing water.
We'll begin the audit for illegally terminating temporary workers...
at Hyung Sung Group...
and issued stocks under borrowed names.
All the account holders who lent their names...
stated that the real owner of their stocks...
is you, Vice-President Han Jae Hyun.
If we add up all the stocks, it calculates up to...
35 percent of all the stocks...
when the chairman, Jang San, owns only 21 percent of the stocks.
The employees with the permanent positions...
make up less than 60 percent of the company.
Hyung Sung Group is a big company.
Why would you do something like that?
I will answer your question after looking into...
that matter.
What do you know then?
If you don't know anything, why did you come?
You should be ashamed of yourself.
Besides,
didn't you work hard campaigning when you were in college?
That's not all. From what I know, you used to be in a labor movement.
What a turncoat.
You're not going to attend the festival?
(May 1994)
No.
Why not? I really want to go.
You should go.
Everyone is attending the festival with their boyfriend or girlfriend.
There's a strike for the subway union.
And there's Uruguay Round,
the school election, and a tuition protest.
That was a lie.
I'm really moody these days.
What?
I've been rebelling without a reason and feeling rebellious.
I feel like...
I've been copying the activists from the 80s...
and playing politics like grown-ups, so I'm thinking about it.
I have a lot on my mind,
so I can't go to the festival and have fun.
Jae Hyun, when will you enjoy your life?
When the world is good?
I hope the world becomes good in no time.
Goodness.
I have a meeting in the club room. You can come with me.
100 liberal arts students.
50 math and science students.
40 law majors. And what about them?
How many?
I'll know once Kyung Ho comes.
If we get 50 students from their side,
we can gather 500 students.
We'll pick out good runners...
and put 40 students in the 1st and 2nd rows.
Then, our form will be somewhat ready.
We need way more than 500.
It's getting worse every year.
It makes me wonder if we should take softer approaches.
"Revolution, purge, and destruction."
Our terms can sound too aggressive.
Hey.
The students from my department can't join.
Why not?
They're giving a last-minute test to business majors.
Come on. Tell them to die.
How do they expect to join us when they're worried about tests?
Well, this test will be reflected on their grades.
We get grades too.
Do you think I get Fs because I want to?
You think I collect Fs?
Seriously. The student council is a bigger problem.
They study for TOEIC.
Or they are dating.
You know?
We are definitely losing our momentum.
It's because we have a civilian government.
Didn't I tell you?
Student campaigning is like a bicycle.
We must keep campaigning without skipping a day.
Endlessly. If we don't have momentum, what should we do?
- We must... - Do you...
just want to ride it?
- What? - Where is the bicycle headed?
What's its destination?
Gosh, you punk.
Because you have a calculative approach and a negative mindset,
our organization is going down the drain.
Since your grades are a mess,
if you graduate with these grades, you won't ever get a job.
So I know that you're trying to get a job in the political world.
Some of us came here to make changes...
in the world while ignoring our studies.
Don't use us to push your bicycle.
Especially, the Jangs of Hyung Sung Group...
have been swindling profits...
to satisfy their own interests...
through countless ways such as...
owning stocks under borrowed-names and creating a slush fund.
However, they terminated...
all of the temporary workers...
and showed immoral conduct at the highest degree.
- Tough day, sir. - Yes.
The account holders must have stated truthfully.
That the real owner of the stocks is me.
They are in a hurry to transfer the title.
I'm thinking about handing out number tickets.
Once the titles are transferred, we'll have to pay taxes.
Seoul Bank is still working on the paperwork.
I've been on their tails.
By the way, we can resolve the civil suit this way.
What about the criminal suit?
Should I meet with prosecutors in advance?
- There's no need. - Why not?
I already did.
- Mr. Jung. - Yes, sir.
How come no one knows...
I negotiated with the terminated workers?
Is the PR team slacking off?
I'll check on it and handle it right away.
I'm sure they all saw it.
- Jun Woo. - Yes, sir.
The black car behind us. How long has it been following us?
I see. Well,
I think it's been following us from the parking lot.
- Since today? - No, it started a few days ago.
- Jun Woo. - Yes, sir.
The black car behind us. How long has it been following us?
I see. Well,
I think it's been following us from the parking lot.
- Since today? - No, it started a few days ago.
What about our car?
I'm checking every day if there's a tracker on it.
(Special Exhibition on Leslie Cheung)
Did you say you like movies?
Yes, I like them very much.
Do you want to watch a movie?
Now?
I know that I shouldn't be watching a movie right now.
But it makes me think...
if I'll have the right time to watch a movie.
I'm totally in.
(October 1994)
My goodness. That was no fun at all. Let's just leave.
My gosh, these movies from Hong Kong aren't like real movies.
You know, the movie with Chow Yun Fat where he shoots guns?
- Let's watch something like that. - What a waste of money.
That was so boring.
That movie from Hong Kong wasn't fun at all.
Let's just go.
- My gosh. - Darn it.
Wait here.
Your arms must hurt.
How did you know that I would be here?
Sorry to break it to you, but I didn't come here for you.
I was doing a protest, but I sneaked out when I saw the poster.
I wanted to watch this movie.
And protesting wasn't fun.
I sneezed because of the tear gas.
I knew it was you when I heard you sneeze.
You should have sat next to me.
I didn't want to block the guys' view.
Those guys wanted a refund.
They thought it was similar to "A Better Tomorrow".
I see.
I like Leslie Cheung in "A Better Tomorrow".
But I liked his role in this movie too.
Right.
I want him to have a long career. Don't you agree?
You know what, Jae Hyun?
There are some people who are destined...
to cross paths again no matter what they do.
I think that's us.
(Payphone)
I'll be home soon, so don't lock the door.
Okay.
Press 1 to call. Press 2 to record a message.
And press three to record the voicemail greeting.
Hi, this is Yoon Ji Su's boyfriend, Han Jae Hyun's pager.
If you're a guy, press 1 or 2.
And if you're a girl, just hang up. He's taken.
Besides, his girlfriend has a bad temper.
What are you doing? I'll scold you.
The recording is complete.
Hi, this is Yoon Ji Su's boyfriend, Han Jae Hyun's pager.
If you're a guy, press 1 or 2.
And if you're a girl, just hang up. He's taken.
- Besides... - Darn it.
How was it?
This movie was very artistic.
And Leslie Cheung is very handsome.
- What did you like about it? - What?
I liked the action scenes.
I heard you snore like crazy.
I'll get the car.
Leslie Cheung once said...
that half of "Days of Being Wild" was his own story.
That was the raw side of him in the movie.
He looked lonely and in despair. Right?
Yes.
(Jang Seo Kyung)
- Hey. - Where are you?
I'm sure you know where I am.
What do you mean?
- He hasn't reported to you yet? - It's not me.
My dad might have sent someone to tail you, but not me.
Then, ask your father where I am.
Wait.
(Jae Hyun: Wait.)
I'm behind you.
I'm being tailed.
Do you remember what you said...
when we watched this movie?
"People who are destined..."
"to cross paths again no matter what they do".
(People who are destined to cross paths again no matter what they do)
(Ocean Music Academy)
(December 1994)
What does this mean?
"Let's meet up, together."
"Let's meet up, cucumber"?
"Let's get together."
That seems far-fetched.
"1010235".
I know this one. "I deeply adore you."
"1200".
"1200"?
"Let's break up"?
"A lot to do".
Oh. I guess you studied a lot.
I also studied music.
Music?
The end.
What song is that?
"The Child Who Counted the Stars".
By Jeong Won Yeong.
How was it?
Are you sleeping?
I think the song is weird.
Why?
It keeps making me cry.
Gosh, what's wrong with it?
- Wasn't that fun? - Yes, it's so fun.
I want to practice at home.
Is this yours?
No, I borrowed it from another club.
Oh, really? Then I should buy one.
Will you help me pick one out?
I'll buy it for you.
No, it's all right.
I have the money.
Once I get my pay for my part-time job.
How am I supposed to let you?
I'm going to get you one, so that's that.
Let's try again.
Try holding it with your fingers.
What do you think you're doing in this sacred place?
I'm learning to play the guitar.
Hey, what does he know about the guitar...
to be teaching you?
You saw me playing the guitar, didn't you?
I did.
You did. I was much better, wasn't I?
You were, but...
Give it here.
What are you doing?
- Come on, give it. - Gosh.
Your silence
And my dry lips
- As you - Dong Jin
How many years have you been playing that one song?
I only dig one hole
And I should dig one up for you.
You're ruining this amazing song.
Don't you feel bad for Yang Hee Eun?
As you turn around
Instead of saying I love you
Come on in.
Hello.
Go and wash your hands and feet.
Yes, ma'am.
How is his mother doing?
Just the same.
She should either go bankrupt...
or turn to something else.
It should be either way.
Are you sure she doesn't have a man?
How would she find someone...
at that age and circumstance?
That may be true,
but she is quite pretty.
There must be something going on.
Mom.
When you're reading this letter,
I may not be in this world anymore.
Each day is so difficult,
and I can't seem to figure it out.
What is the name of the store, sir?
- Hendrix. - "Hendrix".
I still can't imagine it, sir.
That you used to play the guitar.
Did you have long hair and bang your head?
With leather pants, biting at the guitar strings?
I feel like biting you, so just find the store.
There it is, sir.
"Hendrix".
(Hendrix, Guitar Specialty Store)
- Excuse me. - Excuse me.
What?
Do you want "Love Letter" too?
Gosh, Ms. Yoon.
Ma'am.
Goodness.
So you're the piano teacher...
the director was talking about.
Come on in.
All right.
This is so easy to use. And delicious.
- It really is good. - Right?
It's better than going to a cafe.
Will I be teaching Se Ri's little sister?
Yes, she's seven.
She just went to the store. She'll be back soon.
Did she go with Se Ri?
Se Ri went to Jun Seo's place.
Didn't Young Min go?
- Jun Seo's place? - Yes, Jun Seo is having...
a party at a hotel and invited all...
Gosh, I guess he forgot.
I don't think Jun Seo invited Young Min.
They're not close.
Is that so?
(Young Min, what are you up to? Did you have lunch?)
(Tell Dad to buy you a lot of good food.)
Young Min.
Should we transfer schools?
Tell me the truth. What happened?
Nothing.
Then why did you write this?
I was just tired of studying.
And that made you think of dying?
It's school violence, isn't it?
No, it's not.
I can go and ask the school.
I am...
an impatient person.
I was the offender.
I'm so sorry.
- Sir. - Yes?
- Where will you play the guitar? - I'm not telling you.
I want to see you play.
There's nothing to see. It's been more than 20 years.
But still, your body will remember it.
Well...
It remembers too clearly.
What's that guitar for?
I thought I'd start playing again.
Gosh, then you should've asked me.
I used to be great at playing the guitar.
Ask Yoon Ji Su if you don't believe me.
I always played it for her in our club room.
You did. 1 song during the whole 4 years.
At least I mastered that one song.
With these delicate fingers too.
I do feel bad for Yang Hee Eun.
I'm going to apologize to her if I ever get to meet her.
So you do have a conscience?
Anyway, so you want to try playing?
Do you think you can do that here?
- Hey, Dong Jin. - Yes?
Can I do something...
cowardly just for today?
What?
I'm at your place. I have something to tell you.
(Lee Se Hun)
Young Min, what are you up to?
Did you have lunch?
Tell Dad to buy you a lot of good food.
Mom.
Dad found out about school.
What is it?
I have something to give you.
What's that guitar for?
I just remembered that...
I had promised to get you one.
You know that...
I'm not going to take it.
I do. I know that very well,
but this was a promise made long ago,
so I thought you would take it.
And more than that, actually...
It's because I missed you.
My son is friends with Young Min. They are in the same class.
Since you're here, I'll get going.
(Han Jae Hyun)
(Han Jae Hyun, Vice-President, Hyung Sung Group)
("The Love Story Between the Owner's Daughter and the Employee")
(When My Love Blooms)
Do you regret it?
I couldn't change anything, after all.
I wasn't able to protect the most important thing.
You should go your own way.
And I'll go mine.
He called it an affair. What I did.
I'm going to make him take responsibility for what he did.
I'm not here to blackmail you. I'm asking for your cooperation.
Do what you want to do most...
or avoid what you're most afraid of.
This is just the beginning.
It will be a long battle.