What is it?
I have something to give you.
What's that guitar for?
I just remembered that...
I had promised to get you one.
You know that...
I'm not going to take it.
I do.
I know that very well,
but this was a promise made long ago,
so I thought you would take it.
And more than that, actually...
It's because I missed you.
My son is friends with Young Min. They are in the same class.
Since you're here, I'll get going.
(Han Jae Hyun)
(Han Jae Hyun, Vice-President, Hyung Sung Group)
("The Love Story Between the Owner's Daughter and the Employee")
The bus stop is quite a walk from your place.
I don't mind. I can exercise.
Should you be out like this?
You're being followed.
I'm in disguise.
You look just the same.
I'm disguised.
Dong Jin and I are useless like that.
Neither of us is good at this.
How is Dong Jin?
He's the same. He still tells lame jokes,
and his English is still poor.
- Will you let go? - Come on.
Just put it on.
I won't go.
You lunatic.
Your girlfriend went on a blind date,
and you're going to a protest?
She just took her friend's place.
Does it say on her forehead?
Someone could still fall for her.
Plus, don't forget who the guys are.
Are you fitter than them or richer than them?
Don't poke me.
- You must wear this too. - What's this?
It's something pretty.
Are you dressing me up as a DJ?
You country bumpkin.
What do you know about fashion?
Would a rock cafe like The Space...
let someone like you in when you're dressed like a child?
Think about it. Pull up the collar.
Let's go. You look amazing.
- You can go in. - She told me that.
You can go in.
Wait. Next.
Next.
Do you like basketball?
- Yes. - Of course.
No.
Well, it's not like basketball means anything.
- Right? Right? - Right.
I don't like basketball either.
You don't like sports at all.
I guess it must be your major...
No, I like sports.
You like sports.
What kind of sports do you like?
The protesting kind.
Hello.
Who's that?
Who are you?
He has something to say.
He's so darn tall.
What do you have to say?
Are you Ji Su's boyfriend or something?
No.
- I just know... - He's my husband.
Hey. That was way cool.
Let's go, Ji Su.
If I could go back,
it's 1 of the 3 moments I'd cancel out.
To think that I walked about Sinchon, the campus,
and to the rock cafe like that.
Then it wasn't your worst moment.
What was the worst?
The day I followed a senior to my first protest.
If I hadn't done that,
I wouldn't have become a protester.
Do you regret protesting?
I failed to change anything.
And while going out to protest,
I didn't protect what was truly important.
Stop suppressing labor protests!
The government must wake up!
- Wake up! - Wake up!
Guarantee the freedom to work...
and release the imprisoned!
- Release them! - Release them!
Stop suppressing labor protests!
The government must wake up!
- Wake up! - Wake up!
Stop suppressing student protests!
The government must repent!
- Repent! - Repent!
- Stop suppressing labor protests! - Aim!
- The government must wake up! - Fire!
I don't worry.
You're smart and sweet. If you're fighting,
it must be for a good cause.
But...
it's okay even if it's not a good cause.
You're still my son even if you do something bad.
You never did anything bad or wrong...
for the whole time that...
I raised you.
Mom's really okay.
Dad.
You're home.
Why are you outside?
I wanted to take my son on a date.
Protesting is harder...
because the times have changed.
To be honest,
I'd like you to stop.
I know you're fighting for a better world,
but it's not like...
it'll cave in because you give up.
Are you ashamed of me?
No, Dad.
I'm sorry.
I apologize.
If you remember everything so clearly,
why don't you live like that?
You're right.
I have to return to a world with no protesting or guitar.
Can we meet again?
Even if we meet again,
we can't laugh together.
Because I'm fighting people like you.
Mom. Dad found out about school.
(Call history)
(My son)
The receiver cannot be...
Young Min, sorry, I just read your message.
Call and tell me what happened.
Even if we meet again,
we can't laugh together.
Because I'm fighting people like you.
What's up?
I heard.
Don't think of using the school.
It was just an accident and it was dealt with.
I know. And I won't use the school.
I'm a father.
Not a thug.
My heart aches to think why he went that far,
and wonder how much worse you must've felt.
I know you don't mean that,
but pretend that you do.
I won't forgive you if you change your mind.
I'm nice to you, but you're not nice to me.
A different outfit and car?
He's being followed.
She works at a restaurant?
Yes. The victim was a regular there...
and mocked the deceased's family all the time.
What did the victim say?
"Freaks crazy about money", and "beggars".
So she poured the food on her tray over the victim.
They could just settle,
but the victim insists on pressing charges,
and the woman insists on going to prison.
It's a mess.
If you settle, your charge can get acquitted.
I won't settle.
If the court accepts you did this on purpose, you'll serve time...
when you shouldn't serve time.
It was neither an accident nor done in the heat of the moment.
He mocked the accident and ridiculed my bereaved family.
He didn't show any signs of remorse or repentance.
I...
intended to do it.
I'm going to tell the world...
what he did.
I understand.
I'll deal with it for you.
Hey.
A suspended sentence is different from a release.
You must be very cautious,
and if you do the same again, you will definitely be sentenced.
The penalty will be heavier.
I don't care.
I knew it.
If I leave you alone, you'll do the same thing a hundred times.
I...
like you, Ji Su.
I'm not saying we should get together now.
It's just that you're going through a rough time,
and your father's sick.
- You have no one to... - Let's say I didn't hear that.
If I lose someone I'm grateful to,
my life would be so desolate.
("Hyung Sung Under Investigation, VP Han Jae Hyun Could Be Jailed")
Jun Seo must be big by now.
Yes. He's big and that much more disobedient.
You were the same.
You're not my son because you're sweet.
You're sweet because you're my son.
I have a long way to go to become like you, Mom.
How so?
I wasn't nice to him because he wasn't nice.
My gosh.
Eat up.
It's completely broken.
What now then?
I can't live without a radio.
There's one at home,
but it's old and I'm not sure if it works.
Forget it, then.
Mom.
Shall I sing for you? A song that you like?
Na Hoon Ah? Cho Yong Pil?
Or Lee Mi Ja?
How about the song you used to sing a lot?
"Because I Love You"?
That song.
The day you left me
What used to be pink in my heart
All our memories
Turned pale
Yesterday, I hated myself
For not
Being able to forget you
But now
I realize that
I was all yours
For you, for returning to me
I will give you my everything
We will stay like this forever
We will never part
Gosh.
This song is too sad.
Why is that sad?
It says they met again...
and won't part forever.
I wish it were like that, but it's not.
Jae Hyun.
Did you meet her again?
Yes.
Is she doing well?
Not really.
Oh, dear.
How pitiful and sorrowful.
But still,
you shouldn't do anything.
I know.
I took a precious day off...
to come here?
But I can't complain because it's paradise.
I don't have much time.
Did you go online today?
No. Why?
Someone you know well is all over the internet.
("Hyung Sung Under Investigation")
("VP Han Jae Hyun Could Be Jailed")
I thought he got lucky when he married rich.
Things like that make me think nothing's for free.
We met.
Who?
- Jae Hyun. - Gosh.
How?
At Young Min's school.
His son is in Young Min's class.
And?
No. It can't be.
No, right?
He doesn't want to get back with you, does he?
You need to keep your wits about you.
Do you know what his wife's dad is like?
Forget about the wife's dad.
Will he give up all he has and get divorced?
Fine, let's say he does.
What about Young Min?
Will you leave your son...
to care for another kid his age?
Are you done? Let's go.
Hey, I can't eat even if I tried.
I lost my appetite.
Hye Jung.
Don't worry.
How can I not worry?
I won't do anything to hurt myself.
Good. If you think you'll get hurt,
scratch him with both hands.
Then he can't hurt you.
Try it. You must practice.
Do this.
I'll need longer fingernails.
Shall I take you to a good manicurist?
- Yes, sir. - Where are you?
I'm at my mother's.
I sent Seo Kyung to the villa.
- Okay. - This is the first time,
so she might be out of control.
Go and sort her out.
I will.
("Hyung Sung Under Investigation")
("VP Han Jae Hyun Could Be Jailed")
Just a moment.
Hi, Ji Su.
Your father has been lucid all day.
You don't have to worry.
He ate well too.
Okay.
He's been Society Head of the Student Union since last fall.
It's been four years since that branch got control,
so they're very active.
He also leads an ideology group called "Solidarity of Philosophy".
He teaches ideologies...
and recruits people too.
Your daughter joined as well.
What about his family?
His father works at a steel company in Incheon.
He's one of the hardcore labor union members.
He comes from an unusual bloodline.
His mother sells fish at a small market store.
He's the typical son of a poor urban family.
I'd say he did pretty well.
Ji Su fell for a terrible fool.
I don't think he's the terrible kind.
He seems more gentle and warm...
That's why he's harder to get rid of.
The good have a certain power.
Jae Hyun, I have bad news.
What's bad now?
The engineering kids were taken in.
They saw Jae Hyun's name.
Where?
On the list of wanted people.
What is he wanted for?
He hasn't done anything recently.
- For recruiting communists. - What a joke.
Did you start a new group?
Then what is it?
It's not the student union.
Your philosophy group?
Then will we all be taken in?
Why did they suddenly target him?
They got the student union and now they want us too.
They could be after all the old protesters.
Did we get the wrong place?
- I'm not sure. Where, then? - Darn it.
You want to study for the bar? You?
It doesn't suit me, right?
It's not that. I thought you weren't interested in it.
I need to get a job.
Can't you do it in Seoul?
Like in a studio for the test takers?
I can't afford it.
And I want to spend some time where there's no TV or computer.
What about me then?
Can't I go with you?
Forget about a piano. There isn't even a melodeon.
I don't care.
I'll cook and do laundry for you.
Goodness.
Why would you cook for someone like me with your talented hands?
It's not like I'm fighting for our independence.
Then, I'll go visit you every week.
You'll distract me.
I'll just go with you, then.
I'll call you once things settle down.
Things about me and my situation.
Even the remotest area must have some reception for radios.
I'm going there to study.
How can you only study?
Listen to it during your breaks.
You can listen to the radio show that plays movie soundtracks.
Hey, Mr. Wanted Man.
Pardon?
How did you know I'm wanted?
When people decide to come down here,
they are either wanted or studying for the bar.
I can tell by your face that you're wanted.
What is it? Am I spot on?
- Yes. - For your information,
I don't like wanted men.
They don't pay much.
And when I see them getting arrested later,
it just bothers me.
So if I see that you're going to cause trouble,
I'm going to call the police right away.
Got that?
Yes.
(List of Major Shareholders for Hyung Sung Holdings)
What about the company? What will happen to it?
What's Jae Hyun up to these days?
I heard he's not coming to his office either.
Before getting interrogated by the prosecutor,
he wants to get some fresh air, so he's been traveling.
Is that what he said?
What is it? Isn't that true?
The inheritance...
I got from your grandfather.
I told you that I put all of them under borrowed names.
But someone must have leaked it.
The press and the prosecutors are trying to probe and prod.
I have put them under his name for the time being.
And once it quiets down, he'll give them back.
But it seems like...
he may have an ulterior motive with the money.
Why would he do that?
How much do you trust him?
How could I live with him if I don't trust him?
I thought he was just a puppy...
who obeys my commands and do a few tricks for me.
But he must have prepared this...
for a long time all on his own.
Prepare to do what?
To take over the company.
He's meeting up with the shareholders.
He's meeting with shareholders who may side with him...
and winning them over to his side.
I think it was him who leaked...
the information about my accounts under borrowed names.
He's the one who started this.
He must take responsibility for it.
I know that he's all that you want.
But starting now,
give him less of your affection.
I'm going now.
Young Min, if something happens to you, call me.
I am much more powerful than your mother.
Okay?
Hi, Mom.
I'm about to go into class.
Dad left.
Young Min.
Young Min, if something happens to you, call me first. Okay?
Dad said the same thing.
If something happens, I should tell him first.
Just do whatever you want.
Tell me if you want to tell me.
Tell Dad if you want to tell him.
And if you don't want to talk about it, don't tell anyone.
Well, not the last one.
Okay. I'll tell you everything.
All right. Try it.
A cup of coffee outdoors.
It's a small luxury.
- This is nice. - Right?
By the way, do you know who that is?
What?
He's been following us.
Do you think the chairman sent him?
Probably.
Do you think he'll win back all the people we worked on?
This will be a long battle, anyway.
It's been hanging in there. How nice.
(March 1995)
It's small and unbelievably cute.
It's just like Ji Su.
Jae Hyun.
It's nice to be here.
It's fun to look at the flowers.
People here call me a flying squirrel.
I'm good at climbing mountains.
And the principal monk is hilarious.
As if that's true. I bet you're itching to get out.
You can see right through me.
It feels empty at school too.
Fewer students are coming to the meeting every week.
This is embarrassing.
This isn't a turbulent era, but look at me.
I'm hiding out here like a democracy activist.
They don't just make it obvious.
Things are still pretty chaotic.
Until when do you think I should stay here?
Until I'm not wanted anymore?
If that never happens, will I shave my head and become a monk?
Hang in there a little longer.
If you crumble,
those weaklings will run away.
You know, Hwa Jin.
Right now,
I don't know when I should get off the bicycle...
and where I should be headed.
So I'm pedaling the bicycle with everything I've got...
because I don't want to fall.
- Bye, Jae Hyun. - Okay.
There's a payphone at the gate of the mountain.
I bought it only recently, so there's a lot of money left.
- Thank you. - Call Ji Su.
Do you know what Jae Hyun is up to these days?
Didn't you hear?
He went to study for the bar.
Where did he go?
To a temple in the mountain.
He did tell you the truth about that.
If he finds out I talked about this, he'd kill me. Darn it.
That jerk is a fugitive now.
Why?
A while ago, he became a wanted man.
Why do you think? He probably did something wrong.
What did he do wrong?
He formed an organization that benefits our enemy.
But Ji Su, I thought about it, but something doesn't add up.
It's not like he founded the philosophy club.
He founded a movie club,
but it's not a threat to our country.
He's in the student council which is a lawful organization.
They can't arrest him for that.
You're telling me this...
for a reason, right?
You are indeed smart.
Well, I'm probably wrong.
But given your father's occupation...
You're behind it, aren't you?
You put Jae Hyun on the wanted list.
He didn't commit any crimes he should be arrested for.
What do you want me to do?
It's called an opportunity cost.
"Opportunity cost".
You can't have everything in life.
If you choose one, you must give something up.
Choose carefully.
Do what you want to do the most.
Or avoid what you fear the most.
If you promise not to see Han Jae Hyun,
I'll get him off the list.
But if you continue to date him,
I will catch him...
and make him rot in jail for years.
And you'll live your life, waiting for him to get out.
You won't be my daughter anymore then.
You will live your life as Han Jae Hyun's woman.
Don't be greedy...
and force yourself to have everything you want.
You must give up something.
You throw away either Han Jae Hyun...
or your life as my daughter.
"Ride the bicycle."
"You're on your path now."
("Literature for Labor Liberation")
The lines are from...
the last scene of a movie, "Running on Empty".
"Sometimes, like his father, or like his son, River Phoenix,"
"to my loved one who's fighting a lonely battle,"
"I want to say this along with these lines."
"You should be on your own path."
A fan of my radio show sent me this letter.
The song request was "Goodbye" by Kim Chang Wan.
This is from one of our business partners.
But no one needs a woman's bike.
I'm not buying that.
I clearly told him the same thing.
But he just put it in the car and told me to get going.
You always drop things after going grocery shopping.
He said you should put the grocery in the basket.
And carrying heavy things won't be good for your fingers.
Take it back.
I can't take it back.
If I take this back, he'll fire me.
Getting a job these days is hard.
Consider this your good deed. Please take it.
You know that if you don't ride this, it'd be a waste of money.
Wait...
(I'm Yoon Ji Su's ex-husband.)
I'm Yoon Ji Su's ex-husband. My name is Lee Se Hun.
There's something I want to discuss. Could we meet?
Why did you send this to me?
If you were after money, you should've sent it to my husband.
But then, I'm not sure...
if this will be a threat to me at all.
I'm not here to blackmail you.
I'm here to ask for your cooperation.
Now that our family has been in the spotlight by the media,
you must think we're a joke...
seeing how a swindler like you is calling me up.
It's not that.
I came to you because I believe we have the same goal.
I hate it when people beat around the bush.
You put a tail on your husband.
So what?
I want to get my wife back.
And don't you want to get your husband back?
You always drop things after going grocery shopping.
He said you should put the grocery in the basket.
And carrying heavy things won't be good for your fingers.
(Seoul Central District Court)
(Petition to Restore Child Custody)
You said you weren't going to use the school incident.
I had a change of heart.
And you still think you're not a scumbag?
Our son thought about killing himself.
What have you done?
If that softie threw a chair at another student,
something must have happened to him.
Instead of getting to the bottom of it,
did you kneel and apologize to the parents?
Or did you want to turn a blind eye...
because he's the son of your past lover?
Does a woman who left her son elsewhere...
while she enjoyed a romantic relationship in Seoul...
really have the right to raise him?
Aren't you being too greedy,
wanting both the custody and the love?
Give up the custody.
I'm being generous to you.
It's too bad that he's married,
but good luck with him.
Whether I have a relationship, remarry, or grow old alone,
I'm going to be the one to raise Young Min.
I won't ever let him grow into a monster with you.
Then try and fight for him.
What's so serious that you can't even drink?
- Ji Su... - You went to law school, right?
Do you know any good lawyers?
Aren't you going to tell me what's going on?
He filed to take back custody.
Young Min's dad.
Why, all of a sudden?
For what reason?
The school violence issue.
How can he say you have no right...
just because the kids got into a fight?
I didn't study that much at law school,
but I do know that...
no matter how good his lawyer is, you'll still win.
He called it an affair. What I did.
Why would...
Is it...
Jae Hyun?
No, it can't be true.
It's a misunderstanding, right?
Someone took a photo of us together.
But Young Woo,
if having feelings is also considered an affair,
I can't say it isn't true.
(Jae Hyun)
Why on earth do you even want to do this?
I saw it on TV, and it looked fun.
We have an amazing house,
and you want to sleep in that tiny tent?
And why would anyone eat like this?
It's going to be better than any hotel restaurant.
Why are you acting like this?
I didn't want to leave you out.
- Dad! - Yes?
- It's burning. Flip it! - Goodness.
It's quite burnt.
- Will it be okay to eat? - Of course.
If you use this any other way,
I won't let it slide.
Of course.
I will be using it for our goal, only.
I'm saying this to you...
out of comradeship and sympathy,
but we both are having such a pitiful love life.
This is all out of love, isn't it?
Don't be ridiculous.
Do you think what you're feeling is love?
It doesn't look like it to me.
I've been hearing about you all along.
On the internet and the news.
I'm sure nothing was good.
How have you been?
I quit my job...
and opened up an LP bar.
That's romantic.
I'm single, so I can barely get by.
So you're not married?
Is there any particular reason?
It just turned out that way.
I guess I'm making you uncomfortable.
Well, it's my turn to make you uncomfortable.
It was me.
On April Fools' Day.
The one who reported you to the police.
(March 31, 1995)
Thanks.
Do you really think it will be okay?
There were a lot of police officers.
That's why I'll be using the streets.
Where are you going?
To Ji Su.
Ji Su...
was having such a hard time between you and her father,
but you seemed so laid-back.
But Ji Su...
was only worried about you,
so I got angry and jealous.
Why are you telling me this now?
I wanted to be open with you.
That way, I can criticize you...
or even ask you a favor.
I already knew, Young Woo.
That you reported me.
So don't feel bad now...
and tell me.
Which one is it today?
A criticism?
Or a favor?
Both.
Surrender custody.
The suit hasn't even begun yet.
If you don't, Han Jae Hyun will fall.
Open it. It will be interesting.
If you surrender custody,
the video will vanish from this world.
If you don't surrender it,
this video will be known to the world...
while the police investigate Han Jae Hyun.
(Running on Empty)
Don't get off.
I won't be seeing you anymore.
I found out that you didn't go to study for the bar.
I'm sorry that I lied.
It doesn't matter...
whether you lied or not.
My dad won't ever allow someone...
who is an activist and even wanted.
- Ji Su... - To be honest,
I don't think I can even manage.
You should...
be on your own path.
And I'll be on my own path.
"We met as the flowers bloomed..."
"and we parted as the flowers fell."
"That was not our first encounter,"
"and it won't be our last farewell."
March 31, 1995.
This is the last show for "FM Movies and Music".
I should say goodbye now.
My last farewell...
will be with Kim Chang Wan's "Goodbye",
from "Happiness Does Not Come In Grades".
Goodbye, dear listeners.
This was your host, Yoo Jung Ha.
(April 1, 1995)
Was that really you, sir?
- Do you admit to it, sir? - Give us a word, sir!
- Do you admit to the allegations? - Could you explain it to us?
- Please give us a word! - What are you planning to do?
- Give us a word! - Do you admit to it?
You must have given it a deep thought. You look sunken.
I've been thinking about it since that day.
About why you were doing this.
You were the one who had an affair...
before Young Min could even walk.
You agreed to give up custody at court...
without giving it a second thought.
Why would you suddenly want it?
Let's just say...
you somehow developed a love for your son.
Then you would have brought up the affair...
and my incompetence at court to win,
but why were you so focused on destroying the man...
instead of bringing back your son?
How can the custody of your child and Han Jae Hyun...
even be comparable?
And did you find the answer?
My dad once told me about the opportunity cost...
25 years ago.
If you choose one side,
you must give up the other.
You need to choose what you want to do the most...
or avoid what you're most afraid of.
You need to choose either side.
So?
I've decided...
to avoid what I'm most afraid of.
What I'm most afraid of,
back then and even now,
is him falling because of me.
It doesn't matter if my choice is right or wrong.
I will go back to you.
- Please give us a word, sir! - What do you have to say?
(When My Love Blooms)
I wanted to protect it.
If you don't give up on Ji Su,
you will have to spend years in jail.
Why did you make that choice?
It has been so many years,
but I still feel bad and miss it.
I think it's because we never properly said goodbye.
You will lose everything you have.
Go ahead...
and reveal the video.