(All characters, places, companies, )
(and incidents in this drama are fictitious.)
Don't water it too much.
- Please bring that here. - I'm on my way.
Put that over there.
- All right. - We brought snacks.
Come have some snacks.
I brought rice wine.
- Come and have some snacks. - Okay.
- Let's take a break. - They brought snacks.
Come have some snacks.
Come on, everyone.
- Hurry on over. - Come on.
Come have some snacks!
(Good Night Bookstore)
You know what, Hae Won?
I believe...
you're doing well.
(Afternoon Music Journey)
It's time to go in.
You can leave your stuff here.
Just bring your instruments and follow me.
Wait! We need another 30 minutes.
We're not done with the rehearsal.
Okay. I'm sorry, guys.
You'll have to wait a little longer.
I'm sorry.
What on earth?
Can you believe this?
Goodness.
(Afternoon Music Journey)
(Episode 16: After a Long Winter)
Hello, this is Good Night Bookstore.
Yes.
Oh, hold on.
Yes, we have it.
Five copies?
Okay, thanks.
Are you doing well, Hae Won?
I am...
doing well too.
- Is this stew? - Yes.
But why is there seaweed inside this?
It's seaweed stew.
What about this sausage?
Sausage and seaweed stew.
You cook like this...
and yet told me to cook for Hae Won?
What? You don't remember?
When are you leaving?
A week later.
Take care.
Okay.
You're not coming back?
Wouldn't that be better for the both of us?
Suit yourself.
The publishing industry has been stuck in a slump for years now.
In the midst of this situation, you always manage to publish...
bestsellers that sell more than 50,000 copies.
Where do you get your talent?
I'm not sure.
I don't consider it a talent.
I guess it's a gift from the skies above.
Is that so?
Let's wrap up the official interview then.
Sure.
This is off the record,
but I heard you're dating Shim Myeong Yeo,
who's about to publish a book.
Is that true?
No.
We used to date a long time ago.
But we're not together now.
I see. Yet you still collaborated with her this time.
Well, we have such a long history.
It kind of turned into a cool relationship...
where we root for each other now.
I see.
Thank you very much for your interview today.
You talk as if it's our first time.
By the way, please write a nice article about Ms. Shim.
You must really be rooting for her future.
(Myeong Yeo)
Hello?
Where are you?
Gunbam.
Myeong Ju.
Where are the zip-top bags?
Have some of this.
(From Shim Myeong Ju, To Shim Myeong Yeo)
Myeong Ju.
- What is this? - A letter you wrote me.
So what? Why are you giving me this?
Write a letter just like that.
To whom?
Your daughter.
Why?
Myeong Ju, Hae Won doesn't know anything.
Why you refused to see her in prison,
why you sent back all her letters,
why you didn't even live with her,
and why you were so cold-hearted every time.
She doesn't know anything.
So...
write her a letter.
Go on, then.
There are some things people will never know...
unless you actually tell them.
"Dear Young Soo."
"Young Soo, are you enjoying your college life?"
"I'm going to this school where you no longer attend."
"I walked through the empty hallway today..."
"all alone, without anyone by me as always."
"I'm coping with this boring and dull place..."
"each and every day."
All right, let's get ready for class.
Hey, the teacher is here.
Quiet.
Quiet down.
We have a transfer student.
His name is... Lim Hwi?
Yes?
What? Your name is Lim Hwi too?
Yes, it is.
How strange. It's not even a common name.
Her name is Lim Hwi too.
So?
- I like him. - You're going crazy.
Hey, it hasn't even been a month since Kim Young Soo graduated.
His diploma is still hot off the press.
Hyun Ji, I'm sure he's happy and well.
- What? - He has Song Jae In, you know.
Gosh.
I wish her happiness.
May life bring her happiness.
Goodness.
Anyway, I'm really going to date this guy, no matter what.
The thing is, you can't date him...
just because you want to.
Life is not that easy, okay?
Well... Hyun Ji.
Do you envy me?
What?
Well, if things go well between me...
and that super handsome newbie,
I won't be able to have lunch with you.
Is that why you're envious of me?
No, cut it out. Stop it, baby.
- What? - Hush, baby.
Okay, I love you too.
In any case, I'm in love with Lim Hwi, the newbie.
Let me remind you. You're in 12th grade.
With your current GPA,
- you'd barely get into... - My gosh!
It's Lim Hwi. Bye!
Hey.
Lim Hwi!
Hi, Lim Hwi. We have the same name. I'm Lim Hwi, your destiny.
Do you like books too?
Was I talking to myself or what? Gosh.
Which Chinese characters does your name use?
Mine uses the ones from "clinical trials" and "whistle".
- Look! - What? Where?
Hey, Lim Hwi! Wait up!
The books are here!
- You're here. - Yes, hello.
- Thank you. - There are more books than usual.
By the way, this one.
I guess it sells very well.
I notice that people order a lot of it.
Even the bookstore downtown ordered many copies of that book.
Yes, it sells pretty well.
Well, that book.
I heard the woman who lives at Hodu House wrote it.
Is it true?
- Yes, that's right. - I see.
I'll be off, then. Have a good day.
("The Maze of Sisterfield")
Hae Won, how are things with you?
I'm doing very well these days.
- Can we get more kimchi? - Sure.
The weather has been nice.
I have nothing else to say.
Do you still hate me?
About that, I don't really want to explain myself to you.
But Myeong Yeo said...
there are some things people will never know unless you tell them.
You see,
I had you when I was the same age as you...
the year you graduated from college.
And when I was your current age,
I was already the mother of a six-year-old girl.
And back then,
your dad, who I had thought was the sweetest man in the world,
was physically abusing me.
(Our deepest condolences)
In that messed-up life I was living,
I didn't know how to comfort myself.
That's why I was always cold to you.
I only thought about myself.
I was busy looking after myself.
However,
I've always loved you.
I'm just...
not good at expressing it.
Also,
Myeong Yeo is leaving.
She's going far away.
You should visit us before she leaves.
(To Shim Myeong Yeo)
The weather is...
The weather has been great, you know.
Mom! I'll go earn some money!
Eun Seop! Eun Seop, Lim Eun Seop!
Give me some spending money.
- Hurry, quick! I'm in a rush. - All right.
- How much do you need? - Hey, hand it over.
Well, 10 dollars would do.
Thank you.
Oh, Eun Seop. A transfer student just joined my class.
The newbie's name is also Lim Hwi. The same as mine.
I really like that newbie.
Wait, is this newbie a guy?
Yes, obviously.
Eun Seop, I like guys. I really like him. I'm already in love.
I'm going to go out with him.
Hwi, the thing is...
Aren't you a little too young to be going out with...
All right. Just be safe.
- Call me whenever you go on a date. - What the...
Have you lost your mind? Shall I take more money from you?
Go home.
Okay, Eun Seop. Thanks, Eun Seop. Sweet dreams, Eun Seop.
Goodnight, Lim Eun Seop!
("Love Comes Back Like Spring Always Returns After Winter")
Oh, hello.
Those flowers are beautiful. Did someone give them to you?
No way. I bought them myself.
Are you going somewhere?
I'm going to go look at the flowers.
Grandpa, I'm going to school!
Seung Ho, turn off the lights in the room first.
Oh, I forgot.
There you go.
Grandpa.
We're changing seats at school today,
and I want to sit next to Ji Hyun.
Please keep your fingers crossed for me.
I will.
- Promise me. - All right.
I really want to sit next to Ji Hyun.
"Come to the spring garden."
"If you do not come,"
"what would be the point of all this?"
"If you do come..."
Welcome.
We just got married and want to decorate our home.
Please take a look at these bulbs.
Once you install them in your ceiling,
they never have to be replaced after that.
Never, never once in your life.
They never have to be replaced...
- because they last forever. - We'll come back later.
- They're incredible. - We'll come back later.
- Bye. - Please...
If you change your mind, please call me at 010...
(Spring Sale, Brighten up your home with new lights.)
Where was I?
Kwon Hyun Ji!
Aren't you going to school?
It's time for you to go!
Where did she go now?
Hey, what did you take? Why are you running away?
Whatever.
Anthelmintics? Who are you giving them to?
Gosh.
Right, you should take an anthelmintic in spring.
Out of the way!
(Welcome, new students!)
One last time, out of the way!
Let's finish up and eat something.
- Okay. - All right.
Oh, look at that.
(Warm and happy spring)
(Spring filled with excellent luck)
(Warm and happy spring, Spring filled with excellent luck)
How many times does he change a day, really?
Why can't he just wear...
the same clothes all day and change his underwear once at night?
In the morning, he gets mud on his clothes...
and changes.
During lunch, he gets gochujang on his clothes...
and changes again.
It's not like he does his own laundry.
Mother.
Hi, Son. You're home.
Did you eat?
Yes. Well... Take this.
Oh, my.
What is it?
It's your birthday.
Goodness, unbelievable.
That's right, it's my birthday.
My goodness.
My son got me...
a birthday present?
It's nothing special.
Goodness, you're the only one who cares about me, Son.
My daughter and husband are useless.
They have no idea.
Seriously...
Oh, my.
(For my dear mom, Yun Yeo Jeong)
I bought the scarf and then...
I see.
You should go, Son.
I want to be alone.
Okay.
(For my dear mom, Yun Yeo Jeong)
- Welcome. - Welcome.
Enjoy.
How have you been?
I've been good.
You look good in that.
Isn't the coffee good?
It really is.
By the way, the cafe is called...
That's right. It's the name of the song you once played.
What? You almost sound like you've liked me for a long time.
But I have liked you for a long time.
You didn't fall for it?
No, I didn't.
How did you know?
That I didn't really mean it...
when I said I liked you for a long time?
Well, how did I know?
That's because...
Hi.
Did I do something that gave me away?
No.
That's because...
I know the eyes of someone who liked me for a long time.
I think you should redo the whole thing.
Gosh, we're not even getting many customers.
This is annoying.
- Did you hear that? - Nice!
Guys.
Listen up.
I'm going to make something like the Jeju Olle Trail...
- here in Hyecheon. - Hey, that's enough.
Stop talking about Hyecheon already.
He has nothing else to talk about anyway. Let him be.
- Right. - Imagine how nice it will be.
For the city of Hyecheon...
Here comes Ji Eun Sil.
- Hey! - Guys, I'm sorry I'm late.
- Hi! - Hi, Eun Sil!
Why didn't you show up the other day?
It's been so long.
Eun Sil, don't you have to work tomorrow? What are you doing here?
Did you take a day off again?
I quit.
- In times like these? - You're crazy.
After complaining all the time,
you quit in the end? I can't believe this.
When you think it's too late, it probably is.
So you should quit as soon as you can.
Don't you guys know how much I suffered?
- Right, Jang Woo? - What? Me?
- Right, guys? - Suit yourself.
Forget it. Give me a glass.
Here you go.
- Hey, Jang Woo. - What?
You seem quite close with Eun Sil.
I know, what's going on? Something smells fishy.
It's not that. As a proud...
civil servant of Hyecheon, I'm concerned about her unemployment...
By the way, Eun Sil.
When you weren't here last time, Jang Woo said...
you were the one who had a crush on him.
I remember that.
Tell us the truth. Did Jang Woo hit on you...
at the joint reunion or not?
- Really? - Gosh, how did you know?
- Let me see. - Stop it.
I miss Eun Seop. I wonder where he is.
There he is.
- Hey! - It's Eun Seop.
Speak of the devil.
Eun Seop, sit here, handsome.
Take a seat.
You're so funny.
- Gosh. - How's the bookstore?
It's not bad.
By the way, I was always curious about this.
How did Eun Seop and Jang Woo become friends?
I know, they are a strange duo.
You guys don't know? Eun Seop saved Jang Woo.
You know, when those bullies dragged Jang Woo to the mountain...
and tied him up with a rope and beat him up.
Hey, how do you know that?
You told me.
- I did? - You did.
I did? When?
How did he go to Seoul National University with that memory?
Beats me, I guess he got lucky or something.
Hold on a second. When did I tell you that?
It was written in the letter you gave me with 100 roses.
"I'm the school president, Lee Jang Woo."
"Although I may seem perfectly normal to you,."
- Stop. - "to tell you the truth..."
- Who was it? - Jae Yeong.
Right. "I'm being bullied by Jae Yeong and his friends."
Stop. Stop it!
Don't laugh. I told you not to laugh.
- That's so funny. - He looks embarrassed.
Come on, stop it.
He wants us to stop teasing him.
Do you remember back then...
How about a second round?
Hey, I'll let you know how much each of you owes me.
- Thank you. - Thank you for today's meal.
You better all wire me money!
- Thank you for buying tonight. - Come on.
Why don't we go somewhere else next time? Please?
Why don't you try reserving a place? Do you know how hard it is?
Right, you try it.
Stop fighting. What's the matter with you two?
- Seriously. - Why didn't Hae Won come today?
- I miss her so much. - Me too.
Shall I call her?
No, don't call her. She went back to Seoul.
Forget it. Don't call her.
- It's time to go. Come on. - I had fun tonight.
- Bye. - Let's go for a second round.
Have a second round at home.
- Let's go. - Bye!
- Goodnight. - Get going.
- See you. - Bye!
How about a second round with me?
- Of course. - All right.
- Let's go. - Just go home.
- We're going for another round. - Stop drinking, you pig.
Don't call me a pig.
- He keeps calling me a pig. - Are you two going out?
- I feel insulted. Hey! - No!
How could you say something like that?
- I feel insulted. - We're not going out.
Of course, we're not going out.
Myeong Ju, where's the nail clipper?
I can't find it.
- You... - You didn't leave yet?
I came because I thought you were gone.
Wait. What is...
Hey, Hae Won.
Hey, I really can't give you fried eggs for free now.
- All right, whatever. - Stop asking for them!
When are you planning on going back this time?
I don't know, about a week later?
What about your academy interviews?
I failed all of them.
Is that so?
So I'm thinking of...
renting a studio with my classmates from school to open up an institute.
There's nothing else I'm particularly good at...
besides teaching kids.
You said you don't have the right to teach someone.
- That's true. - But?
Well,
I still don't know if I have the right,
but when I tried it again,
I felt what I've done isn't that bad after all.
I don't know what you mean.
What I mean is,
my life in Seoul was so lonely and stressful,
so I guess I started hating what I was doing.
But...
after getting warmed up and trying it again,
I started to see clearly how my life path was.
- And how was that? - Well...
I realized it wasn't that bad after all.
There were times when I was happy. Something like that.
That's nice.
When will you open up the institution?
It hasn't been decided for sure yet.
Mom, are you here for good?
Yes. I sold the house in Paju.
That's nice.
Did you live there?
I did.
I fixed the place up and sold it at a good price.
That's nice.
There may be no seats at this place.
Hey. Hi, Hae Won.
When did you come?
Oh, just now. I came to eat.
Well, I don't see any empty seats.
We have a bunch of empty seats.
No, it's fine. I want to eat in the sun.
The weather is lovely today.
Hae Won, I'll see you later.
Call me later.
Hello... Enjoy your meal. I like your sunglasses.
Well, see you later. I'll call you.
There are no seats left in this place.
What? It looks like they have seats.
No, I already took a look inside.
Let's go. There are no seats.
- But there are... - No, let's just go.
There are no seats. How about some rice noodles?
What do you want? Let's eat something nice.
- See you. - Okay.
Bye, Auntie.
Okay.
Bring my stuff.
Wait, that's it?
I guess you're not the clingy type of family.
Goodbye, then.
- Goodbye. - Bye.
Hey, how could you say goodbye like that?
What? That was good enough.
Are you going to come back?
No.
I won't come back for the rest of my life.
- How about a steamed dish? - A steamed dish? A stew?
Stew sounds good. I know a nice place.
- Let's go. - Good.
- I'll catch up with you guys. - Okay.
Ji Eun Sil.
- Eun Sil! - Oh, my goodness!
Where did you pop out from?
Me? From there. What are you doing?
I'm jobless. I felt guilty sitting at home, so I stepped out.
- I see. - What about you?
Me? I'm not doing anything.
What? But you were...
Oh, I'm going to take the rest of the day off.
Okay.
I'm going to do it now.
- Okay, go. - What will you do after your walk?
I have no plans. I have so much time on my hands.
Why do you ask? Do you want to do something?
Let's think about it.
Shall we go to the movies?
Then do you want to go hiking?
Or how about we go to the market and grab a bite to eat?
How about a convenience store?
- A convenience store. - What?
I've actually eaten, so I'm full now.
Me too. I'm stuffed.
I am craving something right now though.
I want a milkshake.
But you can't get milkshakes anywhere in this area.
Seriously, it's gone.
So how about we try to find ice cream...
that tastes like a milkshake?
- Sure, let's go. - My gosh!
You're so awesome.
What? What did I do?
Forget it. Stop blushing.
Go submit that thing.
I'll wait right here.
Okay, I'll go take the rest of the day off.
Thanks, Cha Yun Taek. For driving me.
You're not going to cry?
I will no longer cry.
Hey, Shim Myeong Yeo.
You're really not going to come back?
No, I'm never coming back.
You can't even visit?
You know, from time to time.
You can visit when you miss this place a lot.
Well...
I don't want to do that.
I won't.
Run.
- What? - Run!
Why are you just standing there?
Why are you in such a rush, Eun Sil? All right, I'm coming.
You'd better run unless you want me to teach you a lesson.
You didn't hear me?
No, I couldn't hear anything.
Why you little...
What?
Gosh, you said you'd be right back.
Hey, why...
You said you'd be right back. You kept me waiting for so long.
My manager is kind of ill-tempered. Let's go.
I'll buy you ice cream.
For real?
Thank you.
Jang Woo.
Yes?
You graduated from Seoul National University. Why did you move back?
- What a random question. - I know.
I could never wrap my head around it.
It's just nice to live where I was born and raised.
Well, I like it here too.
But don't most SNU graduates...
get jobs at those big companies in Seoul?
My parents suggested it.
They told me to consider moving back and working at City Hall.
I thought you were more ambitious than...
- I dream small. - Yes, you do.
But for me,
it guarantees happiness.
It guarantees happiness?
Yes.
So you're saying...
you've happily been following the path...
your parents decided for you so far, ignoring your own will?
You studied very hard, and you were...
always the best student...
in the entire school throughout your school years.
And you even got into Seoul National University.
But instead of moving on to see the bigger world out there,
you moved back home,
took the civil service exam because of your parents, and passed it.
Now, you just sit in your stuffy office at City Hall...
from 9am to 6pm,
and just go home to sleep.
- That kind of life... - Eun Sil.
Well...
You may think that I'm on the hamster wheel, living a boring life.
You may also think that my job is nothing special.
But you see,
I call that mundane life "happiness".
What?
Maybe some SNU graduates...
dream of exploring the universe.
But this is what I think.
Sure, I'm an SNU graduate.
But I want to build and live my life...
doing the so-called mundane things every day.
That is my dream.
Working hard and living an ordinary life makes me happy.
I know that about myself.
Why didn't you write that in your letter?
What?
Instead of the story about you getting beaten up.
"I know what makes me happy."
Had you written that in your letter,
I would've liked you more.
Do you think... Is that cool?
Yes.
Not many people know what truly makes them happy.
Then I guess...
you may have been a little charmed by what I said just now.
I'm hungry.
I got you the ice cream because you said you had just eaten.
You're hungry already?
How big is your stomach, Eun Sil?
Last time we ate together, we went to five different restaurants.
I didn't know you were such a big eater.
You're totally my type.
I've fallen for Lee Jang Woo.
What?
I've fallen for you, Lee Jang Woo.
Gosh, you're blushing again.
Oh, you.
You... You said you're hungry.
- Come on. Let's go. - Hey.
Then are we going to be all lovey-dovey starting today?
"Lovey-dovey"? Where did you hear...
I mean... So are we a couple now?
All right, let's be lovey-dovey.
Okay.
But as you know, my mother wants me to get married soon.
You're probably not interested in getting married yet.
Well, that's something I need to think about...
(Good Night Bookstore)
Are you going somewhere?
Yes, just somewhere.
It's my mother's death anniversary.
I see.
See you.
What's the matter?
Just because.
I want to...
hold you just once.
Can I?
It's dark.
I'm so happy you're here,
Irene.
Hae Won!
I'm sorry.
I was going to pretend I didn't see you,
but when I saw your face, I couldn't help it.
I'm sorry. I'll be going now.
How long...
are you staying this time?
When...
are you leaving this time?
I thought I'd forget you.
Of course.
We only spent one winter together after all.
I'll forget you completely.
But I couldn't have been more stupid.
You're different.
You would...
sit heavy in my heart like winter snow...
and never leave me.
I forgot that for a while.
(Hyecheon Lake Spring Flower Trip)
Are you the letter guy, by any chance?
Yes.
I'm the one who sent you those letters.
I finally get to ask you.
Why did you send me those letters for seven years?
Well...
Reading something nice...
cheers you up.
Really?
- Hey. - Good to see you.
- You can use this. - Hi, good to see you.
Give me one.
I want this one. Give me this.
Spring is here.
The weather has become so nice.
- Right? - Of course, it's spring.
- Spring is definitely here. - The forsythias are in full bloom.
- You can have this one. - Give me one too.
We're going to go look at the spring flowers.
Yes, we are.
Excuse me. One soup and rice, please.
Coming up.
One soup and rice.
Do you have big chickens today?
Yes, they're the best kind.
Hey, there. I'll take this one.
Okay. Take a warm one.
All right.
So, is it for your son?
Do you love him that much?
I can see it in your eyes.
Your real daughter would feel jealous.
I took him in.
So?
I took him in,
and I didn't want to favor my own child over him.
So I tried to love him more than I loved my daughter.
And?
I ended up loving him more for real.
- What can I do? - My goodness.
I can't believe you.
- Look at this. - What's that?
My son did this for me.
(For my dear mom, Yun Yeo Jeong)
What does it say?
"My dear mom".
Goodness.
It says, "my dear mom".
Unbelievable.
(Rice cakes)
Hurry up.
- All right. - Do you want to work all night?
Come help me plant the potatoes.
Gosh, my back.
Hey, when do you think you'll be finished?
I still have a lot left.
Some guys are playing pool tonight.
- Do you think we can go? - We should.
I'll finish this even if I have to work all night.
If you work all night, there's no point.
- Hurry up. - I get it.
Gosh.
("A Piece of Your Heart Kept Until the End")
(Every spring, our laughter, breaths, and words...)
Hae Won once talked about...
happiness.
She said that happiness is hard to notice...
and even if you do, it takes a lot of effort and care...
to make it yours.
She's right.
(We talked and laughed, sitting under a tree.)
We all strive to be happy.
(The tree is filled with our breaths, laughter, and words.)
Happiness...
is hard to get hold of...
and does not stay with you for a long time.
Gosh.
Even if you work hard for a long time,
you might fail to be happy.
Make me some coffee.
Coffee?
Okay. Give me just a second.
- I'll take off my jacket first. - Okay.
One, two, three.
- Hurry up. - All right.
I have to go get a cup.
Which one do you want?
- That one. - This one? Okay.
But...
no one can predict our future.
("Goodnight, Irene" by Lim Eun Seop)
Out of the way!
If we keep moving forward endlessly...
Lim Hwi!
Hi. I'm Lim Hwi, "Lim" as in "limbo" and "Hwi" as in "whistle".
Do you want to ride with me?
Let's be friends.
Wait for me!
If we keep trying...
(The weather is lovely today, Bo Yeong.)
If we keep living our lives...
I believe...
that day will come.
Yes. I believe it too.
(Good Night Bookstore)
Hae Won.
I believe that day will really come.
(Good Night Bookstore)
- Like this. - Like this.
(Good Night Bookstore Private Blog Posting)
(I met Irene again after a long time.)
(I waited and longed to see her again so much.)
(But I tried to hide my feelings and stupidly turned away from her.)
(When she ran towards me and came into my arms, )
(she melted my frozen heart yet again.)
(I spent days and nights blankly without being able to sleep.)
(But I can't believe I'm back in the past now.)
(It's late at night, and she has fallen asleep on my arm.)
(She is light, and smells like the grass from a spring breeze.)
(Guys, the scent of acacia is filling up this place again. Roger.)
(PS. She woke up from her sleep and kissed me on my nose...)
(and fell asleep again with her head buried in my chest.)
(I didn't know kissing was such a nice thing.)
(When the Weather is Fine)
(That's what happiness is like.)
(It's a difficult thing.)
(But even when you...)
(open your eyes in the morning to begin your day, )
(and quietly live your life today, )
(you may be achieving that difficult thing...)
(and making someone...)
(happy at this moment.)
(To some, you are someone to be thankful for.)
(You may not realize it, )
(but just by living like this, )
(you should know you've done a great job.)
(We feel thankful to you.)
(And we wish you a good night.)