(All characters, places, companies, )
(and incidents in this drama are fictitious.)
- Let's do it. - I don't want to.
Come on, just once.
You really don't want to do it with me?
You said I have to sear my skin with an iron.
No, I was lying. You believed that?
- I don't want to. - Come on, let's do it.
I'll draw something cute for you.
I'm really going to get upset.
Okay, fine.
Where do you want it?
- Something cute? - How about a cup of coffee first?
- I want some coffee. - Why do you want coffee suddenly?
- I drink coffee all the time. - Drink it after doing this.
Mom, Bo Guk can fix a meal on his own.
I have plans with Joo Hee today.
Bo Yeong!
- Let's go downtown today. - I can't.
Come on, let's go.
You better come.
Gosh.
Hey. Here.
What?
- You can use this. - What?
(Lim Eun Seop)
- Hae Won. - Yes?
Is this...
really Gunbam?
Yes.
Did Gunbam always have legs this long?
His face looks just like Gunbam.
- It does? - Yes.
- I'll try my best to draw him. - Okay.
It looks like Gunbam.
- I know, right? - Yes.
(Kim Bo Yeong)
The person you have reached is unavailable...
(Lim Eun Seop)
- I'm done. - You're finished?
Yes.
Is it cold? Do you want some hot chocolate?
That sounds good.
Okay.
Hey, I think Gunbam is here.
(Contacts)
(Good Night Bookstore)
Hello?
Is this Eun Seop?
It's Bo Yeong.
It's just that...
I think I lost my footing in the mountain.
I'm sorry,
but can you come and save me?
Please come and save me.
I'll be waiting...
until you come.
I'll be waiting here.
(Episode 13: Teardrop Tea Recipe)
What did she say?
She's close to the entrance of the mountain...
and she wants me to come and get her.
I'll be right back.
No, I'll go.
What?
If she's there, I should be the one to go.
How can you go there...
I'll go, Eun Seop.
I think she and I need to talk.
I'll be back.
What?
Are you disappointed that I came instead of Eun Seop?
It's not like you fell all the way down. You could've...
climbed down on your own,
just like I made it up here on my own without any difficulty.
- Take it easy. - Bye.
You're right.
I'm disappointed that Eun Seop didn't come.
(Lim Eun Seop)
(Chowon Big Education)
I thought this was my last chance.
If you text me your address, I'll send it to...
No.
I'd love to come and have a look before buying it.
- Hello. - Hello.
These are so pretty.
What is the symbolic meaning of tulips?
Oh, it's "confession of love."
Would you like some?
My one last chance.
You have no idea how much effort I've made to date.
A couple goes on a trip after they break up.
While they were still together,
they saved up some money to go on a trip together someday.
They go on a trip after they break up? Together?
No, separately.
Really?
And then? What happens?
I did my very best.
But why now?
You never acted on it, so why now? Why this way?
Because I couldn't win his heart no matter how hard I tried.
I just couldn't make it happen. What was I supposed to do?
You see,
I actually had a crush on you.
What?
For a very long time.
I didn't know.
What if you knew, Eun Seop?
Nothing...
would've changed.
- Hey. - I didn't get into any colleges.
- Gosh. - You can try again next year.
- Hey. - Do you want to do this with me?
Hey, Eun Seop!
- Hey, come on. - No.
You can have this. I got too many. Come, I'll buy you jjajangmyeon.
Come on. Everyone's waiting. Hurry.
Hey, come on. Quick.
- Right? - Oh, gosh!
Sure, I may have had many chances, but so what?
The timing was always off.
As if I shouldn't exist in his life.
Eun Seop! Lim Eun Seop!
You said you'd buy me a gaming console with your savings.
- Did you bring it? - Yes, it's in my backpack.
Oh, nice!
Girls, say hi. This is my brother.
- Hello. - He'll buy us jjajangmyeon.
Bye! Let's go.
- I'll call you. - See you later.
Come on. Let's go!
(Good Night Bookstore)
Oh, right. I heard that hobo runs this bookstore now.
- "Hobo"? - That guy, you know.
The one who used to live in the mountains.
All right, let's go!
Okay.
Son, what do you feel like eating?
Well, something with meat?
That's why I couldn't do anything.
I couldn't talk to him...
or even call him once.
But I suddenly became brave...
after you came.
What?
After you came here,
I suddenly became anxious and determined.
I wanted to get in your way and be mean to you.
What did you say?
Be honest.
There was a time when you intentionally got in my way.
Hey, Bo Yeong!
Hey, why are you crying?
Why are you crying? Did something happen?
Because of what happened in the AV room earlier, right?
Mok Hae Won made a move on Lim Eun Seop, didn't she?
Gosh, I never liked that girl.
That sneaky girl.
Gosh, how dare she?
No, never.
- What? - I never got in your way.
Not even once.
You never made a move on him deliberately,
knowing that I had a crush on him?
No, never.
I speculated that you probably liked him,
but I didn't know that Eun Seop was your crush.
You know what?
I have a crush on someone.
I like him so much!
Never.
That's why I can't understand you at all.
Why would you become so mean because of me?
Bo Yeong.
What made you so twisted?
Yes.
I found her.
No, don't worry. I'll bring her down.
Okay.
Follow me, and don't fall behind.
Out of the way.
Move out of the way, everyone!
What?
Do you need anything?
Just tell me the terms of the deal.
Oh, right. I was supposed to tell you that.
What? You don't like it?
- No. - Then you don't have to come.
Who cares about book clubs anyway?
Fine.
You're early.
Thank you.
I hear you're seeing Shim Myeong Yeo these days.
Yes.
And she's holed up in the woods somewhere in Gangwon Province?
You know, I want you to focus on me...
whether it's as a writer...
or as a woman.
- What? - I want you to stop seeing her.
I'm not telling you not to publish her book.
Her book will be published...
whether you see her or not.
So just publish her book...
without seeing her.
Okay? Can you do that?
It's all true, Yun Taek.
- Can I get some water, please? - Coming up.
What do you mean?
And they say I'm the next Shim Myeong Yeo?
Unbelievable.
What does she have that I don't?
Is my writing not as good as hers?
Am I not as good-looking as she is?
Fine, she was born earlier, I'll give her that.
Have you even heard the rumors?
You haven't?
At the peak of her career,
she suddenly quit writing and went back to her hometown.
What did they say?
Everything people say about me is true.
Right.
That's the truth.
They say she had a fling with her brother-in-law,
and that's why her sister killed her husband.
Believe what they say.
So you didn't know?
Then why did you two break up?
Gosh, it's hot.
Excuse me. I asked for water, not broth.
Okay.
Cha Yun Taek.
Cha...
Myeong Yeo!
Answer me.
You're very persistent.
Just tell me the reason.
Is that so hard?
Yun Taek.
Have a good life.
Get married like you've always wanted,
have kids like you've always dreamed of,
and live happily ever after.
Myeong Yeo.
Please be happy. Forget an idiot like me, okay?
Let go!
I'm going to do everything with you.
Like this.
I'm...
not.
Everything people say about me is true.
That's the truth.
Believe what they say.
- Hae Won. - You woke up?
Yes.
Are you feeling okay?
You didn't catch a cold or anything?
No, I didn't.
How are you?
I'm good.
Did you talk to...
- Did it... - It went well.
That's great.
What? Don't tell me you're sleepy again.
I am.
I thought you had insomnia. Or was it mythomania?
- I do. - You have mythomania?
No, I have insomnia.
No, you can't fall asleep now. Get up.
- Hae Won. - What?
Let me take a short nap.
What short nap?
You slept all this time. Get up already.
I'm bored. Come on.
What?
Hey.
- Get up. - What?
My eyes.
Come on, get up.
Get up. Come on, get up.
- Hey. - Get up.
I'm going to make you into the Joker.
Okay, I'll get up.
Hey, no! Get up.
You're really not going to get up? Come on.
Hey! Get up.
Oh, boy.
- Hello, Eun Sil. - What?
- What a very casual entrance. - Wasn't it?
Gosh, our timing is finally right for a change.
I know.
Look at those roses.
Hey. Aren't these...
the same ones you gave me a long time ago?
What?
What...
Are you asking me out like this?
Yes.
I'm Lee Jang Woo, the student body president.
- I know that you're Lee Jang Woo. - You know me?
Those roses are white.
You must be very kind and innocent, right?
Yes, I am.
But that's too bad.
Baek Gyeong asked me out during lunch earlier today.
And I said yes.
What?
Sorry.
- I guess our timing didn't match. - Timing?
- What is that? - It's nothing.
- Can I read it? - No, you can't. Why?
Don't take it. Put that back down. Why?
- Thank you. - But that's not for you. Why?
- Put that back down. - But I'll have to say no.
- I said no. - What?
Guys, I said no, okay?
Eun Sil, that letter... Eun Sil, the letter!
- Give me the letter. Eun Sil! - He got rejected.
- He got rejected! - She said no!
When did you guys come?
- She said no. - How embarrassing.
- Where are you going? - He got rejected!
Then...
if you didn't go out with Baek Gyeong back then...
- Of course, I would've said no. - Right?
Yes. You weren't my type back then. Not at all.
I was attracted to bad boys back then.
Bad boys?
I guess Baek Gyeong was kind of bad.
I heard you're going somewhere nice later.
- Somewhere nice? - Yes, I'm going to follow you.
It's going to be fun.
Follow me where?
I've already put in a word, okay?
Eun Sil? Eun Sil.
- Eun Sil. - Hey!
Hi, Ji Young.
- Hello. - Hey, you can have some too.
- It's all right. - Okay.
- I'm here. - Hi, come in.
This radish water kimchi is perfectly ripe and delicious.
- Goodness, that looks good. - Come try some.
- Thank you so much. - Sure.
It's so warm in here. Can you make me some sesame oil?
Okay, I'll make it, so come pick it up tomorrow.
Okay, thanks.
By the way, did you hear?
Hear what?
The daughter of Hodu House came here.
The daughter of that family always lived there.
No, not her.
You know, the daughter...
You know, the daughter who killed her husband.
Can you believe it?
How can she come back here after doing that to her husband?
Well, the women from that family are all so spiteful.
Even their mom was spiteful.
Both her daughters were just like her.
How spiteful could one be to kill her own husband...
Right, weren't you close with her granddaughter?
Bo Yeong, what are you doing? Go to your room.
No, I need to go to the academy. Bye.
You promised me...
not to tell anyone either.
I trusted Joo Hee.
And I trusted you.
(Good Night Bookstore)
(Announcements, Introduction, List of New Books, Requests)
(Bookstore Diary)
(My first love letter to you, the 133rd post)
(Tonight, I want to take you to the cottage...)
Hae Won.
Hae Won?
Hae Won. What are you...
Hey!
Irene was me?
You said it was Hwi.
Then was that key chain really from me?
No. How...
How much did you read?
Then what does "Good night, Irene" mean?
No.
That's just from some lyrics of a song that I like.
- Why am I Irene? - That's because...
you gave me that key chain.
But you said you made it.
I didn't know you kept a diary, Eun Seop. How cute.
Can you tell me how much you read?
I'm not sure.
So you were the one who gave me that bug when we were young.
- I don't want this. - What?
I don't want this. Take it back. Now.
That's because I thought you were a boy.
What? Why? Why did you think I was a boy?
Because you were covering your face with a hat.
What? Goodness. This is unbelievable.
Oh, and...
you even slept at my house.
Who...
are you?
That's because Hwi suddenly got sick.
My parents took her to a hospital in Seoul so I had to sleep over.
So that's why you fell in love again with a fairy like me.
This is so fun, Eun Seop.
- Did you read all of it? - Of course not.
Almost all of it.
Now I finally know the secret of the Nakdong River incident.
I was baffled by the timing my aunt came for me.
You were the one who called her.
I didn't even know that and almost believed in fate.
Gosh.
It's all right, Eun Seop. I won't tease you.
My lips are sealed. Come on, don't be so sad.
- I'm ruined. - Eun Seop.
What?
- "That day, Irene asked." - Stop.
- "Over there." - I said, stop.
"Those things that look like marshmallows."
- Be quiet! No, Stop! - "What are they called?"
Wait.
Yes, this is Good Night Bookstore.
What?
(Hyecheon Station)
What are you doing here again?
You told me about the train schedule.
Yun Taek.
I lost hope.
I have nothing left now.
So don't expect anything from me.
Shim Myeong Yeo.
Your hair...
smelled like the "Charming" shampoo my mom used to use.
And your eyes...
reminded me of the night before a rainstorm.
I really loved that about you.
Can you tell me?
That none of it is true?
What's not true?
Everything.
Oh, the rumor that my sister killed her husband...
because he had an affair with me?
Well...
People can believe what they want to believe.
The outcome won't change regardless of what you believe.
Whether I had an affair with my brother-in-law or not,
he died, and that won't change.
And whether my sister killed him or not,
she went to jail.
And even if she didn't go to jail,
I'd still be the mess that I am today.
So it doesn't matter. Whatever you believe is the truth.
- No. - Yes.
That is the truth,
Cha Yun Taek.
(Hyecheon Station)
Even if that is the truth,
you should tell me that it isn't.
That's the least you can do for me. Am I wrong?
I'm sorry.
I'm inconsiderate, you know.
Myeong Yeo.
I...
I have...
wilted.
We all have.
I've wilted as much as you have.
Come on.
I'm the only one who has completely wilted.
I'm the only one...
who's totally dead, Yun Taek.
"I will cut off the tips of my five fingers..."
"and draw a staff with my blood."
"I will be alone tonight, but I won't be lonely."
"And tonight, I will shed tears."
"The first glass is for you, who left me."
"The second glass is for me, who is already so pathetic."
"Another glass for our eternal love."
"And..."
"the last glass is for the Almighty who foresaw..."
"and decided everything in advance."
(Good Night Bookstore)
Hello, I'm Ji Eun Sil.
I work at Gangneung City Hall.
I'm taking some time off work...
because of the event.
That's why I'm here today.
Applause!
My gosh, a number of new members...
have joined us recently.
It's encouraging.
Jang Woo, you look a little spaced out today.
Me? No, I'm not.
- Jang Woo. - Yes.
Did you drink something hot?
No, I only drink iced Americano.
"When I realized I hadn't had a chance to tell you..."
"that I loved you with all my heart,"
"you were already in love with someone else."
"I silenced the passionate serenade inside my heart..."
"as you drifted far away from me."
"You told me to forget everything..."
"before your pretty smile vanished and only remember your beauty,"
"but to a man,"
"a woman either signifies joy or sorrow."
"Love" by Cho Chi Hun.
What's that?
It's a poem.
It makes my heart ache every time I hear it.
Why does your heart ache, Auntie?
Is love painful?
Well...
For me, no. But I'm not sure.
Jang Woo, is love painful for you?
Did your crush who rejected you...
break your heart?
Eun Seop, get me some tissue.
I'll bring it.
What's wrong?
- Hae Won went to grab it? - Yes.
(Bookstore Diary)
(The 130th Story)
(The Bookstore in the Ocean)
(Hae Won, I understand that you will leave this place one day.)
Hae Won.
I understand...
that you will leave this place one day.
Hae Won.
- Yes. - Hae Won, someone's on the phone.
Who?
She said her name is Bo Yeong.
Oh, okay.
Well...
I think Jang Woo was probably...
No, no way.
No, I've never been heartbroken because of love.
I swear...
on the rice field road where I walk every single day.
But one-sided love is sad.
- Hey. - That's what I learned from books.
- Hey. - Seung Ho.
You know so many things.
Seung Ho, do you have a girlfriend?
No, I don't.
The other day, you said you did.
- No, that's not true. I didn't. - My gosh!
- Who's this girl? - I don't have a girlfriend.
- Your face is turning red. - I don't have one.
I don't have a girlfriend.
No, it's not true.
- Why is your face beet red? - It's not.
Giddy up! Let's go!
Faster!
Out of the way!
Hi!
(Hyecheon High School)
Oh, it's Hwi.
Hi!
Good morning, sir!
What a beautiful morning.
(Bukhyeon Three-way Intersection)
(Bukhyeon-ri, Downtown Hyecheon, Seohyeon Village)
I've never had anyone asking to meet up on the bus.
What did you want to talk to me about?
I thought about what you said.
About how twisted I am.
You're right. I was like that.
I really hated you.
I mean, think about it.
You cut all ties with me after just one strike.
Because of one mistake.
You didn't even want to listen to me.
Hae Won, just a moment.
Let go!
Hae Won!
No matter how hard I tried,
you wouldn't even look at me.
When I heard you were here, I went to see you.
So?
Are you saying you still can't forgive me?
So I started waiting.
Waiting for what?
For your forgiveness...
to become overdue.
Then you'd become a petty and cold person,
and I'd become this miserable person,
who is pitied by everyone.
"One strike"?
Bo Yeong.
It might have been one strike for you,
but for me, it was a strikeout.
I told you the biggest secret of my life,
and you didn't keep it to yourself.
You might try to defend yourself...
by saying you only told Joo Hee,
but because you told that one person...
I didn't think of it like that.
I'm sorry.
But I...
couldn't help thinking it was just one mistake.
So I hated you.
I'm sure you didn't hate me. You just disliked me.
- Are they different? - Yes.
They are.
You can dislike anyone,
but you can only hate someone you like.
I really liked you.
Attention. We have a new transfer student.
Her name is Mok Hae Won. She's from Seoul.
You know the mock exam is next week, right?
- Let's try to score... - She's pretty.
A mill and a guesthouse...
are different?
Gosh.
You're very sweet.
That must have been why...
I kept trying so hard and going to see you.
Even if you decided to dislike me...
and never to give me a second chance...
because you only cared about me that much.
Hi, I'm Kim Bo Yeong. Nice to meet you.
Hae Won.
Do you want to team up with me?
You can use this.
I live close by, so I can just run home.
Kim Bo Yeong... Bo Yeong.
See you tomorrow, Hae Won!
Bo Yeong!
This...
(Good Night Bookstore)
Hello?
Mr. Jung Gil Bok?
Hello. I'm...
Wait here for a second.
I'm here to see Mr. Jung Gil Bok.
Fill this out, please.
His neighbor found him on the street and brought him here.
It's nothing serious, but he should stay in the hospital for a few days.
But he's insisting on going home.
I think he's worried about the hospital bills.
Seung Ho.
Uncle.
Don't worry too much.
He'll get better soon.
We had...
rabbits at school.
- Run! - Wait for me!
Hey, stop!
Where are you going?
Eat.
They were so cute.
But they died.
What if the same thing happens...
to my grandpa?
He'll be fine.
I promise you.
I'll help you.
There you go.
Yes, you should pat your face.
Under your eyes too.
Pat, pat, pat...
Auntie, can you take out some blankets later?
I will, Ji Yeon,
but I'm not Auntie. I'm Myeong Yeo.
That's right.
Call Myeong Yeo by her first name.
Don't call her Auntie.
Grow up. What's so bad about being called Auntie?
Eun Seop's parents still treat you...
like a high school girl.
You graduated from high school years ago.
That's because I still am like a high school girl.
You do still have a high school girl's skin. What's your secret?
I put something on just now.
Seung Ho, what is that book?
"Owl at Home".
Can I see it too?
Yes, of course.
That's the story about Teardrop Tea.
Yes.
Whenever the owl thinks of something sad and cries,
it gathers its teardrops in a kettle...
and makes Teardrop Tea.
It's a story about how the owl forgets about its sadness like that.
Then shall we make Teardrop Tea too?
Myeong Yeo, do you really have Teardrop Tea?
Of course.
Wait. You call Eun Seop an uncle...
but call Myeong Yeo by her name like a friend?
I'm glad you pointed that out.
I feel much better now.
Auntie, this is how uncomfortable we are.
Once a friend, always a friend. Right?
Yes.
Seung Ho, isn't it uncomfortable to call her by her name?
No.
- No? - You have to be honest.
Your eyes are shaking.
He's just scared of her sunglasses.
Myeong Yeo, we'll just call you by your name too.
- Myeong Yeo! What do you think? - Let's just drink our tea.
- Leave Seung Ho alone. - Guys.
Can you tell me?
That none of it is true?
So it doesn't matter. Whatever you believe is the truth.
- No. - Yes.
That is the truth,
Cha Yun Taek.
Uncle!
Did you sleep well?
Say bye to Hae Won.
- I'll be back. - Okay.
Hae Won! Wake up your aunt.
- Let's eat breakfast. - Okay.
Auntie.
Auntie, are you up...
Auntie!
Hae Won.
- Auntie. - I understand...
Auntie. Auntie!
Auntie, open your eyes!
that you will leave this place one day.
Auntie! What's wrong?
I'm bracing myself for anything that can happen.
However,
when you leave this place,
I hope you don't leave with a heavy heart.
I just hope you can leave smiling happily.
Auntie. Auntie!
Auntie!
I hope...
I hope you're not hurt at all.
I'll sincerely hope so.
Auntie. Auntie!
(Good Night Bookstore Private Blog Posting)
(Irene saw my private diary. Darn it.)
(I think she saw the bookstore diary category.)
(I'm not sure how much of it she read.)
(Since she teased me about the marshmallow story, )
(I think she read it until the part she arrived in Bukhyeon-ri.)
(How much did she read after that?)
(It's not like anything's going to happen even if she read it all.)
(But I almost lost my mind from sheer embarrassment.)
(When the Weather is Fine)
She was probably in severe pain.
It would've been hard to handle.
You know the guy who works at City Hall, Jang Woo.
I heard he went on a blind date.
I think it's going really well this time.
Hey, Lim Hwi.
Song Jae In and Lim Hwi got into a huge fight because of you.
I told you to live your life to the fullest!
How could I, Myeong Ju?
- How on earth could I? - Oh, my head.
Maybe time will take care of it.
Just like when spring comes after winter?
I think spring is coming soon.